I won't take the exams!
I know what I want!
You're a spoiled brat.
I wanna go back
to when it used to be,
back to when we were little
once again...
Minami...
Chiyomi!
I'm over here Minami!
I heard Chiyomi is missing?
Tokyo?!
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo!
So please!
Let me stay with you Minami!
Wait. How does that happen?
Princess... please wake up.
What is the matter?
The prince of the near kingdom!
Our precious princess...
she has fallen to her death
from the witch's evil spell.
How heartrending...
What a beautiful princess.
How could such beauty ever cease?
Please accept my love...
and breathe once again, my love.
The wicked spell is broken!
The princess is alive again!
My prince...
Hooray!
You saved me from death.
Yes, my love.
My beautiful princess.
Will you...
marry me?
Yes!
The prince's kiss has broken the curse,
and they lived...
happily ever after!
This thing won't dry.
Do you think a prince's kiss
will magically grow me back?
How does that work?
You're no princess either.
So... who's your prince?
No one... in particular...
Is it Riku? Riku Takagi?
He loves you, right?
I know you're over the moon by that,
but shouldn't you try to find
a realistic solution?
I'm not over the moon!
I'm seriously...
Don't look at me!
A MAGICAL LOVE MALLET
Thank you for coming.
Chiyomi is such a troublemaker.
Old photos, weren't it?
Yes, I know it's early
in the school year,
but we want baby pictures
for our yearbook...
I found it. Here you go.
Chiyomi should pick it,
but we need by tomorrow.
I'm sorry. We can't even reach her.
Hello? Can I order?
Yes! I'll be right down!
I'll choose for her.
Thanks. The cafe is really busy.
Do you see it?
Is this it?
That's the one!
Now I have actual clothes to wear!
Shunichi!
Shunichi?
Shoot!
Welcome Shunichi!
-Asuka...
-So happy to see you!
What's up?
I had to get Chiyomi's
pictures for our yearbook.
My sister's pictures are all the same!
They're all identical!
You're right.
Look at this one.
THE FOLLOWING DAY
Hop on.
I like it in here.
Sei Shonagon and Murasaki Shikibu
are most important female writers...
their works are invaluable.
"Classical Literature"
The Tale of Genji...
It's great to be back in school.
Sei Shonagon has not
written about Murasaki Shikibu,
but Murasaki Shikibu has left
severe critique about Sei Shonagon.
They both had unique artistry.
Life goes on without me...
That's all for today.
-How's this?
-Something more normal.
How would I know what's normal?
How about...
-This?
-Not pretty!
-Weird.
How about this one?
Cute!
Good.
Creep.
It's delicious!
Don't get it on me.
It's not bad being small now.
I can eat lots of ice cream!
I envy your optimism.
Sorry.
It's been four days.
Any changes?
I don't know.
All right...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up and eat.
What?
Nothing.
One Inch Princess.
One Inch Princess?
Yes. Our old legend has it,
about a small princess just
like the One Inch Samurai.
A tiny princess? I wanna see!
But in the end, she grows back.
She gets married
and has many children...
and became our guardian angel.
How did she grow back?
She waved a magical mallet
on a full moon night and grew back.
A magical mallet!
What?
Wait.
No, no, no.
Minami?
What are you doing here?
You rushed out of the classroom
to eat an ice cream all by yourself?
You're actually adorable.
That has to be it...
Can I have a taste?
Oh, my God!
Sayori?
Sorry, I gotta go!
Wa... wait!
Unacceptable!
Sayori?
You disappeared on me!
Masaya...
What happened?
Nothing!
You wanted ice cream?
-No!
-Of course.
So it's true Pheromone
has a golfer boyfriend.
Minami!
My grandma said this shrine
enshrines a magical mallet.
I've seen it.
It's displayed only during
the festival for its good luck.
What was it?
You wave the mallet under
the full moon and make a wish?
Yup!
Where can we get in?
Minami?
What?
I can get in from there, right?
I'm off.
Be careful.
Minami. Over here!
Come over here!
Being tiny has its perks.
I know!
So this is the magical mallet?
No way!
Please... please, grow me back.
Please!
Oh, my God!
I can finally go back!
Back to my life! How I used to be!
I can't stand you anymore!
What?
Why?
It didn't work.
No way...
The mallet was glowing!
I knew it was gonna work...
Over there!
Shit! Come on.
Stop! Thief!
Wait? Is that you, Shunichi?
Under pressure, huh?
Not really...
I see.
Maybe you should take it easy.
Ms. Oono said you can get into
any med-school you want.
I'm sorry, I did something weird.
I'm actually relieved.
I thought you'd never ask
for help, let alone God.
But you're still very sweet.
You know, it's okay to complain.
You can choose any college you want.
What?
You're trying to get a scholarship?
You knew?
I heard from the chief.
His daughter told him.
Yeah...
I know we're not rich.
I also know how hard you're studying.
You work hard to protect
me and your grandmother.
So let me help you.
Minami...
Shunichi.
You can go to any school you want.
Trust me, will you?
I can afford your education.
It's easy-peasy lemon squeezy!
Got it?
Easy-peasy...?
Another storm is coming.
Grandma is away tonight.
Let's order some pizza?
-Sure.
-Let's hurry.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
You didn't have a choice.
Minami?
You turned small on
a stormy night right?
Yeah.
Good!
Let's do something stupid again.
What?
This is where you turned.
You blacked out
and woke up tiny, right?
I got it!
If I do the same thing again...
that could work!
These are yours.
You washed them?
I couldn't leave it be.
Thanks.
I'll come back for you in the morning.
Wa... wait!
You're leaving?
You were alone that night?
But...
all alone on a stormy night?
I'm tiny. I'll die before I grow back!
A fairy loses its magic
when it falls in love.
The fairy also loses its smile...
and ages very quickly.
Soon, it will fall into
an eternal slumber.
But when that love is reciprocated,
the fairy will turn into a human
in exchange for its magic.
Humans age, but they can smile.
In the short time of their life,
they feel joy, pain, anger and sadness.
"Updated : 1 week ago"
Chris hesitated.
Could this be love?
If so... if that were true,
she is yet to understand.
Her own doubt...
her doubt is already
the beginning of love...
No update again.
Chiyomi, I hope she's fine.
Morning?
It came so fast.
I grew back!
Yes!!
Where's Minami?
Minami look at me! We did it!
Thank you.
You did it.
I'm happy too.
Hey! Stop that!
Gosh, stop!
This sucks...
A dream?
It didn't work.
Hey, are you all right?
Minami?
I guess it didn't work...
Are you all right?
I'm an idiot.
I think I caught a cold.
You're burning up!
No one's home.
What am I gonna do?
I need to cool him down!
Finally.
Chiyomi?
I couldn't get you anything.
Water...
ice... nothing.
It took me everything to get here...
I'm so sorry.
Just stay here with me.
"In times past,
lived an old bamboo cutter.
A master of all dealings of the bamboo.
His name Sanuki no Miyatsuko.
Upon approaching
the shining bamboo."
He's burning up.
I wish I could cool him down.
Sorry, did I wake you?
No...
How do you feel?
Groggy...
The worst timing...
Are you okay? Can you walk?
I'll be fine.
Are you hungry?
Just a bit.
I'll get you something.
Thanks for always taking care of me.
You owe me a lot.
Hello?
Hey, darling!
Hello!
-Beautiful home.
-Nice and new.
Are you home alone?
Yes.
Our timing is impeccable. Here!
We brought you
something for your cold.
We got udon noodles for you,
and for us...
I don't want it.
Why not? You should eat something.
I'm not hungry.
Well, there is another thing
I wanted to do here today...
I quit kendo.
Think it over...
I've made my decision.
Be that as it may,
I'm here to tell you how
talented you are at kendo.
No, thank you.
It's like talking to a wall.
Come on. Listen to him!
Cut it out!
Can you please leave?
Let's talk about this...
Never.
Okay. Let's get going, shall we?
Yes, coach!
Whatever's bothering you,
I'm here for you, man.
Sure.
Enjoy some real girls for a change.
See you tomorrow.
Excuse us!
I borrowed your tablet.
I learned how to bring down
your fever.
It said to cool your armpits...
I know.
Of course.
My mom is a nurse.
Oh, yeah... figures.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry about this.
I made you catch a cold.
Don't worry.
I did it on my own free will.
Those goons!
Leave me alone!
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I forgot to lock the door.
Hello?
Minami?
Sayori?
Hide!
Minami?
Where are you?
I'm here.
Sayori?
Hey.
I'm sorry to barge in like this.
It's fine. But why?
I was worried, I heard you were sick.
Okay... thanks.
How are you?
A little dizzy, I guess?
What is this?
Yeah, I wasn't that hungry.
How is it?
Great.
Really? I'm glad.
That was delicious, thanks.
I'd cook for you any time.
Minami?
Your fever!
I should've paid more attention.
Go back to sleep.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
Minami...
Sorry.
Don't mention it.
I'm sorry, Minami.
There's nothing I could do for you.
Don't! Stop!
Minami...!
Please, no!
NEXT EPISODE
EP.04 "DON'T GIVE UP, MINAMI"
Damn it! Why should I?
I'm begging you.
Our team could be eliminated!
I know you want to.
You love kendo!
Is it true your father disappeared?
Same here.
My so-called mother left me.
Mom, don't you resent him?
Don't give up, Minami!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!