I wanna go back to how it used to be,
back to when we were little
once again...
Minami.
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Tokyo?!
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo!
Let me stay with you, Minami!
Chiyomi... A new novel!
I wanted to put her in my pocket.
Do you like Chiyomi?
I really like Chiyomi.
Did he see me?
Chiyomi is not at the audition.
What?
Are you really Chiyomi?
I'm sorry about everything.
The worst sleeping posture as always.
Minami?
Get up, we gotta leave for school.
You watched me sleep?
I was marveling at your posture.
I need to change.
Okay.
A lot has happened
in the four weeks since I turned...
Here.
Thanks!
Grandma made it.
Yay! We can eat delicious food again!
Hey, I did pretty good
while grandma was away.
Lately we have this great vibe
between us.
What a great change...
I think we have a good thing going.
You needed me to cook, remember?
I won't argue with that.
That's the spirit!
Shunichi!
A ROMANTIC GETAWAY FOR TWO
Hey Asuka, what's up?
What happened now?
Mom is gonna file
a missing person's report!
What?
You want to report Chiyomi missing?
Maybe you're overreacting?
I agree. That'll make things worse
for Chiyomi.
But it's been four weeks.
Isn't that reason enough?
Why can't we even reach her?!
How could I ever be calm?
That's pretty bad.
Mom...
Little Miss Chobi in Your Pocket
Chiyomi is on a roll.
What are you reading?
I'm reading Chiyomi's online novel...
Chiyomi?
Chiyomi, the girl who's missing?
Mr.Sasaki! Quiet!
What did you say? On-the-line novel?
Moon?
Who do you think it is?
The novel?
Minami!
We need to talk.
Why?
It's important.
Is this Chiyomi?
I haven't heard that name in a while.
"Little Miss Chobi in Your Pocket."
What is it?
I heard she's an online novelist.
Seriously?
She goes by Michaela Moon Rabbit.
Huh? Michaela Moon Rabbit?
Is that true?
But isn't she in Tokyo?
Oh, yeah, the dance thing.
This is bad.
Riku?
You fooled all of us.
I got tons of questions for you.
About your little Chobi too.
Come again? Chobi?
That doll in your pocket!
Are you gonna keep lying?
You put on a great show.
Maybe you should be an actor.
Riku?
Did you know about this?
What is it?
Chiyomi is the author.
Really?
Michaela Moon Rabbit?
I see Chiyomi is famous now.
Did you know about this
Michaela Moon Rabbit?
No.
Really?
Now he knows! Minami can't read it!
But wait. He'll never read it.
Yeah, he's not the type.
Little Miss Chobi in Your Pocket
This is definitely Chiyomi!
She would write this.
So does that mean...
Chiyomi is doing this online... whatever?
I guarantee it! But I'm glad.
I was worried
after her audition incident.
She's updating frequently too.
But why did she have to leave?
You're right. This is no secret.
I think she was embarrassed
to show this to her parents.
But why wouldn't she tell us?
I'm sorry.
I actually knew that she
was Michaela Moon Rabbit.
Sorry, Ami.
It didn't feel right for me
to tell Chiyomi's secret.
That's no good!
You should've told us right away.
I'm sorry.
The day I confessed about knowing
her secret and my love for her,
she disappeared and I felt guilty.
It's not your fault, Riku.
The reason she disappeared
has nothing to do with her writing.
Or so I believe...
You should've told us.
I thought Chiyomi wanted
to tell you in person.
I had no idea how she felt...
What do you call this, self-expression?
I didn't know she had such a gift.
I remember when she told me
she saw a little person.
You saw what?
A One Inch Princess!
You know that's not true?
I saw her at the river with Minami--
Stop. Can't you see Mommy is busy?
Maybe Chiyomi did see it.
She's always been a dreamer,
the imaginary and reality
may seem the same to kids.
I should've been more understanding.
What if Chiyomi transformed
into a little person too?
Please, don't get dreamy on me now.
Maybe Chiyomi had a lot of emotions
she kept to herself.
Where is Shunichi?
Didn't he say
he was going for a quick run?
Leaving Chiyomi behind like this...
What?
The giant gave me this red dress.
Maybe he chose it randomly.
Nevertheless, he chose it just for me.
So, I wear my red dress
and dream of the giant.
In his pocket, I am closer to him
than anyone else.
I feel his warmth and heartbeat.
I could be closer to him
than any other woman of his kind.
So close yet so far.
Dreaming to be loved someday.
But I know the giant
will never love me back.
So I deny myself to dream.
I keep telling myself.
It's enough to be by his side,
I'm in love with the giant.
More than anyone could ever love...
What's on your mind, Minami?
You've been quiet all evening.
Yeah.
It's nothing.
Who is it?
I'm Riku, Shunichi's classmate.
Riku?
Why is he here?
Oh, come on in.
Shunichi!
Riku is here to see you.
Come on downstairs.
Is his room upstairs?
I'll go and find him.
Oh, really?
You need to hide.
Yeah.
What's up?
What do you want?
I need to talk. Man to man.
Let me in.
Hey, wait!
I was studying.
Make this quick.
Your doll...
does she sleep here?
No this is...
It looks like a doll's bed!
Huh? What are you talking about?
This is for my towel!
Is that your best lie?
I'll show you!
Look! She fits perfectly!
What the heck are you talking about?
I'm not into dolls or whatever...
Stop lying.
I saw her.
I saw Chiyomi
in your pocket at school.
You did a great job.
So Riku thinks I'm a doll?
Whatever, that's not why I came.
Minami?
I know you like Chiyomi.
Riku...
I love craft so I get it.
Creating a doll needs passion.
You must really like Chiyomi!
What are you talking about?
She and I grew up together.
That's explains nothing!
Why are you in denial?
I'm not.
It's you! I know you're the giant!
Stop lying to me!
Because...
I love Chiyomi.
I was jealous
when I read her new novel.
I wish I was the giant!
I don't follow.
Then explain this to me!
Show me your doll! Where is she?
Stop! You need to stop!
Where is she?!
I'm telling you to stop!
Sounds like teen spirit...
This...
I made this for Chiyomi.
It's so cute! Did you make this?
It's amazing!
Well...
I knew Chiyomi came here.
Let me see her.
You know where she is.
Let me see her!
That's...
impossible.
Impossible?
Then let me ask...
what is Chiyomi to you?
What...
Mark my words...
you better not make her cry.
Can't you see from her novel?
She's heartbroken.
She believes she has
an impossible crush.
It's your fault!
My fault?
Does she...
Does Chiyomi know how you feel?
Why would you make her suffer?
If you love her, just tell her!
Let her know how you feel.
I'm scared...
to love someone.
In middle school...
my dad left us.
I hate you!
I think my dad...
he meant to love my mom
for the rest of his life.
But...
people change.
Me too...
So, you didn't want to hurt Chiyomi?
I decided never to fall in love again.
Because I don't wanna be like my dad.
But Riku...
When you...!
When you're around Chiyomi,
it really pisses me off...
You're jealous of me?
You?
I know I have no right, huh?
That night...
Chiyomi poured
her heart out to me.
But I...
I should've responded to her.
Then tell her how you feel.
She needs to know.
You're her giant!
The giant is in love with Chobi!
Chiyomi! You're the one for me!
Hey... don't tell me.
Your love is not one-sided!
Chiyomi!
You're already a part of me!
Minami?
Minami!
Chiyomi...
Did I just hear Chiyomi?
Minami.
Me too.
I really need you too.
D-- Doll?
Minami...
She speaks!
Thank you, Minami.
I finally know how you feel about me.
I felt the same way.
Until that night...
I was locking my love for you away.
Chiyomi?
Minami? Is this your doll?
Riku.
I'm sorry. After you told me
how you felt about me...
I transformed into this body...
Transformed?
Is it really you?
Yeah.
So you really are Chobi!
That's right.
Freaky, yeah?
No, no, no... Not at all.
You're so cute.
You're cute!
Minami got you that dress?
I didn't have any clothes
so Minami bought it for me.
Right.
She was wearing that till then.
Thank you.
If I didn't have that,
I probably couldn't face Minami
when he came looking for me.
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Minami!
Without it, I couldn't have survived.
Wow.
I guess I did something good.
That sweater...
it protected me when I had nothing.
You know...
I thought Chobi's small size
was a metaphorical expression.
Who would've thought that...
I knew I should respond to you,
but I wanted to grow back first.
I understand.
But, hey...
I already got your answer.
What?
Reading your novel made me realize
I'm not the giant.
If Minami felt the same way,
then I don't stand a chance.
Riku...
Hey.
Take care of Chiyomi, all right?
Yeah.
You know...
according to the original legend,
you need more than a mallet.
What?
You two already tried
the magical mallet, right?
Yeah.
That's only half the mission.
The old book said, after she
used the magical mallet,
the Princess went to Cape Akebono
and grew back.
Cape Akebono?
Give it a try.
Why do you want to travel alone?
It's only for one night, Mom.
It's a good diversion.
I made you lunch.
Thanks, grandma.
See you later.
Do you have everything?
I'm good.
I'm off!
Good morning.
Hey, Minami.
Hello?
Hello.
Welcome.
Do you have a room for tonight?
A room for one person?
Yes.
Yes. Please come in.
Could you fill out the form, please?
Mom, he's probably still in high school.
Don't snoop on our guests.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
Enjoy your stay.
Here.
We're here.
A room for one?
You're a part of me, remember?
I'm so happy! Thanks for this trip!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Great sunset.
This feels great.
It's nice to relax in the tub.
Yeah, it's been hectic
taking turns to shower.
What if I grew back this moment?
What!
Yeah... I've heard of spa therapy.
Oh, no!
We'll get busted! It's actually two of us.
That's wasn't my point!
If that happens, I'll wear your robe.
What will I wear?
You'll just wear your drawers!
No way!
You have your drawers!
This looks great.
Can I have an extra plate?
I cool my food because
of my heat sensitivity.
Certainly.
Let's eat.
This is delicious!
Yeah, this is great!
I think it's the best meal ever!
I never thought the two of us
could enjoy a meal like this.
Me neither.
Excuse me.
This one is amazing!
Try this one.
Be careful it's hot.
It's true, Mom! I heard a woman's voice!
Maybe it was the TV?
No! I bet he brought someone.
You know, it's strange
he needed that extra plate.
Heat sensitivity? He fooled me!
Stop that!
Welcome back!
Thank you so much.
What time is the sunrise tomorrow?
So, you're going to the cape?
In this time of the year, I would say,
you should leave here around 4?
Thank you.
I hear its good luck.
Especially for couples in love.
They often go together.
I'll make a wish
for me and my girlfriend.
Good night.
Enjoy your stay.
He was alone.
You need to be nice to every guest.
This is a place of relaxation.
So, he has a girlfriend.
That was short lived.
Didn't I tell you
not to fall in love with our guests?
You're one to talk.
I could hear your heart beating fast.
I know.
It's racing.
My heart is racing too.
Are you okay?
I guess...
Well... not really.
To be honest...
ever since you came...
I haven't been okay.
Really?
Minami?
We've endured so long already.
Our second time can wait.
Second time?
So, you remembered.
We're here!
This is it.
Keep looking at the sky.
Okay.
Minami? These are...
You'll need your clothes, right?
I...
I like you a lot.
I really do.
Minami?
We used to spend time together
every day.
We played in the river
and the mountains.
We looked for the Princess.
I was so happy together with you.
Me too.
That was the best time of my life.
I always wished I could be
with you like that again.
We can.
I won't run anymore.
I love you.
Chiyomi.
Minami...
Chiyomi! Look!
Oh, God!
Please grow me back!
I beg you!
Please let me stay with Minami forever!
Please!
FINAL EPISODE
EP.10 "GOOD-BYE CHIYOMI, GOOD-BYE MINAMI"
Why? Will I stay like this forever?
He must be dating Chiyomi.
We need to forget about each other.
Let's make it like this
all never happened.
Minami!
I love you, Chiyomi.
Together forever!
Pinky promise.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!