I wanna go back to how it used to be...
back to when we were little.
Minami.
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Tokyo?!
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo!
So, please...
let me stay with you, Minami!
You blacked out and woke up tiny, right?
I got it! If I do the same thing again...
It didn't work.
Are you all right?
I'm an idiot. I think I caught a cold.
Hello?
Sayori?
Dad, Mom and Asuka...
how are you?
I'm doing well... in To...
Tokyo! I'm doing well in Tokyo.
No, that was bad.
It's obvious you're lying.
I got nervous.
Take two.
Dad, Mom and Asuka, how are you?
I'm doing great in Tokyo!
I know you're worried about me,
but I'm fine. Talk to you soon!
Good.
We got it.
There's nothing weird on the screen.
It's been about a week since
my strange transformation.
I have no idea when I'll grow back.
Hey, no one will know
you're sending it right?
Yeah.
I made a different account for this.
Minami and I used to be best friends,
but somehow we drifted apart.
I thought our friendship was lost.
Enter your dad's address?
But it was Minami who
found me in my crisis.
H-A-N-A...
This is tricky.
Do... ro... bo... @...
...ne. jp.
Send.
Great.
Unable to go home to my family
and friends in my bizarre state...
I'm living as Minami's secret roommate.
Dad, Mom and Asuka, how are you?
DON'T GIVE UP, MINAMI
It's Chiyomi! Look honey!
"How are you?"
I've aged so much thanks to you!
Keep quiet!
I know you're worried about me,
but I'm fine. Talk to you soon!
What? Was that it?
What?!
What is that ugly dress she's wearing?
That's not what we wanted to know!
Hey, but at least we know she's fine.
This is frustrating!
What is that ugly bow?
All she needs to do is call us!
Maybe she's scared of you both?
Remember, it was you who slapped her.
That's abuse, Daddy!
Hey! That's not what happened.
You remember, don't you?
This is Horikiri.
Chiyomi?
Chiyomi? Give it here.
Hey! Chiyomi?
Yeah. Did you see the video I sent you?
We did. What are you doing, Chiyomi?
I told you, the audition workshop.
For how long? You should be home by now!
There's been a hold up.
They're real artists you know.
Artists?
Chiyomi? Where's your cell phone?
It broke.
Then get a new one.
I'm broke.
I'll send some money. Tell me the address.
I need to concentrate on dancing.
So, I wanna be in solitude for now.
What are you, the Karate Kid?
Just trust me.
I'm at a pay phone. No more coins!
Chiyomi?
I'm out of change!
Chiyomi? Chiyomi?
How can you lie like that?
I know it's bad.
But... it's better than the truth.
How can I go back... looking like this?
You wanna be in solitude, huh?
What?
You pinhead!
Take that back!
Don't take it out on the sick.
I'm not... taking it out on you.
Minami got sick yesterday.
Don't. Stop!
Minami!
Please, no!
Chiyomi.
You've got me into a mess, you pinhead!
Minami?
Pinhead!
He's sleep-talking?
What?
Today's absent is Chiyomi.
Take care of yourselves
and be ready for the exams.
Ms. Oono?
Yes?
Have you heard anything from Chiyomi?
Chiyomi called her family
to tell them she's still in Tokyo.
It's freezing.
-Can I have one more?
-Sure thing.
Ami, try this cookie!
What's wrong, Riku?
I thought I heard Chiyomi's voice.
Don't touch it!
Sorry.
What's wrong?
That was weird.
Yeah, what's gotten into him?
Psycho.
Are you okay?
I guess.
Gosh, that hurt.
Minami.
Minami!
There you are!
Damn it! Why should I?
I'm just asking you to come
for one competition.
I quit the club. I can't compete.
But Takatori broke his leg
and we're short one member.
Then drop out of the competition.
Don't be stupid. This is the match
that gets freshmen to join our club!
I still can't help you.
Without new freshmen this year,
our club could be shut down!
Shut down?
You want the legacy of our kendo club
to end with us?
I hear a guy who won fifth place
in nationals is our competition.
Fifth place?
We can't beat him.
But I thought maybe
you can have a fair fight.
I'm begging you.
Ask someone else.
I would if I could.
I can't fail to get into med school.
I don't have time for this.
Come on! I'm your best friend!
I'll call you later. I need you!
Here.
Aren't you gonna dig in?
Yeah.
Hey...
What?
You always practice your swing
after your morning run, right?
I'm building my strength for the exams.
Shouldn't you fight for them?
Like I said...
Isn't Shaw your best friend?
No. That's what he calls himself.
You won't fail the exams
just from one day in the competition.
I know you want to.
You love kendo!
Just stop talking.
Are you scared?
Scared?
You just don't wanna lose
in the competition.
Shut up.
So what if you lose?
You're out of practice.
Losing from doing what you love
is not a failure!
I said shut up!
The Minami I love... is not a chicken!
That was figure of speech.
Who do you think you are?
Sorry.
What about you?
You can't do anything on your own.
Minami?
So, there you are.
Hey.
Sayori?
You always eat here alone, right?
It feels nice up here.
Maybe I should join you from now on.
Okay.
How do you expect me to eat?!
Maybe not.
Why not?
Is there someone else?
That's not what I mean.
Chiyomi.
Do you think Chiyomi really went to Tokyo?
Why would you say that?
Just saying.
Hey...
meet me after school?
Minami.
If you're gonna study
just go to the library.
Why come to a café?
It's like a date!
Aren't you gonna get that?
Nope.
Hey, can you explain this to me?
Where?
Oh, my gosh!
Sayori?
Are you hungry?
Not really.
You didn't have to fake a cough.
Let's order.
They have sandwiches.
Sure.
Is it true your father disappeared?
Why would you ask him that?
That topic is completely off-limits!
He didn't really disappear.
He left us for some woman.
He's not my father anymore.
You've never talked about that with me.
Same here.
My so-called mother left me.
She's not my mother.
What is this vibe?
It's like they understand
each other... perfectly.
See you later?
Yeah. See you tomorrow.
Minami?
Gosh... is it your first time?
Minami.
Can I save this for later?
La--? Later?
It's too loud!
Bye for now.
That pinhead! What about my feelings?
Is it true your father disappeared?
He didn't really disappear.
He left us for some woman.
He's not my father anymore.
Good!
Louder!
Great. That's my boy.
Keep going!
Here.
Hey, Minami?
What?
You started kendo
because of your dad, right?
That came out of nowhere.
You still practice your swing
every morning.
It's because you wanna stay
connected to your dad, right?
I hate you!
You still love your dad.
Stop it right now.
I've forgotten about him.
I don't even care.
That's a lie.
You changed after your dad left.
Of course I did!
My dad abandoned his entire family.
I had no choice but to protect my family!
You don't get it.
Minami.
You have no idea.
I don't.
I won't pretend I do, but...
But I wanted to help you so much!
Help?
I don't want help.
I'm gonna be a doctor.
That's how I'll protect my family.
I don't need anyone's help.
Minami.
That's why...
I have no time for sports or friends.
So, that's...?
That's why you won't compete?
You're still up?
I couldn't sleep.
Were you studying this late?
No. I couldn't sleep either.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Mom...
Mom... don't you resent him?
Resent who?
The man who's supposed to be...
my father.
Noboru?
Don't you resent him?
Do I?
I might have at some point.
I'm serious.
All right.
Well... every day was such a struggle.
I didn't have time to be resentful.
No time?
Yeah. It was tough without him.
But if I didn't marry Noboru...
I wouldn't have met you, Shunichi.
I love living with your grandma.
I guess we break even.
Break even, huh?
Because, you see...
I have the most precious son.
I'm the happiest I could ever be.
My dearest son!
You don't have to try so hard.
Man! You reek of alcohol!
Get older and drink with me!
Mom, you're drunk.
What is all this racket?
Sorry, Grandma. Mom is a bit drunk.
What? With that itty-bitty drink?
Fine. I'll join you.
Grandma?
Great!
You drunk.
Oh, my. Thank you.
I'll pour you a drink.
You're too kind.
There.
-Cheers!
Minami!
That's the spirit!
Go, Minami!
With a sudden change of heart,
Minami suddenly decided
to fight in the competition!
GO MINAMI!
Go, Minami!
Go get them!
HIGH SCHOOL COMPETITION
Awa Higashi High School is
much stronger than last year!
I'm ashamed they beat us all.
That's their captain, Izumi.
No wonder he won fifth place in nationals.
Even Minami can't beat him.
Oh, well. Either way.
Lead, second, middle and vice-captain,
we all lost.
We've lost already.
You keep your mouth shut!
Even if Minami wins,
we'd still lose 4 to 1.
No freshman would wanna join us.
Our club ends this year.
Are you serious?
You need to stop whining
and show some support!
That was close!
Get them!
Minami, defense!
I wanna cheer for him
at the top of my lungs!
Go, Minami!
Go for it! Minami!
Minami! Go for it!
Go, Minami!
Don't give up, Minami!
Tsuki!
One point!
Yeah!
You did it, Minami.
Second match.
Minami almost had it.
He put up a good fight till the end.
He's a great swordsman, Izumi.
He's way out of my league.
I'm kind of glad I broke my leg.
Coach, I was only joking!
Huh? Where's Minami?
Damn.
Minami.
THE BLUE FAIRY - EPISODE 11
No update.
LITTLE MISS CHOBI IN YOUR POCKET
If prenatal memory existed...
maybe it's something like this.
It's dark in here, but it feels warm.
I could always hear
the heartbeat of my love.
I'm surrounded by absolute tenderness.
I'm protected and cherished.
The first memory of happiness.
A new novel, Chiyomi?
Chiyomi?
Is that Chiyomi?
Yup. What do you think?
Oh, my gosh! Is that Chiyomi?
Did you make it?
Yeah. I stayed up all night for this.
Hey, let me see it.
Cool.
It looks like her.
A hidden talent, Riku?
It's not like that.
I've never made a doll before.
Really?
But why?
Yeah, why would you make this?
Why? It's because...
I wanted to put her in my pocket.
Put Chiyomi in your pocket?
That's pretty abnormal stuff.
Totally weird.
Riku, do you like Chiyomi?
You like her?
Yeah. I really like Chiyomi.
Seriously?
I already told her how I feel.
Damn.
That takes balls.
I couldn't say that in front of everyone.
He's still a weirdo.
Minami, why didn't you wake me up?
I'm home.
Hey!
Why did you go to school without me?
I tried, but you didn't get up.
Can I have the dance magazine
I asked for?
I texted you to get me one!
Text?
Yeah, to the address
we sent my video from.
Didn't you notice?
I ran out of battery.
No!
Okay then.
Let's go.
What? But you just got home.
That magazine or whatever...
you want it, right?
NEXT EPISODE
EP.05 "CHIYOMI'S BIG ADVENTURE"
There have been many break-ins lately.
No way. Is that the thief?
What am I gonna do?
I gotta tell Minami.
That's it.
Who the hell are you?
You little shit!
Oh, no!
Minami!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
Chiyomi!
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!