I wanna go back
to when it used to be,
back to when we were little
once again...
Minami...
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Tokyo?!
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo!
Please! I wanna do this!
Let me stay with you Minami!
Wait.
How does that happen?
Is it true your father disappeared?
He left us for some woman.
He's not my father anymore.
I hate you!
Don't give up, Minami!
Yeah!
I'm home.
Hello, this is Chiyomi.
It's been two weeks in my tiny body.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm gradually learning the ropes.
What's that?
I love your handkerchief!
I love this pattern.
How do I plant this?
Hey, can I have this?
We can make a dress...
Minami! What are you doing!
It's looking kind of shabby so...
I got this.
Ivy?
A curtain of ivy is actually nice.
Don't dig around too much!
Why?
Nothing...
How's that? Give it a go.
I can't go on command...
That's my dad's cake.
Yeah. Your dad's cake is the best!
They're great.
You want some?
Yeah, I do, but...
All right, then.
You can have some.
Shunichi, can you help me
change the light bulb?
I'm coming!
Later.
This is actually better.
There are things I can't get used to.
Because I'm a girl!
CHIYOMI'S BIG ADVENTURE
Okay. Please start.
Got it.
Hurry! Hurry!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Be careful.
Nope.
I'm lost.
Ready?
No. My head is stuck!
So, that didn't work.
Ask Riku to make it for you.
He'll be more than happy to oblige.
What?
He made a doll looks just like you
and he keeps it in his pocket!
That's creepy for a guy.
Don't insult Riku.
I didn't...
We can go clothes
shopping after school.
No. I'm good.
Don't you want clothes?
I'm gonna sneak back home
tomorrow.
I'm getting my doll's clothes.
Now that's impossible.
I don't have any more lies
to get us into your room.
I know.
I'm going by myself!
By yourself?
Yup. I'm gonna swing by
when you're in school.
You can't swing by.
We failed when I was there,
you can't do anything alone.
Excuse me?
I would've succeeded
if you weren't there!
We'll see about that.
Go by yourself, see if I care.
All right!
I'm gonna get some cute clothes!
But wait... if it doesn't work out,
will you go shopping with me?
Chiyomi texted you?
She sent me a video, too.
"Ami, I'm sorry I disappeared.
How are you? I'm doing great.
The SOLO audition is tough
but I'm hanging in there.
I'm sending you some
new dance routines."
Here I go!
Even early in the morning
Up, down, up, down
Here are the poses
She looks great. What a relief.
She looks full of energy.
I wish I took the audition, too.
Stop that!
What am I gonna do without you?
Can you forward this video to me?
Yeah, sure thing.
Why won't she text me?
Well, her phone broke
and maybe she lost your address?
What about yours?
My address is simple.
It's "ami" three times,
so she remembered it.
Mine is "riku" four times, too.
First I need to make
an announcement.
There've been many break-ins
in our community lately.
You know,
many elders live around here,
they tend to leave the house
unlocked and get burglarized.
There's been no witness yet.
Call the police immediately
if you see anyone suspicious.
A thief, huh?
Let's beat 'em up if we catch him!
Like you can.
Do we get an award if we catch him?
No! Don't try to fight him!
You never know what he'll do.
Let's begin our lesson,
open your textbook, page 78.
Recent break-ins...
Minami? Please put that away.
I'm sorry.
Yes?
It's you, Sakaizawa.
Mrs. Minami.
You can't open your door
without confirming who it is.
I'm fine. I have this to protect me.
Please stop joking!
So, what do you want?
Don't say it's another
class reunion.
I know you want to
find your future wife,
but it's getting too much.
You were my student
but I can't keep doing this for you.
That's not why I'm here.
Although I do wanna get married.
Anyway. The thing is,
there've been many break-ins lately.
You're often home alone
so I wanted to inform you.
Thank heavens, is that all?
Don't worry,
there's nothing here worth to steal.
But still...
You know, I have to go shopping.
Care to give me a lift on your bike?
I hope you're not serious.
It's against traffic regulations.
I'm an officer, you know.
A thief?
Peace is the only thing
this town has.
But I guess we'll be fine.
Okay. It's time to go.
Off I go!
Good. It's open.
Oh, shoot!
Hey, guys.
Welcome.
Did you tell your wife you're here?
Why would I? This is my safe haven.
She gets angry with me too, you know.
I told Minami I could do this...
but this is gonna be tough!
Finally!
It's like climbing Mount Everest.
My box!
Great! It's still here.
So much to choose from!
This is cute.
I'll take this and this...
I gotta have this!
I definitely need a brush!
It's heavy. Maybe this is too much?
Oh, well.
So heavy...
You were against it too!
But you didn't have to slap her!
Stop saying that.
Don't make me.
Come on, guys...
Don't make this about me,
I didn't ask for this.
Chiyomi didn't leave
because I slapped her.
She left for the audition,
it doesn't matter what I did!
You've got it all wrong, dad...
You keep changing the subject!
Let's stop this, Ritsuko.
Don't tell me. Tell him!
You keep rolling your eyes.
I didn't.
You do! You wish you didn't marry me!
Guys, I'm the customer.
I never wished that!
Then why do you make that face?
Fine. I'm always the bad guy, right?
You always like to play the victim!
Stop the brutal honesty!
Hey!
I knew I'd find you here.
Oops... busted.
Ouch!
Come on!
You're hurting me!
You keep wandering off.
Let go of my ear.
I did all the prep work!
You're gonna rip it off!
So heavy.
Tomiko is not home yet.
What happened to them?
Is it all my fault?
Shoot, it's Tomiko!
Oh, no!
Or not...?
No one's home!
There's been many break-ins lately.
No way, is that the thief?
What am I gonna do?
I gotta tell Minami.
I'm happy to study with you again.
I can't stay for long.
I know.
Sayori. You're really tall.
What? Do you like petite girls?
That's not what I...
But someone as tall as me
would look better with you.
Sayori?
Masaya?
Winner of Kendo Competition
Noboru Minami
My hands...
So, you're okay!
I was worried. I couldn't reach you.
You know him?
Who the hell are you?
Stay away from my woman, punk!
Stop, didn't I tell you? We're done.
I don't believe that for a second!
-We were great together...
-Let go of me!
Let her go.
You little shit!
What do you think you're doing!
What?
I'm busy.
No one's home.
It's just me.
What do you expect?
You bailed on me!
No. I can't leave empty handed now.
No. I'll be fine on my own.
I'm fine! I gotta go!
She's had enough.
Can't you see she's avoiding you?
Be a man and take a hint.
Avoiding? Is that true, Sayori?
I have a boyfriend now.
So, I don't have time for you.
A boyfriend? Is it...
Is it....
Yes. We're gonna be engaged.
Right, Minami?
Yeah, right.
Stalk her again and I'll sue you.
Stalk?
You little shit!
I'll get you for this!
Give it back!
Oh, shoot!
Thief...
Thanks for protecting me.
It was nice.
I just said those things
on the spur of the moment.
But I meant it.
I wanna be with you.
I only wanna be with you, Minami.
Minami, what do you think of me?
Well...
...is here.
The thief is here.
No time!
Send!
Sorry.
From : Chiyomi
The thief is here.
What am I gonna do?
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
Sorry. I gotta go!
Wait, Minami?
I'm sorry!
What now? I'm busy, can't this wait?
You're here? No!
Foot cramps!
What do you think you're doing?
Why did you come?
This is ridiculous!
Ridiculous?
We're not thieves!
What? An accomplice?
I don't wanna do this!
I told you, I'll make this right.
How?
Well, you know...
You have no plan!
Anyways,
you're not in your right mind.
Let's go home, okay?
I know. This isn't right.
But whose fault is that?
It's all your fault! You're a fraud!
A fraud?
No answer. Where's grandma?
Chiyomi!
Incoming Call
One Missed Call
Let's go.
Let go.
Come on.
Kanae, we can't do this!
Winner of Kendo Competition
Noboru Minami
Come on. Let's go.
No.
What if someone comes home?
We haven't found it yet!
We're leaving!
What am I gonna do?
They're coming!
That's it!
Come on. We'll find it soon.
I'm begging you, we need to leave.
I think it's upstairs.
It can't be upstairs.
Stop!
This is a bad idea, Kanae.
We need to run!
Hurry! Let's get outta here!
Someone was home!
I did it!
Hurry! We can't get caught for this.
You got us into this situation.
What happened to your divorce paper?
I sent it!
She said she signed it
when I called her.
Why won't she file it?
Well...
Maybe she's lying.
Maybe she threw it away?!
Emiko is an honorable woman!
Kanae?
I'm sorry! I didn't mean it like that.
Wait.
Grandma?
Why are you in a hurry?
So, you're home.
My teacher warned us
about recent break-ins...
I was worried.
We're fine.
Good.
Chiyomi!
Minami!
Minami, you're home!
I'm so glad to see you!
Chiyomi, you're safe.
Minami...
So, I clawed up the stairs
in a hurry to send you a text.
I was almost found
and things got really bad...
So, the thief didn't come to my room?
The woman came, just for a second.
But her accomplice came...
Accomplice?
I didn't get to see his face.
But he seemed useless.
He was so freaked
and they even started to bicker.
So, I ran them out of the house
with loud music!
That's weird.
Grandma said there was no break-in.
Well, she wasn't home.
But still.
I don't understand.
I think they left a mess.
Sis? I'm gonna borrow your book.
Is this it?
What's this doing here?
Did he hide this?
Shunichi?
What does he want
with doll's dresses Chiyomi put away?
What for?
Hello, this is SOLO audition workshop.
I'm a friend of the participant,
Chiyomi Horikiri.
Miss Horikiri?
Yes. I was hoping
to get in touch with her.
Is she available?
-Miss Horikiri?
-Yes.
Her full name?
Chiyomi Horikiri.
That's odd.
There's no one here by that name.
No... are you sure?
Yes. There's no one here
by the name of Chiyomi or Horikiri.
Is that so? I understand.
Thank you for calling.
Good news, the thief was arrested!
Our neighborhood watch
caught the thief on their patrol,
and called our officer.
Were they a couple?
No, it was a man in his 20s.
Shunichi?
Why did you think they were a couple?
I just thought.
How terrifying.
Notification of Divorce
You!
Mother...
Noboru?
It's been a while.
You look great.
Why are you here?
I wanted to see your face.
Leave!
You have some nerve coming here.
Have you any idea
what you put your family through?
I'm so sorry.
Mother, I just...
Say no more.
I have no son.
Leave.
Right now!
-Leave!
-I'm sorry.
Never come back!
Hey, look at me.
How do I look?
Good, I guess?
What about this one?
They all look the same.
You want some cake?
Not now. I can't eat before bed.
Fine. I'll finish it off.
No! Did I put on some weight?
Hey, look what I brought!
How cute is this!
I knew a brush would come in handy!
I love it! So pretty!
I wanna get back to my life.
That feeling won't change.
But on days like this...
I wish time could stop.
Just once in a blue moon.
NEXT EPISODE
EP.06 "I KNOW I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH"
Minami, I'll protect you.
You know how I feel, right?
You shouldn't be here like this.
Go on.
You can have your way with me.
A group blind date?
Why are you crying?
Just leave me alone!
Let me out!
Chiyomi!
Just relax okay?
I can't!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
Is Shunichi a pervert?
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!