One Inch Princess?
Really? Is that true?
Well, I wonder...
You never listened to your mom!
What are you saying?
I know you had a shotgun wedding!
I wanna go back to how it used to be...
back to when we were little once again...
Minami...
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Tokyo?!
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo!
Let me stay with you, Minami!
Wait. How does that happen?
Can't you see...
my heart can get hurt too.
Why are you crying?
Just leave me alone!
No... are you sure?
Yes. There's no one here
by the name of Chiyomi or Horikiri.
one inch princess@beeble.co.jp
This email address...
If that's so...
Shunichi and Chiyomi are...
She's sewing that
for the One Inch Princess.
One Inch Princess?
You know the legend about a tiny princess.
Tomiko said she saw one yesterday.
A hobbit princess?
If it wasn't for Shunichi,
she would've started a fire.
Really?
Grandma, the stove is on!
What?
Hey, Noboru.
I'm glad she seems better, but ...
Okay, I'll check on her
when you're at work.
Thanks, Ritsuko.
You must have enough problems.
This will help me
when I get some fresh air, so...
Thanks for the tea.
Bye now.
Tomiko, see you later.
See you later.
I'm sorry, Mom.
18 YEAR OLD PROPOSAL
What? You're staying home?
Yup.
But didn't my grandma find you?
She's gonna try to find you again.
Not me, but the One Inch Princess.
I guess that's okay
because she's a bit off...
No, that's not okay at all.
Please! I'm worried about her!
I'll call you if something happens.
Pheromone is absent again?
This sucks!
What's the point of coming to school
if we can't smell her?
Really? That's great.
I finally got a text from Chiyomi.
What did she say?
It was mostly
about the audition workshop.
She said it's challenging but fun.
I'm just happy to hear from her.
But I really wanted her
to send me a video too.
About that audition...
Yeah?
I don't think Chiyomi is actually there.
What?
The Legend of the One Inch Princess
Riku?
Ms. Oono?
So, you knew Chiyomi
is Michaela Moon Rabbit?
Yes.
I think her new novel
is based on this legend.
The plot is similar.
I wonder why she suddenly
began to write a new novel.
Blue Fairy was just about
to reach its climax.
Maybe...
something happened and Chiyomi
had a change of heart.
Change of heart?
I just wrote down everything
I had bottled up inside.
Then it must be your own
unique imaginary scenery?
Miss Little Chobi in Your Pocket.
Maybe that's her current scenery?
And then she turned into Chobi?
What?
I'm kidding.
But maybe...
What?
Chiyomi has an impossible crush?
Why is that?
Chobi falls in love
with a man she could never have.
So, the physical size difference...
may be a metaphor
for unapproachable love?
I see.
Then who is the giant?
Is he the giant?
Well, see you later.
I'll get this to you when I'm done.
Sure.
Minami is reading it too?
Is that why he made the doll like me?
Riku and Ami know about the audition!
One Inch Princess? Come on out.
Are you over here?
There you are.
Wow! You made this for me?
You should be properly dressed
as the One Inch Princess.
This is beautiful! Thank you.
I am most delighted.
Someone's here.
It's Ritsuko.
I'm coming!
You should hide.
Ouch!
I don't think he wants me around.
Why? You used to be so close.
I don't think he ever loved me.
He once was in love
with someone else.
But when his heart was broken,
he decided to settle for me.
It's ready.
This is nice.
We have two daughters
and a successful business.
So, we forgot about our past...
But with Chiyomi gone,
we have more time for each other
and now we just fight every day.
I thought Joji was head over heels for you
after you got married.
Not at all! You know...
He never even proposed to me.
No!
Is that so?
We decided to marry because...
I was pregnant with Chiyomi.
The shot gun marriage was true.
That stupid Joji!
I'm sorry, he's your husband.
I still remember him as a little brat.
It's all right. He is stupid Joji.
But when that stupid Joji married you,
I thought he finally
got his act together.
Before that, what was it he liked?
Heavy metal?
Heavy metal?!
That's right.
Stupid Joji was in a heavy metal band.
He sang in his silly getup!
He was a full grown man with no job.
He just kept saying he'll be
a famous musician in Tokyo.
Tokyo? Really, Dad?
No way.
But he became a hard worker
when he married you,
and raised money to start the cafe.
So, you know...
it's you who made Joji
the good man he is today.
That's a stretch.
Didn't you marry Joji because
you fell in love with him too?
Mom?
Maybe.
Exactly.
Maybe he drives you crazy
because you still love him?
Well, I don't know anymore.
Ritsuko, you work too hard!
What?
You need to cut him some slack.
Sometimes you need to relax.
It helps you a lot.
Why isn't she texting me back?
Welcome home.
Hi, Shunichi.
Hello.
Oh, no! Minami is back from school.
Thank you so much, you two.
A present. For your restaurant.
-Lucky me!
-That's nice.
-Thanks.
-Not at all.
Alstroemeria or Inca lily,
the language of flowers is...
Don't bother, I'll forget it.
She won't answer.
Chiyomi's friends. Been a while.
Hello.
Wait.
Did she go home again?
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
Hey, Shunichi!
Hello.
Hey.
-Hey.
-Hi there.
Cake?
I'm here for some coffee.
Really?
You're usually here for cake to go.
I wanted a coffee break.
I see.
Here you go.
Can I have iced coffee?
Well, isn't this nice.
Chiyomi...
where did she go?
Shunichi,
I heard you're studying hard.
I wish Chiyomi would do the same.
Apples don't fall far from the tree,
but I want her to go to college.
Chiyomi is hard-working too!
She may not like to study from a book.
But she can write...
and you know!
She's working to achieve
her dreams with dance.
Personally...
I admire that about Chiyomi!
Here's your iced coffee.
Minami,
your grandma found me today.
Chiyomi.
Maybe she's with grandma.
You're Riku... right?
Thank you for coming
and looking out for my daughter.
Not at all.
Thanks for the coffee.
So fast!
Hey Shunichi.
Sorry that I stayed so long.
Tomiko cheered me up.
Excuse me.
You can come out now,
One Inch Princess!
I'm sorry that took longer
than I thought.
It's always like that with Ritsuko,
but she always bring treats for me.
So, I can't complain.
Thank you.
We couldn't tell him.
Sorry, I said things
that made it difficult.
What can we do?
Chiyomi has her reasons too.
But maybe we should've told him
that Chiyomi isn't at the audition.
Where could she be?
What did you say?
Tell me! What's going on?
I used to be jealous of Noboru.
He's smart, handsome
and a kendo national champion,
and he lived next door!
With a beautiful wife!
He married Emiko!
In high school, we used to travel
all the way just to go see her.
She was the famous beauty.
But Noboru swept her away.
So what? You have a cute wife.
You see, men are romanticists.
We need to treasure sweet memories.
That's right.
You're back!
It's nice to see you back.
Where were you? We were swamped!
I was next door.
What?
I see that even when
our daughter is missing,
you have the audacity
to talk about Emiko.
Not in front of everyone!
We can talk later, okay?
When? You go out for drinks.
Point taken. But not now okay?
Then when? When will we ever talk?
Chiyomi is not at the audition.
What?
Then where is she?
I don't know! Do something!
You don't know? She's our daughter!
Don't yell at me. I can't stand this!
That sash looks nice too.
Guess what? I have
some delicious dessert for you.
I'll get you some. Wait here.
Hey!
Hey, Minami.
What are you doing?
Stop wandering around.
Sorry.
Yes?
We have a lot of company today.
This is our chance. Let's go.
But your grandma...
What?
Who's this?
Hello, Asuka.
Hello, Tomiko. Is Shunichi home?
I think you just missed him.
Why don't you wait for him inside?
Thank you.
Come on in.
There you are, Shunichi.
Yeah.
Shunichi.
Asuka?
I have to talk to you.
What?
Wait, Asuka, what is this about?
You know where Chiyomi is right?
Do you need to go?
What?
Well, actually...
I'm fine. Go on.
We can have our dessert later.
I know Chiyomi used this tablet
to write to us!
I'm sorry.
The last time I was here...
I looked inside.
What?
And then, the e-mail app was on.
Ouch!
It hurts...
Then later I realized...
it was my sister's address.
There's an explanation...
Chiyomi used this, right?
That's the only explanation.
Please, Shunichi!
Tell me where Chiyomi is!
My family is falling apart.
Asuka...
You knew my sister
didn't go to that audition.
Ouch!
I can't believe her.
Asuka.
Chiyomi has her reasons.
She just can't tell you yet.
This is tough on her too.
She's trying hard to get back home.
So...
give her time.
Can you give her a little more time?
Shunichi?
Does that mean...
you and Chiyomi...
are you two dating?
Chiyomi shares her secret with you,
something she can't tell her family.
Isn't that right?
Shunichi?
Chiyomi...
I have to protect her.
Chiyomi needs me right now.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you earlier.
Me too.
I liked you.
Huh?
I've had a crush on you too!
But whatever... forget it.
I trust you, Shunichi.
Bye.
Minami?
Chiyomi?
Are you all right?
You look dead tired.
What? Well... this is...
What should we do?
Grandma believes you are
the One Inch Princess.
We can't lie to her anymore.
I'm sorry.
I have big news!
My dad never proposed to my mom.
Huh?
Japanese Tavern: Izakaya
Gantaro
I feel you.
You do?
You know, I had to quit my
heavy metal band when I married her.
I went through some tough jobs
to make money to start our cafe.
I'm selling sundries and flowers.
-I'm trying my best!
-You sure are!
I've never cheated on her.
Something I could never do!
Once in a while I enjoy gazing
at a beautiful woman.
Emiko, right?
But I can do that because I love my wife.
I feel you!
This is Izakaya Gantaro.
Who is this? You need to speak up.
Exactly.
Women don't understand that.
Chiyomi? Is that you?
Joji, it's Chiyomi.
I think you should go get Ritsuko.
Good idea.
Chiyomi?
Dad?
You idiot!
Is it true you're not auditioning?
Where are you wandering about?
I am wandering about.
I just can't tell you where.
Just like you and heavy metal,
I'm trying to figure myself out.
How did you know that?
I know everything!
I know you quit your band
so you could provide for us.
Are we bugged or something?
A bug?
-We're not bugged!
-But this can't be...
Dad, are you there?
Yeah.
I know you work hard for mom,
Asuka and me.
I know you love us very much!
I'm eternally grateful!
Yeah?
But, Mom...
she is a romantic,
way more than you think.
She still loves you very much!
Mom gets scared because
she doesn't know how you feel.
She seems tough...
but she's a romantic!
More than you know!
She wants to believe she married
for love and not from obligation.
She really wants to believe
that her love was mutual!
Yeah.
So...
You gotta tell Mom how you feel.
Tell her?
Yes. Dad...
because that's really important
for every girl.
I understand.
Thanks, Dad.
Bye.
Wait a second, Chiyomi.
I think you've got one thing wrong.
You know...
I didn't get married because of you.
I married your mother because
I loved her more than anything.
I still do.
I love her very much!
I'm crazy about her.
Yeah.
Ritsuko?
What? What's going on, Dad?
Chiyomi, I forgot to do
something very important.
It's been on my mind forever.
What is it?
With alstroemeria and my love.
I'm sorry it took me so long to tell you.
Thank you for putting up
with me for 18 years.
Will you...?
Will you marry me?
Will you stay with me
for the rest of your life?
What do these flowers mean?
The language of these flowers is...
"Hope for the future...
devotion and love."
Hope for the future.
Devotion and love.
My answer is yes.
Dad!
Cut it out!
Look at me, I'm a mess.
Did I get proposed to
looking like this?
Chiyomi is on the line!
Chiyomi?
Mom.
Honey.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you, Chiyomi.
Chiyomi?
What?
She hung up.
She's impossible.
But I'm happy for you.
Chiyomi was worried about you.
Chiyomi is a good girl.
Why don't we celebrate?
I'll cook up a feast!
Maybe that was...
Shunichi?
Everybody, get together!
Are you ready?
Where's Asuka?
What? Where is she?
We're taking a photo.
Great!
Hey, Shunichi!
I invited Shunichi.
The more the merrier!
It took Joji 18 years to propose.
This calls for a celebration!
Come here. Let's shoot.
Come on.
Is everyone ready?
A group photo?
I wish I could be in it too.
Here we go!
Get in, Chiyomi.
Really? But...
Come on.
Say cheese!
You surprised me when you
pushed me out of your pocket.
But you got to be in a special photo.
But still...
what if someone finds out?
Don't worry. No one will notice.
But...
Stop worrying.
Even if someone finds out,
I'll protect you no matter what.
What do you mean by "protect?"
I mean exactly what I said.
No, don't get the wrong idea.
Minami didn't mean it like that.
But...
Oh, my God.
My heart keeps pounding!
Where are you, Chiyomi?
It's beautiful.
Huh?
NEXT EPISODE
EP.08 "BLUE FAIRY"
Look what I found!
Chiyomi?
Don't go, Fairy.
Fairy?
Thank you and goodbye.
Chiyomi!
My mommy hates me.
No, she doesn't!
Every parent loves their child!
Fairy!
Don't you wanna know
how your mommy feels?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!