Hey, Michaela Moon Rabbit.
Now you're a famous online novelist.
I love... Michaela Moon Rabbit.
I love you. Chiyomi Horikiri.
I'm...
I'm in love with Minami.
All this time...
I won't take the exams.
I know what I want.
You're a spoiled brat.
I wanna go back
to when it used to be.
Back to when we were little again.
Minami.
What?
Why?
I turned into a One Inch Princess?
No...
No way.
Go away.
I said go away.
Leave me alone.
Come. Stay on the road.
Come on, boy.
UNDER THE SAME ROOF?!
What am I gonna do?
What could I do?
Please find her.
We're counting on you.
She's a teenager after all,
so, keep your cool okay?
Your secret's safe with me.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Shunichi.
I just heard Chiyomi is missing.
Missing?
She didn't come home last night.
The officer just told me.
What would you say that? It hurts.
We used to be best friends.
I can't stand you anymore.
Her phone is off.
The officer saw Chiyomi
around Misaki Park last night.
There was a big storm...
I hope she's safe.
-Shunichi?
-Going for a run.
Chiyomi?
Chiyomi.
Minami?
Chiyomi?
Minami.
Chiyomi. Where are you?
I'm over here, Minami.
Over here.
Minami.
Is that you?
You're not dreaming.
It's really me, Chiyomi.
Minami.
Chiyomi?
Hey, you're up early as usual.
Good morning.
Hey.
Did you hear about Chiyomi?
Yes. My mom told me.
Can you believe she ran away?
I heard Chiyomi was getting abused.
You know what I think?
I think she eloped.
What?
Really?
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Chiyomi is only a teenager,
she doesn't need a bad rumor.
Eloped?
This is getting out of hand.
Abuse is not acceptable.
It's not abuse.
Sometimes you need
to show them who's boss.
But she didn't come home last night.
Guys, stop making this into a big fuss.
You all need to learn
how to keep your mouth shut.
Sakaizawa, it was you
who started running your mouth.
What am I gonna do?
You know what to do.
You need to explain what happened.
Calm down.
Wait. Wait, Minami.
Why?
I can't. I can't go back.
Eat this.
Thanks.
Don't touch my stuff.
Don't let my mom
or grandma find you.
Grandma is downstairs.
Got it.
What now?
This plant's dead.
I don't need it so you can use it.
What?
Shunichi, come and eat your breakfast.
I'll be right down.
That was close.
Ms. Oono.
Where's Chiyomi?
I'm worried.
Her mom called me last night.
I know you kids were close.
She's not sick, is she?
You don't need to be worried.
I know it's impossible...
but we've all decided
to keep this quiet.
Ms. Oono.
- Ms. Oono.
- Mr. Sasaki?
Oh, my God. I just heard the bad news.
I heard Chiyomi went missing?
Missing?
So, this is Minami's room.
He's Mr. Perfect in school.
But his room is a mess.
I guess he still plays kendama.
You're so silly, Minami.
Wait.
I don't know how long
it's been sitting here.
An honor student has great notes.
Is that me?
Oopsy daisy.
Boy's room is always a mess.
So, Grandma cleans his room, huh?
He shouldn't leave this out.
Good.
My gosh, he left the window open.
All done.
It's cold.
I'm freezing. I'm freezing.
I wonder what Chiyomi is up to.
I hope she's not hungry.
May I join you?
Sure.
You know those two.
Sayori is so proactive.
Hey, Minami. Are you here?
Hey, man, time for lunch.
Eat in your own classroom.
Dude, can't you see
I'm doing you a favor?
You'd be eating alone without me.
Hello.
Pheromone!
Shut up.
You didn't tell me about Phe... Sayori.
We're class presidents.
Class presidents?
Okay then.
Aren't you here to persuade
me back to kendo club?
Not really.
I told you I'm done with sports clubs.
Man, you're so boring.
Hey, I just heard from Sasaki.
Who?
Our kendo coach, dummy.
That blabbing meat head.
Well, he said your neighbor's missing?
I know you hated her,
but she's actually my type.
I think you're great too.
Well, thanks.
Who would've thought that Chiyomi...
You never know what those
innocent types are up to.
- Pheromone.
- Ami, stop.
What's up?
Do people...?
Is it possible for people to shrink?
Come again?
Never mind.
Minami?
Sayori, can you tell
Ms. Oono I went home?
What, are you sick or something?
Something like that.
Hey.
You're home.
Hey, Grandma.
What's gotten into that boy?
Chiyomi.
Did you clean my room?
I did.
Minami.
I'm over here, Minami.
I'm out here.
Thank God.
Thank you.
What's going on?
It's nothing.
All right.
I was so scared.
Thanks for coming back.
Bad news, everyone from school
knows you're missing.
Seriously? I have news too.
The neighborhood is
gathering a search party.
A search party?
We left my stuff back there, right?
They're gonna think I got kidnapped,
raped and murdered.
Kidnapped, raped and murdered?
Chiyomi?
I hope we don't find her here.
A runaway won't come down here.
Why am I doing this?
She owes me big time.
Hey, what are you doing
out of school?
I got a stomachache.
Really?
Chiyomi is still missing.
Did anything happen at school?
Not that I know of.
What's that?
I got a lot of pills for my stomach.
Ouch. If you'll excuse me...
Now he knows I'm hiding something.
Don't worry. He's not that sharp.
Just go home already.
Why won't you go home?
Because...
my dad might understand, but my mom...
You saw what?
A One Inch Princess.
You know that's not true.
I saw her at the river with Minami.
Enough. Can't you see Mommy is busy?
No way.
But they're your parents.
That's why.
My parents can't see me.
They'll be in shock.
I'll make them suffer.
But why do I have to...?
At least let them know you're okay.
I'll make it anonymous.
There.
What could I say?
Shunichi.
What's wrong?
They found what might belong
to Chiyomi at Misaki Park.
I told her to go buy soy sauce
in the rain.
It's not your fault, Mom.
I should've never sent her away.
Pull yourself together.
We know nothing yet.
Ritsuko.
Emiko, Tomiko.
We heard you found something.
Thanks for coming.
Emiko, thank you.
Really, thanks for coming.
Riku, Ami?
Minami.
We were really worried about Chiyomi.
So, we went to Misaki Park
to look for her...
and we found what Chiyomi bought.
Soy... Soy sauce.
Ami.
Chin up, everyone.
We can't assume the worst.
But this is way out of our hands.
Someone could've taken her.
I actually agree with him.
All day long, I've been searching,
and I've come to one conclusion.
There is someone suspicious...
right here among us.
The suspicious one in question...
The one in question...
That's...
you!
Me?
Why me?
I've been worried about Chiyomi
since yesterday.
We've been searching for her.
That's my point exactly.
You were worried since yesterday?
The only ones who knew about her
disappearance was her family and me.
I called Ami last night.
She did, and I called Riku immediately.
That's classified. You can't tell him.
She could've ran away,
or maybe even worse.
But we are best friends.
It's because...
I love Chiyomi.
It's true. I told her yesterday.
Just as I've predicted.
Chiyomi dumped you yesterday,
and in rage, you must've--
Will you stop? She didn't dump me.
I have a chance.
I saw you on a date with her.
-Is that true?
-It wasn't a date.
It's you! Give me back my Chiyomi!
Hello? They're busy at the moment.
Is that you? Chiyomi.
Hello? Chiyomi?
Give it to me. Chiyomi?
It's me. I'm sorry you're worried.
I wanted to call, but my phone broke.
You idiot. Where are you?
Come home right now. We're not mad.
I'm sorry. I can't.
What do you mean?
I'm in Tokyo.
Tokyo?
What is this?
Have you any idea how worried we are?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo.
Please. I wanna do this.
Trust me.
I won't do anything to upset you.
I won't allow it. You fool!
Chiyomi?
I just wanted to let you
know that I'm okay. Bye.
Wait. Where are you staying in Tokyo?
I'll call you later. Bye.
Hey. Chiyomi.
Gimme the phone.
Sweetie, are you there?
She should've told us.
I'm happy she's okay.
Keep me updated?
I'm sorry about all this.
I'm lost for words.
I'm happy she's safe.
-Sorry to trouble you.
-Thank you.
See, didn't I tell you not to worry?
A runaway. Simple as that.
Hey.
What was that about?
Well, you told me
I should call home.
Tokyo? Aren't you going home yet?
I'm going home.
Of course I wanna go home.
When I grow back.
When you grow back?
I can't go home looking like this.
My parents would be devastated.
It's better to make them mad
than breaking their hearts.
I see that, but...
Plus, I won't stay like this forever.
I know I'll grow back soon. So...
So, please.
Let me stay.
Let me stay with you, Minami.
Wait. How does that happen?
I'm begging you.
I won't get in your way.
Just let me stay.
This is great.
This bathtub is perfect for me.
This is insane.
Minami? I can't reach the soap.
Can you get it for me?
Will you please?
Don't look.
Don't want to.
And she said, "just let me stay."
I'm done.
Okay, my turn.
That was a shocker.
I guess he works out.
This is awesome.
Hey.
Minami?
What now?
Thank you so much.
Thanks for letting me stay.
Don't.
But...
Just go to bed.
Okay.
Isn't this our first sleepover?
Of course.
It's my first time to be in your room.
I got this room in junior high.
You're the first girl here.
Really?
Is Sayori... your girlfriend?
What?
I saw you with her yesterday.
Why don't you ask my father?
I'm sure he'll help you find a solution.
A solution?
My father is an influential man
around here.
He can get you a scholarship.
If you are up to it.
Up to it?
Isn't it a great idea?
I'm busy.
He has long eyelashes.
Minami.
My beautiful princess.
NEXT EPISODE
EP. 03 "A MAGICAL LOVE MALLET"
Marry me.
-What's this?
-Something more normal.
It's delicious.
Don't. Stop.
My grandma said this shrine
enshrines a magical mallet.
He used it and grew back
on a full moon.
Oh, my God.
I can finally go back.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!