Take care of Chiyomi, all right?
Yeah.
You know...
according to the original legend,
you need more than a mallet.
The old book said, after she
used the magical mallet,
the Princess went
to Cape Akebono and grew back.
Cape Akebono?
Give it a try.
Please...
Please grow me back!
Please grow Chiyomi back.
The day is here.
I can finally grow back!
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Ever since the day the boy I loved
came to my rescue...
I've felt every joy and heartache
of being with someone I love.
The Minami I love is not a chicken!
What about you?
You can't do anything on your own!
He's burning up.
At times I felt powerless...
I felt helpless.
A lot has happened.
You love Chobi!
Chiyomi, you're the one!
Your love is not one-sided!
You're already a part of me!
Minami!
I finally know that our feelings
were mutual.
Now our hearts beat as one.
I wanna grow back for him.
GOOD-BYE CHIYOMI, GOOD-BYE MINAMI
Why?
Will I stay like this forever?
Don't worry!
There has to be another way.
But I don't know what else I can do.
It's gonna be all right.
You can count on me.
Minami.
But...
Riku was so sure this would work,
but look at this.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
All right.
We came all this way.
How about we lodge here
for one more night?
He won't go home yet, will he?
Take care of Chiyomi, all right?
Yeah.
The old book said, after she
used the magical mallet...
the Princess went to Cape Akebono
and grew back.
Cape Akebono?
Give it a try.
He must be dating Chiyomi
and they will meet up.
Chiyomi?
Do you have any requests?
Yeah.
Where should we go?
Can you...
please take me home?
Home?
Not your home...
but my home.
Chiyomi?
I'll tell my parents about everything
that's happened.
Wait a minute. We don't know
if you can't grow back yet.
I can't be your burden like this.
Don't worry about me,
and you are not a burden.
Minami.
Is he okay? He's been
talking to himself a lot.
I think...
we need to forget about each other.
Let's make it like...
this all never happened.
Don't say that!
There's no way I can do that!
You'll never be happy
stuck with me like this!
I can't do anything for you.
Don't! I wanna stay with you.
But I can't!
I can't stand being your burden.
You'll regret it one day.
I'll regret if I leave you!
I know...
I'll protect you no matter what.
I won't leave you.
Minami.
I love you.
Stay with me!
I'm sorry.
We need to end this.
Minami!
Chiyomi.
Shit!
He's not moving.
Ouch...
What are we gonna do?
Shit!
Shut up! How the hell would I know?
Let's get outta here!
Minami?
Minami!
Wa-- Wait!
Stay with me! Please!
Minami?
Minami? Answer me please!
Minami!
Chiyomi?
Mom?!
Mom...
We gotta help him...!
What if Chiyomi transformed
into a little person too?
Mom!
Minami is not waking up!
What do we do?
Calm down!
Panicking won't help him!
We need to stay calm.
Hello? There has been an accident!
Come quickly!
NOMURA HOSPITAL
Doctor! How is he?
Will he be all right?
The operation was a success.
Bleeding in his brain is contained.
I don't see other trauma,
so let's wait and see.
I assume side-effects are unlikely.
Thank you, Doctor Kawamura!
Thank you so much.
So, he's your son.
He's young, he'll heal fast.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Thank you again.
That was great news!
Minami...
I'm so happy.
We're home.
I'm home!
Chiyomi! Where is she?
In here.
In what?
Dad?
I'm home.
I'm sorry about everything.
It's Chiyomi.
I see...
Asuka, why didn't you tell us
if you knew about this?
I mentioned it the other day!
I thought you were joking!
But you'd never believe me!
Even so...
What's done is done!
What matters is that she's home.
Dad...
She's so tiny and cute!
Welcome home, Chiyomi.
Welcome home.
I'm happy for you, sis.
I'm home.
He doesn't seem to be waking up.
He just had surgery,
but is this an expected?
Anesthesia should be wearing off.
He should be conscious by now.
We were so adorable!
Chiyomi?
-Chiyomi!
-What is it?
I heard Minami is still unconscious.
What?!
Daddy...
How could this happen?
Ritsuko! Thanks for coming.
Minami.
Why?
He should be awake by now.
But his prolonged coma...
is apparently abnormal.
I thought he was recovering...
The doctor said he may never wake up.
No way!
Daddy!
Mrs. Minami? The doctor
would like to speak to you.
Of course.
Ritsuko, can you stay
with him for a while?
-I'm going.
-I'm coming with you too.
Minami.
Mom?
Just for a while...
can we have a moment alone?
Minami?
Wake up.
Please open your eyes.
Please!
I'm so sorry, Minami.
I was only thinking of myself.
Even if I can't grow back...
I was happy to be by your side.
I'll never leave you again.
Even if you never wake up...
I love you, Minami.
You and me together forever!
Minami.
Minami!
Chiyomi?
Yeah.
It's me.
Can you see?
Good... you're safe.
Minami.
Thank God.
I'm glad.
Chiyomi?
Minami.
Minami... Look, I...
Chiyomi.
Yes, Minami.
-Chiyomi!
-Yes!
Chiyomi!
Yes!
Can you put something on?
Don't look!
Wait a sec!
I won't.
I'm okay now.
It's impossible.
The kiss...
Do you think a prince's kiss
will magically grow me back?
How does that work?
Darn it.
My plan backfired.
What?
I should've kissed you.
We can as much as we want.
Chiyomi, they're back...
Shunichi?
Chiyomi?
Oh, my!
Hey, it's Chiyomi!
Chiyomi!
-Where have you been?
-We were worried!
I was on a mission.
What? A mission... seriously?
Minami! Are you all right?
I'm all better.
Don't run off like that.
I'm still kind of weak.
Oops, I won't do it again!
You...
What?
What is this vibe?
Why are you two talking?
Didn't they hate each other?
Wait, while Chiyomi was away...
Did you and Minami...?
Yeah. We're dating now.
Hey! Minami!
Why not? We should be open.
Ami...
Ami!
I'm sorry...
I left you behind.
How could you?
I was worried to death!
Ami... I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry!
Let's do this!
This is Chiyomi's choreography.
The tournament is in a month!
We're gonna dance till we drop!
Yuka, music please!
Okay! Here we go!
Chiyomi! Minami!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
The bride was also a member
of this dance team last season!
That's right!
We got married right after
our high school graduation!
Chiyomi also danced that routine,
and won the dance tournament
last year!
Next up, the dance team member,
and the next captain, Yuka Ueno!
She wrote a song for the happy couple!
Take it away Yuka!
Yes! We get to hear Yuka sing!
Congratulations on your marriage!
I'll sing a song for your happy future.
Please enjoy.
"Just by your side"
Our small encounter
Led me to this big beginning
The days we spent together
I slowly cherished my love for you
Snuggled next to you
We walk side by side
It's like the moon in the sky
Though we may seem close
My outstretched arms
I can never reach you
I just love you
I always think of you
So much my heart aches
Longing for you for eternity
I just wanna be honest
And tell you that I love you
So forever and ever
Be by my side
She's so talented, huh?
She is.
We've finally come this far.
It still feels like a dream.
Really?
What about you?
Me?
I've never thought of marrying
anyone but you.
Stop crying and get a grip already.
You've been crying all day.
But, honey...
everything gets in my eyes
when I recall her.
She was just a little girl.
She was literally teeny tiny
last year.
You're beautiful.
Shoot. It's coming back
in my eyes again...
Oh, honey. Here, here.
I've always thought those two
would be together someday.
Me too.
So cute! Is it a boy or a girl?
It's a boy!
Did you hear that? So precious!
Is she a pretty bride?
So, will you two be next?
What?
Sayori?
Oddly you make a good couple.
Sayori.
Huh? What do you mean by oddly?
Here we go! Say cheese fondue!
Thanks.
Let's see.
You look really cute!
Really?
I'm good huh?
Me too! I want a picture with you!
Sure.
Riku? Can I call you my brother?
Big brother!
Asuka?
Hey, isn't your brother over there?
Riku, let's take another!
-No it's my turn!
-Riku, me too!
I should've taken a picture of Chiyomi
when she was tiny.
It's too late now.
We have one.
See?
It's Chiyomi!
See, it's you!
I know! I was in it too!
There you are.
Today marks exactly one year
since the day I turned tiny.
I'm off.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Did you finish packing?
I forgot my tracksuit and shoes!
You can't go without those!
Minami was accepted
to a med school nearby.
He's a med student now.
I moved in with Minami...
which is next door, you know.
We're in our honeymoon phase.
I can't stand two weeks
away from you.
Or so I thought.
Today I'm heading to the audition
I missed last year.
So, I'm off to Tokyo!
You're gonna be
a writer and a dancer?
Yeah.
I'll go when I finish this.
Is it almost done?
I'm writing the climax.
Climax?
The giant led Chobi to a special place.
That is...
Be careful.
Oh, my gosh, hard to believe
all this happened recently.
Yeah.
It reminds me of when I was tiny.
Is that all you remember?
What?
It's not the best crown.
Chiyomi?
I love you.
I want to be with you.
Marry me?
Burying her face into his chest,
she heard the sound she once heard.
Chiyomi.
Look!
They gazed over the rainbow.
It was the same rainbow
they saw together as children.
The rainbow we saw...
may have been an arch to our future.
Chobi... is no longer in his pocket.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION