I wanna go back to how it used to be...
back to when we were little once again...
Minami...
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Tokyo?
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo.
Please. I wanna do this.
Let me stay with you, Minami!
Wait. How can that happen?
Is it true your father disappeared?
He left us for some woman.
He's not my father anymore.
I hate you!
No way. Is that the thief?
FROM CHIYOMI
The thief is here.
What's wrong?
Sorry. I gotta go.
-Wait. Minami?
-I'm sorry!
What do you think you're doing?
-Why did you come?
-This is ridiculous.
What happened to your divorce papers?
I sent them.
She said she signed them
the last time I called her.
Watching someone you love sleeping...
is a happy moment for every girl in love.
Even in my tiny body...
feelings like that don't change.
Chiyomi?
No way.
Is it my turn...?
Don't worry, Minami.
I'll protect you.
Wait!
Stop! Wait a minute!
It's kind of tight in here. You got big...
I can't move. I can't breathe.
Wait! Get me out of here!
I can't be in your pocket.
Sayori?
Hey, can I kiss you?
Now? I'm too tiny for that.
You're so adorable. I wanna eat you.
She's gonna swallow me!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I guess.
Good morning.
Morning.
I KNOW I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH
Ami. Did you call Chiyomi?
Well, let's see...
That's odd.
There's no one here by that name.
No... Are you sure?
Yes, there's no one here
by the name of Chiyomi or Horikiri.
Sorry, I forgot.
I'll text her later
and tell her you're worried.
I hope she texts me soon.
Can I get through?
Sure.
Ami...
Riku...
Did he see me?
I think he saw me for a second.
What's wrong?
Minami?
What?
Well... I...
It looks like her.
Did you really make this?
Yeah.
Be nice to her.
Oops.
She drives me nuts.
Minami has a doll, too.
-That was better than mine.
-Riku?
Okay.
NOMURA HOSPITAL
DR. NOMURA - DIRECTOR
-Yes?
-Dad? It's me.
Perfect timing, Sayori.
-This is my daughter, Sayori.
-Hello.
Sayori, this is Dr. Reiko Koide
from Hokuryo University Hospital.
She's coming to work for us.
Nice to meet you, Sayori.
Likewise.
Now, if you'll excuse me, doctor.
Goodbye.
To what do I owe this rare visit?
Do you need something?
I don't need anything.
I'll buy you whatever you want.
It's about Minami.
Of course.
Dad?
Were you crazy about Minami's mother?
That's nonsense.
I'm just helping out an old friend
by hiring her.
Dad...
She turned down
my letter of recommendation.
She did?
There was nothing more I could do.
Sayori...
I have something to tell you, too.
What is it?
I'm thinking about getting married again.
What?
It's time I find happiness of my own.
-With whom?
-With Dr. Koide, whom you just met.
Wasn't she great?
Sayori, wait.
-Just do whatever you want.
-Sayori.
Do you actually think
you can have a happy marriage?
Have you ever thought
about why Mom left us?
This isn't the right place.
We'll talk about this later.
Why?
Why can't we talk here?
You value how you look
over your own daughter.
That's enough!
Sayori.
Excuse me.
What's this?
So, Shunichi did take these.
Hand-sewn?
Oh, no.
Hold on.
I'm gonna make you a pretty little dress.
Is Shunichi a pervert?
No way.
Wait.
In this, too?
I'm sorry, Shunichi.
He was sending an e-mail.
What? The address...
"oneinchprincess at beeble"?
I'm home!
Grandma?
-Hey, you're home.
-How do you feel?
Hey, Shunichi.
Asuka!
Asuka?
What are you doing here?
She's such a sweetheart.
Asuka came to check in on me.
I'm glad you seem well.
And I thought you'd help me out
with my studies,
so, I was waiting for you upstairs.
What is my sister up to?
I'm sorry about the mess.
I don't mind it at all.
So, what was I gonna ask you...
Asuka?
You see, I'm a guy...
You shouldn't be here like this.
Does that mean...
you see me as a girl?
Huh?
Go on. You can have your way with me.
Asuka!
I got you!
Asuka! Let's just study.
My bad. Let me see.
I'm home!
Hey, Mom.
Come on in, Sayori.
This way.
Hello.
What?
A houseguest?
Sayori?
Hi, Minami.
Make yourself at home.
Now Sayori is here?
What's up with girls today?
This is nice.
It's delicious. You're a great cook.
Really?
-Do you like it?
-Yeah, it's great.
Sorry we made you cook for us.
Not at all.
I don't have a mother,
so, I always cook for myself.
I'm sorry to bother you
when you're not well.
Don't worry. I'm all better now.
She has an appetite, too.
This is a treat.
This is really nice.
I always eat alone.
I'm sorry. What's gotten into me?
It's all right. You can let it all out.
Grandma.
Were you shocked
about your father's engagement?
You know...
I'm a daddy's girl.
So, when my so-called mother left,
I got over it pretty fast.
It was better
than seeing my mother cry all the time.
It's the opposite of our family.
Listen.
It's best to forget
about those who've left us behind.
But...
I'm starting to understand
what my mother must've felt like.
My father paid no attention to her.
My mother would cook for him,
but he never came home to eat it.
Now I can see...
this is how my mom felt.
The ones who leave
have their reasons, too.
But my father...
he's about to make the same mistake.
He never loved my mother.
He just married his professor's daughter.
But really...
he loved someone else.
I think my mother was lonely.
I'm sorry to bring this up.
I know we all have problems.
It's okay.
It's all right.
You poor thing.
Minami?
I forgot my towel in my room.
Could you get it for me?
Sure.
It was a rough day.
Yup.
You and Sayori have a lot in common.
That's why you...
What?
Nothing.
Go on, tell me.
It's nothing.
Minami, are you still up?
Hey.
Were you asleep?
No.
I couldn't sleep.
Can I come in?
What?
My dad told me.
Your mom turned down
my dad's recommendation.
-Yeah.
-Are you okay with that?
You're going so far away
for a school with a scholarship.
Do you know about all their restrictions?
I'll try other schools, too.
My dad can get you
into Takase Medical University.
You can get a scholarship
and you can stay here...
Thanks for everything.
But...
I'm not cut out for that.
Sorry.
But thanks.
You know how I feel, right?
What?
How much longer
are we gonna stay this way?
No! Get away from him! Please!
Don't you... like me?
Well...
No, Minami...
Is there someone else?
What?
Could it be... Chiyomi?
No way.
Then can we do this?
Don't! Minami!
You're so adorable. I wanna eat you.
She's gonna swallow me!
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
Do what?
I'm sorry, but...
I can't be doing this.
I have other things
that I should be doing right now.
So...
Okay, I'm done.
You're like a neurotic virgin.
Can't you see...
my heart can get hurt, too?
Sayori.
Good night.
Hey.
She's gone.
Chiyomi?
Why are you crying?
It's nothing.
-No, it's not.
-Just leave me alone!
The giant is sweet to me
only because I'm so small.
A suitable woman for him
should be his own kind.
Someone who can embrace him
and mend this heart.
All I can do is dance in his palms.
LITTLE MISS CHOBI IN YOUR POCKET
There are updates...
I could only be his burden.
I shouldn't dream
about receiving his embrace.
Chiyomi?
I knew from the start.
But I can't stop my tears.
Minami...
Sayori?
It's your turn, Minami.
Wait.
Wait... stop!
Minami? Minami!
Oh?
So, this is where you've been hiding.
Let go of me, Sayori!
Can't you be quiet?
Ouch!
Minami!
Hey! Let me out!
Chiyomi?
You can't do this!
Get away from each other! No!
Just relax, okay?
We can't.
-But Chiyomi...
-Minami!
You can't do this!
Don't!
I'm going home.
Okay.
I'm giving this back to you.
How was it? Not bad, huh?
Never...
bring me this crap.
Got it.
This is not what you really need.
I've got you covered.
Karaoke?
What are you up to? I'm not gonna sing.
A blind group date.
A what?
Listen, you gotta loosen up.
If you're girl crazy,
you gotta find release.
-I'm leaving.
-Wait, wait, wait.
Two college girls are coming. See?
They're both hot, right? We're lucky.
Will you look at her?
They're on their way.
-They're coming!
-Let go of me!
The party's here! I'm Nanami.
I'm Hiroe. Enchanté.
Real high-school boys!
Are you boys virgins?
Don't know about that one,
but I bet Pretty Boy is taken.
It's actually the opposite.
I did it already.
But him... probably not.
Really?
Don't be afraid.
The cutest cherry boy ever!
If you'll excuse me.
Shaw, I'm sorry.
Chiyomi?
Hey.
Minami...
your grandma found me today.
What?
She saw you?
I went out, and when I came back...
No! Let me out! Please!
Let me out!
Oh, my.
Please, let me explain.
So, this is where you've been hiding?
I've been looking for you.
Why aren't you surprised?
I thought you'd be in shock
seeing me like this.
You're cute as a button.
What? Was that all?
Then she gave me some treats,
we talked for a while, and she let me go.
But she didn't say anything.
She was just cooking dinner.
Do you smell that?
What? This chair costs 30,000 yen?
What a rip-off.
I've never heard of anything like this.
Grandma, the stove is on.
How silly. Who'd buy such a thing?
Only a fool would buy that.
-Grandma, the stove.
-What?
Hey, Noboru.
-Huh?
-I found something really rare today.
Guess what it was.
Grandma?
One-Inch Princess!
The One-Inch Princess came
to see me today.
One-Inch Princess?
I hope she comes to see me again.
oneinchprincess@beeble.co.jp
TO: AMI
I wish she'd write more often.
oneinchprincess@beeble.co.jp
TO: JOJI HORIKIRI
This e-mail address...
What?
"Oneinchprincess@beeble"?
"Oneinchprincess..."
Did my sister use that tablet
to send us the video?
If that's so...
Shunichi and Chiyomi are...
I hope your grandma is okay.
I don't know what happened.
I'm worried.
Isn't it too late for you to eat?
-It's not 10 yet.
-Crazy rules.
So sweet! Delicious!
I love these store-bought puddings.
Hey, you got caramel on your face.
-Where?
-There, left cheek.
Right here.
Feels like Minami's become sweeter
toward me.
Maybe...
Hey!
Maybe not.
NEXT EPISODE
EP. 07 "18-YEAR-OLD PROPOSAL"
My dad never proposed to my mom.
I don't think he ever loved me.
You made this for me?
Chiyomi has an impossible crush?
Then who is the giant?
I can't stand this.
Please. Tell me where Chiyomi is.
-My family is falling apart.
-Asuka...
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
Dad, you gotta tell Mom how you feel.
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!