"So then, the One Inch Samurai...
wore needle as a sword on his hip
made for him by the old man,
boarded a bowl for a ship
given to him by the old lady,
and sailed off to the capital."
That's cool for a little guy.
That's right, although his body was small,
he was very brave.
I wanna see him.
There is a legend in our city
about a One Inch Princess.
One Inch Princess?
Really? Is that true?
Well...
I wonder...
One Inch Princess.
One Inch Princess?
Where are you?
Hello?
Miss One Inch Princess?
Where are you, One Inch Princess?
Over here?
I hope we can find her.
We'll find her.
Maybe behind these grasses.
It's a frog.
Maybe over here?
One Inch Princess.
Where is she?
Oh, no. I got all wet.
What happened? Are you okay?
One Inch Princess...
She was for real. I just saw her.
Look, over there.
You see the stream over there?
What about over there?
I love you, Chiyomi.
I love you.
I love you, too, Minami.
So, you and me together forever.
What?
Together forever.
Pinky promise.
-Cross my heart and hope to die
-Stick a needle in my eye
Minami, look over there.
Awesome.
I fell asleep.
The sun's up already.
Why that dream now?
All right. Let's do some more work.
AUTHOR: MICHAELA MOON RABBIT
THE BLUE FAIRY - EPISODE 10
Childhood memories are unreliable.
Reality and fantasy are muddled together.
I don't know what's real anymore.
The One Inch Princess, was she for real?
The beautiful rainbow,
was that an illusion?
What about the promise
I made with Minami?
Morning.
Chiyomi, don't be late
on your first day of school.
LONG FORGOTTEN FIRST LOVE
I'll just have juice today.
The new school year starts today?
Lilacs are in season.
The language of flowers for lilacs...
Did you stay up late?
Net surfing for dance sequences?
Wrong.
Are you studying hard?
I guess I'm sort of studying.
You're a senior now,
you need to be ready for your exam.
Okay, okay.
Asuka, you need to get
into a good high school.
You girls need to know how lazy you are,
just like your father.
Okay. I got your message.
Honey. you need to be concerned, too.
Because I'm too lazy.
Hi, Chiyomi.
Could you give this to Shunichi?
What?
He forgot his lunch...
Thanks, here.
Sure...
My lunch.
I'm sorry.
This is from your mom.
Okay, bye.
No way. That just did not happen.
TATEYAMA DAIICHI HIGH SCHOOL
Chiyomi? Earth to Chiyomi?
What?
What's wrong? You zoned out.
It's nothing...
I'm so happy you're in my class, Ami.
We have the same course.
Thank God Riku is with us.
Show me your homework again?
Yes, please.
Is that all I am to you?
That's not true.
How convincing.
Sayori's in our class, too?
Pheromone?
Who?
Oh, you're talking about Sayori.
I can't stand it,
watching the guys go crazy over her.
Check her out.
She's so hot.
Man.
She's a knockout.
Same class with her,
can you believe our luck?.
I wanna go out with her.
She melts my heart like butter.
I'm not like them.
Minami.
CLASS PRESIDENT ELECTION: BOYS
This means our boy class president
is Minami.
Minami, we're counting on you.
No way. I wanna work with Minami.
I wanna be class president
with Minami, too.
Your neighbor is as popular as ever.
He's a cold fish.
Next up, the girls.
CLASS PRESIDENT ELECTION: GIRLS
Sayori.
Chiyomi.
Why me? My grades suck.
Remember last year?
Come to our crepe shop!
Have our crepes!
That's because our class wasn't
selling enough.
What about field day?
That's because our class was losing.
Now everyone knows you elevate the class.
This is the last one.
Chiyomi.
No way.
This means Chiyomi will be
our girl class president.
Wait a minute...
Do it.
Can we count on you?
But... wait. I don't know...
Ms. Oono.
Yes, Sayori?
If it's okay, I really want to run
for class president once again.
But Chiyomi was just elected president.
Chiyomi, do you wanna do it?
Me?
Not really.
Well, I...
I wanna be class president.
Ms. Oono.
Why hesitate? She's willing.
You're right.
Since Chiyomi is not so willing...
shall we ask Sayori to do it?
Okay, Chiyomi?
Chiyomi?
Yes. Of course.
Give a round of applause
to our new girl class president.
My best regards.
Likewise.
You know, the tournament is coming up.
Can you two help with our choreography?
Okay. We got it.
Really?
Yeah. I really wanna
do something really cool...
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Choreography for the tournament...
It's gonna be great.
We have to start thinking.
You know what...
Hey, girls.
Riku, I didn't know
handcraft club worked so late.
Well, yeah.
What's up, Chiyomi?
To tell you the truth...
SOLO DANCE TEAM AUDITION
What? You're kidding.
Your idol dance team?
I wanna audition, too.
Right?
It's in Tokyo?
Audition in Tokyo? I can't go.
My parents would never let me.
That's the problem.
If I pass, I have to move to Tokyo.
Move to Tokyo?
If you pass, are you dropping out?
Your parents will kill you.
I know.
You can't be serious.
Just a bit.
Hey, Chiyomi?
Let's talk about this another time.
I actually have plans today.
Fine.
Riku, can you walk her home?
Bye, guys.
What? Wait.
Chiyomi, aren't you interested in dating?
It's not that I don't,
but I don't have faith in it.
No faith, huh?
Okay, then...
Have you ever liked anyone?
Maybe when I was little,
but I forgot all about it.
All right.
I got into reading novels
on the Internet lately,
and I found this cool online novel.
An online novel?
Yup.
Thanks for walking me home.
Not at all.
Remember Blue Fairy by
Michaela Moon Rabbit I talked about?
It's really great.
I really love it.
And you.
Will I? I guess I have to read it.
Yeah, you should.
Bye.
Chiyomi?
Well...
What is it?
Never mind.
Tell me.
What is it?
No... I'll tell you tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
Riku read my novel.
All right.
A fairy loses its magic
when it falls in love.
The fairy also loses its smile...
and ages very quickly.
Soon it will fall into an eternal slumber.
But when that love is reciprocated,
the fairy will turn into a human
in exchange for its magic.
Humans age, but their smile...
Hey, Michaela Moon Rabbit.
Ms. Oono.
Don't worry, I haven't told a soul.
Promise me.
Why not? You're doing something you love.
No way. I'll be mortified
and never come to school.
Now you're famous among readers
of online novels.
It's only luck. I just wrote
everything I had bottled up inside.
Then it must be your own
unique imaginary scenery?
No, now you're exaggerating.
What is this about?
First of all...
This is for you.
But it's not my birthday.
Yeah, I know.
I wanted to give it to you yesterday,
but I couldn't.
What is it?
It's so cute.
Did you make this?
-Yeah.
-It's amazing.
Moon and rabbit?
Does this mean...?
I'm a big fan of Michaela Moon Rabbit.
Okay.
That's why I want you to have it.
You knew.
Sorry I didn't tell you.
So, you knew about it yesterday.
I just couldn't tell you yesterday.
Darn, all this time you knew.
What are they blathering about?
Go on. Tell her.
So, listen.
I...
I love...
Michaela Moon Rabbit.
Thanks.
I love...
you.
Chiyomi Horikiri.
Yes.
What?
I know you got a lot on your plate...
and you don't have the time.
But I had to tell you
how I feel about you.
I wanna nominate myself.
So, I'm not gonna rush you.
Riku?
I'll walk away if there's someone.
But if there isn't someone else...
I'll always be waiting for you
to choose me.
Riku is such a great guy.
He's fun to talk to. He's sweet.
And he likes me,
which means he clearly has great taste.
Shoot.
The rain... I forgot my umbrella.
Are you studying for med school?
Why?
Why does it make me cry?
I love you, Chiyomi.
I love you.
I'm...
I'm in love with Minami...
all this time...
You're going to Tokyo?
Explain yourself.
My favorite dance team
is having an audition.
But you don't have to go now,
you have your exams this year.
But I wanna go now. I wanna go.
You're not going.
You're too young to go
to Tokyo all by yourself.
I agree. Your silly dance team can wait.
"Silly dance team"?
Well, I'm not going to college.
I won't take the exams.
I know what I want,
and college is just a waste of time.
Listen to yourself. You got into
a decent high school, don't waste it.
Your mom is right.
You'll regret this later.
Why are you two suddenly teaming up?
You never listened to your mom?
What are you saying?
I know you had a shotgun wedding!
Honey...
Chiyomi. We're not done here.
The lightning is getting closer.
What?
Chiyomi?
BUOY ME A BOTTLE OF SOY SAUCE. MOM
Why is she making me run errands?
It's "buy," not "buoy."
Are you okay?
Are you studying for med school?
Yeah.
I don't mean to pry,
but can you afford it?
Your mother is single, right?
Why don't you ask my father?
I'm sure he'll help you find a solution.
Minami.
What?
What do you want?
I'm going home.
Why do you ignore me?
I said, why do you ignore me?
-No, I'm not.
-Yes, you are.
You're nice to Sayori.
Were you with her this whole time?
Are you gonna date her?
Please. It has nothing to do with you.
You're right.
I'm nothing to you.
Sorry. I didn't mean to...
Damn.
You need to stop showing up
everywhere I go.
When did I ever?
Earlier, when I was with Sayori.
-I didn't plan it.
-Not that I care.
I'm out here because
I fought with my parents.
A fight?
They're mad at me
for not wanting to college.
You're not?
I have my goals.
They wouldn't hear me out.
You must be joking.
You're a spoiled brat.
What?
What would you say that? It hurts.
We used to be best friends.
Why?
Don't you get it?
I can't stand you anymore.
Hey!
Hold on!
Wait!
This place...
Where is she? Her phone is dead.
I thought she'd come home after my text.
Let's go find her.
-A storm's outside.
-That's why we go.
Can you two chill out?
Chiyomi. She's home.
-Hey, Sakaizawa.
-Is Chiyomi home?
No, why?
Just as I thought. I saw her at the park.
Officer, he slapped her.
Stop that.
She was in tears. I'm gonna arrest you.
Arrest him.
Stop the nonsense. Now take me to her.
My jacket.
Dad, shoes.
Come on.
Be careful.
It's getting worse.
No way. Come on back.
Wait.
Shunichi...
-Don't go.
-Shunichi.
I'm so sorry.
I hate you!
Shunichi, let's go inside.
Bye, Mom.
Hey.
Don't you get it?
I can't stand you anymore.
What happened to us?
We used to be best friends.
I wanna go back to when it used to be...
back to when we were little once again...
Minami...
Why?
What would you say that? It hurts.
We used to be best friends.
Why?
What happened?
I turned into a One Inch Princess?
No...
No way!
Chiyomi?
NEXT EPISODE
EP. 02 "UNDER THE SAME ROOF?!"
I'm over here, Minami.
Chiyomi's gone missing?
Just between you and me,
I suspect she eloped.
They're gonna think I've been kidnapped.
There is someone suspicious...
right here among us.
This bathtub is perfect for me.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!