I wanna go back to how it used to be...
back to when we were little once again...
Minami...
Chiyomi!
I'm over here, Minami!
Tokyo?!
What is this?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm auditioning in Tokyo!
Let me stay with you, Minami!
Is it true your father disappeared?
He left us for some woman.
He's not my father anymore.
I hate you!
No way, is that the thief?
What happened to your divorce papers?
I sent them!
She said she signed them
when I last called her.
Why won't she file them?
What?
Here you go.
Wow, the sea breeze feels great!
It's been three weeks since
my secret life with Minami started.
My feelings for Minami
are growing more than ever.
Stop worrying.
Even if someone finds out,
I'll protect you no matter what.
What do you mean by "protect"?
Exactly as it sounds.
Hey, Minami?
How do you really feel about me?
I wanna know.
Minami?
What is it?
Nothing.
THE BLUE FAIRY
I'm home.
Grandma!
Tomiko!
Grandma?
Grandma!
NOMURA HOSPITAL
I hope she's okay.
Shunichi.
How is she?
She's stable for now.
But she'll be hospitalized
for a full examination.
Can you take this to reception?
Sure.
Hey, I have to go.
Wait for me.
Okay.
What?
Ouch!
Oh gosh! That hurt!
Look what I found!
You are...
Chiyomi?
So, you have no idea
where your sister is?
Unfortunately.
Ouch!
Don't run away, Fairy!
Fairy?
Maybe it has nothing to do with Chobi...
but I saw a little person too!
What?
On the next door's balcony.
Next door? Minami's place?
Yes!
I know it's unbelievable, right?
Maybe I...
Wait. It's possible.
You believe me?
I think you saw a doll.
A what?
So, Minami can make
a more elaborate doll.
Is that your mom?
She seems really sweet.
But Mommy hates me.
What?
Mommy!
Miyu, did you tell your doctor
you don't want the surgery?
Can't you see we're all worried
about you?
I wish you'd listen to me for once.
If you keep saying no,
you'll never get better.
In here.
Minami!
Hello, she's my mother in law.
This is my son.
Nice to meet you.
Minami! I'm over here.
Miyu, will you be our granny's
new friend?
Minami, please find me.
Is there anything you need?
All right.
I have to get back to work.
See you later, okay?
Honey, pouting won't
make you get any better.
Excuse me.
Have a nice day.
Emiko?
Grandma?
Tomiko, are you awake?
Yes. Where am I?
You're at the hospital.
Tomiko, you fell ill today.
Oh, yes.
Noboru was there to help me.
So, you're staying here
to take a full examination.
I'm sorry to bring this on you.
Don't worry about a thing
and get plenty of rest.
Well, aren't you a cute neighbor.
Nice to meet you.
I think I'll like it here.
I have the night-shift.
Sorry about dinner.
Yeah.
I have to get back to work.
Alrighty.
I have to go look for something.
No!
Look for what?
Just some stuff.
I'm over here! You're looking for me!
Chiyomi?
Where are you?
Chiyomi!
So, your name is One Inch Princess...
Yes, little lady,
I am the One Inch Princess.
You know...
the One Inch Princess only comes
to those who needs her.
Who need her?
That's right.
She appears only to those
who strive for happiness.
So, she will disappear if you tie her down
or be mean to her.
Got it. I'm sorry, Fairy.
You call me a fairy.
Yup. You're a fairy to me.
So, you might disappear
because I'm a bad girl.
You're a good girl.
Nope.
I always do stuff Mommy hates
and I also make her mad!
Mommy doesn't smile because of me.
That's why I got sick.
-That's not true.
-But it's true!
You should show your drawings
to your mommy.
I think you'll make her smile.
But I can't.
Mommy only thinks of me as a bad girl.
She won't like my stupid drawing.
If it wasn't for me,
Mommy could be happier.
Miyu...
That's not true.
No mother hates their child...
not one in the entire universe.
You're lying!
I'm not.
Every mother loves their child!
Miyu, you love your mother so much...
and you deserve to be happy.
Isn't that why you came to her?
Yes, little lady.
Now go to sleep.
Good night.
Shoot... I can't get away now...
MIYU WAKASUGI
TOMIKO MINAMI
Miyu.
I'm sorry you're suffering.
I'm so sorry.
Minami.
Thank you for everything.
But...
it's time to say goodbye.
What do you mean?
I mustn't...
I can no longer live here with you.
I must...
return to the moon.
Return to the moon?
Are you kidding me?
Thank you.
And...
goodbye, Minami.
Chiyomi!
Hey, wait!
Chiyomi, wait!
Don't go, Chiyomi!
Chiyomi!
Chiyomi...
Noboru?
Did you find it?
Grandma.
No.
I couldn't.
Could it be...
the One Inch Princess?
What?
Your One Inch Princess is right here.
Chiyomi.
Minami!
You idiot!
I was worried about you.
Minami.
Shunichi!
What's up?
I'm off to the hospital to see Tomiko.
I'll go with you.
Okay, then I'll buy some cake
and wait for you outside.
Okay.
Wake up! We're going to the hospital.
Miyu must be looking for you.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to take your time.
Not at all. Tomiko is my best friend.
Really?
Thank you.
But can grandma eat all these?
Those are for the nurses
who are taking care of your grandma.
Of course.
I'm so sorry!
-Let me get you a towel!
-Are you okay?
Here.
Thanks.
You came prepared.
My pants too!
You should go home and change?
I think I will.
It's so cold!
This sucks!
What?
Shunichi has a cute handkerchief.
Dad, Mom and Asuka. How are you?
This is it.
What does this mean?
So, that's what Miyu thinks of
her mom.
Yeah.
But I know Miyu's mom
is really worried about her.
Because...
I'm sorry you're suffering.
Hey, Minami?
Do you think we can help her?
Shunichi?
Asuka?
Who were you talking to?
What?
Was I talking to myself again? Oops.
What's that?
What are you hiding? I wanna see it.
It's nothing.
Could it be...
Chiyomi?
I knew it.
Hey...
can I see her?
Asuka.
What's going on?
That...
We don't know.
I don't know. No one does.
Are you really Chiyomi?
I'm sorry about everything.
Don't be.
I should've known sooner. I'm sorry.
Asuka.
Hey.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Miyu does love her mom very much.
Yup.
They're coming.
Here we are.
Stay here until your mommy
comes back, okay?
Hey, Miyu.
Fairy!
I'm here to cast a spell on you.
Don't you wanna know
how your mommy feels?
Hey! Miyu's mom?!
Please come with me!
Miyu!
Sweetheart?
Miyu.
She seems much better now.
Miyu was in pain.
I was gonna call the nurse,
but she stopped me.
So I found you instead.
You need to know Mommy
is always here for you.
Miyu was drawing you all day long.
Watermelon at the beach
Miyu and mommy
All of her drawings are of you and Miyu.
I love mommy
I'm sorry, Miyu.
I had no idea how you felt...
and I...
I couldn't tell you how I really felt.
You must've been lonely.
I'm so sorry.
Miyu, I love you more than anything
in the whole world.
I love you very, very much.
So, honey, please...
will you stay with me?
Please...
get well soon.
Mommy.
What happened?
Please! Save my daughter!
I beg you!
What happened to Miyu?
I'm not sure, but she was in pain.
Will she be all right?
Doctor, how is she?
Are you happy about something?
What?
I see a big smile.
She's all right.
There's nothing to worry about.
Let me know if you need me.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Doctor!
What is it?
I was thinking...
I'll take the surgery.
Miyu!
Let's schedule it later.
Yes, please!
What happened?
-We'll beat this thing!
-I can beat it!
Good girl!
Minami, I need to talk to you.
Sayori...
I'm sorry to spring this on you.
Not at all.
I guess you should know by now
how I feel about...
But I want to clear the air.
If you're turning me down,
I want you to do it now.
You know, I need to make up
my future plan for romance.
Do you...
like Chiyomi?
I...
finally realized that...
for the longest time...
Chiyomi was always in my heart...
for always.
So...
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
The most humiliating way
for a refusal ever.
Thanks.
I'm gonna leave now.
Can you at least watch me
until I'm gone?
I will.
That's a mean old lady!
Yeah, I feel sorry for Kotoko.
What in the world are you talking about
with Sayori, Minami?
A little kindness goes a long way.
But, you see, that's not Irie's character!
Kanae... was it? How is she?
I owe you an apology.
Don't. It's too late anyway.
We're having a baby this October.
I see.
Congratulations.
So, it's time we settle this.
Here.
What is that?
The divorce papers you sent me.
I saw you here yesterday,
so I brought them just in case.
I'm sorry it took so long.
But I wanted to give this to you
in person.
Bad disguise.
Deception was never your strong suit.
That jerk!
You asshole!
Taizou!
Do you have any idea
what Emiko went through?
Taizou!
She worked day and night!
She put food on the table
and raised her kid on her own!
Emiko...
Shunichi.
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of my mother from now...
No, you won't.
I'm gonna take care
of Mom and grandma.
I made that decision when you left us.
I'm sorry. But Tomiko is our family.
I understand.
Shunichi, take good care of them.
I don't need you to tell me.
And...
Shunichi, don't give up on kendo.
You still got a score to settle.
You better make her happy
this time around.
Oh, my! How could this be?
We gotta cheer for Irie.
Minami!
Is Sayori your girlfriend now?
Grandma, I'm taking off.
Thanks for coming by.
I think I'm gonna stay awhile.
Hey, come on, Princess.
Yeah.
Fairy?
Thank you for the magic!
You're most welcome.
See you later.
What?
What is it, Minami?
Don't...
Don't you go away.
Because...
this is where you belong.
What? What did you just say?
Nothing.
Forget it.
NEXT EPISODE
EP.09 "A ROMANTIC GETAWAY FOR TWO"
This is Chiyomi?
I heard she's an online novelist.
Now he knows!
Minami can't read it!
Mom is gonna file
a missing person's report!
I know you're the giant!
The One Inch Princess went
to Cape Akebono and grew back.
It's like a secret love affair!
Oh, God, please grow me back!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
STAY TUNED FOR NEXT TIME!