3 MONTHS LATER
Can we go with 20 inch increments?
Yes, it's cheaper that way.
All right, I'll go and confirm
the colors now.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right.
Hot.
Tokyo, hot!
We're proud to introduce
our new collaboration line.
LAUNCH OF EMOTION'S SECOND LINE
Em by Emotion. Samples are now finalized.
Mizuki Nishizawa is our designer.
She's worked under chief designer
Mayumi Nanjo for the past eight years,
and has been entrusted with this project.
Please, take a look at the products.
We've used an abundance of detailed lace
in order to give it a glamorous look.
Each color scheme
creates a different feel,
so you have different options,
depending on your mood.
Thank you very much.
Em by Emotion targets
20- and 30-year-olds
who want to add luxury into their lives.
We would like to create products
that reflect this desire.
We are now passing around
promotional photos.
-No, it's these ones.
-I'm sorry.
The concept was called,
"Meeting a beautiful you."
Emotion is custom-made for the...
Excuse me, Ms. Ida,
will you stand here for a moment?
But Mizuki should be the one who...
Don't worry, this is just for
an internal presentation.
All right, then.
It looks good.
You're very photogenic.
We can probably use this as is.
That's too flattering, Mr. Fujimura.
The image of the designer is important.
It would be wonderful if President Nanjo
could be the face of Em.
But Em is factory made, not handmade.
Nanjo's very specific about that.
She's a stubborn, old shopkeeper.
Shall we make this one more decorative?
Yes!
How about this for lace and ribbons?
I apologize for being so difficult.
I love challenges.
I'd love to add a cute charm here.
Let's see.
Excuse me.
I'd like to show something to Ms. Hayashi.
That is too cute!
These other ones are cute too!
It's exactly what I was looking for!
Excuse me.
Here are the parts for Ms. Hayashi.
Leave them there, please.
Of course.
Are you all right, boss?
It can't be helped.
Mizuki and Fumi aren't here,
and I made the mistake
of having you fill in on your own.
I only have myself to blame.
I apologize.
However...
you did a good job with the charms.
That's exactly the kind of response
that customers appreciate.
Is that an actual compliment?
Take it as you will.
Yes, ma'am.
But...
Wasn't there an important presentation
over at Vanderbilt's?
What?
Are you worried about that?
No.
I was just wondering
if you didn't need to be there?
What?
-Hey.
-Yes?
These numbers haven't been corrected yet.
I'm sorry.
And the wording here is
totally misleading.
I'm sorry.
Fumi.
Aren't you getting a little too friendly
with Mr. Fujimura?
Please, keep your head on straight.
Mizuki!
Everything's going well.
You don't have to worry.
Worry about what?
Well, you seem a little stressed.
Of course I am.
We were only supposed to
start with three series.
But Mr. Fujimura spoke with Fumi,
and now suddenly, there's five.
The designs, the materials.
I had to do all the work.
It was only possible thanks to you.
Don't placate me.
You think that makes me happy?
In any case, Fumi needs to cool off.
Fujimura is too slick with his words.
If we listen to him,
Em's going to run into problems.
Oh, my.
What?
I thought the pressure was getting to you,
but you're completely clearheaded.
EMOTION'S SECOND LINE
EMOTION TEAM
BOSS - REIKO - MAYU
EM BY EMOTION TEAM
MIZUKI - FUMIKA - SARUHASHI - HIME
-Good morning.
It's been lonely around here, hasn't it?
It's almost time to launch Em.
What do you mean? You guys have me!
-You're looking good as always, Mayu.
-Here!
Work hard, intern.
Yes, ma'am.
What was the boss thinking?
Hiring a part-time worker like that.
What kind of college senior says
they don't need to look for a job?
I wonder if the boss
is really doing all right?
She's working on all the orders herself.
Her pride keeps her working.
Yes, that's true.
Are you feeling a little left behind?
Of course not!
I don't feel that way at all.
Please!
I'd like to be involved with Em too!
I knew you'd ask.
I'll continue to get fabric and parts
so that it doesn't affect your work.
-So, please...
-No.
I want to see firsthand
the process of starting a new line.
I want to learn.
You.
Do you think that selling
to a hundred customers
is more important than helping
that single customer in front of you?
No.
You can't compare them.
They're completely different things.
That's correct.
Well...
you've grown into an Emotion employee.
Please, don't make fun of me.
But, you're attracted to large numbers.
Well...
Working with a lot of people,
creating something that could make
many people happy,
did sound a little interesting.
That's also correct.
But right now, it's important to endure.
Endure?
Good evening.
Were you looking for something?
You're still here.
I was looking for the Fujix catalog.
Oh, that.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-What's this?
-That's...
Just for me. So I can practice.
You were studying.
I didn't go to fashion school,
so I don't have very much knowledge.
Design, patterns, sewing.
There's so much I have to learn.
That's bad.
I know.
No, no! I meant me!
What?
The boss would be impressed with you.
No, she would just be very sarcastic.
It wouldn't mean much to her.
Well, the boss is a perfectionist.
But...
has the boss
made any mistakes in the past?
Why do you ask?
She said something about enduring.
It's nothing. Never mind.
EM BY EMOTION
The presentation went well.
I've been asked why we don't produce
on a larger scale.
I mean, 100 units per series
is such a small number
from our standpoint.
It's nice to be praised.
This is just in theory, of course,
but have you considered
nationwide production?
We'd cover the initial costs.
You could make 1,000 units per series.
That would be a hit for sure.
So, 5,000 for five series?
Nanjo would never approve.
Production is already underway.
Why settle for such a small scale?
In business, that's unthinkable.
Let's stop.
I mean, it's no different
from your small store, then.
Em by Emotion is a wonderful product.
I can proudly push the product
to our customers nationwide.
You can even start your own brand.
Thank you for your kind words,
but it's not very realistic.
You're so lucky.
I wish someone would tell me that.
Fumi.
You have an aura about you, Ms. Ida.
You can easily become a fashion icon.
Well, that was smooth!
Yes, I'm impressed.
Did I lay it on too thick?
You told the boss you wanted
to work with Em too?
Mayu!
I'm not unsatisfied with my current job.
But there's so little I can do here.
It kind of makes me feel bad.
The boss is able to do everything herself.
It's the same for me.
Mr. Saruhashi does just fine without me.
I shouldn't complain!
I just need to do what I can.
Yes.
I tried this at the market,
and it was delicious.
You can have it.
It looks so good, but I can't.
Here, I got it.
Right?
Oh, my.
-You're so friendly with each other.
-How nice.
It's not like that!
Yeah, they're not like that!
About the October trunk show.
I'd like you two to produce it.
That'll be a challenge.
Did something happen, boss?
It's a matter of logistics.
My hands are full just filling the orders.
And so--
If you had to plan the show as well,
it would be too much, boss.
Unfortunately, I'm not young anymore.
Fumi and Mizuki can come back
once things at Em have settled down.
I'm so sorry we can't help now.
Don't worry, I know.
That's why, this time,
I'd like for you both to work on the show.
That's a great idea.
You have to challenge the young, right?
-What about me?
-You, be quiet!
It might be a nice change of pace.
So, it's decided!
Of course, I'll decide on the theme.
Your first job will be to gather material.
Find ideas to inspire my creative juices,
and write a proposal for me.
Yes, ma'am.
Good luck!
Yes!
EMOTION TRUNK SHOW
MAYU - HIME
These are the past spring
and summer lineups.
An encounter.
La Primavera by Botticelli.
Resort.
Van Gogh's Sunflowers?
Should we go with an art theme, then?
Perhaps.
Should we hit the museums?
Should we use a foreign image?
-The Carnival in Rio de Janeiro?
-Brazil does have a strong lingerie image.
And it's summery.
Salsa from Cuba and Puerto Rico
could be interesting too.
How about New York's Ray Barretto
for the show's music?
It might give off an urban feel.
Salsa.
You know a lot about music.
But....
will it be difficult to visually present
Latin culture?
Anna...
What happened?
Are you hungry?
Should we eat something?
No, I'm not hungry.
What is it this time?
We got sandals last time.
Is it makeup?
You can use anything of mine you want.
I can't!
We're different sizes.
You wear the expensive ones from Emotion.
What?
I need a bra.
Everyone has cute ones.
You're making them now, right, Mom?
Cute, inexpensive ones?
It's your debut work, right?
Please?
Just one.
Can I?
Of course.
You can have one as a gift.
I can show it off in the locker room.
And then your bra will sell like hotcakes.
You think?
The February issue.
Here it is!
THE 38TH ANNUAL DESIGN AWARD
TOKYO FASHION INSTITUTE FUMIKA IDA
APPEALING TO WOMEN OF HER GENERATION
BY WEARING HER OWN DESIGNS...
-So, this is Latin culture?
-Yes.
Let's dance!
Come on!
I can't dance!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
You gotta dance!
Good morning!
Good morning.
You have cleaning to do!
How's the show coming along?
I turned in the proposal yesterday.
Already? That's fast work!
I can't believe I pulled an all-nighter.
My skin.
I'm sorry, Reiko.
I'm going home.
If it's just for this morning,
that's fine.
Great, I'll leave it to you.
Boss!
What about the proposal?
Yes.
2015 TRUNK SHOW PROPOSAL
Sorry, I didn't feel it.
So, it isn't good?
If you're going to push for a Latin theme,
there should be more passion.
Something that expresses excitement.
You two are too serious!
THE HISTORY OF LATIN MUSIC
Why are you explaining Latin music?
It doesn't help me visualize anything.
What is it?
Right, there's no Emotion.
See you later.
I need a facial mask right away!
I need to moisturize!
It seems like the 1920s
would be the boss's thing.
Maybe not for this show.
The theme for this year's Paris show
was The Great Gatsby.
It would be too similar.
Yeah.
There's a brand that even used
the Murder on the Orient Express
as a theme.
It was for the fall and winter line.
You did a lot of research.
I figured I should study, too.
But...
what really is "emotion"?
Can I interrupt?
Of course, Miki.
I think it's good to research art,
but being new to the field,
I don't think anything creative will come
from just gathering information.
Do you work in fashion as well?
Don't worry about me.
In times like this, Mayu...
steal.
Steal? Steal what?
That's all I'm going to say.
You two lovebirds are making me jealous.
Miki, there's Yuri, your favorite.
Good evening.
Hi, Yuri.
Welcome.
Come and sit.
See you later.
This is my friend Yuri.
-We moved to Tokyo together.
-Yes! You've mentioned her.
-This is Sosuke Himeji, from work.
-Hello.
Mayu said you've helped her out a lot.
No, I haven't.
I should get going.
You don't have to leave on my account.
Don't worry.
I'll put together what we talked about.
See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Come again.
Here you go.
-So, what's this?
-What?
Sosuke?
He seems nice!
It's pretty common, you know,
falling for someone you work with.
What are you talking about? Of course not.
Well, it sure seemed that way to me.
Everything seems that way to you.
Did you find someone you like?
That's usually the case when you...
Am I that easy to read?
So you did? When?
Maybe a month ago?
-Someone from your company?
-No, but I met him through work.
The more we worked together,
the more I started to like him.
What's he like?
How old is he?
I'll tell you next time.
It's kind of complicated right now.
Are you okay?
Of course, I'm fine.
So it could happen to you too, Mayu!
With Sosuke...
No way. Forget it.
What's wrong? Do you have a headache?
I'm having trouble coming up with ideas.
For Emotion.
I'm sorry, Mayu!
I have to go to the bank now,
but I'll help when I get back.
Okay. Have a nice trip.
Is there anything wrong?
I'm going to borrow him for a while.
What am I thinking?
It's all Yuri's fault!
What are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
Are you making your own coffee, boss?
I have to. You're busy, right?
What?
Nothing.
It smells good.
Boss.
What is it?
What do you feel when you're creating?
That's a straightforward question.
What makes you feel like creating?
That feeling of, "I want to make this!"
What?
You're putting me on the spot.
I have no idea!
It smells so good!
Please!
So, you were serious?
Because last time--
Unfortunately, I'm in a position
where I must back Vanderbilt's decision.
If I support the production of
only selling 100 units per series,
then this contract...
Will disappear?
What?
Increasing the number is impossible.
You know our boss.
You know where she stands on this.
If we can convince Nanjo,
the contract will remain intact?
Why do you keep listening to him?
Why do you keep repeating the past?
-What?
-The last trunk show.
You didn't get to make your debut
in the end,
though your designs were good.
You're good enough to have your own brand.
Are you really satisfied?
We'd like to increase production
for Em and sell nationwide.
Wait, I didn't agree to this.
That was just Fujimura's wish.
He says that otherwise,
there will be no Em at all.
What?
I don't want that to happen.
You're the one who said not to take
Fujimura's words at face value.
Don't worry.
There's enough merit for them as it is.
Even if we sell at a slightly lower price,
to 100 customers instead of 10,
then it's just like Mr. Fujimura says.
Nothing has changed.
Wasn't the point of making a second line
to introduce our lingerie
to women all over Japan?
That won't mean anything unless
we consider taking it to a bigger scale.
I understand what you're saying.
We need to sell in a way that appeals
to all women.
Specifically?
Appeal to their desires.
Your words are passionate.
Create a strong brand image!
"All stylish women wear Em lingerie!"
It'll spark every woman's interest.
Your thoughts, Mizuki?
I think...
It's dangerous to recklessly
increase the production scale.
But I agree on widening
the range of our target customers.
Even young middle school girls
want stylish bras nowadays.
Teens are susceptible to trends.
Women buy out of desire.
"I want to be like her.
I want what she has."
It's the number one motivation for women.
If we appeal to that thinking,
the product will sell.
I don't doubt that.
But...
"I want to be like her.
I want what she has."
This is not how I want customers to feel.
Least of all, say, "You must have this."
That would be talking down to them.
Don't you think that's far from how
we should feel as creators?
Maybe so, but...
It should be up to the customers.
I want the customers to learn
how to recognize quality for themselves.
How many people in society
actually recognize quality?
That's a good question.
No one knows anything!
No one knows what to choose.
We're helping them by telling them,
"You'll be okay if you buy this."
Isn't that the power of a brand?
You're right.
But is there a story there?
Even if we're saying,
"You'll be okay if you buy this,"
is there a story there?
What story are you talking about?
If I had to create a green and yellow bra
for the simple reason that it was spring,
I couldn't, even if I was told to.
But if I was asked to create a bra
for a 17-year-old on her first date,
I could design one immediately.
Because I can picture her face.
I can see the story.
Of course, no one else
would get to see it.
But she'd want to wear
something a little sexier.
She's only 17, so she'd laugh at herself
if it was too sexy.
So I'd want to design something
bright and airy like a dandelion.
Maybe in green and yellow.
I know what you mean.
When a customer decides to buy something,
there's always a story there.
Even if you never see the customer,
you create with the customer in mind.
That's the true form of craftsmanship.
To blindly tell the customer,
"You'll be okay if you buy this..."
is too impertinent.
What's wrong?
Em seems to be in a difficult spot.
Yeah.
But I think I understand now.
That's it!
What are you guys doing?
Why is this happening?
Why'd you go with him? That's so stupid!
Just say you like him!
Finally! The kiss! Finally!
I'm going to go back to work now.
How about this?
How about to the right?
This much?
How's that?
Were you sleeping just now?
I was not.
It's done!
Will you explain it?
The theme for the show is...
"Story."
Every woman has a story.
Especially during spring and summer,
there are more opportunities
for new stories.
That sense of excitement and wonder
for what might happen next, is the theme.
The main point is to have a specific story
for each of our products.
The first date, as you mentioned,
or a deep confession of love.
Does it focus on love, then?
Isn't that a little too simple?
CASE 1: THE FIRST DATE
Love is just one example.
But it will be the most familiar.
Love stories are universal.
It seems like the right way
to quickly grab the customer's attention.
If we're introducing ten sets in the show,
we should have six to seven sets
containing love stories.
Because...
THE ME THAT'S IN LOVE WITH YOU
In these stories...
there is undeniable emotion.
Story.
Sounds good.
Really?
Well, it was really my idea.
-Yes.
-And also...
there aren't only stories
about beginnings.
There's also the story about the past.
An unforgettable story.
The story you keep in your heart.
Let's express that in the last set.
It's going to be a good show.
Yes!
Mayu!
Clean up the rest.
So what's the "story in your heart"?
You already know.
I know you've got a few yourself.
Perhaps.
When you live this long,
it's bound to happen.
So true.
But I've forgotten.
I've forgotten, I've forgotten.
We forget without trying.
Why did I walk over here just now?
I spoke with Sagawa, head of marketing.
I let him know that if you try to force us
into a nationwide market
with the threat of ending our project,
we'll have no choice
but to cut ties with you.
Emotion's goal is not just to make
a product that will be a hit.
We're providing our customers
with what we consider to be
a beautiful product,
using a method we believe in.
It's not a matter of quantity.
That sounds like a religion.
The church of Nanjo.
And I'm a proud member.
That's fine.
I appreciate your understanding.
But, Mr. Saruhashi.
Business doesn't run on idealism.
Let's go.
For this show, we'll take...
You.
And...
EVERY WOMAN HAS A STORY
EXPRESS YOURS THROUGH EMOTION LINGERIE
Nice!
Yes.
Looks good.
That looks pretty stylish.
Where's Mizuki and Fumi?
I think they're over at Em.
I told them to stop by this morning.
She's not picking up.
Maybe she's on the train.
-Hello, delivery!
-Coming!
I guess you lovebirds are making progress.
We're not lovebirds.
Of course not.
My shoulder's in pain.
I'm going to get acupuncture.
What's this?
It's for you.
I can't move my arm.
Will you open it?
Yes.
Boss, I'll massage your shoulder.
Thank you.
What?
What's wrong?
Notice for the launch of a new brand.
Dear Ms., we're happy to announce...
Vanderbilt's Tokyo
will be introducing a private label...
Vanderbilt's Factory will begin
production soon.
As part of the first step...
A lingerie brand...
Vanderbilt's Tokyo...
What?
DESIGNER FUMIKA IDA
DESIGNER MIZUKI NISHIZAWA
Mizuki and Fumika...
Every woman has a story.
EVERY WOMAN HAS A STORY
What's this?
What does this mean?
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.