Hello?
It's finally arrived?
Right. Okay.
Coffee beans?
For the after-party?
Yes.
They were supposed to come in through
Narita Airport yesterday.
But they arrived only now.
You're going to Narita now?
Don't worry, I've got a car.
Okay. Just call if you need anything.
Hello, Sari?
Here, give it to me.
Thank you.
Mayu, I just found out.
I made it into the Paris collection!
Really? Congratulations!
I can't believe it.
You're a supermodel now!
Not yet.
But this is my chance.
I had to tell you.
I'm sorry, I know the show is today.
Yeah, we're getting ready now.
I'm in Singapore right now.
We just finished the shoot
and I'm about to head home.
I probably won't make it.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll show you the video
next time I see you.
Anyway, congratulations!
It's no time to slack off! Come on!
The day has finally arrived.
As you can see,
my trusted team
will finish getting the floor ready,
so there's no need to worry.
The progression of today's runway show,
both front and backstage,
will be directed by me.
However, during the show,
I'll be upstairs in the control room
and won't have access backstage.
All directions for the models,
including fitting and timing,
will come from you.
Normally,
my assistant takes care of all that.
I'm sorry,
we weren't able to cover the cost.
Either way, failure is not an option.
The run-through is your only opportunity
to determine your exact positions.
Use it to figure out
exactly what you need to do.
Got it?
Ms. Nanjo, Mizuki, this way.
-Okay.
This area is for final checks.
This is where the designers
check if everything looks right.
Make sure the models look
perfect at this point.
I understand.
This is the runway entrance.
At my cue,
you'll give the models the go-ahead.
You and I will control
the pacing of the show.
I don't perform very well under pressure.
Even if you have to throw up, just do it.
That's how this industry works.
Mr. Saruhashi,
you'll watch over the staff.
You'll line up the models
in their proper order.
Keep them on the alert.
Smack their butts if you have to.
I might get in trouble if I do that.
For today, it's fine.
You'll communicate with the fitting area.
You're not the type
to get flustered by naked girls, are you?
My sister used to tackle me
after coming out of the bath, naked.
Perfect! I'll leave it to you then.
You, make sure the guests are seated
in their designated spots.
If we can fill the first row
with celebrities and industry big shots,
the show will be 90% successful.
Yes.
I'll drag them here if I have to.
Don't be afraid to ask for help.
-Please help her.
-Of course.
I'll seat the Emotion customers
so that you can attend to the guests.
I'll do my best.
Got it?
You understand your roles?
For the most part.
Then let's hear a word from the designer.
Right now?
But it's only 10:30 a.m.
We won't have time later.
It's funny...
that a day like this would come.
This will be a day
I'll remember on my deathbed.
Let's make sure...
we present our guests
with an amazing vision of Emotion.
All done?
Well then, the show begins at 7:30 p.m.
Let's aim for a safe and perfect show!
Go!
All right!
Yes!
All the apparel is ready, right?
They'll arrive here at...
They'll be here at 2:00 p.m.
Then let's go over the style board.
ANNA CALLING
Excuse me for a second.
Hi, what's up?
I'm--
I'm sorry, Mom.
I can't come to the show today.
What? Why not?
Sayuki asked me to hang out with her.
Just turn her down.
I really want you to be here, Anna.
I know. But...
Was it really Sayuki?
Who really asked you?
And hang out where?
Never mind.
Wait!
What was that about?
Twelve years old, right?
It's a boy.
I hate you for being so straightforward!
Wow.
Professionals are amazing, aren't they?
Yes.
I thought we'd come across
a lot more challenges.
But everything is going so smoothly.
Yes.
Are you nervous?
You're acting a little--
The models will arrive at 1:00 p.m.
So have the staff
take their lunch break now.
Yes.
Let's go.
Here are the bentos for lunch.
There's also coffee and tea.
Thank you.
SHIKISHIMA COFFEE
MR. YAMAZAKI CALLING
-Hello?
-Yes.
I'm at customs in Narita.
We still haven't gotten
the coffee cleared.
But I'll make sure to be on time,
so please don't worry.
Well, worst-case scenario,
we'll just use the coffee we already have.
Okay?
I know you're going out.
I'm asking with whom?
Anna?
Hey!
This section is "N" for north.
And this side is "S" for south.
The front row is A,
the second row is B
and the third row is C.
Seats six to 12
will be for the main guests.
So seat nine is the best seat.
And seat SA-09 will be for Ms. Nagai,
from Conscious.
She'll be our VIP guest this evening.
Yes.
CONSCIOUS EDITOR-IN-CHIEF
MS. CHIKA NAGAI
In seat NA-13,
we have Mr. Fujimura from Vanderbilt's.
NA-14 will be for Fumika.
I wonder if Fumi will come.
I think she will.
Something isn't right.
Oh, no. Here it comes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to do this over.
What?
This access code on the invitation,
when you enter it on our site,
it'll direct you to the Em pre-order page.
And at the end of the show,
we'll start taking orders.
Each of the six Em series
is limited to 200 sets.
I hope our product sells out today.
PAGE NOT FOUND
That's strange,
the site should be accessible.
Excuse me.
I'm going to make a call.
Wait! Wait!
Will everything be okay?
I'm glad I brought it.
You're really going to do it over?
Now?
Well...
it just didn't seem right to me.
Not that again!
You always do this at the last minute!
That's normal.
Mr. Miki.
Designers always try to perfect their work
until the last minute.
Attempting to reach their limits
is what professionals do.
Well...
I suppose.
That's how it is.
You.
Come here.
Okay.
You're burning up.
What's this?
You need to go home.
I'm okay. I took some medication.
I can do it--
No.
You're in charge of communications.
If you collapse backstage
and the show is ruined,
will you take full responsibility?
-I won't collapse. I can do it!
-You can't!
Go home.
You've already been working
for half a day.
You could've gotten someone else sick.
Do you understand
how inconsiderate that is?
Please, leave.
Mr. Miki, please be considerate
of Kaji's feelings.
Thanks to Kaji, this venue--
Today, I have only one criteria.
I will do what I have to for the show
to be executed perfectly.
Your feelings are not important.
Are you okay?
Should I call a cab?
I'm fine. I can walk.
I'm fine, really.
And yet...
But...
what Mr. Miki said--
I understand.
It's so frustrating.
I really thought I'd get you drunk
at the after-party.
That would never happen.
Well...
I wish you good luck for tonight.
We've started the technical rehearsal.
The run-through will begin at 5:00 p.m.
I told you that hurts!
It pinches here!
We've added cushioning
and an adhesive bandage.
I can't walk like this!
Get me a different size.
That's the only size
we could get for that model.
Then get a different pair.
You were fine with these
during the auditions.
Then it was fine, but now it's not!
Please, wait a moment.
Models act like everything is fine
during the auditions
because they want the job.
But now, it's totally different!
Maybe she just wants to complain.
The other girls were saying that
Kaoru failed an audition earlier
and she's in a really bad mood.
She's been doing well lately.
Her ego must be hurt.
Kaoru's presence does add value.
She's up for the main and last parts
of the show.
She has the spotlight.
We'd better do something about the shoes.
Wait! Hold on a second!
How about these?
Don't worry, I've only worn them once.
What?
I was going to change into them
when it would be time to
greet the guests.
It's the same brand.
I really liked them at the fitting.
So I bought them too!
They were so expensive!
What?
Here,
you can try these on too.
Ms. Nanjo.
Or these.
I just bought them.
I was going to wear them today.
But I'll be backstage.
Mine are not very stylish, but...
And these too.
Try them.
These as well.
If they don't work,
I can cut the straps.
Maybe I can add ribbons.
We'll make it work.
We'll make you walk no matter what.
The straps!
Maybe the straps...
It's because this piece faces forward!
I'm so sorry.
How about now?
Stop, stop!
The timing is really off!
Mizuki.
When I say go, you tap their shoulder.
It's very simple.
I'm sorry! One more time, please.
Excuse me.
It's a little hard
being back here on my own.
Don't worry.
An angel is coming down.
What?
Hello.
Mr. Miki asked me to come.
I'm Yuri Konno, Mayu's friend.
Yuri?
She's very elegant.
I can't believe
she's a country girl like you.
Backstage, elegance is irrelevant.
Let's start from number 13!
Models, stand by.
Go!
I can direct in the fitting area.
Please.
Stop, stop!
Again?
What's wrong with Kaoru?
Turn on the lights.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Kaoru?
The light hit my eye.
This bruise stands out.
This is where it stands out the most.
I'll use foundation to hide it.
Please, let me walk!
Please.
Let's find a replacement.
Is there anything you can do?
Yes, I realize it's last minute.
No? I understand.
I understand...
Thank you for trying.
Can you make it in time?
We need it by 8:30 p.m.
I'll make it happen!
They don't do lingerie.
They also said no.
Boss.
We can't find a replacement.
I see.
It's the main and last parts of the show,
so it can't be just anyone.
I can do it.
I apologize for earlier.
I had a bad audition this morning.
I let my emotions get the best of me.
I'm very embarrassed.
I promise, I won't fail.
I can walk!
Please, let me walk!
From afar,
maybe you can't see the bruise.
Can you stand?
Yes!
With this...
It's almost time.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
The beans just got cleared!
I'm going to get them now
and head back--
I'm sorry!
-You can forget about the coffee.
-What?
I have a favor to ask you.
Check! Switch to audience lights.
Okay.
Please, take one.
There are 67 guests
in the waiting area, Mr. Miki.
I'll let the press in first.
This way, please.
Guest interviews
are in the waiting area only.
We're on schedule.
The start time is 7:30 p.m.
Let's make it happen.
Open the doors.
Good evening.
May I see your card?
Thank you for coming.
Good evening.
This way, Mr. Tamaki.
On the invitation card envelopes,
there's an "E" for Emotion,
an "M",
or an "O" marked on each one.
"E" is for the front row.
"M" is for the second row.
And "O" is for the third row.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Tamaki.
This way, please.
The second round
will be a race against the clock.
Worst-case scenario,
we'll send out whoever is ready first.
So please, follow directions.
We want to avoid confusion.
So in here,
please listen to my directions.
Double-check the photos on the rack.
Please.
Welcome.
Thank you for coming, Ms. Yamakawa.
Sitting next to Ms. Nagai
will be the actress
Ritsuko Yamakawa
and her husband.
MR. AND MRS. RITSUKO YAMAKAWA
She's a regular customer.
Here we are, Mrs. Yamakawa
and Mr. Yamakawa.
Please enjoy the show.
Thank you.
SA-9 CONSCIOUS EDITOR-IN-CHIEF
MS. CHIKA NAGAI
In seat NA-11,
we have model Mariko Tamura.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
And she'll be here
with former soccer player Yuuya Kizaki.
So after the show,
I'll guide them to the press interviews.
Please enjoy the show.
Editor-in-Chief Kawashima is
here from Robe.
What about Ms. Nagai?
She's not here yet.
This way, please.
NA-9 on the north side
will be Robe Editor-in-Chief
Erina Kawashima.
Seated next to her
will be designer Satoru Sasaki.
So the nine on that side
will be an editor too?
Robe and Conscious are rivals.
It's best to keep them apart.
The best seat in the house.
It's a beautiful runway.
Thank you for taking time
out of your busy schedule today.
Hello.
We meet again.
Mr. Sasaki,
how late did you stay last night?
-Excuse me.
-It's a secret.
Is it really okay?
This is such a nice seat.
Yes, Ms. Nanjo made sure of it.
It feels like a dream!
Mayu.
I'm glad you came.
This way.
Ms. Tokita.
Don't worry about us.
We'll wait in the lobby.
You can bring us in last.
Last?
You should have backup pieces.
Pieces?
Aya, let's go back to the lobby.
Don't hyperventilate.
Boss!
Stand proud.
After all,
it's Designer Mizuki Nishizawa's show too.
Yes.
She's got a good sixth sense.
-Is that your daughter?
-Yes.
Let's do it!
Yes!
You came.
Of course.
It's Emotion's show.
Models are on standby.
It's time.
Fujimura is here.
Where's Fumika?
She's very busy right now.
My apologies.
She said to say hello.
I see.
Where's Fumi?
I wanted her to come.
This way please, Editor-in-Chief Inoue.
In seat SA-12 will be Editor-in-Chief
Inoue, from the fashion magazine
Dolly Pink?
It's a very casual
fashion magazine, right?
Yes, it's geared toward young people.
But they have a higher circulation
than Conscious.
I see Dolly Pink is fashionably late.
And yet they only cover cheap brands.
Stop it.
Well...
They've got sales, though.
They might have more influence than
the high fashion magazines these days.
Who said that?
Isn't it time yet?
We're on a tight schedule, you know?
They don't want to leave that seat empty.
Who else is coming?
Conscious?
Well...
Backup pieces...
Mrs. Ono, please watch your step.
This way, please.
Is she someone famous?
An actress?
Someone in the industry?
Watch your step.
Please.
Thank you.
It wouldn't have worked if it was me.
But with her...
I'm going to go sit.
SA-9 has been filled.
Okay.
Let's begin.
Am I too late?
Hold on, Mr. Miki!
-What's wrong?
-Ms. Nagai is here.
-Ms. Nagai, from Conscious?
-Yes.
But you just filled the seat.
This way, please.
Here?
Mr. Takeuchi.
I apologize,
but may I ask you to sit here?
All right.
That's fine with me.
And me?
This way, Ms. Nagai.
Hello.
I apologize,
but may I ask everyone
to move over by one seat?
Fumi's seat.
Sure. That seat is empty, so why not?
Why don't you ask her to sit there?
What, you want this seat?
That's a little rude.
I'm very sorry.
We're deeply indebted to Conscious
for years of running articles
about our lingerie.
And so,
we'd really like for Ms. Nagai
to see the show from here.
Playing favorites, I see.
I apologize.
Can I ask you to move over by one seat?
Here we go.
That's fine.
It's just a seat.
Thank you so much.
Ms. Nagai, please have a seat.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Let's start.
Oh, no! What should I do?
It's time for my lessons.
Mayu, I'm so sorry.
I have my shamisen lesson.
What's happening?
What's going on?
She's a little off, isn't she?
The exit.
Where's the exit?
Mrs. Ono.
If you must go, come this way.
I'll take you.
-I can do it.
-Please, take her seat.
I can't leave that seat empty.
I understand.
This way, please.
It's like playing musical chairs.
That's all because someone arrived late.
That's true.
Mrs. Ono,
thank you so much for coming.
Just knowing you came by
makes me happy.
See you soon.
Yes.
Let's start!
Lights, stand by.
Okay.
Okay, ready.
Models ready?
Ready?
-Go!
-Go.
Second round, please change quickly!
Double-check order and styling!
We'll do a final check here.
Please, come here.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
-Can you walk?
-I can do it!
Turn around.
Please.
Go ahead.
Em is next.
Today,
it's finally your debut, Mizuki.
Yes!
Excuse me.
Can I still get into the show?
Sure, if you have an invitation.
Turn around.
Okay.
Go get 'em.
Em is looking good.
Yes.
Can I ask you to take over for a second?
Stand by for the finale.
Come this way.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on!
Please, stand by!
I...
What's wrong?
Ms. Kaoru, please.
Tonight...
you're not being professional.
Ms. Kaoru,
this is as far as you'll go!
I...
will do whatever I have to
for the show to be as perfect as possible.
That's all.
Your feelings are not important!
But, we don't have a model.
I leave it to you.
Sari Machida?
Bravo!
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.