Welcome.
May I help you?
You can bring me this bra.
It's for my allergies.
You know, it's fall.
It's all that ragweed!
Don't worry.
I'll bring you the bra.
DESIGNER MIZUKI NISHIZAWA
DESIGNER FUMIKA IDA
How and when did you come up with
the concept of Story?
It was while discussing marketing
with President Nanjo at Emotion.
That's when the term "Story" came up.
So the Story concept was Nanjo's idea?
Is that right?
Well...
we were inspired by her words,
but we made it into what it is today.
Nanjo had nothing to do with it.
Have you parted ways with President Nanjo?
That sounds so final.
Story is a new brand,
aimed at a younger generation.
All products have a shelf life,
so it's normal
for new things to come along
with every new generation.
It sounds as though you're saying that
Emotion is obsolete.
APPOINTMENTS
9/22/15
EM BY EMOTION TEAM
MIZUKI - FUMIKA - SARUHASHI - HIME
So you actually went there?
Yes. A little while ago.
How was it?
Can I see?
The store was beautiful.
It was full of customers.
I see.
This is nice.
You should stop looking at this stuff.
"We wanted to express
the story inside every woman."
How can they do this?
A PRODUCT BY TWO WOMEN
FOR ALL WOMEN
The product, the concept.
It's all Emotion's.
This.
This, this and this!
All of it!
Why?
How many magazines did you buy, Mayu?
They never used to run
articles on lingerie,
and now, suddenly,
"All women need a Story."
What's going on?
It's good, isn't it?
Let's see. "Story.
It's what's inside a woman that matters."
They got that right.
Boss.
The orders for Ms. Kubo and Ms. Hayashi
are ready.
Find out when they're available
for a fitting.
All right.
So, all our orders...
Are done!
Now, I can go rest.
This is good.
Where's it from?
Does that really matter?
Well, someone's in a bad mood.
Why haven't you said anything
about what happened, boss?
It's great!
They're now running
more articles on lingerie.
What do you mean?
They stole everything from us!
Stole what?
Mizuki made those, right?
But it's an exact copy of Emotion's style.
That's right.
Down to the concept of Story.
Story is not a patented term.
We can just do our own version.
We haven't yet printed
the invitations for the show, have we?
No. It's been on hold.
Change the date and have them printed.
The trunk show is still on.
The theme will be...
Story.
Well? There's no time to waste.
Let's make it happen.
That means I'll have to make
many more items.
I must be in hell!
She's right.
Let's show them who the original is.
We can do it!
We've finalized the plans.
We've purchased the materials.
The models are ready to go!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
We apologize for canceling the order.
We'd be happy to pay the fees.
DETAILED INVOICE
I'm sorry, but we do have to charge you.
I mean, we have people on the payroll.
Of course.
We understand.
You'll get paid by the end of the month.
Is everything all right?
Don't tell me
the company's going bankrupt.
Of course not.
I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-We're glad you're back.
What's going on?
We're moving forward with the trunk show.
The theme will be "Story."
Seriously?
Yes!
Here it is.
One hundred and seventy-three copies,
please.
Sure.
I submitted the invitations.
I'm meeting up with Sosuke in Ebisu,
and we'll go see
the people in charge of lighting.
Yes.
Bye.
Wait! Stop!
Hold on!
Yes?
It's dangerous.
What's wrong, young lady?
Are you lost?
Where do you need to go?
I'll help you.
Isn't this area interesting?
The shops here have been around forever.
The dorayaki here is delicious!
They're often mentioned on TV.
Do you live around here?
Yes! Very close to here.
I've been in Ginza for 50 years now.
I'm a walking encyclopedia!
We're here.
Here's the yakitori shop
you wanted to go to.
The oyakodon here is delicious!
It shouldn't be too crowded at this time.
Goodbye.
Wait!
What is it?
I'm sorry.
May I?
I feel like a princess.
Thank you very much
for helping me.
Make sure you eat lunch
so that you can get back to work.
Yes!
Three more to go.
It's so beautiful.
FOR SARI MACHIDA
Call everyone over.
No.
Will you wait a moment?
I understand.
TOGASHI LAW FIRM
Wait a second.
Can I see that?
"Your new product,
including samples
to be used in your trunk show...
LEGAL NOTICE
...holds too close a resemblance to
the Vanderbilt's Tokyo brand, Story.
Your company has deemed to be
infringing upon copyrighted material,
including all marketing strategy
and promotional items
related to the product."
We're being sued?
They can't be serious!
They stole from us!
We'll just turn it back on them!
That's right. If that's what they want,
we'll just prove in court
that we came up with it first!
We can't do that.
Why not?
The fees are outrageous.
The trial could go on forever.
And since they went public first,
we'd be at a great disadvantage.
But we were first.
The printing company and the models
can be witnesses.
That may not make for
strong enough evidence.
Then what should we do?
They're offering to settle...
if we stop the trunk show.
So they don't want us to compete with
the same Story.
If we force the trial and lose,
they'll ask for
exorbitant fees in damages.
If that happens,
Emotion will go bankrupt.
The trunk show will have to be canceled.
You've both worked so hard.
Thank you.
The trunk show
has unfortunately been canceled
due to unforeseen circumstances...
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
But I still don't get it.
I can't accept it.
Neither Mizuki nor Fumika
would do something like this.
Well, you just never know with women.
They're scary creatures.
Even I never suspected them
of conspiring together.
So this is what it must feel like.
A guy could think
that he's betraying two women,
when in fact, the women get together
and make sure he gets burned.
Why are you joking about this?
Wasn't it funny?
Mr. Saruhashi,
you always stand off to the side,
as if you're not a part of all this.
But you're just afraid
of having to face challenges
and getting hurt.
You just look away!
Mayu.
I know that you worked
as hard as everyone else did on Em.
It must be upsetting to you too.
You should just admit it.
Don't act like it doesn't affect you!
Just another day at the office.
What do you mean?
You're suing Emotion?
I'm just trying to protect the company.
We won't really go to trial.
Is it to protect Story?
That's exactly right.
The product was a hit,
and sold twice as much as expected
in the first week.
Not only in Ginza, but nationwide.
We want to protect our assets.
This isn't right.
Story originally came from Emotion.
Well, I apologize.
I didn't realize that.
That's a lie.
It was all calculated.
So what if it was?
What will you do about it?
Will you testify
that we, all of us,
stole everything?
We can't go back!
Everything's good, isn't it?
Your daughter's happy, right?
She buys all the magazines.
With the little allowance she has.
She's a good girl.
She is.
You designed the concept.
Aren't you happy it's doing so well?
Of course.
But this way of doing things,
it isn't me.
Whatever the method,
our current success
is exactly what I dreamed of.
This is what I wanted.
For women all over Japan
to wear what I designed.
So, I have no regrets.
I'm going to push forward with this.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
But still, it's work.
That's true.
I'm disappointed I lost the job.
I'm upset.
But...
I understand how you feel.
I do.
Poor girl.
2015 SALE PROJECTIONS
EMPLOYEE COSTS
It's already been a month
since we got a new order.
Canceling the show really hurt us.
But even our regular customers
haven't been ordering anything.
Perhaps they all went to Story.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
The last deposits
were from Ms. Hayashi and Ms. Kubo.
We're in a tough spot.
We still owe a debt
from when we launched the Em line.
2015 SALES PROJECTIONS
You already have our business plan.
Here is our sales projections.
And this is our budget.
For the next year, we plan to--
Listen. I can feel your passion.
But extending the loan may be difficult.
Why is that?
We've heard what's been going on.
We understand
you're involved in a lawsuit.
It's a tough situation.
The matter has already been settled!
Depending on how things unfold,
we may have to withdraw altogether.
Please, wait!
We came here to have the loan extended.
There was no prior talk of withdrawal.
If you do this, we'll go bankrupt!
The lawsuit is hurting us.
We still owe payments
to our client companies,
but we have no cash flow.
I was too naive.
Expanding the business
changes our financial structure
into something completely different
from our small cash business.
It's my fault that we lost Em.
No.
I'm the proprietor.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Sosuke wants to speak with you.
I know it's a selfish request.
And the timing couldn't be worse.
But I always felt
this job wasn't right for me.
I'm still not comfortable
around women's lingerie.
I'm probably useless to you anyways.
But you've been working so hard lately.
That's why...
I want to find a job
I can excel at.
Please accept my resignation.
I apologize for the sudden notice.
Please.
You scared me!
Are you all right?
I'm a terrible person.
I allowed my employee
to make the sacrifice.
You mean Sosuke?
He quit in order to help save Emotion.
I'm repeating the same mistakes.
I force those close to me
into making tough choices.
And yet, I'm still incapable
of overcoming the same issues.
Can I really move forward like this?
Everyone knows why you did it.
Everyone's wrong.
I wanted to help Emotion,
but I couldn't.
That's why I'm giving up.
That's not true.
How can you be so sure?
Because
you were working so hard.
I'm getting out of there.
But...
I wish I'd gotten Mr. Saruhashi's approval
at least once.
Up until the very end,
I was of no use to him.
Well, then.
Let's work until you get his approval.
I was telling the truth.
I really want to find a job
I'm good at.
A job that allows me to evolve.
That's the way I really feel.
Is that so bad?
So.
Is Emotion not that kind of place for you?
Emotion's not for me.
We had fun though, didn't we?
All those galleries
and salsa dancing.
Don't make that face.
Mayu.
I think Emotion is right for you.
So.
Don't give up.
Wait!
Do you really expect
we'll get customers this way?
Have some faith.
We just have to do it.
Here!
Even just one customer would help.
Please, take one.
Thank you!
So brave.
And cute.
Please, take one.
-Please, take one.
-We make custom lingerie.
Please, take one.
Wait!
Thank you.
Mayu? Where did she go?
You used to be a geisha?
A long time ago.
Now I teach shamisen.
And what do you do, young lady?
I work in lingerie.
At a shop that makes women's underwear.
How beautiful!
But I'm sorry,
I usually wear a kimono, you know?
So, I don't wear a bra.
That's all right.
It brings back memories.
I used to go dancing with my husband.
Dancing?
I never had a nice underwear set.
So I brought my husband with me
to a store I used to pass by near here.
The beautiful young woman at the shop
made a bra for me that fit just right.
Was that...
It was my husband's only gift to me.
I still have it.
It's a little beat up now,
but I still have it.
You know what?
COURTHOUSE
I have to stay for the next trial.
Thank you so much.
-Hello.
-It's been awhile.
Looks like you're working hard.
We don't all have company lawyers
that can take care of everything for us.
It's been quite a hassle.
Shall I introduce you to a good lawyer?
You have no shame, do you?
You're so brazen, I'm not even sure
"unscrupulous" is the right word for you.
Unscrupulous?
That's not it.
You said that numbers were not an issue.
Numbers are the issue.
Whether it's capital stock or sales,
sponsors or employees,
you're working
on a completely different scale
than Vanderbilt's Tokyo.
There's a gap in power between us.
Justice and idealism
can never bridge that gap.
Always remember that
numbers equal power.
When you get power from numbers,
even if ideas get stolen from a small,
unknown company,
you can come out of it unaffected.
Wouldn't you call that being unscrupulous?
It seems you still don't understand.
Business can get ugly.
I've already told you that.
Yes, this was it.
It brings back memories.
Please.
Welcome.
Mrs. Ono.
Is your name Ono?
How many years has it been?
I'm so glad to see you again.
You're the shop girl who helped me.
Yes.
Please, come in.
I'm glad you called ahead.
We pulled the customer list
from 30 years ago.
It was easy
since you organized the stockroom.
DOB 7/19/46 - MRS. AYA ONO
OCCUPATION: GEISHA
Did the boss recognize her right away?
Geishas were rare.
Even so, that's amazing.
Do you remember?
Excuse me.
Here is the bra.
It's so old.
I've had it for 30 years, after all.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
You've taken such good care of it.
The lace has slightly come undone.
But I just couldn't throw it away.
It holds memories of your husband?
That's right.
Let me fix it for you.
May I take some new measurements?
Of course.
I've changed quite a bit.
I've been wearing kimonos
since I was a teenager.
I never really owned any underwear.
So my husband suggested buying some.
We must have been
around 40 years old, then.
I was a little embarrassed.
When I walked into the store,
my face turned bright red.
I remember.
Your husband seemed like a nice man.
In the end,
my husband never looked at it.
I suppose that's not very surprising.
A wife's underwear
can be quite embarrassing for a man.
It's done.
How wonderful!
Will you try it on?
I've pulled the wires
and changed the shape,
so that you can wear it
under a kimono as well.
I hope you will wear it.
Thank you.
I almost forgot.
How much do I owe you?
Don't worry about that.
The lace was from the excess pile.
And we never charge for repairs.
That doesn't feel right.
Please, let me pay.
It's not much, but please take it.
Thank you so much.
I happily accept your offer.
Boss.
Thank you for everything.
I know we didn't make a profit.
I'm sorry.
This wasn't about the money.
It's only normal
to want to mend a garment
whose owner has given it so much love.
Yes, you're right.
Thank you
for bringing her here.
I remember now.
I had no regular customers.
No customers came to the store.
And yet, I still had confidence back then.
I had the courage to run this shop.
Confidence and courage.
As long as you have those,
you can go on with your work.
Mr. Imai! How have you been?
-Long time no see!
-Indeed.
I've come to ask for a favor.
Can I borrow some money?
-What?
-Just a little.
It won't be possible.
Please!
Hey, how are you?
What have you been up to?
-Please!
-Wait up!
-Where's your pride?
-No way!
I have a favor to ask--
-You! What are you doing?
-Will you lend me some money?
Does 7:00 p.m. work?
Thanks.
AMOUNT OWED: 10,000 YEN
Hey, how have you been?
You surprised me!
Please, just 20,000 yen.
I, Saruhashi,
promise to return the money lent to me...
What kind of man are you?
I'm sorry!
Please, lend me some money!
We didn't get together for your sake.
Please, every little bit will help.
Thanks!
You're doing this for women's lingerie?
Are you stupid?
Thanks!
It really helps!
TOTAL: 640,000 YEN
What's going on?
Is it a party?
Is there something going on today?
I apologize for the ruckus.
Welcome.
I came to thank you
for what you did for my mother.
Your mother?
It seems you mended her lingerie?
Mrs. Ono!
Yes.
Recently, she hasn't been well.
She may have been a nuisance to you.
No, not at all.
Right?
She's very spirited and cheerful.
Thank you so much.
Ever since she came here,
she's suddenly become very lively.
Ma'am, I like this one!
Choose whatever you like.
I'll buy whichever one you like.
Thank you so much, ma'am!
Mrs. Ono!
Women should take care of themselves.
You should wear high quality garments.
Yes.
Thank you.
Welcome, Mrs. Ono.
You...
My bra is now so comfortable,
even under my kimono.
You've been wearing it?
Thank you so much.
Yes, it feels wonderful.
It's incredible,
considering it's 30 years old.
I have better posture when I wear it.
It's as if my husband is telling me
that I need to stand up straight.
Ma'am, look at this one!
Do you think this'll work under a kimono?
I think so.
She wasn't legally married.
She was considered a mistress.
She worked hard as a geisha
and raised me all by herself.
She slowly collected coins in that purse.
It may not seem like much,
but it's her way of expressing gratitude.
I know.
I like that one.
The lace is so pretty.
Yes, it's very pretty.
Eighteen sets all at once!
We did it.
I'm not sure what's going on, but yeah!
But we'll need to purchase
a lot of material.
We need cash, right?
We're going to need cash.
Shall we ask for the payment upfront?
No.
We can't do that.
I could pay out of my own pocket.
Why don't you hand over your paycheck?
Now that Sosuke quit,
why are you still here?
You guys only pay for my travel expenses.
I don't quite have
the financial means yet.
Where did you get all this?
I borrowed from my ex-girlfriends.
There's about five of them?
Women have a soft spot
for men who are in trouble.
If we can get through this,
Emotion will make it.
It's not much.
But please, use it.
Otherwise, I couldn't forgive myself.
I allowed Hime to make the sacrifice.
It's heavy.
It must be the weight
of the pride you had to set aside.
He must have been so frustrated.
Saru.
It was my fault.
Business isn't always pretty.
I thought I could just make and sell
whatever I wanted to.
Perhaps I was the presumptuous one.
What, you're still here?
Yes.
What?
Why are you standing there?
I'm very sorry.
For what?
For saying you were just looking away.
For telling you to
just express your feelings.
It was stupid of me.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize!
Don't apologize.
I'm the one who encouraged him.
Fujimura.
It's now my responsibility
to make things right.
Yes, thank you.
We look forward to it.
-I'm heading out.
-See you later.
Reiko, is the order form
for Ms. Hashimoto ready?
Yes, it's ready to go.
ORDER FORM
Lace with glitter.
Did we have that in stock?
It's later than I thought.
Hello?
Welcome.
I figured it's been too long
since I had something made.
I'm so glad.
Thank you for stopping by!
Thank you so much!
Sorry. I didn't hear you.
What is it?
I'd like to try again.
I want more people to know about Emotion.
Will you let me work on
another second line?
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.