This is not good.
Please put this champagne
in the fridge immediately.
Preferably in a wine cellar.
What about the payment?
It's already been paid for by Ms. Tokita.
I see.
This is good stuff, isn't it?
It was for the guests of the trunk show.
Yes, it was flown in from France.
Yes, yes! It was flown in.
Would a refund still be possible?
Of course that's not possible!
That wasn't for me.
Where would we sell this second line?
Right here.
In this shop.
You're just upset that Story was stolen.
You just want to get revenge!
And what's wrong with that?
That's not beautiful!
Here we go again,
"It's not beautiful."
Everything's always "not beautiful."
You just say that to shut me up.
You are so--
Please, cut it out!
We're expecting a customer.
It's like watching a parent and child
bickering.
I don't recall having a child like this!
And I don't recall ever being your child!
We're so glad to see you here again.
It's such a shame that
the trunk show was canceled.
Indeed.
We worked so hard on it.
Yes.
Everything was ready to go.
The new line?
I wish I could have seen it.
I was so looking forward to it.
Do you have it here now?
Yes.
Well...
Will you let me see it?
Come this way.
Excuse me.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm honored to be able to see
President Nanjo's work up close.
This nightie
is really beautiful.
I wish we could have shown it...
more properly at the trunk show.
Especially to customers like you,
who truly love Emotion.
I'm very sorry.
No.
THE LUXURY OF CHOOSING
STORY LINGERIE
POPULAR LINGERIE BRAND
STORY
FEATURE WRITTEN BY
SHUKO OYAMA
You're like a child,
getting upset when
things don't go her way.
You want them to admit they're wrong.
You have a strong ego.
You said it yourself, boss...
that maybe you were the presumptuous one.
That's right.
All I'm doing
is giving the business of mass production
the respect it deserves.
That doesn't mean Emotion is ready to
take on that kind business.
So then, nothing will change.
Is being consistent such a bad thing?
By remembering how I felt 30 years ago,
I was able to go back to my roots.
But this!
You want us to just stand back and watch?
We can't just instantly start
a second line.
We have no money or personnel.
You must face the facts.
I know.
And yet, if you were to suppress
your annoyingly persistent feelings,
that would really be
a shame!
Don't focus on revenge.
Pour all that passion into
something you can do right now.
I...
want everyone to know.
This shop sells
the most beautiful lingerie
in the entire world.
No matter how beautiful the product is,
if no one knows about it,
it's as if it didn't exist.
So...
In these.
In all of these!
I'll have them run an article
about Emotion.
PUBLIC RELATIONS
MAYUKO TOKITA
Public relations?
The boss said to do what I wanted,
so I had a card made.
Is that weird?
It's a necessary part of a brand.
It's a great idea.
Is that your business card?
I want one.
Here you go.
Your cell number's on it.
If this is how they play,
I've got a plan too.
I'll get Emotion into every magazine.
I'm looking forward to it.
What are you doing?
Supplementary work.
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry!
Really?
Getting materials will be a piece of cake.
So don't worry, Mayu.
Just focus on public relations.
Choosing materials is very important.
I know that!
Do you remember where we first met?
Yeah, you were working in a textile shop.
I've worked longer than you
in the textile business,
so I have some knowledge--
Are you okay?
What's this?
This?
It's the champagne for the trunk show!
I forgot to cancel the order.
The boss will be so angry.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
What are you going to do?
Story is a nationwide hit.
We've been given the go-ahead
to begin a second production.
Now I see what you were talking about.
Whatever the method used to get here,
I feel satisfied with where I'm at.
I'm glad you're onboard.
...Story will be Vanderbilt's main line...
I'm doing PR work now.
PUBLIC RELATIONS
MAYUKO TOKITA
I thought I should look the part.
So that's why you came by today.
Thank you for coming in.
Here's my card.
I'm Rin Nakatani.
Thank you for the other day.
MANAGER
RIN NAKATANI
You're the manager of the Ginza shop?
Yes.
Wow.
-That's amazing.
-Thank you.
Since you're the Ginza shop manager,
do you have any magazine contacts?
Not at all.
We always deal directly with customers.
Of course.
-I apologize for the sudden question.
-It's okay.
Are you looking to advertise?
No.
That costs a lot of money.
I was hoping we'd be featured
in an article.
But I have no leads with the publishers.
How about Conscious?
I've read many of their lingerie articles.
Perhaps you know someone
on the editorial board?
Conscious.
Yes.
Women are attractive as they are.
SHUMEI PUBLISHING
I'm very sorry.
Takeuchi is currently out of the office.
Did you have an appointment?
No. Thank you.
I'll come back.
Hello.
Ms. Oyama.
What are you doing here?
Well...
Well, you should probably call
and make an appointment first.
And speak to Ms. Nagai,
the editor-in-chief.
I'll let her know as well.
Thank you.
You'll just have to talk to them
one at a time.
I have a friend...
Well, maybe that's not quite right.
Any introduction would help.
It's a magazine for teens.
Teens?
10:00 A.M.
MS. NISHIO
Ms. Nishio.
Looks great!
Now hold that pose.
Wonderful.
Now with more energy.
Great, great.
Looks good, Mari.
Are you looking for someone?
Yes.
I have an appointment with Ms. Nishio.
I was told she's here?
Thanks, everyone!
Great work!
Yumi and Chi were so cute!
And so was Mari!
Ms. Sawada!
Is that...
It's the new line!
All brand new!
It's so cute!
Look!
We've got five different colors.
It suits you perfectly, Mari.
We thought you might like one.
We can really have this?
I love Grazia's bags!
They're all yours!
Mari, that color looks great on you!
Try carrying it!
Mayu?
Sari?
Are you here for work?
Yes. I just passed an audition.
Congratulations!
What about you?
-Sari?
-Yes.
Gotta go.
Let's go for lunch sometime.
Good luck!
Excuse me.
Do you work in the industry?
Please take these if you'd like.
No!
POPULAR BRANDS...
AUTUMN/WINTER COLLECTION
You should've just taken the bags.
VORE KYOUHEI TATSUNO 03-9467
VIVAN MASATO ONO 03...
Of course not.
Did you get to meet the editor?
Yes, but it's a magazine for teens,
so Emotion's not really aimed at them.
That's true.
It creates custom-made lingerie.
But I was so surprised.
It wasn't just that brand.
Other brand representatives
kept coming by!
And they'd leave their products.
Having models use the products
is the quickest way to sell.
It doesn't cost any money.
Money?
Models take pictures of themselves
to put on their blogs.
And on social media.
If we can see even a glimpse
of their clothing or their bag,
it sells out the next day.
Sells out?
Women buy out of desire.
I guess that's true.
Someone I know said that before.
So then, they understand.
Even top brands get their PR people to
make sure celebrities carry their product.
I see.
But Emotion can't do that.
Right.
So a magazine is probably the way to go.
Especially one of the higher-class ones.
Like Conscious, for example?
Then again,
bloggers are more influential now.
What?
Nothing.
Miki, you never told us,
do you work in the fashion industry
or something?
What?
What is it?
Sorry.
Is there anything in there
that could even interest you,
Mr. Yamazaki?
This is...
My daughter!
What?
LATEST TRENDS MODELED BY OUR READERS
CHIKA YAMAZAKI
16 YEARS OLD
She's cute!
No way!
For part two of Story,
we will be going with the concept, Flower.
Our production goal is 40,000 units.
We'll introduce the product
at the Ginza store.
We'll use Ms. Nishikawa as the model--
Hold on a second.
When was this decided?
At last week's meeting.
Considering the marketing team's numbers,
and the concept for the next term
at Vanderbilt's,
the development team--
I haven't heard anything about it.
We're the designers, right?
I think it's a great idea!
"Flower" is a very feminine concept.
We're short on time, so shall we?
SAMPLE IMAGES
What are these?
They're from another brand
with a similar concept.
They're selling well,
so we can analyze the design.
Analyze?
SAMPLE IMAGES
These!
They're great, aren't they?
It would be wonderful
if we could make ours more like these.
We're counting on you.
It's just business.
Mr. Fujimura!
Mizuki!
I know what you're going to say.
Was this your plan all along?
Story was Emotion's trunk show theme.
You stole it, didn't you?
It doesn't matter now!
If I can just do my job,
I won't say anything
about what's already done.
I'll even go along with your concept.
But this is not right!
I'm not President Nanjo.
Story is not Emotion.
That's fine.
Feel free to do as you like.
Ignore the concept,
as well as the marketing team,
and design whatever you want.
But...
Make something that sells.
After all, Story is not Emotion.
It's the new line for November.
Please, take it.
What's it like?
Hello, it's been a while.
I apologize for any trouble
I've caused you in the past.
You're looking better.
It still needs work.
I came here today
to give you this.
Emotion makes lingerie, right?
A camisole?
It's a nightie.
I see.
It's pretty.
It's what I'd expect from Emotion.
Thank you.
We thought that if you wore it,
you could feel its quality.
Takeuchi?
Yes?
What do you think?
What do you mean?
Are you imagining me in it?
Should I?
Or shouldn't I?
It's creepy either way.
This isn't really my style.
So what's your budget?
Budget?
I'm not here to discuss advertisement.
I'd like for you to write
an article about us.
A tie-up?
Then you should discuss the budget
with the ad agency.
We'll have a storyboard,
but we'll have the final say
on the product and the story.
Well.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean by budget?
Takeuchi?
Hello, Ms. Akibara?
There's a limit to one's ignorance.
What?
You want Emotion on the cover?
Yes, please.
Then you need to pay what they paid.
What?
I'm sure the price is two digits more than
what you would have imagined.
Can you afford it?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
I met Ms. Tokita the other day.
So Emotion is finally doing PR?
How much?
Story was featured in every magazine.
How much did you get?
That's not it.
Vanderbilt's paid out
all the publishing companies.
And I suppose the writers
just have to write what they're told.
"Beautiful and strong,
yet light and graceful.
Story is an expression of today's woman.
These two facets are the epitome
of the modern woman."
Don't read it out loud.
You don't have to show it to me!
What crap!
This article.
It has the same pictures
and the same story
as every other magazine.
It's just empty praises,
urging everyone to buy the product.
Is that what's expected
of a lingerie critic, Shuko Oyama?
I've adapted to the times.
No location scouting, no interviews.
There's nothing about
what you actually saw and felt.
How can you call yourself a critic?
You're right.
But...
That's why you're stuck.
Always doing what's right
won't win you any votes.
You're setting up your own obstacles.
Ms. Tokita?
So you went to Conscious?
Yes.
Can I show off a little?
What?
Concerning our sales
from last year and this year,
I came in first in my company.
Wow.
Everyone at the Ginza store does well.
It helps that we get a lot of customers
from other Asian countries.
I didn't do it all on my own.
But if a product sells really well,
I feel as though it was thanks to me.
The company even rewards me for it.
And yet, all I did
was deal with customers.
But I feel as though I created the trend,
that I'm somehow influencing people.
When really,
it's simply a financial transaction.
The truth is,
Emotion has the most honest way
of doing business.
You were right, boss.
If you're looking for a way to sell
a high-quality product honestly,
Emotion has the finest business model.
If you don't have any money,
then you can't get this magazine to print
even a single word about you.
Boss,
you're right.
Do we only want to be right?
Mr. Saruhashi.
"For women to have the luxury
of choosing their lingerie."
Isn't that what you've always wanted?
We can raise the money.
Here are the forms to submit
to a finance company.
APPLICATION
The lawsuit's been settled.
We can now get a loan.
But only if you agree to it.
I...
want a second line as well.
Mr. Saruhashi?
Yeah.
He worked out the financing on his own.
And he said he wants a second line.
I was so surprised.
What did the boss say?
I see.
"Mass production is not easy."
I get it now.
I can't believe Mizuki and Fumika!
I'm only here part-time, but I'm upset!
I think that they knew.
About money. About people.
They knew the timing was right.
Still.
Yeah.
Wanna go somewhere?
What?
I just meant if you were hungry.
I don't have any ulterior motives.
Shall we go then?
I'm so full!
You're so friendly with everyone, Kaji.
That chef was hilarious.
He told terrible jokes!
I finally got to hang out with you.
I feel as though I have more energy
after having laughed so much.
I'm glad to hear that.
By any chance,
have you spoken with Sosuke lately?
What?
I mean...
I haven't. Why?
Because...
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
You know, I'm not--
No really! Never mind.
Okay, let's get back to work!
Hold on.
I think you're right.
No matter how beautiful the product is,
if no one knows about it,
it's as if it didn't exist.
So...
I want to help.
Make something that sells.
It's just business.
After all, Story is not Emotion.
You're still here?
Why is this so wrinkled?
That's strange.
Growing old is not very pleasant.
Why the sudden remark?
I can barely keep up with change and yet,
I'm over 50 and still trying to figure out
how to grow up.
It's so unattractive.
I hate it.
What's wrong with that?
If you have nothing left to learn,
you end up being like
dried-up seaweed left on a shelf.
What kind of analogy is that?
And the kids here are learning from you.
How are you?
Fine.
Thanks to you.
Thanks to me?
Sarcasm?
Yes.
And you?
Are you happy to have your own brand?
I feel satisfied.
That's unfortunate.
What?
The concepts and designs,
had you done them all yourself,
you could have been happier.
I can do that.
From now on.
I understand.
You had no choice
if you wanted it to sell.
Everyone does things
thinking they don't have a choice.
What a stubborn woman.
What?
President Nanjo.
Outspoken, willful and very tenacious.
That's true.
But...
I believe she's the real deal.
That's why I want to find a way to sell
without compromising how I feel.
You can have Story.
It's just one idea out of many.
That's why I'm apologizing!
Now you're upset?
You feel entitled
just because you're young?
I was the one who hid it. I'm sorry.
I was the one who forgot to cancel.
It's not your fault that you forgot,
it was bad timing.
But what is this?
1,000 YEN PER PERSON
What if a bunch of
perverted old men show up?
We won't get any new customers
if we don't do this.
That's right!
I think it's a great idea.
I'd definitely come.
That's the problem.
Then we'll come up with something else.
Getting more customers is what matters.
That's exactly right.
A trunk show isn't enough.
We need something to bring in a new crowd.
Otherwise, we can't beat Story.
I don't care about Story anymore!
I don't want to think about it.
Besides, this champagne...
Mizuki.
Please.
Let me work here.
What?
What did you say?
Am I hearing you right?
I don't deserve it.
I know that.
No matter what,
I have no right to enter this store.
I know that, but,
I had to come.
I couldn't turn that corner near here.
I've walked this path so many times.
But my feet wouldn't move.
I kept walking back and forth.
It doesn't matter what you felt.
"What am I doing?
It's the path I chose,"
and I'd try to leave.
But then,
my feet would move this way on their own.
My body feels torn apart.
I don't know what to do.
But one thing is clear to me.
I can't come up with any ideas.
I claimed I would only design
what I wanted,
and I was told to do just that.
And yet,
I just can't seem to
come up with anything.
"What would the boss do?
This kind of looks like what she'd do.
The boss wouldn't like this, the boss..."
What it comes down to...
is that your designs are what I like best.
I don't ask that you forgive me.
Please let me work here again.
I'll do anything!
The trunk show back in April...
Will you stop that?
Look at me.
At the trunk show in April...
I realize it now.
I should have used your designs.
They were well done.
It would have represented Emotion well.
It was wrong of me to drop it.
I regret it.
I'm so sorry.
Shall we do a second line then?
Creating a second line
would be much better
than doing something like this!
Saru?
We've got the funds, right?
Yes.
And we've got a persistent PR person.
And an optimistic part-timer.
And someone who's supported us for years,
our very sweet veteran.
We've got a designer.
We've failed twice now.
But I think we can do it this time.
However,
I'm going to sell as honestly as possible.
Let's do it.
Who cares what others say,
let's do it right!
Don't speak as if others didn't like us!
Do they?
Why shouldn't they?
I'm such a sweet person.
I see.
Very well, then.
Let's drink.
It's on me, the very sweet boss.
Let's chill it.
I'm glad.
No.
She's too cute.
What?
It was Fujimura, wasn't it?
I'm going to beat him.
Excuse me?
Yes, I'm coming.
Ms. Hiromi Tsukamoto.
Hello.
I know it's past closing time
but your light was on.
Please, come in!
Boss!
Hello.
I brought this.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy!
This really makes me happy.
But it's only 2,500 yen.
It's wonderful, isn't it, boss?
How much have you already had to drink?
This is the kind of customer we want.
Right, boss?
I know, calm down.
We want you to see more lingerie.
Not in magazines like this, but more...
Boss, let's do a show!
What?
Good. Very good.
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.