After giving it some thought,
I think we'll try doing
a second line of undergarments.
We're discussing it
with Mr. Fujimura from Vanderbilt's.
That means mass production
to be sold in stores?
Prêt-à-porter.
I see you remember "prêt-à-porter".
Yes, I do.
But boss, won't this go against
our custom-made policy?
Our philosophy stays the same.
It doesn't change a thing.
Someone else will be
overseeing the second line.
But that person must remain faithful
to the Emotion design.
Exactly.
Which aspects of my design will be kept,
and which aspects excluded?
It must be selective,
yet harmonious.
But at an affordable price.
Which means?
Whoever is overseeing the second line
must be more skilled than I am.
What that means is,
while preserving the design qualities
and policies of Emotion,
we must develop a production plan
for a unit price under 10,000 yen.
-What? Me too?
-Of course.
-You do have good taste, Fumika.
-Taste.
Well, Mizuki and Fumika,
you'll be competing with each other.
What?
One of you will become
the chief designer of the second line.
Of course, it's also possible
you could both fail.
Mr. Saruhashi, you'll be studying closely
all practical aspects
of the line production process
with Mr. Fujimura.
-You too, Sosuke.
-Right.
If we can't find
a high quality sewing factory,
we won't be able to develop anything.
-This is essential.
-I'm against it.
I think our style is fine the way it is.
There's no point in repeating
the same mistake.
The same mistake?
Well, that isn't even an issue
until we can produce something
and establish a procedure
towards a manufacturing line.
But I want to try it.
Come on. You quickly get old
if you aren't competitive.
This is exciting.
The undergarment industry
will take on a new direction
if we can come up
with something different.
I've been thinking of doing
something like this for quite some time.
Hey.
Sorry. I--
You need to figure out
if you want to continue working here.
What?
Am I being fired?
No, you're not.
I'm only saying you should decide
what to do with your life.
If you stay at Emotion, you won't be able
to develop your own ideas.
You're right, but--
Or do you still wish
to continue working here?
Think it over.
I will.
Taste? Policy? Sense?
I don't understand
any of this fancy stuff!
What's the point of having
all this frill here?
So, we'll be rivals for a while.
I hate being so serious.
I'm just here to make you look good.
Can you do something for me?
Sure.
Ms. Tokita, I'm designating you
as our delivery person.
Really?
We've established a mail order system
for distant customers.
We do have customers from Nagoya.
Delivering our product to those customers
is of crucial importance.
I trust you because you're so punctual.
Reiko.
Reiko, why did you start working
at Emotion?
What?
Where did that come from?
Well, the boss told me I should decide
whether or not
I want to keep working here.
What is she talking about?
You just started.
I'm not sure if it's really for me.
I have no sense of style.
Do you think your job
is right for you, Reiko?
I just like the president.
I just want to work with her.
That's all.
I know you're busy,
but here's something important.
No! I completely forgot.
What is it?
Do you know this?
Yes.
That, at least, I know.
There will be a party for
the 30th anniversary of the first issue.
-Do I have to go?
-I'm going.
I love those things!
It's the only magazine featuring lingerie.
It's good for us
to regularly show gratitude.
Well, the president's going too.
Reiko, do you want to go?
Sorry, but I'm going
to the opera that night.
-Ms. Tokita.
-Yes?
Can you deliver this
to one of our customers?
Oh.
They asked us to deliver it.
I didn't know
your shop made them.
Thank you.
And your customer?
Doing final checks on a dress.
She wanted to see it with this bustier.
-Konno.
-Yes?
-Did the bustier arrive?
-I'll bring it now.
-I'll see you later.
-Best of luck.
Sorry.
It just came in.
How beautiful.
I think it would go well with this tiara.
This one is particularly elegant.
What do you think?
It's really beautiful.
Okay.
I'll need a sewing machine.
Wasn't there one here?
How old is this thing?
Made in 1978?
How ancient!
Okay.
It's done!
Thanks.
So sorry!
I bought it.
So, how does it feel?
Well.
Can I see?
Go ahead.
-It feels great on the skin. Really.
-No, no.
It looks like an outfit
the devil would wear.
I'm sorry for making you wear
something so weird.
You definitely look better without it.
Really?
That's shocking.
What is?
I thought it was a compliment.
People say that to me a lot,
that I look better without something on.
What does that mean?
I'm really bad
at modeling clothes.
That's not true.
Even now, you look totally hip.
Something's missing.
I'm not at the level
of a professional model.
What do you mean?
That's so awful.
What's "style", anyway?
Why take such a vague word so seriously?
I don't think modeling is really for me.
But I can't stop.
It's my way of getting revenge.
What?
I'll get famous
and show everyone
they were wrong.
Sorry.
I got rejected at an audition today.
I'm really dark inside.
You have such an angelic look,
but you also carry darkness inside.
But,
I kind of like what's inside.
What?
It's total mud.
Well.
Maybe this actually suits you.
Come on, I'm not that devilish.
What?
This week, I need to go to a factory
in Fukui to select some fabric.
Would it be all right
if I don't attend the party?
I wanted people to meet you,
since you'll be overseeing
the second line.
But first, we need to
actually produce something.
Well, all right, then.
Thank you.
However, I want the number of people
who are attending to remain the same.
You.
Come here.
Me? You mean...
Really?
Go fill your head with everything
that pertains to sense and style
until you can't take it anymore
so that you can understand
what the word "fancy" really means.
How did you know I was having
a hard time understanding fancy things?
But only if you wear
something appropriate and beautiful.
Think of it as a test
to see if you have what it takes
to do this job.
What?
I'm losing my mind.
That's fine!
It suits you.
Take that one.
You look cute.
If you really think so,
then I'll get it.
But...
I'll only be wearing it once,
so why should I pay so much?
Do you want to rent from my store?
We have a good rental selection.
No. I'll buy it.
This is a test
to see if I have what it takes
to work in this industry.
Excuse me.
I'll take this.
Thank you very much.
I can make some adjustments
so that it fits you better.
It won't work
unless you take about 10 inches here.
It's too loose.
Too loose?
What?
One week?
That will be too late.
Is there some way
I can have it done by Friday?
Let's see.
The soonest it could be ready is 6:00 p.m.
Would that be all right?
Yes. Thank you so much.
That's very helpful.
I made it in time.
The boss finally completed them.
Aren't they beautiful?
Yes.
Please, have them delivered
by tomorrow evening.
-Confirm the orders.
-Right.
Casablanca to Nagoya.
Lily Magnolias to Tokyo.
Yes.
Ms. Nishida. Lily Magnolias.
Leaver lace.
Ms. Kondo. Casablanca.
Beige base.
Ms. Tokita,
you're a good wrapper.
Origami has always come in handy.
I'm sending them off.
They'll be delivered tomorrow.
No, Miki.
Welcome.
Is it that time already?
Your model friend.
She must be suffering.
She has such an innocent look.
And she said it would be her revenge.
I was so surprised.
Well, anyone would be.
People always hide their true feelings.
And if someone is always cheerful
both inside and out,
it's so boring.
Like Yuri?
I'm gonna hit you.
But what about that party?
I wish I was going too.
I'd wear a dress and very high heels.
That would be awesome.
Heels?
Shoes!
I don't have shoes!
I just can't get used to
seeing you in those.
Is my walk that strange?
I'm sorry for laughing.
I just bought these this morning.
They told me I should wear them all day
and break them in.
Pardon me, but I'm off now.
At what time will you arrive in Fukui?
Past 2:00 p.m.
There's a meeting
at the factory at 3:00 p.m.
Take care.
Best of luck at today's party.
It will be worth it.
You'll get a good idea
what this industry is all about.
I'll study it closely.
Don't worry,
I bought some shoes.
-How cute. See you later.
-Okay.
We need to head out, too.
Of course.
Isn't the party at 7:00 p.m.?
I'm off to a meeting
at a reputable sewing factory.
They're making a sample for us.
Wait, that means I won't have enough time.
Hime, can you deliver
this manuscript to the editor?
Here's the proof of the interview
for printing by 5:00 p.m.
You can go home after that.
I'm leaving early.
I'm going to get changed.
Be at the party for 7:00 p.m.
Don't be late.
Right.
Do you have a dress, Ms. Tokita?
It'll be ready at 6:00 p.m.
You're in a good mood.
Am I?
It's a genetic predisposition.
Genetic?
A woman instantly becomes happy
when she's wearing high heels.
-We're born that way.
-What?
These hurt so much.
Hello. Thank you for calling.
You have reached Emotion.
They received the wrong order?
It's the customer from Tokyo
we delivered to yesterday.
The customer from Tokyo
ordered the white Lily Magnolias pattern.
Leaver Lace.
White Lily Magnolias?
What?
Lily Magnolias are white?
I had mistaken the purple Casablanca
for Lily Magnolias!
I'm so sorry.
I thought I'd been extra careful.
My daughter's violin recital is tonight,
and I really wanted her to wear it.
I'm very sorry.
It will be delivered to you,
guaranteed.
Yes.
DEPARTURE: NAGOYA 3:54 P.M.
ARRIVAL: TOKYO 5:33 P.M.
For Nagoya,
I can get there and back.
I'll go. It was me who didn't check.
You need to get to that party.
No, it's my mistake.
Please, let me go.
-But...
-You have the opera to go to.
Besides, if I can't do this properly,
I don't deserve this job.
I couldn't tell the difference between
a Casablanca and a Magnolia.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll tell the president.
I'm so sorry.
I'm off.
No!
I'm so sorry.
I'll have it delivered to you by 6:00.
It's huge.
I'm so sorry.
This is your item.
Thank you for being so courteous.
This one is beautiful too.
White Lily Magnolias.
Thank you.
Pardon me.
You're leaving already?
Please,
stay for some tea.
Here you go.
Thank you.
That was wonderful.
Please, the next time you're in Tokyo,
visit us at Emotion.
I apologize for getting you so worried.
I'm so glad you made it in time.
I apologize again.
I really wanted her to wear it today,
so I made sure to have it ready.
I'm so glad I made that choice.
How beautiful.
I'll make it!
I've been waiting.
Your dress is ready.
-Thank you.
-Would you like to see it?
Sorry. I'm in a hurry.
I'll take it as is.
-I would like to show you what we've done.
-It's fine.
Pardon me. Thank you so much.
Hurry, hurry!
What?
Yes?
I'm so sorry.
I'm afraid I gave you the wrong dress.
I'll deliver the right one immediately.
Hello?
It's all right.
I appreciate your concern.
You don't look weird.
You're even wearing proper shoes.
Well. Some people go to parties
dressed casually.
I was wrong!
I saw that on TV.
I'm so glad you came.
I knew you'd be here.
Come with me.
I want you to talk
to the new editor-in-chief.
Why me?
-Stop messing with me.
-No, really.
-She's dropping the articles on lingerie.
-What?
The tall one.
She says she's dropping
all features on lingerie.
How young is she?
She's 37.
Why is she dropping lingerie?
They said, "If you specialize in anything,
it should be in advertising."
So in other words,
increase revenue.
With an editor like that,
the magazine will become
a mail order catalog.
Rumor has it, Ms. Nagai,
that you're an expert in fashion
despite being so young.
I heard your latest edition
sold very well.
Well.
It fills me with pride
to have President Nanjo from Emotion
give me such praise.
It's an amazing feat to increase
circulation in the publishing industry.
It's all thanks to my dedicated readers.
This is my deputy editor, Mr. Takeuchi.
Don't just stand there.
Pardon me.
-Pleased to meet you.
-Likewise.
Clothing is becoming a luxury item.
We need to focus on lingerie.
Is that a pitch?
Japanese women with refined taste
should know the pleasures
of selecting lingerie.
Especially those who like material things,
such as yourself, Ms. Nagai.
Sure, it may be a genuine form of luxury.
Mr. Takeuchi, it's been a while.
Emotion?
I've always been grateful
for the lingerie features.
-You're exaggerating.
-We usually don't get many opportunities.
Even Ms. Nanjo says that
this is a good opportunity.
-I guess your boss is a real woman.
-Who, Nanjo?
Well, I've got to go check
the guests' arrival.
I apologize for having disturbed you.
Hello?
What?
High heels?
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
Please, don't be shy.
Come in.
Well, I'm not...
My name is Mr. Takeuchi from Conscious.
NORIHISA TAKEUCHI.
DEPUTY EDITOR.
Deputy editor.
We're so grateful.
I'm Ms. Tokita from Emotion.
Please, excuse me
for being dressed like this.
I'll be leaving very soon.
No, really.
Pardon me.
-It's fine.
-What?
What's wrong with what you're wearing?
There's nothing wrong.
Please, come in.
Your outfit is adorable.
Thank you.
I'm quite relieved.
Well.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, boss.
I'm late.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
Is she from Emotion?
Yes.
She's new.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Ms. Tokita.
Lingerie designers
have a lot of confidence.
Instead of decorating the exterior,
they focus on the inside.
What's important is to compete with what
you can't see. Just like with lingerie.
Don't you agree?
Isn't that why you can come in here
looking like that?
It's remarkable.
I can really understand
your policy now, Ms. Nanjo.
But then,
why did you wear that,
instead of wearing
your company's lingerie?
This is a meeting place for people
who make decisions about fashion.
Don't you think there's a limit
to how impolite one can be?
I'm so sorry.
It's not that...
No...
I'm sorry.
Please,
I apologize for disrupting
this formal gathering.
It reflects the deficiencies
in my training.
The next time we meet,
I will ensure that we're appropriately
dressed for your gathering.
Please, forgive us.
That would be very helpful.
We'll leave immediately.
However,
there is one misunderstanding
I must address.
Lingerie isn't something
that should be exposed on display.
Even if this woman
was wearing lingerie that was just as
elegant and beautiful
as what any one of you are wearing,
it would be absolutely forbidden
to show it here.
That's the charm of lingerie.
What the trends are,
or how you compare with others,
doesn't matter.
It's your own world.
There are no pretensions or lies.
It's a fascinating world.
Please, do feature lingerie
more in your magazine.
I look forward to it.
Now, please excuse us.
Sorry, our president can be like that.
I'm truly sorry.
Wait a minute.
What did you say to my girl?
Did something happen?
Just because you're fed up
with a younger female boss,
you think you can pick on a girl
who doesn't know better?
No, she did know better.
No matter how you put it,
she knew her clothing
was inappropriate for this event!
You ridiculed her.
Don't take your frustrations out on her.
I didn't ridicule her.
What?
Women are attractive
as they are.
Right.
Coming from a man,
that's the truth.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
My feet hurt.
I can't wear these anymore.
These things hurt,
no matter how beautiful they are.
It's too bad.
Boss?
Where are those heels you bought today?
-I took them off.
-You idiot.
Sorry.
And your dress?
You got one, didn't you?
I took the wrong one at the store.
You're a complete idiot!
-I'm sorry.
-Don't cry.
You understand now?
That's why you wear lingerie.
It seems pointless.
But you wear it for yourself.
Beauty is a weapon.
I guess we didn't make it.
I guess not.
The main bottleneck is stock.
We don't have much experience
with pattern grading,
as we haven't had to do it before.
If the cash balance goes down
while carrying an inventory,
our cash flow will start to suffer
right away.
There's too much risk
with mass production.
However,
this completely
encapsulates the Emotion design.
But with very affordable materials.
You found a good manufacturing factory,
right?
Of course.
And our retail outlets are already set up.
So it's decided.
Emotion will produce a second line.
The chief designer will be
Mizuki.
You deserve it.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
It's very close.
It's almost there.
Its youthfulness is remarkable.
I'll study it further.
-That's all.
-Don't you have anything to say?
Beauty aside,
it doesn't have a shred of sensibility.
How can you just slap things
on together like that?
You completely lack any sense
of aesthetics and a feel for balance.
However,
you do have a flair
for choosing materials.
From now on,
Mizuki will be busy
with the actual design work,
so you'll be selecting the materials
and sourcing the pieces instead.
That is, if you still wish
to keep working here.
I'll do it. I'll keep going.
I'll never stop!
That means,
you'll need a new job title.
Welcome, Ms. Tokita?
Being in charge of materials
is a big responsibility.
I'm sure you'll do well.
Thank you very much.
You want to go out and celebrate?
I guess so.
-Huh?
-You bought such a wonderful dress.
It would be a shame for it to go to waste.
-Well.
-Don't worry, I won't say anything.
Just dress up nice,
and go out with a man.
That will say a lot about you.
No, no.
You don't want to be alone with me.
How about we take him along?
Huh?
No, it's not about
whether or not Sosuke is there.
Why?
It's okay if he's around, right?
What is it?
You completely lack basic female powers.
That's obvious.
What are you looking for?
Naturally, your interest
in clothes and makeup
should be emphasized.
Didn't you ever secretly wear
your mom's lipstick?
I didn't have a mother.
Well, don't worry about that.
I'm perfectly happy with having been
properly raised by my father.
Right, then.
You're the one using that machine, right?
I apologize for not asking.
It's the first sewing machine
I ever bought.
I guess it still works.
Yes.
I miss it.
I used to work with that thing
day and night.
I just didn't want to lose to clothes.
But then, I failed.
Actually, I regret it.
That's why I put that machine away.
We've been through so much.
Yes.
Is that what it means?
What is?
To make something that people can't see.
Like hidden thoughts,
or the desire to fight.
Here?
Pent up in here?
Come on, now.
It's just underwear.
Here.
Huh?
You're beautiful!
You look so different.
Wait, did you get taller?
She's transformed into a goddess.
The boys aren't quite up to par.
Be quiet,
this is a style too.
Shall we go?
See you.
I'll see you all later.
All right. Let's go.
Yes.
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.