RUNWAY SHOW REHEARSAL
Line those up right here.
Hey, be careful with that!
I'm sorry to interrupt!
The models have arrived.
The fitting starts at 2:00 p.m.
All right.
What should I do with this?
Wait. Let's see.
I'll put it right here.
Good morning!
Good morning.
You'll be provided with dressmakers
for the actual show.
Today is just a rehearsal,
so please get dressed by yourselves.
You can use those robes.
We only need two rows of chairs.
It's just to get an idea for the show.
Watch out for the runway.
I'd like to leave the kimonos in here
if there is enough space.
Hey, watch out!
I'm sorry.
Mayu!
Mayu?
Will she be all right?
Did she hit her head?
We just did an MRI, so we'll take a look.
Please, give us a moment.
But why won't she wake up?
Please, hold on.
5 WEEKS EARLIER
The venue.
As long as we can secure a venue,
we can proceed with the show.
But with our tiny budget,
our options are very limited.
And--
Japan Fashion Week takes place in October,
so most venues are already booked.
It would be great publicity
if we could do it during that time.
But with our tiny budget--
Will you stop saying "tiny"?
Mr. Saruhashi worked very hard
to get investors.
I'm sorry if it's too tiny for you.
Not at all.
Which days would work?
There are three venues still free
during the last week of October.
Okay, that works.
Let's go with whatever is easiest
and cheapest.
That sounds like fast food.
The exact opposite of
what Emotion stands for.
Even if it's cheap and easy,
if we're happy with the outcome,
then that's great, isn't it?
That's true.
Just like your wonderful second line.
That's right.
The samples for Em are so cute.
We can let customers pre-order
from the Em line during the show.
The factory's ready to go,
so we can sell at least 200 units.
EM PRODUCTION PLAN
There's no issue with making
the product ahead of time.
Em is not custom-made.
We want to avoid having excess inventory.
We have the date and venue.
October 31st, Ebisu Square Hall.
Boss! Boss!
What is it?
I'm busy looking for models.
Why are there so few lingerie models?
Lingerie models are looked down upon
in Japan.
Why? It means they have a great figure.
Great enough to show it off in lingerie.
I completely agree.
-Mayu has some news.
-What is it?
Well...
We're all set for October 31st
at Ebisu Square Hall.
As for the budget,
out of the 12 million yen
Mr. Saruhashi has brought in,
we'll use seven million.
We can use the rest
to produce garments for Em.
So we can only put the show on once.
We can only afford one day at that venue.
So we'll have to do the rehearsals
on the same day.
We'll invite 200 guests.
Sixty regular clients.
Forty guests from the public.
Eighty journalists.
And we're planning for
twenty celebrity guests as well.
As for the public guests,
we've advertised on shopping sites.
We're expecting to receive
100 or so entries.
We've taken care of the venue.
We've taken care of the guests.
And once we'll have chosen the models,
we'll just have to go through with it.
Emotion's first runway show.
We can do this.
Well...
Can I have your attention for a moment?
What's wrong?
I want to say something.
I'll only say this once.
And never again.
For Emotion,
this little shop was everything.
It was my own little world.
Therefore,
I've never made a single compromise.
I'm proud to say that everything I've made
has been nothing short of perfect.
However,
that sort of obsession
only created a difficult situation
for someone trying to follow
in my footsteps.
It made someone
who works with so much pride
throw away that pride.
And it crushed the hopes
of any young employee
wanting to enter the workforce.
And yet,
I refuse to change my ways.
I know now
that we must keep challenging ourselves.
Using Mizuki's designs,
we'll launch Em,
a mass-produced second line.
Our little trunk show
will now take place in a grand hall.
Scaled up to a runway show.
And many customers
new to Emotion will watch the show.
I hate to say it,
but for someone my age,
these challenges are very scary.
But I want to do this!
So please...
will you help me take on this challenge?
For the show,
we'll have 30 different styles
for 12 models.
And six different styles for
Mizuki's Em line.
The show itself will last 20 minutes,
but if we include the reception
and after-party,
we're looking at an hour and a half--
Wait.
For the show,
we'll start with 15 sets from Emotion,
then six sets for Mizuki's Em,
and then back to nine sets for Emotion.
That's 24 styles for Emotion alone.
We'll include past designs.
Of course, we'll need new designs as well.
But we want to show
as many of our products as we can.
If we do this,
we have to be better than Story.
You really hold a grudge.
I'm being serious.
Sorry.
The purpose of the show
is to increase brand awareness.
Which is why we invited the press,
as well as celebrities.
I know this isn't really your thing.
We're doing all of this for
Emotion and Em.
I know.
There's one thing that bothers me.
Yes?
What's the theme?
Here we go again with the theme.
Who's directing?
I know!
But we're out of money.
We have to do it ourselves.
I'll do the research.
I'm very determined.
I'll make it happen.
This is so cool!
But I'm sure it's very expensive.
That's so original!
So original!
That's so beautiful.
All right, that's enough.
I need to come up with a theme.
Who said you could eat that?
That's from Kyugetsudo, in Ginza.
It's their limited edition tsukimi dango!
They were so hard to get!
I'm sorry.
They were just sitting here.
You're not supposed to inhale them.
You're supposed to savor them
while watching a full moon.
I can't believe you!
Okay, fine. I'm the tsukimi thief.
Where I'm from,
children were allowed to sneak away with
the sweet offerings made for tsukimi.
We called them "tsukimi thieves."
That's funny.
But I could never bring myself to do it.
So my mom told me,
"More luck will come
when sweets are stolen.
It makes people happy."
She said, "It's okay.
Go ahead and have fun."
I think I was two at the time.
I don't really remember my mom very well.
But when I see the moon,
I feel as if I could see her face.
How strange.
These really go well with coffee.
It's really nice.
That image.
It's true.
The moon gives off a feminine image.
For the Emotion runway show,
we have a theme for
the 2016 spring/summer collection.
MOON
Moon.
Moon?
Why?
I was originally thinking of "Flower."
But "Flower" was stolen by Story.
That's a low blow.
I'm just teasing.
I really want to go with "Moon."
Any reason?
The moon gives off a feminine image.
It's said that more births occur
during a full moon.
I feel that there's a relationship between
the moon and a woman's biorhythms.
And the moon is multifaceted,
which is a very feminine trait.
That's true.
"Moon" would be perfect for Emotion.
The theme will be "Moon."
Let's go with that.
A lingerie show?
I heard from a photographer
that Emotion is planning one.
It seems the press will be there.
It'll be a pretty big deal.
Well... I see.
So...
Only the white rose
required a correction, right?
I'll be able to take care of it this week.
It's refreshing to see you being so calm.
What?
Excuse me for saying this,
but I didn't expect you to have
that much talent for design.
But you consider ideas from both
the marketing team
and the development team.
It's truly wonderful.
Thank you.
When Ms. Nishizawa left,
I was worried
that if you failed,
it would be the end of Story.
No, you weren't.
How much of an impact
can one individual have?
If I fail, you'll simply replace me.
For that reason,
I'll hang on to Story
no matter what happens.
And I won't lose to Emotion.
Welcome.
Thanks for coming on your day off.
I'm so excited to hear that
Emotion is doing a runway show.
Any knowledge you can share
on how to show a collection
would be very helpful.
"Save the date"?
What's that?
It's useful for confirming guests.
For guests you really want at the show,
you send them save-the-date cards
before sending out the invitations,
so they can keep their schedules clear.
Follow an order of priority.
-The most important guests first?
-Yes.
Such as the editor-in-chief of
a fashion magazine?
It looks good.
Wow.
I'm so disappointed.
It's such bad timing.
I really wanted to be a part of your show.
It's okay.
You're going to Paris.
It was so sudden.
I still can't believe it.
You were chosen as the face of Sumeragi!
It's amazing!
You look beautiful.
It's limited to the Asian editions.
That's still amazing!
You've got an interview in five minutes.
-We'll then start the afternoon shoot.
-Yes.
I'm sorry. You're busy.
You're meeting with Ms. Nagai, right?
She's here today.
Conscious is an influential magazine.
You should go for it.
Thanks.
Beautiful. Beautiful.
Looking good.
What do you think?
It looks good.
We're good!
That's it for today.
Ms. Nagai.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm Ms. Tokita, from Emotion.
I know I've repeatedly been discourteous
in the past.
I came here today to ask
if you would come to our show.
SHUMEI PUBLISHING
I'll leave that up to you.
Good morning.
Thank you for letting me observe the shoot
the other day.
I wanted to ask again
if you would come to our show.
I've already told you
I'll be busy that day.
It's true, having Ms. Nagai at the show
would make a big difference.
Wherever she goes, the celebrities follow.
Yes.
For some international collections,
if there's a guest they absolutely want,
they'll even change the date
to accommodate their schedule.
But our venue...
What do you mean?
If you can't make it,
there's no point in even doing this show.
So we've already canceled the show
for October 31st.
You canceled it?
We've decided to change the date
in order to accommodate your schedule.
I'd like to ask again.
Which day would work best for you?
Well, let me take a look.
If it were on November 1st--
Thank you!
So we'll schedule the show
for November 1st.
I'm so glad.
We're looking forward to seeing you.
I'm sorry.
We'd like to cancel for October 31st.
By the way, how does November 1st look?
It's fully booked.
Of course it is.
I see.
I'm sorry.
It's November 1st.
Yes.
How's it going?
I see. Don't worry.
I'll find a venue.
You have to work on the show.
We're running out of time.
But still.
Thanks to you, what's important
is the show, not the venue.
You should hire a professional director.
We can transfer a part of the budget.
Your expression says otherwise.
You're right.
I can use every yen we have right now.
The shipping costs are really hurting us.
Don't worry.
We can direct the show ourselves.
We know Emotion better than anyone.
We can do it.
Shoes?
Yes, of course.
We need shoes.
Yes.
We'll have them ready for the models
come audition time.
SHOES
No. I said, "Moon."
Yes, the theme is "Moon."
Can we install a device
to display that image?
SET INSTALLATION
Usage rights fees?
Of course there is.
To play music,
we have to pay usage rights fees.
MUSIC
Do we need that many
hair and makeup artists?
So we need separate people
doing hair and makeup?
We need 10 artists?
And their assistants?
What's a fitter?
What should I do?
Mayu, Mrs. Ono is here.
She wants to see you.
Okay.
Welcome.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
I'm sorry,
things are a little crazy right now.
ANMITSU 700 YEN
CREAM ANMITSU 900 YEN
That's silly of you.
Trying to do everything on your own.
Yes.
But I understand the feeling
of wanting to do things yourself.
Yes.
But you know, a strong person
isn't afraid to ask for help.
Amazing.
These are furisodes, right?
Are they all made of silk?
My son is married
to the daughter of a kimono shop owner.
These are all too old for the shop.
Please, take them.
I also have obis and fans.
Just let me know if you need them.
Kimonos could work.
The moon and the kimono.
It's like the tale of Kaguyahime!
Thank you so much.
Good luck.
Really?
That sounds wonderful.
I'll ask my teacher
if she can play the violin for you.
Thank you so much!
This is Ms. Matsubara, who does our PR.
I've already told her about the show.
I'm Ms. Matsubara.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Ms. Tokita, from Emotion.
We'll lend you the 12 pairs of shoes,
along with three backups for the runway.
Please let me know if you also need bags.
Thank you so much!
If you could include our brand name
in the press kit,
along with shots of our shoes,
we'd appreciate it.
Ms. Tokita.
I can't thank you enough for your help.
I'm back!
I got shoes.
Welcome back.
That's great!
The Em line has also been taken care of.
Really? You're done?
They just came in from the factory.
Look!
They're so cute!
They look good.
They don't look like
they're part of a second line.
I'm quite proud of them.
These will sell.
We'll sell them!
-I'm back!
-Kaji?
Are you okay, Kaji?
Capacity of 200 to 300.
1.2 million yen per day.
I negotiated the extra fees
from 300,000 yen to 200,000 yen.
The Aoyama Garden Hall, November 1st.
I got it!
Kaji.
Are we ready for this?
Yes.
Please, have the money ready.
What's it called?
The Aoyama Garden Hall.
It's nice, right?
Yes, I see.
The evening moon is mysterious,
and the daytime moon is modest,
hidden within the sky.
That's right.
It's an expression of a woman's
multifaceted nature.
My daughter's mood is constantly changing.
Right?
Speaking of the moon,
the wedding we just coordinated
had the moon as a theme.
We still have the set that was used.
Should I get it for you?
Are you serious?
I'll call them now.
Kaguyahime?
I wonder if my daughter will disappear
to the moon someday as well.
Hello?
There's even a really beautiful
bridal kimono.
I think it'll be gorgeous
if we use it at the end.
Bridal kimono?
I see...
We'll have live music,
and turn it into a celebration.
She's like a celebrity now.
I shouldn't have let her model
for that magazine.
They agreed.
Where should they take it?
We can really have it?
Yes, and it looks really nice too.
They spent a lot of money on it.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I'm just so happy.
So many people are helping me.
I'm glad.
Okay.
You're still working?
Just a little longer.
Have some coffee.
Thank you.
It's so good.
I've got hair, makeup
and the fitters covered.
There will be two of each
to fit the models.
I'm so glad. Thank you.
I'm just disappointed that
I couldn't get a better deal.
That can't be helped.
It's very glamorous.
It's really happening.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Are you getting enough sleep?
If I were to lie down right now,
I'd fall asleep in a second.
Me too.
Then you should go home.
You need to rest before the event.
You too, Mayu!
I'm fine.
Go home.
But...
Okay, good night.
Thank you for your help.
Wait.
The image of the moon...
REHEARSAL DAY
Yes.
The doctor saw her.
But she hasn't woken up?
I'll head over to the hospital.
No, you can leave her to me.
Let me know if anything happens.
Yes.
Don't let your hair fall forward.
Okay.
I hope Mayu is okay.
It's really nice.
That image.
It's true.
The moon gives off a feminine image.
It's so beautiful.
Yes, it is.
I slept so well.
What? Kaji?
A hospital?
Mayu.
Are you okay?
The runway hit you.
Actually, it didn't.
But you fell and lost consciousness.
Sorry.
I think I just fell asleep.
-What?
-Well, I fell.
And my body became limp.
The ground felt so nice and cool.
And then, I passed out.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Did you worry about me?
Well, you'd been working so hard.
But I'm really glad you're okay.
If anything had happened to you,
I would have--
The fitting!
I'm so glad you're okay.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
What's wrong?
Do you feel sick?
No.
Will you stop it?
Please, stop it.
I'm sorry. Please, stop it!
I'm sorry.
Please.
Just forget everything.
What I had in mind
wasn't this.
I want to impress people,
but not like this.
The kimonos.
The accessories.
The lights, the music.
Everything is beautiful.
But this is not it.
What I want...
the guests to see...
is what I see.
Emotion's...
truly beautiful lingerie!
Nothing else.
Everyone left.
I know it's wrong of me.
After what happened with Story,
I wanted revenge,
I wanted to get back at them.
But I was wrong.
And there were people
who pushed me in the right direction.
So many people have helped me.
But none of that matters.
Does it?
You now have a clear image
of what you want.
But if you create something that doesn't
feel right to you,
then you're not being true to yourself.
It'll be okay!
I'll make the formal apologies.
What should I do?
The invitations just need to be sent out.
The press kit is done.
Ms. Nagai is coming.
The celebrities will be there.
The press will be there.
And yet!
I rejected everything
just based on gut feeling!
What should I do?
I only have one week!
One week...
Are you okay?
I should get the brandy.
How much can you pay?
STAGE DIRECTOR
TSUNEHIKO MIKI
I usually don't work
for anything less than
one million yen.
But my plans for November 1st
happened to fall through.
After Japan Fashion Week,
I was planning to go to the Maldives
with a model I've had my eye on.
But she turned me down yesterday.
-Female?
-Male.
I feel depressed, so I want to work.
How much will you pay?
I won't do it for free.
I'm a pro, after all.
Pro?
I've seen this name before.
Tsunehiko Miki.
Wait! Are you the Tsunehiko Miki?
Here it is.
Take a look.
Wait.
You staged this, Mr. Miki?
This one too?
This is the one I said was so original!
I watched all of these
while doing my research!
Research?
So, what are you going to do?
No.
I couldn't possibly ask
anyone else for help.
Are you stupid?
You know what I can't stand?
Amateurs who think
they can impress people
without spending any money.
Thinking they can move people's hearts,
and put on a polished show.
All on their own!
You're just an amateur.
And you think you can pull it off?
I can't stand that kind of naive thinking!
This isn't some school festival.
Don't underestimate my job!
A job that impresses others
can only be done by a skilled pro.
Now that you work at Emotion,
you've had the opportunity to see that.
Determination alone won't get you there.
Hand over the cash.
My fee
is open for negotiation.
This runway is very simple.
The invitation cards?
Invitations
are like magic cards.
On each envelope,
add a mark.
Okay.
The seating chart?
Who will you seat in the first row?
Just hand me your guest list!
That looks nice.
How long have you been working on it?
You're so mean.
You already had a plan in mind.
You should've told her from the start.
At some point,
I have to let go of her hand.
Otherwise, she won't grow.
And neither will I.
And neither will Emotion.
It's good, isn't it?
She concluded that what she created
wasn't good enough.
And she was right.
THE DAY OF THE RUNWAY SHOW
FOR EMOTION
THE AOYAMA GARDEN HALL
-Good morning!
Thank you.
The day has arrived.
Yes.
Thanks for everything.
You really helped me, Kaji.
We don't have time.
Let's hurry.
You're right.
Let's go.
Yes.
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.