Perfect.
Time to go.
POLYESTER - SILK - COTTON
MODAL - TRIACETATE
Silk, okay.
ISHIKAWA TAILOR
Mayu!
Yuri.
I knew it.
You forgot.
Sorry.
We were supposed to have tea before work.
You should have called me.
Well, I hit it off
with a guy sitting next to me.
We started talking,
and time flew by.
Friends already?
I'm starting to feel like
I can make it here.
Hey, do I look okay? I had a really
hard time deciding what to wear.
-Do I look weird? Like a hick?
-No.
You look like you've made an effort.
You'll make a good impression.
Can't you just say I look cute?
You know,
we studied textile at college,
and you chose to wear that
on your first day?
What?
But it's a suit.
Well, whatever.
Oh, my office is this way.
Bye.
We're off to a good start
on our new lives!
We won't let Tokyo stop us!
I'll e-mail you later.
AZUMA INARI SHRINE
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-The new hire?
-Ms. Tokita.
Found this place all right?
I'm Mayuko Tokita.
Pleased to meet you.
Um, am I late?
It's not that.
Just--
Ms. Tokita. You just got here,
but I need to give you a task.
Yes.
Could you take this fabric sample
to Sekiguchi in Nippori?
I'll give you the address.
It's a fabric store.
Nippori, the fabric district.
Sorry for rushing you like this.
-Hime.
-Yes?
-Give her the map.
-Okay.
Sorry for the chaos.
We're having a trunk show this weekend.
-Trunk show?
-Unveiling of our new products.
We'll put on a show here in the store.
2015 FALL-WINTER PRODUCT LAUNCH
-Hey, photos of the fitting?
-Yes.
Sorry about that.
Isn't this gorgeous?
These walk right in front of you.
Heaven for men.
Right?
I look at those strictly
from a professional--
You are mumbling.
-Stop fooling around.
-Mizuki's edgy.
It's her debut.
Changed your style too, right?
She designs shapes first.
Straight as an arrow.
Say what you like.
I'm staking my whole life on this.
Hurry up.
I'm off.
Wait, the map!
Design change?
We only have five days.
THESE THREE DESIGNS WILL BE CHANGED
FOR THE APRIL 11 TRUNK SHOW
Ah, the design change,
as expected.
The boss seemed
to be in that kind of mood.
And what's more,
three of them!
Only five days until the show.
Well, what's that saying?
Nothing new.
We'll just move on.
Fumi, do we have the new designs?
Um...
We have two out of the three.
All these are my design.
She came up with something, again.
So we'll make these two,
and the last one...
We'll just wait.
NEW HIRE
TRUNK SHOW
Will she change the staging too?
Talk to the boss.
I don't think she'll change that.
We can't postpone it now.
We've already sent out the invitation.
We'll go on with the show on the 11th.
That's our schedule.
Okay.
-Give it to me.
-Yes.
I'm sure you'll go through a lot,
but we'll do this together, okay?
Okay.
"Emotion is a made-to-order
lingerie maker.
We take detailed measurements
of our customers,
listen to their requests,
and make the one and only lingerie
in the world for each of them.
So, these are just images
that our president Mayumi Nanjo offers.
They're not for sale."
Perfect.
I couldn't say it so smoothly.
These are called haute couture, right?
Well, strictly speaking,
they're not.
They're one of a kind.
Lavish, isn't it?
It's really amazing,
creating all the way from fabric.
Indeed.
What, fabric?
I'm so excited.
I studied textile at college.
It's my dream to develop new materials
like microfiber or carbon fiber.
Wait.
We don't develop new fabrics.
Huh?
But Ms. Nanjo said we create
from scratch.
I think you have the wrong idea
about our job.
You should have a talk with her.
That's her atelier.
This material...
Bare jersey made with rayon
and polyurethane.
Stretchable and so sleek.
I'm in heaven!
Quite a soliloquist.
Ms. Nanjo...
Good morning.
You're cute.
I envy young girls.
They don't need any effort to be cute.
Such radiant, firm skin.
What do you eat to keep it?
No, I'm wrong.
It doesn't matter what you eat.
You eat salty and greasy food to death,
but it stays smooth.
I'll bet mosquitoes just slide off it.
Nowhere for them to bite.
Just joking.
What's good about that fabric?
That.
Rayon bare jersey.
Oh. Um...
Stretchable,
produces great colors,
and absorbs moisture well,
very functional as underwear.
Very soft texture.
Processed to prevent shrinkage,
-so it's washable--
-Bad things?
-It's heavy.
-So knowledgeable.
I'm Mayuko Tokita.
Thank you for hiring me.
But...
may I ask you a question?
At the interview, I heard I could
develop fabrics that can be used--
But too bad.
You're tacky.
You have firm and smooth skin,
you know a lot about fabrics.
But you're tacky.
Grossly tacky.
Stand two meters away from me.
Pardon?
Women who don't care about beauty
make me want to punch them.
Okay, okay.
I'll take care of her.
I was going to ask you to run an errand.
You're going shopping in Ginza.
It'll be fun!
Thank you very much.
Give my regards to Ms. Nanjo.
I hope the show is a success.
Thanks.
Wait.
I'm a regular customer of Emotion too.
That's...
Thank you very much.
Sorry for my outfit.
Please tell Ms. Nanjo I'll let her know
when we get more good stuff.
Okay.
Here's the Raphael Collin's piece
Ms. Nanjo ordered.
Those shoes look comfortable.
I'm a working woman.
These shoes are perfect.
Huh?
Sorry for being tacky.
What's so wrong with this outfit?
I hate this town!
Something like this,
in green this time.
I'll gather up torchon laces for you.
7,000 yen...
70,000!
MRS. MUROI
PURCHASE AMOUNT
-So, the trunk show is this Saturday.
-Yes.
Most brands have already finished
showing their fall-winter collection.
What delayed your show?
Any issues with you, Ms. Nanjo?
No particular reason.
Everyone's wondering.
"What will Mayumi Nanjo create next?"
It determines the lingerie trend in Japan.
I, for one, keep doing this job
just to see your new creation.
I'm very flattered.
But I'm a little worried.
I can attest to the fact that Emotion's
lingerie is the best of the world,
but today your products are
more like traditional craft than fashion.
You did not just say that.
You're welcome.
I make the same things again and again?
It's none of your concern.
A critic should not meddle with
a maker's creative process.
All you need to do is evaluate
the finished products.
It's always a critic with good eyes
that leads the culture.
Wanna hear more? You're in a rut.
No novelty.
Laces, silk, embroidery, silk again.
Shut up, you noisy hag.
We're two of a kind.
Well, okay, let's stop there.
Please, Shuko--
Quiet, Saru.
Listen, I have only one criterion,
and that's whether it's beautiful or not.
And what makes it beautiful
is not just design or how it looks.
Top class material,
elaborate patterns,
high-quality sewing,
maximum comfort,
reasonable prices,
customer satisfaction.
Only the products that have all of these
can be called beautiful.
-But--
-Novelty? What's novelty?
No one knows what it will be.
Don't expect us to be new.
I have made and will always make
only beautiful products.
Big mouth, as always.
Okay, let's wrap it up then.
Looking forward to the trunk show.
It's rare
to see you in such distress.
I am aware of all the noise around me.
You've been an icon
in the lingerie industry for 30 years.
You wanna quit?
Did I say such a thing?
Organize the stockroom.
It's so messy.
That's why my head is messy inside too.
These are...
I feel so at home!
Straps, adjusters...
Loops go there.
Good, perfect.
Such a soliloquist.
Tough first day, isn't it?
Wish we could give you a welcome party.
It's okay.
I love doing this.
Better than a welcome party
or a drinking party.
A hundred times better.
You're funny.
Mayuko Tokita. Where did you
go to college? Oh, yeah, Nagano.
What are you doing with those?
-Throwing them away.
-Why?
They're very nice.
This silk is among the best.
No matter how good they are,
we never put them out
if the boss is dissatisfied.
That's our motto.
Hello, um...
New girl!
The boss?
Yes!
Bring me coffee.
Okay!
-You don't mind that?
-What?
Drink whatever you like.
Fits for a fashionable office.
It's not so rare though.
Fumi, has the boss
given you the new design?
Not yet.
She's never been this late before.
Right.
She must be so shocked.
This trunk show was the first time
her design was chosen.
Three of them.
But then...
That thing this morning?
Samples had already been made,
but all of them were scrapped.
The ones Mr. Saruhashi threw away...
You're bringing coffee to the boss, right?
This is the only kind she drinks.
Thank you, er, Hime...
Call me Sosuke.
-You're acting superior.
-I'm not!
-I'll show you how to drip brew--
-I know how.
My father loves drip brew.
It's good.
You're good at brewing coffee.
Thank you very much.
You're a woman, right?
Tell me what "dissemble" means.
Um, well...
To adorn only what can be seen
and hide the true nature,
to pretend to be something else.
You're right.
But it can also mean...
to spruce yourself up nicely
according to time and place,
strive to make yourself fit,
and try not to give discomfort to others.
Now that you're here,
learn to dissemble like a woman.
You give me discomfort.
You know why?
Because you're not beautiful.
You're right.
I'm not beautiful.
If you like beautiful women so much,
hire a super-stylish model!
Excuse me.
Sorry for interrupting.
Next.
Stand there.
So sleek.
I'll bet the water just runs off your skin
after a shower.
Models for the trunk show.
The boss hand-picks them.
Face to the right.
Face back to me.
Here it is.
I'm sorry, but you're not hired.
Of course.
I can't land a job if I faint like that.
So hungry.
I haven't eaten for three days.
To keep my stomach flat.
But you're already beautiful.
Why?
I'm back.
Mizuki?
Ah, 1.2 million yen of product cost...
1.2 million?
Don't worry.
-See you tomorrow.
-Yes...
You can go home too.
You give me discomfort.
Because you're not beautiful.
FOUR DAYS TILL TRUNK SHOW
Good morning.
Sorry I'm late.
Wow.
Same outfit as yesterday.
Not only young and firm,
but also stubborn.
Youthfulness is a scary thing.
I'm sorry.
I fell asleep here.
I need to emulate your strong spirit.
I'm so pure-minded and wimpy.
"Says who?" Saruhashi,
you just thought that, didn't you?
-Boss, the last design--
-Not yet.
This is not good.
Then we'll do the trunk show
with just what we have.
One less item
won't affect the staging much.
Then it's the same as before.
We have to show progress.
A surprise at the end.
Or we'll cancel the show.
We can't do that!
Then shut your mouth!
Why?
We had products finished on time.
So why are we making new ones?
What's wrong with this one?
Hey, Ms. Tokita--
The material is hygroscopic cupro,
regenerated fiber
made with natural materials.
Thin and delicate,
ideal for underwear.
Cups are silk
of very high quality.
Wonder how many hands
went through to make it.
So why?
Why does it have to be cut to pieces?
Why can't this be in the show?
Because it's not beautiful.
That...
is in the eye of the beholder.
I think it's very beautiful.
Don't use the word "beautiful" lightly.
This doesn't meet Emotion's standards.
Also, you don't meet
our company's standards.
Emotion's not just a lingerie maker
but a leader that maintains
the highest standard of beauty.
As such,
we can't be insensitive to beauty.
What is beauty?
Underwear touches people's skin.
So hygroscopicity,
elasticity,
weight and allergy sensitivity
must be considered.
In other words,
functionality is what's most important.
There's no room for beauty there.
Are decorations
like lace really necessary?
To throw away 1.2 million yen
for a slight design change
is absurd!
Debauchery of the rich!
You don't show off your underwear.
-Why in the--
-What a big mouth.
I'm so sorry.
I apologize.
Forgive me for being rude.
Wait.
Finish your speech.
"Why in the..."
Why in the world
do women have to
try to be beautiful?
Styling our hair,
choosing cute clothes,
taking time to put on makeup.
Why wear expensive lingerie
and make our breasts look bigger
and our body look sleek?
Why do women have to dress up themselves
and look beautiful?
It's absurd!
It's so unreasonable!
Follow me.
Look at this.
Throughout human history,
in Asia, Africa, North and South America,
and of course Europe,
all women,
in every age and every place,
have been trying to be beautiful
all through their existence.
And humans have been admiring
the beauty of women.
Your questions are nonsense.
The human history
is the answer.
Perfect place to mope.
I'm really sorry.
For saying those things to her
even though I don't know anything.
No, you don't.
You started just yesterday
and negated the sensitive nature
of our job.
We feel humiliated.
My sincere apologies.
Although, you do have a point.
No one knows for sure what beauty is.
But, because no one knows,
someone like our boss, Mayumi Nanjo,
has to keep pursuing it.
Otherwise, our world would be
filled with ugly, cheap,
low quality stuff.
Well, for now,
that frown needs to go.
Yes.
The trunk show is coming.
Our sales this season will be determined
by a dozen or so attendees there.
So smile and do your best.
Okay.
No good.
THREE DAYS TILL TRUNK SHOW
-Good morning.
-Morning.
You're early.
How did it go yesterday?
Good.
I'm so sorry for causing trouble.
For a new hire, I was insolent.
Let me guess where you went after that.
Art museum.
Don't worry.
All of us have been there.
Why?
It's beautiful.
The problem is weight.
Yes, it is heavy.
But it should be okay if used in parts.
Or use a less dense type
to make it lighter.
No good.
It's gym clothes.
Gym clothes are evolving too.
You really are stubborn.
If you want beauty,
printed rayon bare jersey
will have bright and beautiful colors.
It has a different feel from silk
and drapes well.
Stretchable, hygroscopic,
and beautiful.
This is functional beauty.
"Functional beauty."
Yes.
Give it to me.
I see.
Print is a good idea.
That's your response?
TWO DAYS TILL TRUNK SHOW
Here it is!
Pattern, fabric, colors.
All there!
I'll make a spec.
What's this?
Rayon bare jersey...
She wants to use this material?
And print?
Let's hurry up. We only have one more day!
Are you kidding?
DAY OF THE TRUNK SHOW
Here you go.
Please.
What do you think?
This is
an amazing world.
Thank goodness we made it.
Have I withered?
Still beautiful, Reiko.
The number is much lower this time.
The boss had a very hard time.
This is a very famous brand.
I know this store!
This is a textile company.
And this...
What's wrong?
They rejected me when I was job hunting.
Classic, delicate, graceful.
That's Mayumi Nanjo's design.
But this time,
novel!
There it is. "Novel!"
She said "novel!"
Any complaints?
No way.
You make a new trend,
and the whole market moves.
I'll get more jobs.
Thank heavens.
See you later.
Good night.
Why don't you say anything to her?
Well, because I can't compete with her.
I doubt that.
I think you have better taste.
What?
This is what I don't like.
I love it because it's taking risks
on colors and design.
But...
I just don't like this.
It's like wearing a jersey.
Can you use silk here as usual?
-Excuse me, this material--
-Ms. Sato.
I'll use silk here.
Is the color okay as it is?
Wait, wait.
What is it?
I thought we put out
only what satisfies her.
-That's right.
-Then why did she agree to change it?
And Mizuki's design--
Customers are allowed to be irresponsible.
Even though we pride ourselves
for making the best and latest,
if we push our products to customers,
it's no longer made-to-order.
What the boss wants
is to make the one and only
for our customers.
That's what pleases them.
Look.
That's right.
It's fun, isn't it?
What are you doing?
See you tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Well...
What do you really think?
Hmm?
What you think is beautiful
is different than what sells.
I agree.
But, do you really think
it's the right thing to do,
to make whatever customers want?
Does anyone show
what their true thoughts are?
It's a true thought because we hide it.
You really are a mismatch here
if you don't understand
the beauty of hiding.
That's not true.
A surprising response.
I don't know if I fit here,
but I find underwear fascinating.
It's fascinating because it's enigmatic.
You're fascinating
because you're enigmatic.
I'm flattered.
Plus, I like this.
I think this is very good,
especially here.
When I saw this,
I thought this job was nice.
However, I can never buy
70,000 yen underwear.
People here have too much money.
What?
Are you saying you're tacky
because you're poor?
Don't underestimate the poor.
You're not poor.
You just look poor.
Excuse me.
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.