Tokyo has everything.
I know! I never imagined
I'd be eating sanzokuyaki in Ginza.
Apparently, I'm too unsophisticated.
It's impossible
for someone to work in Ginza,
unless that someone is you.
Stop being biased towards rich people.
It's Dad's money.
You know what?
Don't listen to your boss.
You're not poor and unsophisticated.
You eat three meals a day.
You have a place to live.
Your clothes might show you lack taste,
but at least you're wearing them.
Taste. I hate that word.
What do you mean?
If you're buying the same cheap thing,
it makes a huge difference!
It's a matter of taste.
Will you stop emphasizing "taste"?
I'm not!
And besides, I mean "taste in fashion."
When I become a wedding planner,
I'll plan yours,
and it'll be tasteful and amazing!
You're being too loud.
You'd better get used to it.
Me? I have my phone in one hand
and a bra in the other.
I can go outside like this.
I, I can too!
Mr. Fujimura!
I was just about to come and get you.
Thank you for meeting me.
2015 STORE EXPANSION AND PRODUCT PLACEMENT
Mr. Fujimura, we can't mass produce.
We only do custom made garments.
Yes, I completely understand.
Is there a way we can work around it?
You know how Ms. Nanjo is.
That's why I'm asking you.
Mr. Fujimura.
May I join the conversation?
Well... I should be going now.
"He that would the daughter win,
must with the mother first begin."
We plan to win you over soon enough.
Our motto is to provide all customers,
from all walks of life,
with quality products.
What a wonderful motto.
Excuse me for saying this,
President Nanjo.
You...
only deal with customers
that can afford to walk through
that fancy door.
There aren't many people in Yamagata
who can afford to walk through that door.
Don't you think that's unfair?
He was from Vanderbilt's Tokyo.
Wouldn't it be great
to have our products there?
The boss believes in
doing things custom made.
But even haute couture
has the option of prêt-à-porter.
Pru... Pre?
Prêt-à-porter.
High end, ready-to-wear.
Clothing stores in Ginza
generally all carry prêt-à-porter.
Prataporte, prataporte.
Did Pierre Cardin coin the term?
Everyone switched to ready-made
because they realized custom made
didn't make for very good business.
But top brands like Dior and Chanel
all began as custom tailors, right?
We should have more pride.
Well, that's true but...
Ladies.
We have three more clients today.
Get back to work!
Reiko has so much energy.
I'm so exhausted already.
The trunk show did really well this time.
But there are so many orders!
I have to take the last train every night!
That's wonderful.
It means we have a lot of customers.
Speaking of customers,
Fumi, don't we have to
work on Mrs. Hashimoto's pattern?
Yes, we do!
Yes.
Boss! Please give me a project too!
But not getting coffee, running errands,
or stocking up.
Something more like
working directly with the customers?
You can stand still.
I have no time to be teaching you.
Welcome, Ms. Kondou.
We've been expecting you.
Do you have a specific outfit in mind?
If it's a dress, we can design it
with a low neckline.
Yes, I do have a dress in mind.
Let's start by taking the measurements.
Then, we can discuss the details.
I'm so sorry.
It's a little warm in there.
Let's air it out.
It'll be ready in five minutes.
-Please, bring the tea menu.
-Sure.
Boss, I can bring the tea.
I have the perfect job for you.
Did you know that dust
is mostly made up of fiber?
Your favorite.
You get to collect it.
Isn't that wonderful?
Yes!
The final design is ready!
Here you go.
Here it is.
An irregular pattern!
Casablanca.
Do we have it in stock?
It's perfectly organized.
It's the only thing I could do.
I'm so sorry.
We're swamped with orders.
I'll teach you once things settle down.
Okay.
The light beige fabric won't come in
until the day after tomorrow.
I'll go pick it up tomorrow night,
so tell them to make it happen.
Sure thing.
Am I that messy?
Please take a look.
Thank you.
You're like Cinderella.
You're making me feel bad for you.
Don't worry about me.
Dust is mostly fiber, you know?
If you love fiber,
you have to take care of it.
It shouldn't stay in the corner of a room
with the rest of the dust.
That's way too sad.
That's taking it a little too far.
Why do you love it so much?
It's going to be a long story.
I'd appreciate a condensed version.
I'm from Nagano.
My father worked for
a company that made silk.
As a child, I was impressed
by the cocoons of thread.
I fell in love with the final fabric.
That's how it all started.
I left out the most important part!
Do you mind if I go on?
Go ahead.
The "Mayu" part of my name...
comes from the "Mayu" meaning cocoon.
I see.
-That explains your love of fiber.
-Yes.
If you love beautiful threads...
then you're in the right field.
Even if you're Cinderella now.
Not to worry.
Because cleaning and organizing...
I love it.
Let me tell you--
Next time!
-Yes?
-That.
That's so cool.
What?
This? Is it?
Is it very difficult to measure the bust?
Yes, it's difficult.
It should require national certification.
National certification?
Doctors, hair stylists...
jobs in which you touch another person
require national certification.
Yes.
To have access to a person's body,
as well as information
pertaining to their body,
is no small matter.
So it requires certification.
Customers can therefore
have some peace of mind.
You're right.
Being a lingerie consultant
is a job that also requires
skill and training.
Reiko.
What is it?
Never stand directly
in front of a customer.
It could make her feel uncomfortable.
Stand a step off to the side.
As for the measuring tape, the zero
should be on your left, kept short.
The tape should never touch the floor.
You're going to use it on your customer.
First, start with the bust.
Bring the tape around the back
and slide it.
You need to measure
the highest point of the bust.
Next, the lower bust.
For the waist...
the area between the hip bone and ribs.
And finally, the hips.
Meanwhile, subtly check
the hip bones and bust.
Keep touching to a minimum.
Our boss can instantly get a feel for
a customer's body shape.
Lines and curves.
Those can't be expressed in numbers.
Here.
You can only learn from experience.
Experience.
It's finally becoming interesting.
But they won't let me do anything yet.
That's too bad.
The Black Velvet.
It's ready, so I'll put it here.
Thank you.
Coffee for the boss.
This is all she drinks.
It's so comforting here.
Grandfathers used to hang out
in places like this back home, right?
And it would turn into
a karaoke bar at night.
This is how we set up after 10:00 p.m.
Welcome.
So, what's the news?
So tomorrow, I get to help
shop for a bride's dress.
And next month,
I get to do it all on my own.
-Already?
-Yes!
The company wants the newbies
to learn from experience.
Experience?
But it's overwhelming to suddenly
have so much responsibility.
I haven't learned anything yet.
You're so lucky.
Experience.
You want me to hold down the fort
on my own?
Don't worry.
We have no appointments
scheduled for today.
There shouldn't be anyone coming in.
But if anyone does comes in,
just call me and I'll come right over.
Got it?
Understood.
Here.
The key to the shop.
For you.
For me?
My own key.
It's here!
The dress from the new line.
It's the design you wanted.
I'll bring it to the church right away!
I'll make sure it's there on time!
It's so empty.
I'm so bored!
Welcome...
Do you... Do you have an appointment?
No... it's my first time here.
Really?
Please, feel free to look around.
I'll get my manager.
Reiko.
Excuse me.
Do I just choose something from here?
Well... That...
That section is not for sale.
Can you help me?
Of course.
What are you looking for?
A bra and panties set.
Did you have a specific outfit in mind?
If...
If it's a dress, we can design it
with a low neckline.
No, I was just curious about
trying something from this store.
Do you take measurements?
Yes!
And please, try on the sample.
You'll feel the difference.
It's so spacious.
Thank you.
If you'll excuse me.
Do you have a specific color in mind?
Are there any particular concerns
with your normal wear?
Changes you wish for?
Please, take a look.
We can start with these.
TOTAL: 105,840 yen
I guess I'll go with that.
-Great! Then we'll proceed with this.
-All right...
That's an unusual lace.
Is it organza?
And the lace, it's very detailed.
It was left over from when
I made my daughter's costume.
She takes ballet nearby.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
See you again soon.
I got an order from a new customer!
You helped the customer on your own?
I told you to call me if anyone came in.
It wasn't a problem.
I took her measurements,
fitted her with samples.
Measurements?
But you never...
Reiko taught me.
What kind of person was she?
It was someone who already had an interest
in trying out Emotion Lingerie.
This is a pretty expensive order.
She ordered this from the trunk show.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Yuri, it's Mayuko.
How did it go today?
You were right,
one learns from experience.
It's the best kind of training.
I wish someone would let me
measure their bust.
Here you go.
Why don't you go and have some?
Please.
I know it's a very strange request.
But I really want to review
what I learned today.
This was no problem.
I wanted to have some anyway.
I know it sounds crazy
to have a complete stranger
ask to take your bust measurements.
I'm fine with it.
What?
I mean, we are both women.
This is totally normal for work.
But I just ate,
so don't pay attention to my stomach.
The food was so good.
Wait... Wait a second!
I want to start from the beginning.
So, you can walk in through that door.
Is there something wrong?
Beautiful.
It's like we're different species.
The human body is so interesting!
Especially women's breasts.
It's such a complex and strange shape!
And yet, it's so beautiful...
that we can make something
that fits this form so perfectly.
Fabric is so amazing!
No, thread is amazing!
Fiber is wonderful!
You're very strange, Ms. Tokita.
We finally overcame this hurdle.
We got through all of our orders for now.
This round was really rough.
Thanks for your help with the trunk show.
That's my line.
It was your chance to shine.
Don't worry about it!
Emotion is Emotion
because of Mayumi Nanjo's designs.
Is it?
You can only do so much on your own.
Ideas, talent...
If it all depended on only one person,
wouldn't it just run dry someday?
That's what I really like about you, Fumi.
What do you mean?
From the way you look,
one wouldn't expect you
to speak so frankly.
What do you mean, from the way I look?
I mean you look so cute.
But really, it's people like you
who can overturn tradition.
Sounds like quite a feat.
How about if we use this kind of fabric.
If you can't see the form
at the pattern stage...
You have to apply the actual fabric.
Of course, but it still needs work.
You're acting differently from yesterday.
That was yesterday.
Today is today.
We're at work.
This is Emotion.
Thank you for yesterday!
Yes?
What?
Yesterday's customer
wants to cancel her order.
I see.
I tried to ask her why,
but she just apologized--
The reason is simple.
She couldn't trust you.
Have you tried on any of our products?
-No.
-Then, how could you recommend it?
Your insensitivity is so impressive,
it makes me angry.
I'm sorry.
Listen.
In order to satisfy a customer's needs...
you need experience, not heart.
You need skills
learned through accomplishment.
For that, the customer gives us
their money and their trust.
What can you offer
that's worth their money and their trust?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I gave her an incomplete lesson.
That's exactly right.
However...
if you had the sincere desire to serve
the customer when she came in,
she would have certainly
talked to you on the phone.
We could have had a long relationship.
Emotion has now lost
an important customer.
Thanks to you.
She will never...
walk through our door again.
YURI CALLING
The dress was one
the bride had been looking for.
When I found out there was one left,
I promised I would get it for her in time.
Mayu, are you listening?
Sorry.
I found the dress,
and brought it to her in time.
I'm so sorry.
But the size didn't fit.
Why didn't you tell somebody?
Of course, I had checked first.
But that brand of dress was made tight.
And the bride was a little chubby.
Everyone else already knew that
and told her the dress was sold out.
Out of consideration for her.
I thought I was doing the bride a favor.
But a newbie like me with no skills
shouldn't have butt in.
Skills.
That's true.
We made the same mistake on the same day.
We must be close.
It's not the same.
Your mistake is better.
A better mistake? Is there such a thing?
You were thinking about your customer.
Well, yes.
But I wasn't.
At all.
Excuse me.
I'd like to call that customer.
Absolutely not.
A phone call would be rude.
Then, I'll go to her home.
Her address should be on the form.
She didn't fill in her address.
Ms. Tokita.
Do you even remember her name?
I'll tell you her name.
It's Hiromi Tsukamoto.
Hiromi Tsukamoto.
Thank you very much.
Didn't she mention
a particular train station or something?
Lace.
That's an unusual lace.
It was left over from when
I made my daughter's costume.
She takes ballet nearby.
Ballet!
Ballet class.
Ballet.
Here it is!
KISHIKAWA DANCE SCHOOL
JUNIOR CLASSES – WEDNESDAY, FRIDAY
Look at me! Look.
So cute!
-Bye!
-See you later! Have fun!
Hello, it's very warm today.
We'll see you later.
Mrs. Tsukamoto!
I'm...
I know... From Emotion.
I'm sorry I canceled my order.
I'm so sorry!
I entirely misunderstood
what's most important
in meeting a customer's needs!
Excuse me.
I'm glad you finally came in.
You always stop and look at
our window display.
Yes.
I always pass by
when I go pick up my daughter.
And the trunk show the other day.
-What?
-I saw you there as well.
You remember me?
We'd been waiting
for you to come into the store.
I didn't have the courage.
But...
you took the leap, and came in.
And yet,
we weren't properly prepared
to receive you.
We sincerely apologize.
Please.
We'd like to try serving you again.
No.
I'm sorry, but no thank you.
I came here today...
to apologize for canceling.
Emotion Lingerie is too beautiful,
and too luxurious.
It wouldn't suit someone like me.
I actually laughed when I tried it on.
I thought, "What am I doing
in such a fancy lingerie store?"
It felt a little uncomfortable.
A housewife like me
should stick to what's comfortable.
So, please.
I'm sorry!
The truth is.
It's too expensive.
TOTAL: 105,840 yen
Will you give us...
another chance?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
We don't want to compromise on quality.
And we use the best craftspeople.
So the price will reflect that.
No matter how much
we try to keep costs down,
the price...
will be something like this.
TOTAL: 43,200 yen
But this is less than half
of the original price.
Isn't it too cheap?
Not at all.
With this price,
you'd be able to buy four high end
sets of lingerie at a department store.
I always buy mine at the local store.
I'm sorry.
How much do you usually spend on lingerie?
I know the question is terribly rude.
But would you tell us?
About 2,500 yen.
That's about how much I spend too.
I understand.
TOTAL: 2,500 yen
Let's do this for today.
What? You couldn't possibly...
It's fine if it's a little bit at a time.
Whenever you can.
How many times would it be?
Let's see.
Divided by 2,500 yen.
I'm so bad with numbers.
About 17 to 18 times.
Let's do 17 installments.
Whenever you stop in is fine.
We won't come chasing after you
every time you pass by the store.
Please, stop in again on the way
to your daughter's ballet class.
-But--
-I really want for you to wear this.
You fell in love with our product.
And so...
this is fine for today.
I look forward to
seeing the finished product.
It's very unusual
for the boss to make it entirely herself.
It's like I have a whole new body.
You look so pretty, Mommy.
I want one too!
When you're older.
Promise?
Please, don't ever say,
"It wouldn't suit someone like me."
I sincerely hope that one day
you'll come back for our garments
with more confidence.
Yes.
I think I wanted the confidence...
to return to work after maternity leave.
But I didn't have it.
If I could become the kind of woman
who wears Emotion Lingerie,
it would make me happy.
What made you go through the trouble?
Trouble?
You made everything from scratch yourself.
And for such a low price.
She made me remember something.
What was it?
Long ago, I...
You?
I'm not going to tell you.
What is it?
So pretty.
Saruhashi!
Hello?
2015 STORE EXPANSION AND PRODUCT PLACEMENT
What was his name,
the man from Vanderbilt's Tokyo?
You know, that guy with the slick hair.
The unpleasant guy with glasses.
Mr. Fujimura?
I'd like to speak with him.
Why is that?
Because I want to.
Do you mind?
Your prize.
Is this for me?
It's for cleaning.
What's the size?
Oh my!
Will I turn into a D-cup if I wear this?
-Don't be silly!
-Silly?
Big doesn't mean better.
That's one of my best works.
Everything you want to know is there.
As well as the job you want.
Job?
Use it as you like.
Motif.
Strap.
Side belt.
This is a satin net!
Is this urethane foam?
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.