WE ARE CLOSED FOR THE REST OF THE MONTH
A summer break in January?
How amusing.
It can't be helped.
It's been too hectic.
We haven't had any time to rest.
-Can I have a tomato please?
-Sure.
I'm impressed that Emotion
was able to pull it together.
You could have gone out of business.
-And I'll have some tofu too.
-Sure.
-I'll have some tofu as well.
Yes, we went through some rough moments.
-Miss?
-Yes?
We'll have this Daiginjo, cold.
Of course.
For Mayumi Nanjo,
all is fish that comes to the net.
Here's the tomato,
and the tofu.
And one more tofu.
That's your last dish.
This...
I'm okay.
I can have sake with rice, no problem.
It looks good.
I'll have one as well.
Here, you can have mine.
No, you should eat yours.
I don't want it right now.
You ordered it.
You're responsible for eating it.
You said you wanted it.
Why responsible? It's just tofu.
That's nothing to be arguing about.
We got together to celebrate, right?
That's right.
This is my way of thanking you.
I'm grateful.
What?
For over 30 years,
you continued to write articles
about lingerie.
And had them published.
My work was recognized by the public
thanks to the words you wrote.
Yes, it's a wonderful relationship.
You must be feeling ill. Or dying.
Should I take you to the hospital?
You look happy, Shuko.
That will not happen.
Of course not!
You don't have time to die.
Emotion is drastically growing
for the first time in 25 years.
Growing?
You can't be blamed
for what happened the first time.
You were young and couldn't keep up.
But closing the shop after one year
was a wise decision.
Shuko, you don't have
to bring up the past.
You're okay with it, right?
You've finally recovered
from your past mistakes.
I suppose.
Don't make that face.
Stop giving her a hard time.
That's not a look that says,
"Bring it on!"
"Bring it on"?
I'm too old for that.
What are you talking about?
Now's the perfect time!
You may only be able to move around freely
for another 10 years or so.
Be quiet.
I'm just tired and need a small break.
Don't just stand still.
Shuko.
When a talented designer,
who grows old and becomes satisfied
with her mediocre work,
takes a little break, she finds herself
no longer able to design.
I've seen it happen too many times.
So don't stop.
What exactly are your plans for Emotion?
Will you develop Emotion
and pass it on to the next generation?
Or will you keep it in your hands
until the day you've grown too old...
and then extinguish it?
You have to make a choice.
It's now time for you to focus on a goal,
and start moving towards that goal.
It's just a summer break.
It's only two weeks.
What's wrong with that?
I understand.
I have more urgent things to do
than be lectured by some old hag.
I understand.
You're leaving?
You're leaving for Kanazawa tomorrow,
right, Reiko?
Say hello to your husband for me.
And here.
I'll get you your change next time.
Thank you for your warning.
You're welcome.
-Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
What?
You know she can be sensitive.
It's very likely that
she hasn't really gotten over the past.
May there be many customers.
What are you doing?
Nothing, nothing.
Please come in.
Welcome.
What are you doing here so early?
I'm on summer break.
Wait. Now?
I see.
I went to the museum
I'd been wanting to go to.
I watched the movie
I'd been wanting to see.
I went to the textile factory.
I went shopping at a famous boutique.
There really isn't much
to do during a break.
So you're here because you're bored.
I lament my life at times like these.
I'd have nothing if I didn't have work.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Delicious!
Really? I'm glad.
You're picky about coffee, Mayu-chan.
Don't call me that.
That's from high school.
What's wrong with that?
You're Mayu-chan, I'm Yama-chan.
Mayu-chan, Yama-chan.
Mayu-Yama-chan!
-Stop that!
-You liked it.
This shop...
-Did you buy it?
-No, no.
Who was here before you?
I was hired as the manager.
This is one of Mr. Shikishima's
coffee shops.
He's the one who taught me
all about coffee.
I see.
So you quit the company?
Yes, I just felt it was time.
I see.
But...
I quit without saying anything...
to Mr. Yoshioka.
That's okay! It's your life, after all.
Besides, I'm sure he's not concerned
with others.
He's only interested in himself.
Sharp words, befitting an ex-wife.
Stop that.
It's already been 30 years.
Besides, it's your fault
for having introduced us.
You're the one who pestered me
into doing it.
You were in oil painting,
but you switched into industrial design
just for him!
No, I didn't!
You don't remember?
You have a selective memory.
You always do that.
Remember the summer of our sophomore year?
I totally didn't do it.
You brought the fireworks.
But you shot the fireworks
into the teacher's office.
I went to apologize for that.
I got into so much trouble.
What? You're the one who said you'd go.
-There you go again!
-No way!
You're wrong.
You told me you'd go apologize for me.
I did not! It wasn't...
Did I?
I did.
I forgot...
that I had been married.
I thought you guys made a great couple.
Mr. Yoshioka has talent.
You have talent.
He...
Well, yes.
When I joined the car development team,
Mr. Yoshioka said to the guys
building the engine,
"The body I've designed is perfect.
And the engine you build
should fit my design."
It usually works the other way around
in the auto industry.
The body is supposed to fit the engine.
That sounds like him.
Someone so full of confidence
became so wretched.
Marriage is scary.
What would the two of you
talk about now, I wonder?
If I see his face,
the first thing I'll do is smack him.
I'd beat him to a pulp, and be taken away
for inflicting bodily harm.
I think you really would.
No, I wouldn't even recognize his face.
I've wiped him from my memory.
But you remember your son, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I know you don't like to talk about him.
But...
He's been dying to see you.
Your son, Seiran.
He wants to see you.
He called me the other day.
He saw your show on the news.
It's amazing.
He's an adult now.
It's been a while since I heard...
that name.
Seiran.
It's the name of a color.
A mix of blue and indigo.
I was young and foolish when I named him.
It's a beautiful color, though.
Rather refined.
And masculine.
He's become quite a man.
I see.
He was five when his father and I split.
But you saw him once
when he was in middle school, right?
This would be a good opportunity,
as you have some time now.
-I can contact him, his number is--
-Stop it!
I have no intention of seeing him.
What's wrong?
Ms. Emi Mizuno
is currently in London for work.
She's extremely busy
and won't make it back
until the day before her wedding.
What? The day before?
Is her fitting finished?
Only for the dress.
Not for the accessories and headdress.
We've been communicating with photos.
I want to make something
only I can make.
I've been thinking.
About what only I can make.
KAJI
Welcome.
-Is this Emotion?
-Yes.
I'm so sorry.
We're closed for the month.
Is Mayumi Nanjo the president?
Yes.
The store opens again in February?
I'm sorry.
Please come again.
Thank you.
Well...
What's wrong?
You have no energy.
Really?
What happened to that amazing aura
you had during the show? It's gone.
Maybe it's this gloomy shop.
It's not this shop's fault.
Yes.
At the time, I was always ready
to make something better right away.
I feel a little too satisfied right now.
It's easy to lose sight
of what to do next.
Especially after you've completed
a grand project.
It's hard to see what's next.
Is that why you're making coffee now?
My grand project
was to make a tiny groove.
A groove to put your tablet
on the dashboard. A tiny groove.
But you completed it.
I don't know. Maybe I just felt like
that was enough and turned away.
You're not turning away,
are you, Mayu-chan?
Maybe I just can't.
There are too many other things
I've turned away from.
What exactly are your plans for Emotion?
Retail Space For Rent
Can you stop?
I'm talking to you.
ORDERS
NEW STORE DESIGN PLAN
You're opening next month?
The store will be in Ginza, right?
That's quite a feat.
He's always alone, you know.
I'm there.
His grandma's there.
And still,
he's always alone.
He's your son!
Emotion.
Feelings?
Do you even have any?
FINANCIAL CONSULTANT
SEIRAN YOSHIOKA
Someone claiming to be your son
came by the store.
He left his business card.
He said he'd like to see you.
Really?
He was here...
21 YEARS AGO
Welcome.
-For one?
-No.
-You're meeting someone?
-Yes.
Seiran.
He wants to see you.
What? Why?
Why can't I have lunch here today?
Well, you see...
There's a special customer coming today.
I apologize.
Important? Who is it?
Well that's...
It's Ms. Nanjo, isn't it?
How did you...
Am I right?
I was so surprised
when I heard you were classmates.
And that you quit your job to work here
to serve coffee, her favorite drink.
That's totally--
No, we're just long-time acquaintances.
Working at this shop
was just a coincidence.
-What? You're lying.
-It's true.
So you asked her to come to the shop?
Is that why she's coming today?
You're nervous.
I'm not! This is just...
Mayu-chan... I mean...
It's not about Ms. Nanjo.
It's because her son is coming.
Ms. Nanjo has a son?
No.
Is it a big secret?
Please keep this between us.
Please!
Of course!
I'm sorry for getting involved
in your business!
No, that was my fault.
Okay, okay!
I'll leave.
I'm leaving. See you later!
Hello.
Hello!
Ms. Konno. It's nice to see you.
Do you work near here?
Well...
I'm not here for work.
By any chance...
Yes?
Nothing.
I'm leaving now.
-I'll see you next time.
-Okay.
See you.
Seiran's at the shop.
He's waiting for you.
I'm sorry to be so blunt.
It's fine...
But,
I knew by looking at you.
Knew what?
That you come from a good family.
Do I?
You're going to a good school, yes?
You play tennis.
Your shoes and bag are of fine quality.
Maybe that's all there is.
Isn't that enough?
It's no small feat to raise you so well.
Aren't you using the fact
that your mother is not your real mother
as an excuse?
I'm sorry.
I tend to speak my mind.
It seems so.
I thought maybe
my birth mother would understand me.
Or is that just a fantasy
that happens in the movies?
It's a fantasy that's usually crushed,
even in the movies.
Just one more question.
You might find it childish.
Go ahead.
Why did you come?
-Here.
-Thank you.
Will she come?
I'll try calling.
EMOTION - MAYUKO TOKITA
Why are you ignoring it?
-Why don't you go see him--
-Your meddling has gone too far.
You've done your part.
If you go any further,
I won't forgive you.
I'm sorry.
But...
if my mother was alive,
-I'd want to see her--
-That's enough!
You don't know the circumstances.
What are the circumstances?
I don't know what happened.
But,
a child wants to see his mother,
and he's right under her nose.
And yet his mother won't see him.
What kind of circumstances
could justify that?
If you truly believe that
you can't see him,
then you're wrong.
Unless one of you has died,
there's no circumstance
under which a mother can't see her child.
You really love that color,
don't you, boss?
Indigo.
That's indigo too.
I'm sorry for meddling.
I'm so nervous,
I keep going to the restroom.
I guess she's not coming.
Wait, I'll call her.
Thank you for coming.
I've wanted to see you for a long time.
But,
Father never talks about you.
And well,
there's also my mother and sister.
I've had a difficult time bringing it up.
Will you say something?
Since we're here.
I'm sorry.
Your first words are...
"I'm sorry"?
No, it's fine.
So...
That thing.
You still have it.
The sculpture of a woman
wearing lingerie.
When I saw it at the store,
I thought, "It's that thing."
It brought back memories.
You remember it?
Yes, I remember.
Father bought it.
The fact that the sculpture
was wearing underwear
was so funny, I laughed.
But you were...
so happy.
Father's doing well.
I see.
Here you are.
Mr. Yamazaki,
my father is indebted to you.
I'm the one who's indebted to him.
Mr. Yoshioka's risen to the top.
He's the company director.
My father is an ambitious man,
but you already know that.
He's an accomplished man.
I'm sorry.
Please enjoy.
It's delicious.
You've become...
a fine young man.
You work for a prestigious company.
My business card.
No.
I was good at studying.
But I have no special talents.
It's quite an accomplishment.
Your father...
and your mother...
must be very proud.
It's hard to say.
My father always tells me
what a dull guy I am.
He's proud of you.
That's not it.
I didn't come here
just to make small talk.
I'm getting married.
The wedding is in two weeks.
I see.
Congratulations.
I don't know why.
But I really wanted you to know.
I know it's not a big deal or anything.
But I wanted you to know.
That's all.
I'm going to start my own family.
So please don't worry about me.
I'm not alone.
Actually, I've never been alone.
Like you said long ago,
my parents cared for me.
And...
I clearly remember...
the sound of your sewing machine.
I was always at your feet,
watching you press your pedal.
I was fascinated.
The machine would hum.
I'd look up
and I'd see the handles turning.
Bits of lace that looked like spider webs
would fall.
I'd gather them up into a ball...
and stuffed them in my tiny truck.
The factory was under the table.
It was made out of a cookie box.
My truck would go back and forth,
and I worked just as hard.
It was fun.
I really had so much fun.
I was...
never alone.
I'm sorry, I'm making this all about me.
But...
I feel better now that I've talked to you.
I'm glad I got to see you.
After the wedding,
we're going to Europe for our honeymoon.
And then my wife and I
will live in London.
So I wanted to see you now.
I see.
I won't be back in Japan for a while.
You must be working hard.
Like your father.
It's not like that.
I'm actually following my wife.
My wife's been recruited
by a think tank in London.
A think tank?
I'll be leaving my job in March,
and attending a university in London.
I wanted to study theater.
Theater?
I'm sorry.
I'll be working part-time for a while.
My wife and I will make it work.
Because,
unlike my father,
I won't be jealous of my wife's career.
I'm sorry, my lunch break is over.
Thank you for the coffee.
Of course.
Thank you.
Say, can I introduce you
to my wife sometime?
-She's in London now, but the wedding--
-Let's not do that.
The happiness you've found...
is for you and your family to share.
With your father,
and your mother,
and your sister.
Whatever little bit of happiness
you experience,
you must not...
share it with me.
This will be the last time we meet.
You haven't changed.
It was...
when I was in middle school, wasn't it?
You were the same then.
I tried to get closer to you,
but you wouldn't let me near you.
I don't care if you blame yourself.
Because...
your attitude hasn't changed.
Though it may seem
as if you're being tough on yourself,
it's quite the opposite.
You know that I'm holding back.
And so,
you calmly step back from your child.
You show regard for my family,
as if you're a stranger.
You refuse to show
any unpleasant part of yourself.
How skillful of you.
But...
it's all for your own satisfaction.
It's unfair.
I'm revealing so much of myself to you.
But I get nothing from you.
Don't you feel anything?
I felt...
that I needed to go to you.
Back then,
when you contacted me,
I thought something had happened.
And that I had to go to you.
I couldn't stand still.
I ran out of the store to go to you.
It didn't seem that way to me.
Because...
you looked so different.
In my memories,
you were this small,
and always by my feet.
If you didn't see me
for even one moment, you'd cry.
But...
the boy that appeared in front of me
was all grown up.
He looked like an adult.
You were wearing a uniform.
Your voice had changed.
You ordered ginger ale.
You spoke so well and so confidently.
I...
no longer know anything about you.
What makes you laugh,
what makes you cry,
or what worries you've been carrying
throughout your life.
I...
don't know anything!
I realized...
that this is the price to pay
for having let go of my own child.
And after that,
all I could do was act
as if I was a stranger.
It's all right.
We are strangers.
We've been spending our times differently.
We've been caring about different things.
That's the truth about you and me.
Perhaps.
And so...
this will be the last time we meet.
I understand.
I'm glad we got to talk.
I'll go now.
One more thing.
Just once,
will you call me by my name?
It's the name you gave me.
I don't know if it's a color, or what.
But it's been giving me a hard time
for 36 years.
No one can read it.
I guess not.
I'm sorry I asked.
Seiran.
I'm sorry...
for giving you such a strange name.
It's okay.
I kind of like it.
And also...
why did you come?
Because...
your face.
I wanted to see it.
He's a good boy.
His father...
must have re-married a wonderful woman.
I have to be grateful.
Are you okay?
I hate it.
He's just like him.
His fingers, his voice.
From the back,
I thought it was his father.
The type of man I like.
I told you,
you've always liked the good-looking ones.
A sucker for good-looking guys.
That's why it never works out.
Be quiet.
But he's like you too, Mayu-chan.
Do you think so?
He's eccentric, just like you.
Thank you.
Will you put this on the house?
What, really?
Fine, I guess.
You're leaving?
I'm going to work.
You know me.
That's all I've got.
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.