Excuse me.
Were you inside just now?
How was the show?
Was it good?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It was...
a beautiful show.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you for coming today.
There will be a photo session,
and we'll be serving snacks
and refreshments in the lobby.
So please feel free to stay.
Did you enjoy the show?
Yes.
Congratulations on a successful show.
Thank you.
We've decided to join in the numbers game.
A smart decision, I believe.
However,
we won't make 5,000 or 6,000.
I suppose Vanderbilt's would make
10,000 or more.
We won't inundate the market
simply because they sell,
and just turn them into
any ordinary product.
Otherwise...
we can't protect
the value of the Emotion brand.
Mr. Saruhashi!
Six Em products, with 200 orders each...
have just sold out!
Thank you.
But the total adds up to only 1,200.
That's a decent number.
That doesn't begin to compare with
Vanderbilt's Story line.
Well...
I'm leaving now.
Say hello to Fumi.
-Reiko!
-Yuri!
I was so nervous!
You did very well!
Thank you so much!
The show was wonderful!
All thanks to whom?
Mr. Miki!
Stop that, I'm all worn out!
Thank you so much.
It was a lot to ask of you.
Not at all.
I wanted to be a part of it.
I hope your agency won't be upset.
Your fees are probably sky-high.
Don't worry.
I got this job six months ago.
Six months ago?
I think my fees back then...
could cover the cost of five hamburgers.
Will this fit?
Thank you...
for what you did today.
I heard that you brought in
Sari Machida from Narita.
You saved our necks.
It just happened to work out.
How many years has it been?
Who would've thought you'd have
your own coffee shop in Ginza?
Yeah.
Is that person...
doing well?
Probably.
You should've sent an invitation.
Voicemail.
This is Ms. Tokita.
The show's over.
How are you feeling, Kaji?
It's over now.
It's as if it was all a dream.
Yes.
It's so beautiful.
Today...
was all you.
What?
You were amazing.
Someone seems to have matured.
How annoying.
You were pretty amazing yourself, boss.
Me?
I just worked within my capabilities.
It wasn't enough.
I'll do even better next time.
And put on a more amazing show.
Me too.
All I did was get help from everyone else.
I haven't made anything on my own.
Next time...
I'm going to make something...
with my own hands.
Well, let's clean up, shall we?
I'm so hungry.
The Em section looks good!
What do you think, Mizuki,
now that's it's all laid out?
It's terrific.
It's beautiful.
Thanks.
My designs on display at Emotion...
I'm sorry.
How embarrassing.
Where's Kaji, by the way?
I think he's still sick.
We haven't seen him since the show.
Is he making it to his classes?
I'll give him a call.
He's not picking up.
Maybe he's dead.
Don't say that.
Hello?
He picked up.
Kaji? Are you okay?
Help me, please.
For real?
You asked for help!
Don't mind me.
Stay in bed.
But I...
Do you mind if I clean up?
TECHNICAL TERMS OF FABRICS
Wow.
Yeah, it was amazing.
I wish I'd been there.
Next time.
The boss seems eager
to do these regularly.
Next time.
Are you feeling better?
Yes!
That's good.
Everyone was worried.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Can you get up?
Yes.
Thank you again.
No worries. Here.
This is amazing, though.
I was surprised.
It's my senior year project.
I see.
It's called Chusen.
A dyeing technique.
Chusen?
My family runs a workshop
back in Takasaki.
It's old and very tiny.
They dye fabrics for yukata kimonos
and tenugui hand towels.
Like these?
Yes, like those.
So you're going to take over the business.
Well, yes.
I see.
It's beautiful.
But these are just for my project.
For fun, really.
It's nothing compared to my dad's work.
My dad's like that too.
What?
He used to run a factory
that made silk out of cocoons.
Really?
That's why your name is Mayuko?
But the factory closed down.
A long time ago.
I really loved it...
watching the threads being made.
I wonder why the things you see as a child
seem so beautiful.
What?
You're beautiful.
Really.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
Aren't you overreacting?
It's because...
It's because you suddenly...
I was caught off guard!
What was that?
You came over to my place!
Should I not have any expectations?
-Expectations?
-Expectations.
On my part, at least.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Do you really dislike me?
I mean, never mind.
Of course you do.
I know you don't see me that way.
That's why you came over.
This isn't about
whether or not I like you!
That's exactly what it's about.
Okay, maybe.
Which way are you leaning?
Toward liking or not liking me?
That's... That's really unfair!
I know.
I know I'm grasping at straws here, but...
I want to touch you because I like you.
Is that bad?
It is!
-Of course.
-No!
No, I mean...
Let me explain.
I have a very personal reason
for not being able
to answer you right now.
Because... Well, because...
I can't help but imagine
what it all leads to.
And I definitely can't take my clothes off
right now!
I wasn't planning on going that far.
Well, even if we did go that far,
you don't have to worry.
I'm not proud of it,
but I'm wearing very old underwear.
What? No!
Today, I'm wearing Emotion's
very glamorous, lacy, sexy bra.
The kind President Nanjo likes.
And it's purple.
So, definitely not!
So it's really pretty then.
All the more reason--
Definitely not!
That's not it!
This...
No. I can't let anyone see it!
I just can't.
So, goodbye.
Wait, wait!
What does that mean?
Welcome.
This is Emotion and this side is Em.
Has anyone here come for
Emotion's custom-made products?
Please fill out this card,
if you don't mind.
This is a bigger crowd than we expected.
I'm happy the show did so well.
We don't want to disrupt the flow.
I'll order another production of
Em garments right away.
We've ordered the materials
already, right?
Yes! The plastic from AGN
is coming in tomorrow.
And the rest is already at the factory.
Thanks.
He's got a lot of energy.
-Did something happen?
-Perhaps.
Can I put these ones out?
Boss, Ms. Suzuki is here
for your 2:00 p.m. appointment.
I'm sorry.
No worries!
These are the new Em products.
Well...
You... You can leave them there.
Whenever you're ready, boss.
Well, show me the additional Em products
once they're finished.
Yes, we'll make them quickly.
We should leave him alone.
Are you ready?
Hurry up and show us.
Here we go.
This one.
And this one.
This.
And these too.
And this!
Wow, really?
All of them have articles on Emotion!
Let's see!
Wow!
Here!
It's a big feature.
-What about that one?
-This one too.
I wish I was at the show too!
Here you go, boss.
Conscious?
That old hag wrote the article, right?
Mrs. Oyama, you mean.
But...
EMOTION
THE NEW WORLD OF LINGERIE
Wow.
Our logo's on the cover.
Where?
Wow!
Did we pay for this?
No.
It must be Ms. Nagai.
It's gratifying.
Yes.
FUMI
EMOTION'S RUNWAY SHOW
THE NEW WORLD OF LINGERIE
To a job well done.
It's amazing.
It's everywhere.
It really means something
when a fashion magazine
runs an article on lingerie.
It's a big success.
I can't thank you enough, Yuri.
Stop it!
And Mr. Miki.
Yeah, he's not here.
Thank you.
He's in the Maldives by now.
I guess they made up.
Him and his boyfriend, or whatever.
Thank you too, Mr. Yamazaki.
Did you meet our boss?
Yes.
She greeted me very politely.
Really? Isn't she something?
Well, yeah...
I wonder why there aren't many articles
on lingerie.
Because it's too sexy?
There's too much nudity?
It's not something
you normally show people.
It's only for special occasions, right?
I finally understand.
What?
What lingerie means to women.
You're getting philosophical again.
I never really thought about it.
I thought that as long as it's pretty
and well-made, it was good enough.
But I was wrong.
Lingerie has to be
a reflection of yourself.
More than your clothes, bags, or shoes.
A reflection of yourself?
It's fine as long as it's cute.
No.
Cute lingerie works for you.
Because of your personality.
That's why.
Welcome.
Hello.
So you're Kaji?
Have you heard about me?
No, not at all.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
But I wanted to talk to Mayu.
Yes, of course.
I'll just be over there.
Please stay, it'll be quick.
Okay.
Things have become awkward
since that time.
-Yes, since that time.
-Cut it out.
Do we have to talk about this here?
I'm going back to Takasaki next spring.
So I'm not sure why I'm trying so hard
to get you,
when it won't amount to anything.
I know you're planning on
staying in Tokyo.
But you're obsessed with
fiber and threads,
so I know you'll understand my work.
Your work?
Here.
Did you dye this?
My dad did.
I want to be able to do this someday.
And I want to make something
only I can make.
Not just traditional patterns,
something more modern and polished.
Not only yukata kimonos
and tenugui hand towels.
I guess I'm not being very clear.
That's not true.
I want to show...
something I make.
Something only I can make.
To you.
I'm sorry, I know I'm being self-centered.
But you don't have to
think about it too much.
Well, I guess you do,
now that I've talked about it.
But yeah...
that's it.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry I didn't order anything.
-Please come again.
-Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
He really likes you!
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
But...
Do you realize it's already December?
What? Really?
Mizuki, do either of you ever go home?
Don't worry.
My daughter brings me clean clothes.
I don't know about him, though.
We're a little too busy.
Here are the materials
for the new client's order.
Is it already ready?
All the laces and fabrics you like,
it's all in here.
You don't even know how to sew!
Starting today,
I'll be the newest member of Emotion.
I'm Rin Nakatani.
Ms. Nakatani?
Mizuki and Reiko
have reached their limits, right?
So I've decided to have her help us.
But...
I'm the one who asked President Nanjo.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
I'd like to do more of the creative work.
After the runway show,
I couldn't wait any longer.
It was really good timing.
I studied fashion in school.
I can sew and create patterns.
That would be very helpful!
It's very different from having
some fiber fetish.
-What?
-It's so helpful.
Good morning.
It's so cold!
You let your hair down.
Good morning, senior co-worker.
Senior co-worker?
What?
I have a general grasp of things now.
Thank you very much.
You changed your hairstyle.
I felt like I needed a change.
It's nice.
That was a gutsy move, Ms. Nakatani.
Not really.
I've thought about it for years.
I see.
But...
that show made me want to take the plunge.
I'm in love with Emotion's lingerie.
I get excited choosing...
which to wear every morning.
I'd love to make exactly
what I'd want to wear...
with my own hands,
and have customers wear it.
I mean,
what a wonderful job that would be.
Yes, it would.
I'm sorry,
I don't mean to preach.
No, I understand completely.
I also love Emotion's products.
I really love them!
But...
But?
Boss.
Boss!
It's the end of the year.
We have to close the books.
Otherwise, the banks will get--
I know, I know.
I'll go with you to the bank.
Please do!
I'll be there on New Year's Eve.
Tell Grandma--
Em's shipment has arrived.
I finished cleaning!
HAPPY NEW YEAR
Em's first round of 1,200 orders
has shipped.
The second round of orders
has completed production.
Emotion's custom orders are also complete.
Today's January 6th,
and if we ship everything here today,
we'll get over the hump for this season.
Sleep! I can finally sleep!
But it's going to come up soon,
the fall/winter trunk show.
Yeah.
That's in March, right?
March?
Let's not talk about that now.
Let's rest.
If we keep working, we'll be exhausted.
We need energy
in order to make something good.
Absolutely.
Let's take a long break.
Let's see.
How about until February?
Two weeks.
For Emotion,
it'll be a summer vacation.
Yeah!
It's so heavy!
Why are fashion magazines so heavy?
THE IMPACT OF EMOTION X EM
STRETCH FABRIC PROVIDES FASHION FREEDOM
Fabric?
THE EVOLUTION OF SPANDEX GIVES SPORTSWEAR
THE VERSATILITY OF CASUAL WEAR
LINGERIE IS TRENDING TOWARD
ACTIVE AND SIMPLE
WE WILL BE CLOSED ON THE FOLLOWING DAYS
Are you guys going anywhere?
I'm going to take it easy at home.
And I have a cat.
You have a cat?
Is it really a cat,
or did you mean something else?
I don't know what you mean.
What about you, Mizuki?
I have to cater to my daughter.
Hot springs and crab for me.
I'm going to Kanazawa.
-Jealous?
-Don't forget souvenirs.
Okay.
And you, Ms. Nakatani?
I'm going to New York.
What? Wow.
Mr. Miki is putting on a show
for Fashion Week.
So I thought I'd go observe.
Such a dedicated learner!
What about Mayu and Kaji?
Why are you asking about us together?
You're not together yet?
Wait, what?
Well, you know.
I've got to finish my senior year project.
That's right, you're graduating.
Then you're only working here until March?
-Yes. I'm taking over the family business.
-We'll miss you.
And you, Mayu?
Are you going home to Nagano?
Well...
I'm going to study up on lingerie.
Everyone's so admirable.
I'll bring back treats for everyone.
Sushi? Sweets?
Crab?
Where are you going, boss?
On vacation.
Okay.
Well, have a nice break!
Yes.
-See you later!
-Shall we go?
-Let's go.
See you.
Don't look so alarmed.
Sorry.
I want to talk to you
about something else.
Okay.
It's cold.
Let's talk inside.
Okay.
The coffeemaker's turned off,
so I made tea.
Thank you.
-Hot!
-Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I just poured boiling water.
Don't worry.
This? I really like it.
Thank you.
And?
Well...
I wasn't sure if I should tell you.
The day of the show...
I couldn't go home.
So I kind of hung around outside.
You were outside the entire time?
Yeah.
That's why your cold got worse.
Fumika was there.
I talked to her without realizing it.
I asked her how the show was.
She said the show was beautiful.
I felt her love for Emotion.
But I can't speak for her.
I think Fumika--
I know.
She just wants to make
what only she can make.
Right?
Me too.
I understand how she feels now.
I'm glad you told me.
Thank you.
I'm glad that's how you feel about Fumika.
What is it?
I...
I just saw something.
You saw it?
You mean...
my ulterior motives?
What only I can make.
Yes, it's true.
I want to make what only I can make too!
Everyone is creating something!
Mizuki made Em.
Fumika made Story.
You're still a little unclear,
but you're working on it.
Sorry for being so unclear.
So what can I create?
I've been thinking.
But looking at your face just now,
I saw it!
I'm glad...
I could be of service.
I'm...
going to create!
2 WEEKS LATER
This is...
What is it?
It's what's most natural for me.
It's what I'd want to wear.
The kind of lingerie I want to create...
is this.
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.