You're here.
You're early.
What do you mean, I'm early?
Why don't you pick up your phone?
I keep telling you
not to call me at night.
I'm at an age now
where I keep having to get up at night.
What do you mean?
I was worried!
Worried?
Because you said you were going to retire.
You thought I was being serious?
-What?
-I was just feeling a little tired.
But after a good night's sleep,
I feel rejuvenated.
How come you look so refreshed?
Yes.
I had an idea.
Every day, Conscious is getting
increasingly more calls
from customers
who want to buy this product.
We need to respond in some way.
If we want to fulfill
our customers' needs,
we should market this product right away.
Or we can just say this was a sample
and not a product for sale.
What do you think, Ms. Tokita?
I don't think we should market this.
You don't want to sell it?
This isn't an Emotion product.
We can't sell something
the boss doesn't approve of
as an Emotion product.
That's true.
It's cute,
but perhaps too different in style
from what we make.
It might confuse our customers.
So I guess we should respectfully decline.
Why?
If people are saying they want it,
why should we turn them down?
But...
You said this wasn't lingerie.
What I think is beautiful...
and what the customers want
are two different things.
I've often experienced
this kind of situation in the past.
And when that happened,
what did I do?
You've always responded 100%
in accordance with your customers' needs.
That's right.
But this is...
completely different
from the type of lingerie Emotion offers.
Even so,
if the customers say
this is what they want,
then we will make it for them.
That's our job, isn't it?
The extra income could come in handy.
Extra income?
That's...
It's true,
Em is too confined as it is now.
We don't have enough space
for customers to browse at their leisure.
Yes.
You have a good location, right?
Does that mean...
If this sells,
we should have enough funds
to open the new shop.
This is an opportunity.
Emotion will make this product
to fulfill our customers' needs.
And we'll use the profits to fund
the opening of the new Em shop.
Really?
If we're going to do this,
let's aim to open in March.
Wait!
Wait, wait.
What about the trunk show?
Of course, we'll do that too.
We'll make that, open a new shop,
and put on a trunk show?
All that in March?
I don't actually mind
being very busy.
Kaji. Let's get him over here now.
The cups don't require a changeover.
They will be processed at the factory,
so as long as it's in the specs...
Then why do I have to create patterns?
I want to clearly convey
the purpose of making this product
to the production line.
I don't have any patterning skills,
so please, boss...
For mass production,
this is important, right?
That's right.
The specs document is a love letter
to the craftspeople.
Then, please...
Our boss isn't someone
who wouldn't do her best
just because she doesn't like the product.
I can't believe that...
I have to create something
while following your instructions.
That's so annoying!
No!
I can't sew to these specs!
How many stitches
do the side nets require?
It's not clear at all!
Even when comparing the same two inches,
sewing ten stitches versus 14 stitches
gives completely different results!
These details make all the difference!
I'm sorry!
She's totally back to her old self.
You seem very motivated, boss.
Working with these,
I realize they aren't too bad.
For older customers
who desire a comfortable fit,
this may work.
So you approve of my work?
I didn't say that. If it were me,
I'd make something more beautiful.
That could be interesting,
if you made products geared for seniors.
Then, why not have size-15 mannequins?
Right.
We can take it even further.
Rather than having such a polished design,
something with a lot of flowers
would be more appealing to seniors.
Flowers. I was wondering...
Why do older women like flowers so much?
It doesn't always start off that way.
It's when they realize
they're going to die soon
that people start to love flowers.
Someday, you're going to love flowers too.
Remember this when your time comes.
We don't have time for this!
I have to finish the specs by end of day!
In any case, I'm going to sew.
Ouch!
Did you stitch your finger?
Of course not, I'm not an amateur.
Fourteen stitches for every inch.
Make sure you get that down.
The specs document--
Is a love letter to the craftspeople.
What?
Nothing.
Reiko! What's with her?
After having rejected the whole idea,
she's now totally serious about it.
Once she decides to make something,
she tries to make it the best it can be.
That's President Nanjo for you.
I'm sure customers will be really happy
to find the product being much better than
what they see in the magazine.
Hey, why are you slacking off over there?
We're not done yet!
The boss is a devil.
It's as if she's in a hurry
to nurture her successor.
What?
Reiko, there's something going on
with her, right?
Here I am, the reliable helper!
So, what should I do?
This is the product's final design.
The materials, the grading,
the color variations,
everything is in the specs.
It looks really good.
I want to sell it at the new shop too.
But first--
So maybe we can order 2,000 units.
The materials?
Yes, we've ordered plenty.
Then let's get it made
as soon as possible.
But first...
there's something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
What name should we put on the tag?
This isn't custom-made.
So it wouldn't be right
to put Emotion's tag on it.
Since Mayu made it,
Em doesn't seem quite right for it either.
What should we call it then?
Mayu?
My name?
Alas, it's also my name.
Mayu. I like it.
And it fits the feel of the material.
It's perfect for evoking
an image of nature.
I'd like for the upcoming trunk show
to display our new outlook.
New outlook?
Emotion, Em and Mayu.
We'll display all three of them
to many customers.
And of course, we'll announce
the opening of our new shop.
This show will be very different
from the previous ones.
We'll not only open up the shop,
but the office area as well,
and we'll reveal everything.
What we've made so far
and what we'll be making in the future.
Like a showroom?
More like an exhibition.
I want people to see
the past and present of Emotion.
And we'll announce the future of Emotion,
Em and Mayu.
We'll invite people
from all walks of life,
talk with them,
and be inspired by them.
We'll use this opportunity
to allow Emotion to become more open.
But...
is it really okay to have Mayu in there?
Are you admitting that this is beautiful?
Does this ribbon confirm that?
What you said,
about this not being lingerie,
are you taking it back?
It can't be helped.
When a dependent becomes the provider,
no one can kick her out, right?
-Impossible.
-Please.
I think the boss would speak freely
with you, Mr. Yamazaki.
We're just old acquaintances.
I'm curious too.
What does Ms. Nanjo have in mind now?
I won't be able to get it out of her.
Please!
I want to know how the boss really feels.
Your fingers. I see...
That's a little tough.
It's not so bad, really.
My fingers were merely the spark.
But they did remind me of my age.
I've seen many people in this business.
It must be difficult
to make decisions all on your own.
I can't make them on my own.
My whole life is there.
But external factors begin to pile up,
and before you know it,
you find yourself forced into realizing
that this is the only path for you.
And then finally,
that's when you're able
to make a decision.
The place looks spacious when it's empty.
The office too.
Yeah.
Should we count the mannequins?
Sure.
If you need more, we can borrow them.
Thanks.
We'll have Emotion products at the front.
We'll need to have enough.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Kaji.
Yes?
I love this shop.
Yes.
Wanting the person you admire...
to remain the same forever...
is that childish of me?
Kaji,
I need to ask you a favor.
CLOSED TEMPORARILY
Like this, here.
Mizuki, for this mannequin
in front, I think...
this one is good.
What do you think?
Yeah, I think so too.
Let's go with that.
Hey, what about Mayu's?
What's wrong?
She's...
I'm sorry. The shipment from
Hashiguchi Tailors is running late.
But I think it'll get here soon.
Yeah?
Let's get it done by tonight.
Feeling quite emotional?
Yes.
I made some of these a long time ago.
This kind of display
makes it look like
a Mayumi Nanjo retrospective.
Seriously,
President Nanjo's work
was truly wonderful.
Stop talking as if I'm already dead.
I emphasized "work."
Did you not notice?
Yes, I understand I have issues
with things other than work.
This was a great idea.
Getting to see everything you've made,
even we've never had that opportunity.
Yes, it's really wonderful!
If we tour departments around the country,
I'm sure we can attract many customers.
-Yeah, that would be great.
-It feels good.
Shall we open a bottle?
-Thank you!
-Here you are.
Are you really...
going to say it?
I've made my decision.
Cheers!
Aren't you drinking too much?
I'm glad you're yourself again.
I'm sorry.
Reiko.
May I have your attention?
I feel so good right now,
I've decided to say this now.
Boss?
This exhibition...
is actually...
a retrospective of Mayumi Nanjo's work.
But until I saw it
actually taking shape,
I didn't know
how I would really feel.
Looking at it now,
I know.
I...
Mayumi Nanjo,
-once this exhibition is over--
-Excuse me.
First,
may I say something?
You...
I'm trying to say something
very important right now.
Why is your timing so terrible?
What I have to say,
I believe, is more urgent.
Urgent?
Yes.
What is it?
Mayu products...
can't be displayed at this exhibition.
Mayu is not an Emotion product.
It's what I made.
My taste and policy
are completely different from yours.
To put that out here,
next to Emotion and Em,
I can't allow it.
What do you mean?
I'm saying Mayu is mine.
I made it on my own.
But it's somehow been absorbed by Emotion.
I can't agree to that.
I'm sure its profits
will be greater than yours.
Wait...
You said so yourself, boss.
As a creator,
if this is what I want to make,
then Emotion is not for me.
But now that you expect it to sell,
you change your mind?
That's enough!
I'm...
going independent.
Emotion is...
no longer the place for me.
How can you say that, Mayu?
The boss was planning on
helping you grow--
I'm sorry!
I don't need any help.
Mayumi Nanjo and I...
have very different goals.
I'll make what I want on my own.
So boss, please continue...
to make products...
that fit Emotion's style.
Now...
that space will be empty.
I'm sorry, boss,
but can you make something new right now?
The theme for the trunk show in March
was supposed to be "Elegance," right?
But...
you haven't made anything yet.
A retrospective?
You're admiring your past work,
but you're not capable of
making anything new?
That means...
you're finished as a creator.
So,
I know this is sudden,
but thank you for everything.
Excuse me.
Wait!
What is this?
Say how you really feel!
Do you think there's anyone
who goes around saying,
"This is how I really feel"?
I've learned how to hide things.
I'm also...
a lingerie maker.
Hey!
What's going on?
No,
I...
ROSE - "LOVE"
AZALEA - "TEMPERANCE" - "FRAGILITY"
Then, why not have size-15 mannequins?
CHARACTERISTICS OF STRETCH SATIN
"In the past few years,
the demand for underwear
that helps seniors stay active
has been increasing.
And although there are
casual sports underwear,
thus far,
none of it can be called
beautiful lingerie.
Please create comfortable lingerie
to satisfy older women
who love flowers."
The specs document
is a love letter to the craftspeople.
"The theme is...
'Comfortable Elegance.'"
From Mayuko Tokita
All right, then.
You want me to make it, right?
"Elegance."
That's right.
Every woman...
will age...
and will always...
go back to seeking elegance.
Because...
lace...
and embroidery...
will never become obsolete.
Because...
every woman,
before she dies,
will come to love flowers.
She was planning on quitting.
She lit her fire once again.
Thank you.
-Welcome.
-Hello!
This is from the show.
I was looking for something like this!
I bow to you, Mayumi Nanjo.
From now on,
I'm going to make more products
for mature women like us.
I'm so glad you're here!
How creepy.
I hope you're not dying tomorrow.
As long as people like you
persistently go on working,
I feel like I can do it too!
I'm certain the women who'll wear this
will feel the same way.
This has no wire in it.
Really?
Hello.
Congratulations on further progress.
I hear Vanderbilt's will be starting
a new private label.
Yes, in casual wear.
I'm sure it won't happen again,
but please don't steal from us.
Don't put it like that.
I'm only looking at it
so as to have a reference.
I hear you're opening a shop in Harajuku.
-Yes.
-I'm certain you'll succeed.
I did recruit you, after all.
I'm sorry for the trouble I caused you
at the time.
How is Fumi doing?
She's quite ambitious.
A new idea from Story.
Socks?
Apparently, socks are the next big thing.
If you'll excuse me.
We can't lose.
DESIGNER FUMIKA IDA
You're right.
Mr. Miki is here.
-Hello.
-Mr. Miki.
It's beautiful.
It's like an art museum.
Ms. Nanjo's over there.
Then I'll go say hello later.
Thanks for your help at the show, Yuri.
Not at all. It was fun!
But...
it's sad...
that Mayu isn't here today.
Is she really...
gone for good?
Excuse me.
Is this Mayuko Tokita's shop?
Yes.
Let's bring it in.
Careful!
I need to buy a sewing machine.
A sewing machine, for sure.
But I have no money.
What should I do?
Thank you!
Thank you.
What's this?
Please sign here.
Kaji?
I'm sorry.
I told them.
You go over there, got it?
Let her know, all right?
This is a handyman I know.
I've asked him for new sewing machines.
HANDYMAN TAMINATO
CALL US FOR WHATEVER YOU NEED!
This is from the boss.
I can't accept this.
I have to return it.
Why not just keep it?
But I said those things--
Why can't you accept their kindness?
I'm sorry for yelling.
But...
This is from the boss's heart.
To send it back...
That wouldn't be right.
And also,
about me...
I'm going back to Takasaki this weekend.
So, will you...
turn me down officially?
It was all thanks to you.
Thanks to you,
I now understand how women feel
when they pick out their lingerie.
Or rather,
it would be more accurate to say that
I've begun to understand.
I think that when making something,
what you feel is important.
I know that now.
I wish I could--
I'm sorry.
This will be the last time.
Think of it as a goodbye gift to me.
Also,
everyone is waiting for you.
The boss is waiting.
In the end, you'll regret it
if you don't face them.
After this,
I'll have no regrets.
We don't develop new fabrics.
I think you have the wrong idea
about our job.
I'm sure you'll go through a lot,
but we'll do this together, okay?
If we can get through this,
Emotion will make it.
It's been awhile since I've had...
You give me discomfort.
You know why?
Because you're not beautiful.
Everything you want to know is there.
You understand now?
That's why you wear lingerie.
Beauty is a weapon.
Someone seems to have matured.
How annoying.
Amazing.
I made them as per your instructions.
So you'll have to inspect them all.
Yes.
Well, even if you hadn't said anything,
I would have made them.
That's a lie.
You were planning on retiring.
That's why you accepted what I made.
You gave in despite not approving at all.
By saying Emotion should be more open,
you tried to wrap it all up.
Selling in this shop
a product you don't approve of...
is not something Mayumi Nanjo would do.
I won't let you quit, ever.
Whether your fingers hurt,
or if you fall into a slump,
or become outdated, or lose confidence,
it doesn't matter.
If someone like you disappears
from the creative front,
then who will teach everyone
how beautiful things are made,
or how to do beautiful work?
No, you don't even have to teach.
You just have to be there!
Right there.
You must be kidding me.
I just have to be here?
I'm not a fool.
I don't plan on retiring.
I can still create.
Besides, I'll let you in on something.
I...
love this job even more than I used to.
There's freedom because
it's something you don't show others.
But you're also free to show others.
Just as our tastes completely differ,
you're free to decide
what you consider beautiful.
I realize now,
that more than I'd ever imagined,
the world of lingerie is wide.
Lingerie is interesting.
No job could be more fun.
Yes.
There's no way I could quit.
Don't you think?
Until the assignment of business
and ownership change is complete,
we can't open the shop.
I understand, but there's no point
unless we have the merchandise.
Will you two stop fighting
over every little detail?
-Sorry.
What? Dad's coming too?
Okay, bye.
That's right.
Today's appointment is at 2:00 p.m.
Beautiful.
Beautiful!
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.