Kotoko!
-Hey!
-Kotoko?
Kotoko!
Are you all right?
Move!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sure you're aware...
that she and I are married.
Don't try...
anything with Kotoko.
I'd take better care of Kotoko than you.
I'd love her more than you.
Is that right?
And when I woke up,
there was Naoki,
so worried about me!
He's usually cool-headed,
but he looked at me so tenderly...
I should faint more often.
By the way, who's that hunk?
Hunk?
The one that carried you
to the health office.
Keita?
Keita Kamogari is a classmate.
Is he a hunk?
Naoki Irie may be the only man
in your heart...
but...
seeing how panicked Kamo--
Whatever his name is. --was,
I could have sworn
that he was in love with you.
A love triangle!
Keita? No way!
It would have been fun
to see him challenge Naoki.
Why would anyone fight over Kotoko?
Right?
Hey...
One month later...
Our first summer break had begun.
Hey!
You're finally up.
Come on.
He had to wake you up a dozen times.
Was I sleeping?
Calling, "Naoki...!" in your sleep.
You even dream about him, don't you?
It was just a dream.
Sorry! Sorry!
We had to forgo our summer plans
to work on our report every day.
I'm exhausted.
Another day of hard labor.
While some of us were sleeping.
Now all we have to do is summarize
-our assigned sections.
-Okay.
So, is this the last time
we're working as a group?
Right.
Oh...
Shall we go have some fun?
We worked on our report all summer.
Let's celebrate!
-Sounds good!
-Let's go!
It's decided, then.
How about you, Tomoko?
Sorry, but I have to work.
You're working part-time?
Where do you work? At a florist?
-A bakery?
-A restaurant?
In the food section
of a department store.
As a cashier?
At the fish market.
How perfect.
No, nothing.
I'd better leave. Bye-bye.
-Bye.
-See you.
Shall we get going, too?
-I guess.
-Yes!
How about bowling?
I have my own ball.
His own ball?
I need to get cash from the ATM.
Wait, Moto-chan!
Meet you at the school gate.
-Okay!
-Right.
Shall we go?
The gate is this way.
-This way?
-Yeah.
Mr. Irie.
We're going out for a bite after this.
Care to join us?
I'll pass.
I knew it!
His wife is waiting for him
with a home-cooked meal.
I'm envious. It sure beats eating out.
I want a wife, too.
That's too bad. I wanted
to have a drink with you
and discuss molecular cell biology.
Speaking of cellular biology...
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
You're on a roll, Kotoko.
A GENIUS AND JEALOUSY
I told you to leave it to me.
-Here, Marina.
-Thanks.
Let's take a short break
before the next game.
Bring it on!
Teach me, too.
-Follow me.
-Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
I yelled so much, I feel refreshed.
Right?
You sound pretty frustrated.
Having problems with Naoki?
I wouldn't say that.
Well... maybe.
He's so busy nowadays.
I hardly see him at home.
But when I do see him...
I may be imagining it,
but he's kind of cold.
Your problem is...
you try too hard with him.
Loosen your shoulders. Relax.
You're hopeless.
I'll be your better half today, okay?
I don't need your sympathy, Keita.
Just accept it graciously.
Thanks for treating today!
I can't believe we lost to you.
What a disgrace.
How about karaoke, then?
Sounds good. A karaoke sing-off!
We'll win for sure this time.
I'd better get going.
Are you abandoning us?
I'm a housewife after all.
I'm not letting you leave!
No skipping out midway!
-Yeah!
-Let me go!
She needs to cook dinner for Mr. Irie.
That's exactly right. So, I need to go!
No! You need a break sometimes!
Hey!
The nursing group!
It's Mr. Irie!
It's Naoki!
Good evening!
What are you doing here, Naoki?
Dinner. With the guys.
I see.
Miss Marina. Fancy meeting you here.
We must be like eudiplozoon nipponicum.
Eudiplozoon...?
Twin parasites found on goldfish gills.
Once they find each other,
they're conjoined forever.
Isn't it romantic?
Aren't they a funny pair, Naoki?
Yeah.
Guess what? We just went bowling.
-Bowling?
-I did great for my first time!
I thought of you
and threw strike after strike!
I wish you could have seen me!
Irie, we'll be late. Let's go.
I have to go.
Hey!
If you have time to drink with them,
spend some time with your wife.
Wait a minute...
I know you're trying to impress Kotoko,
but I'm sick of your lecturing.
That's rude, Naoki.
Keita was just thinking of me!
He knew I was... feeling down...
Then why don't you go home
with Kamogari?
He seems so worried about you.
How mean.
Why would you say that? That's stupid!
Kotoko!
Aren't you going after her?
If you're not going after her, I will.
Keita! Wait!
Moto-chan! Wait!
Hurry up, Marina!
I can't believe Naoki said that.
I just wanted to be with him.
Are you sick of me?
-Hey!
-Nao--
It's not Naoki.
Sorry, Keita.
I know that was unpleasant.
All because of us...
It doesn't even concern you...
It does concern me.
Don't say that it doesn't.
You should...
leave him.
Ta-da!
I splurged and made sushi rice!
My favorite!
Looks delicious.
You could serve this at a restaurant.
I'm just an amateur.
I'm embarrassed to serve it to a pro...
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Please...
"Cut" me some cuttlefish, will you?
And what's this salmon-colored fish?
Salmon.
Correct!
This roe is so good,
I'd eat it twice in a "roe."
You got me on that one!
I'm done.
Already? Naoki...
I'm taking a bath and turning in.
I'm done.
You, too, Kotoko?
I'm feeling a little tired.
Dad?
Can I use your library?
Of course you can.
I have a test right after the break.
Then study with Naoki.
But he's going to sleep.
Don't worry about him!
I don't want to bother him.
I'll wash dishes later.
Something's wrong!
This has been going on for a while...
What shall we do?
It's only a matter of time
before they divorce.
Yuki! Don't say that!
It's natural for couples to fight.
Let's leave them alone.
The interbrain...
...bridge?
No, brain stem.
It's no use! I can't focus!
I keep hearing Keita's voice.
You should...
leave him.
You must be kidding, Keita!
You're always joking!
Don't tease a married woman.
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
Thanks!
We walked in total silence.
Whether he was joking or not,
I had never been held that way
by anyone other than Naoki.
I was panicked.
I haven't spoken to Naoki since.
I want to make up...
but he's avoiding me.
It's no use thinking about it.
I'm going to sleep!
He looks so sweet.
How did we end up like this?
You're right here,
but I can't even kiss you.
The long summer ended,
and a new semester began.
Morning!
Oh, it's you.
Are you avoiding someone?
Not really, but...
Hey, Keita.
Long time, no see.
Yeah...
Kotoko.
Yes! What?
Did you...
summarize the section
on pathophysiology?
Pathophysiology?
Don't tell me you forgot.
That was your assigned section!
I'm sorry! Sorry...
Thank God. He's the same old Keita.
He was joking that night after all.
Calm down.
I'm sorry!
Naoki...
I want to do well to impress Naoki.
So, we can make up.
Okay...
EXAM DAY
You're leaving already, Naoki?
I have some research to do.
I'll rush and make you breakfast.
Don't bother.
But you don't look so hot...
I'm going.
Good luck.
Begin now.
Stop.
Before I knew it, exams were over.
We're finally finished.
I'm exhausted.
How did you do, Kotoko?
I feel pretty good about it.
Wow!
-Are you sure?
-Of course!
Miss Marina!
Miss Marina...
What do you want?
Do you remember our passionate vow?
Remind me.
If I beat Naoki Irie
and became Number 1,
you vowed to go out with me.
Were you serious?
I'm always serious.
I didn't go anywhere this summer.
All I did was study.
And how did your exams go?
Today's test...
was perfect! I just know it!
I'm 99.9 percent sure
that I beat Naoki Irie!
Excuse me!
Where is Mr. Irie?
Don't worry. Naoki won't lose.
Right?
I'm sure you're right, but...
let's go ask Mr. Irie
how he did on the test.
Let's go! Hurry!
You, too, Keita!
You're here, too?
Mr. Irie!
How did you do on the test?
Test?
Not good.
What?!
Impossible! You must be joking!
It was the worst I ever did.
I did it! I'm Number 1!
Miss Marina...
Is it true, Naoki?
Yeah.
Are you okay? Do you have a fever?
Forget it. I'm fine.
See you later.
I sense an awkward tension
between you two.
Did you have a fight?
No...
But he acts as if he doesn't like you.
No way! He's just a little tired!
Now that Marina is with Funatsu,
my rivals are dropping like flies.
He's just tired!
Calm down.
But...
Has it been this way for long?
It's been a month since that night.
Is it me?
No! It doesn't concern you at all.
I told you not to say that.
It concerns me.
But you were joking that night, right?
I wasn't joking.
I'm serious about what I said.
Keita...?
That's how I feel.
You'll never be happy
with someone like him.
Get a divorce.
Kinnosuke, I'm done over here.
Let's close up, then.
Are you closed already?
Yup! Come again tomorrow.
Irie!
Oh, Naoki!
What'll it be? Anything you want.
I'm the one who's cooking!
Something simple.
Fried chicken maybe?
That's not simple at all!
Kin-chan!
Coming right up.
Please wait a few minutes, Naoki.
Here you go.
Kinnosuke's cooking is the best!
Don't state the obvious.
It's good.
Right?
Kinnosuke is working hard for me!
Whatever...
You get along so well.
Are you kidding? With her?
Of course!
You and Kotoko get along well, too.
I wonder...
But not lately.
What do you mean?
Are you making her cry again?
No... I think it's me.
What? Are you sick?
You're a doctor. Shape up.
No, I'm not sick.
I'm not sleeping well.
What is it, then? What's wrong?
I don't even know myself...
why I act the way I do towards Kotoko.
Ever since Keita Kamogari
has been hanging around Kotoko,
I feel so irritated every time I see her.
You really don't get it?
What?
Are you an idiot?
And you call yourself a genius.
You understand something that I don't?
You're jealous.
It's just plain jealousy.
Me? Jealous?
No way. I'm not you.
Idiot. I'm telling you!
Listen. Thanks to you...
I'm a six-year veteran of "jealousy."
And as a veteran, I can vouch for it.
You are jealous of Kotoko
and what's his name!
Even a genius gets jealous.
So, tell me,
who's this fool hanging around Kotoko?
I think he needs some discipline.
Kinnosuke!
You can be jealous of me, too!
You idiot!
Jealous, Kin-chan?
Are you kidding me?
People are starting
to dress for cooler weather.
But Naoki and I still haven't
gotten past our summer...
Naoki...
How did you do on your test, Kotoko?
You were super confident.
Stop stalling and show us!
What? Fifty-one points, 36 points,
48 points, 43-point average?!
Cut it out.
We're just having fun.
Here.
Thanks, Keita.
You...!
How could you be confident
with test scores like that?
You think you can become a nurse
with scores like that?!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
I'm scared!
Maybe I'll go to the shrine to pray.
Nothing's working out for me lately.
You still haven't made up with Naoki?
No.
I thought I'd get good grades
on my tests
so I could impress Naoki
and we could make up.
But it didn't happen.
You need an excuse...
What should she do
in this situation, Satomi?
Are you all right?
Did you eat too much cake?
Are you... pregnant?
I am.
I think...
I'm pregnant.
What?!
I took a home pregnancy test.
What are you going to do?!
Does Ryo know?
Yeah.
What did he say?
"Let's get married."
What? Married?!
He wants me to have the baby.
I should get married first, but...
It's common nowadays!
Congratulations, Satomi!
Congratulations.
Thanks!
So, when is the wedding?
Once the pregnancy has stabilized.
Satomi... a mom.
You should hurry up
and make up with Naoki
and make a baby, too!
I want you both to come
to my wedding!
Yeah... I guess.
Oh, my! Satomi?
How nice! A wedding and a baby!
We have to celebrate.
She's due around June next year.
My goodness.
I'm sure it'll be a cute girl,
just like Satomi.
I wish you and Naoki would...
Just wishful thinking.
I'm sure mom really wants
a grandchild...
but we haven't even kissed lately.
They say that happiness is infectious.
I'm sure something good
will happen to you soon.
Mom...
Thank you.
I can do this.
Naoki... can I talk to you?
What?
I have some good news.
Satomi is going to marry Ryo!
And she's pregnant.
That's nice.
And...
she plans to get married
after her first trimester.
She wants us to attend
her wedding together.
Yeah.
I wonder how Satomi's wedding will be.
I can't wait.
I wore a wedding dress, but Satomi
would look good in a kimono, too.
I love weddings!
I wouldn't mind getting married
all over again!
I'd love to have another wedding.
Just kidding.
Is that all?
Sorry to disturb your studies.
Kotoko?
-You!
-What's wrong with you?
You! You!
Hey! Kotoko!
Stop! What are you doing?
This is all wrong!
This isn't how it should be!
I hate this.
I can't stand it!
You don't even look at me!
You don't care about me at all.
You don't care what I do!
Keita told me he loved me!
He told me to leave you.
You don't love me anymore, do you?
That's not it...
You never loved me!
-Calm down!
-No! Why...?
Why...
...did you marry me?
I'm the only one... that loves you.
I can't do this!
Kotoko!
What happened, Kotoko?
Where are you going?
Kotoko!
I was always too scared to ask him.
But the question was always
in my heart, and I finally said it.
I put an end to it myself.
Are we... finished?
Want to come live with me?
NEXT EPISODE
"A VOW WITH A NURSE CAP"
You'll have to retake the test.
Why do you want to become a nurse?
To support the doctors
and dedicate ourselves
to people in our care.
You're a man...?
Forget it!
My... dream....
You're going to be a doctor,
so I want to help you.
Naoki...
can you hear me?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2