Take this patient to the ward.
-It's a femoral compound fracture.
-Yes, doctor.
Dr. Nishigaki!
He said to wait.
It's too risky to wait.
But...
The artery needs to be sewn up.
I have to be strong.
I can't be a burden.
Forceps.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
My mind is blanking out.
The patient, Naoki... It's all my fault.
What should I do?
Hey.
Stand up.
I can't use my hands.
What are you scared of?
Aren't you scared?
Of course not.
Listen. I studied this for years.
I'm totally confident.
I'm probably better than Dr. Nishigaki.
This patient is lucky.
I would never allow your little mishaps
to endanger his life.
Just listen to me.
Okay.
Then go wash up
and pick up those instruments.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Nurse Shimizu.
Dr. Irie, do you have
Dr. Nishigaki's permission?
-No.
-What?
His condition deteriorated suddenly.
I needed to act quickly.
Dr. Nishigaki is operating now.
He couldn't leave.
-I decided to do it.
-You decide...?
-Kotoko, go.
-Yes.
Ms. Irie.
Fine. But I can't let her
do this by herself.
I'm going to assist you, too.
Tell me what I can do.
Thank you.
I can breathe again.
I can see clearly now.
Okay. I'm fine now.
-Forceps.
-Yes.
-Scissors.
-Suture 6.0.
-Yes.
Everything went
so smoothly after that.
Naoki was so sure of himself.
-Prepare the saline.
-Yes.
Even Nurse Shimizu,
who was uncertain at first,
seemed to trust him.
This was only
my second time assisting,
but Naoki's words
were so full of confidence
that I knew he was right.
You can do it, Naoki.
Okay.
-Gauze.
-Yes.
It's done.
Yes.
-You did it.
-Dr. Irie.
Thank you. You did a wonderful job.
Thank you.
Can you check the operating room?
Yes.
Naoki.
The patient's surgery
went smoothly, too.
Good.
Naoki.
I'm so glad it went well.
Your judgment and skills
saved his life.
You were amazing.
I was so happy.
If...
you didn't...
knock my head,
I may have run away.
I was petrified.
I didn't know what to do.
Naoki?
Me, too.
I...
was scared, too.
But you... were so confident.
That was for your benefit.
Your mind went blank, right?
That was my first emergency.
I'm surprised.
At what?
That you get scared, too.
I'm glad...
that the patient made it.
I'm glad you became a doctor.
Yeah.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
CONFERENCE ROOM
It is unprecedented
STAND UP FOR LOVE
for an intern to perform
a procedure without guidance.
It was unthinkable
when I was an intern.
It's unthinkable now.
Dr. Nishigaki is Dr. Irie's advisor.
Yes.
I understand Dr. Irie
is a very capable intern.
But even still...
Luckily, this time...
the procedure was successful.
If something had gone wrong,
the responsibility would have been
too large for an individual to bear.
Once a precedent like this is set,
we expose ourselves to great risk.
Confidence is not always good.
Right, Dr. Nishigaki?
If I had been Dr. Irie's medical advisor,
this would have never happened.
In any case, this is not a simple
problem we're dealing with.
Who will take responsibility?
What kind of problem is it?
I became a doctor
to save patients' lives.
-Hey.
-Rules don't apply in this case.
The patient's life was in danger.
Dr. Nishigaki was
performing another surgery.
I had to do it. That's all.
But you should have
respected Dr. Nishigaki's...
His patient was in critical condition.
He needed to remain focused.
I was confident I could save the patient.
So, I performed the procedure.
If someone needs
to take responsibility,
you don't have to talk
through my advisor.
You can talk directly to me.
What an ego this intern has.
Dr. Nishigaki.
What have you been teaching him?
In that case,
we'll have to let Dr. Irie
take responsibility.
Naoki is an amazing doctor.
You're saying, "intern this"
and "intern that,"
as if interns are helpless little chicks.
How impertinent.
Naoki's confidence
is supported by his actions.
He may have broken some rules,
but in that moment,
all Naoki cared about
was saving a patient's life.
That patient is alive because of Naoki.
He still has a life ahead of him.
Doctors...
Doctors... are amazing.
Ms. Irie! What did you do now?
I'm sorry, doctors.
This is preposterous.
Who is this girl, Nurse Shimizu?
She's out of line.
But, doctors...
I also assisted Dr. Irie
in the procedure.
I have assisted many surgeries.
Dr. Irie's work was that of
a capable surgeon.
If not for him, that patient...
Nurse Shimizu...
The patient is recovering well.
That's all I wanted to report.
So...
Excuse us.
Let's go, Ms. Irie.
Excuse me.
So...
What do you think, Dr. Nishigaki?
Well...
He may have acted rashly.
But...
There were many challenges that night.
That patient could have easily died.
But he survived.
So, I cannot refute Dr. Irie's actions.
I wouldn't have done that
as an intern, though.
I see.
Well, shall we leave it at that, doctors?
-But, professor.
-The precedent...
Dr. Irie.
I commend you on your judgment
and skills at such a young age.
But a doctor and patient
must trust each other.
Patients don't see interns
as full doctors.
We must avoid
making them feel insecure.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Okay. Then we're finished.
Dr. Nishigaki, please write up
an incident report.
It's your responsibility as his advisor.
Yes.
My record was impeccable.
Now it's marred because of
an overly confident intern.
Shall I write the report for you?
Shut up!
Act more like a humble intern.
And write up the report.
No, wait. I'll do it.
They'll chew me out again.
Watch out.
Are you Konomi Sagawa?
Sorry to approach you like this.
Yes.
It's Konomi. Konomi!
What?
This guy wants to talk to you.
I go to West High School
by the station.
I saw you walking by.
Right near here.
Who are those guys?
Shut up. Be quiet.
Oh, sorry.
I see you on the train every day.
I think you're cute.
You've been on my mind lately.
So...
Will you go out with me?
You go to Tonan High, right?
It's nearby.
Will you see me sometime?
I know he's my friend,
but he's a really good guy.
But...
Oh, my God.
He's asking Konomi out.
What are you going to do?
What am I going to...?
Do you...
Do you have a boyfriend?
-A boyfriend.
-You're so cute.
Do you have a boyfriend?
A boyfriend?
Tell him. Tell him, Konomi.
Tell him you have a boyfriend
named Yuki Irie.
Hey.
I don't.
Yes!
So, will you go out with him?
He's really nice.
Start off by texting.
But...
I'm sorry.
What?
Really.
I'm sorry.
Wait. Just your number,
or e-mail address.
Konomi is so popular.
Right, Yuki?
Yuki?
I'm going home.
Wait. Yuki.
First, you loop the yarn around
and pull it tight.
Right. So, pull it through.
That's it. Don't get it tangled.
Pull.
That's not exactly right.
Will I make it in time for Valentine's?
You can do it. Try again.
Another knitting student
for Valentine's Day.
She's here.
Yes. Come in.
Hello. Thanks for having me.
Come in, Konomi.
How's it going?
Pretty well.
Oh, my God. I've only gotten this far.
Hello, Yuki.
Thanks for having me.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
She came to see you of course, Yuki.
So, you came to see me, huh?
Yes.
Why are you acting like my girlfriend
when you're not?
Don't be mean, Yuki.
Yeah. That sounds so mean.
Sorry.
You're right.
I'm not even your girlfriend
and I come over all the time.
Who do I think I am?
This isn't right.
Sorry.
I'm going home.
Konomi.
I'm sorry.
-Konomi?
-Konomi.
What's going on? She was crying.
She was?
Yes?
Are you busy, Naoki?
Hey. What?
Well, it's nothing, really.
-You're not on duty tonight?
-No.
What are you studying?
Respiratory distress syndrome.
Sounds complicated.
Do doctors really...
What do you want?
Well... I wanted to...
ask you... Well...
What do you like about Kotoko?
I mean, she's not your type or anything.
So, when did you start liking her?
What's going on?
Is it Konomi?
No.
I never thought this day would come.
Well...
She kept saying, "I love you"
as if it were a spell.
It was so annoying.
What?
But I started to get used to it.
When she said she was
going to give up on me,
I remember feeling mad.
I...
I'm going to give up on you.
I should have been relieved.
Kotoko...
can't do 90 percent of what I can do.
But she can do the 10 percent...
that I could never do
in a hundred years.
Maybe it became a habit.
I don't know anymore.
How Konomi feels or how I feel.
I tutor her.
She drags me to movies and cafes.
I say it's annoying.
But I wonder if it really is.
When I saw another guy
confess his feelings for her...
it pissed me off.
I said some harsh things to her.
Sorry.
I realized...
we really are brothers.
What about?
If you aren't sure, ask Konomi.
That's the simplest answer.
Sorry for bothering you.
Yuki.
I'll tell you the one thing
that Kinnosuke taught me.
According to him...
it's called "jealousy."
Let me say this up front.
I wasn't waiting for you
because it's Valentine's Day.
It just happened to be
Valentine's Day today.
Then...
why were you waiting for me?
Why?
S... Sorry.
Sorry about the other day.
But it was partly your fault, too.
My fault?
You said you didn't have a boyfriend.
To that guy who asked you out.
So I...
How did you know?
I happened to be passing by.
You always said that you liked me.
So...
But...
What can I do?
I do like you. A lot.
That hasn't changed
since middle school.
But no matter how much I like you...
As long as you don't like me back...
I can't call you my boyfriend.
I feel like I'm threatening you.
I don't care if it's a one-way love.
Although it would be nice
if you felt the same way.
This is perfect.
It's your Valentine's Day present.
How is it?
Good. It suits you.
I just...
Just...?
That wasn't on a whim.
I like you.
I like you, Konomi.
So, when other guys ask you out,
tell them you have a boyfriend.
Okay.
Don't cry.
Tell me again.
What?
That you like me.
I can't repeat it so many times.
-But it was only twice.
-I said it twice.
It's not easy to say it twice.
Thank you.
I'm...
Hey.
You'll catch a cold sleeping here.
You're home, Naoki.
I guess I fell asleep.
I'm going to take a bath. Go to sleep.
Here. I made you some coffee.
Coffee? Before I go to sleep?
Help you with your nursing report?
Please?
Because...
I've rewritten it a dozen times,
but they're so critical.
For once, I'd like to turn in a report
that they don't tear apart.
I just need your advice.
Just the main points. Please?
Unbelievable.
Sit down.
Really?
Yay!
Thank you, Dr. Irie.
Take care.
Take care. Thank you.
You look tired.
Nurse Hosoi.
I'm a little sleep deprived.
I see.
That's your last patient
for the afternoon.
Go get some rest.
You have another surgery
this afternoon, right?
Yes. Thank you.
Kotoko is really shaping up lately.
I can tell by her report
that she really studied hard.
I see.
Irie!
Irie! Where are you?
Come out, you idiot!
Hey, Irie.
Do you know Naoki Irie?
Kin-chan. Chris.
Kotoko.
Kotoko, where's Irie?
He's seeing a patient in there, but...
What's going on? This is a hospital.
What is it, Kinnosuke?
Irie, I need your help. It's Chris.
Calm down. What's wrong?
Naoki.
I messed up.
Gauze.
Bandage.
Chris was splattered with hot oil?
Yeah.
She burned her leg in the kitchen.
I... My mind went blank.
I should have gone to the nearest
hospital, but I ended up here.
I always give Irie a hard time,
but when it came down to it,
I could only think of him.
If anything happens to Chris, I...
Don't worry. You did the right thing.
Naoki is a miracle worker.
I hope you're right.
Chris.
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
A little.
Nurse Hosoi, she's my friend.
I'll take her.
Go ahead, then.
Her husband can go in
and speak to Dr. Irie.
Her... husband?
So? How is Chris?
I'll explain in a minute.
Sit down, husband.
Her burns...
are pretty bad.
It's penetrated the inner skin.
She'll be in pain for a while.
She should be hospitalized
until she's stable.
-Regarding scarring...
-What?
There may be a little.
She may need cosmetic surgery.
Wait a minute.
There may be scarring?
Chris is an unmarried woman.
If her body is scarred,
what if she can't get married?
But you're marrying her, right?
So, what's the problem?
What are you saying?
Are you going to let
another guy have her?
Are you kidding?
No way.
I won't let that happen.
I'm not giving her to anyone.
I see.
Got a problem with it?
Then why don't you tell Chris?
I know.
Okay, take it easy, Chris.
Ready?
-Okay.
Kotoko, you're a real nurse.
I'm impressed.
Really?
And what about Kin-chan?
He was so desperate.
I've never seen him like that.
He was more panicked than I was.
He's so rash sometimes.
I guess I can't talk.
He must think you're very special.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-How is it, Chris?
-See?
-Kinnosuke.
-Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
The painkillers are kicking in.
By the way, what did Irie say?
The pain will only last
a couple of days.
What about scarring?
Don't worry.
I told Irie to take care of it.
I'll beat him up if he leaves a scar.
-Kin-chan.
-Don't worry about a thing.
Irie and Kotoko are here.
I'll come every day, too.
Okay.
Kin-chan.
I gave Mr. Suzuki in Room 205
painkillers at 3:00 p.m.
Please check on his pain level.
Okay.
I'll be going, then.
-Good night.
I'm starving.
-See you.
-Good night.
Now for the night shift.
It's not good for my skin.
-Ms. Irie.
-Nurse Hosoi. I'm going.
Good night.
Does Dr. Irie seem tired at home?
Naoki? Why?
He's had one major surgery
after another.
I don't think he's getting much sleep.
The action plan is to discuss
pain remedies with the doctor.
He had another emergency case
right after his outpatient clinic.
Then he went into surgery
without eating anything.
It's going to be another long one.
I know you're working, too, but...
please take care of
Dr. Irie's health and nutrition.
A doctor's hours are never fixed.
It's both physically
and mentally taxing.
You're a doctor's wife, after all.
Yes, thank you.
She's right.
I haven't done anything lately.
Mom does all the cooking
and cleaning.
I asked him to help me with my report
instead of getting sleep.
Naoki, it's been six hours
since the surgery began.
Okay.
What is all this, Kotoko?
Naoki has a long surgery tonight.
I thought I'd bring him
a nutritious meal.
Oh, my.
How wonderful.
He'll be so happy.
I hope so.
Just wait, Naoki.
I made you lots of good food.
Naoki.
You just finished your surgery.
I wanted to bring you
something nutritious
that will give you stamina...
Naoki.
Naoki?
Naoki!
No!
Naoki! Naoki!
Naoki!
Naoki, get up!
It's my fault.
Next Episode
Ep.15 "Tearful Proposal"
My goodness, Naoki.
You're so lame.
What happened to your
triple flip landing?
I'll be your private nurse.
Don't try to find the spot
with the needle in.
Too much garlic in it.
Can we talk?
How did you propose to Kotoko?
I decided to do it in front of my family.
I knew she'd say yes.
-Did that help?
-Hell no.
Will you break up with Naoki
and marry Kinnosuke?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2