How did you do on the test?
Aced it.
Are you serious?
How do you ace a test like that?
Like what?
It was super hard.
It was.
Will you ace the next one?
Probably. If I study.
What do you want?
What's wrong?
A stray cat's been following us.
Stray cat?
Whatever.
Excuse me... Yuki!
I...
Well...
What?
I'm Konomi Sagawa from F Class.
Sagawa from F...
Do you know this girl?
No.
You may not know who I am,
but I've known you for a long time...
So what?
I want to be your friend!
You're so popular, Irie!
No way.
Can't we be friends?
I don't want any stupid friends
from Class F.
What? You already told him?
Kotoko!
Sorry, but you're moving so fast!
You've never even
talked to him, right?
But I was the same way,
so I can't blame you.
I was so encouraged
by our last conversation.
I decided to "go for broke!"
I see! And what did Yuki say?
He'd think about it if I made
the top 100 on the upcoming test.
Really? Sounds exactly like
what I've been through!
But it's okay now.
I think I'll give up on Yuki.
What?
I told Yuki how I felt.
That's enough for me.
And I'll never make the top 100 anyway.
Why are you giving up?
You need to make the top 100?
Bring it on!
Kotoko, that's impossible.
How can I do that?
I'm in Class F!
I was in Class F too.
But I climbed my way
to 100 in the class!
Wow! Amazing!
There's nothing
you can't do if you try.
But even if I start cramming now,
the top 100...
Don't worry! I'll help you out.
I'm half responsible anyway.
I'll help you study!
Really?
Leave it to me!
I feel so motivated!
Watch out, Yuki! She's going
to make the top 100!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
KISS OF GOODBYE
Yes?
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Well...
Come in Konomi!
Kotoko!
You know her?
Kind of.
I'm going to tutor her from today.
What? You?
Konomi, you just leave it to me!
Okay!
Let's go to my room!
Excuse me.
Hey!
My heart was pounding!
I'm so envious
you get to live with Yuki.
Really?
This may be your first step
toward a life with Yuki!
But first, the top 100!
Thanks for helping me!
No problem!
Okay, let's get to work!
What shall we study first?
Wait a minute ...
This is ...
I think you use this formula.
Excuse me, Kotoko?
It's been over an hour
and we're still on question 1.
Don't worry! We're almost there.
Here, have some snacks, okay?
I'm home.
Welcome back, Naoki!
How do you do.
Hello.
What are you doing?
This is Konomi, Yuki's classmate
at Tonan Middle School.
I'm helping her study
for her final exams.
I don't know if she's going
to be much help.
What are you saying?
I have to get Konomi
into the top 100 of her class.
Top 100.
That sounds familiar.
Doesn't it bring back memories?
This becomes 4.
And what is 4 squared?
We studied behind closed doors.
Now that I remember the moment
that was the beginning
of our relationship!
Behind closed doors.
Just don't waste your time.
Naoki, you're disturbing our studies!
All right.
Shall we start?
Yes!
What were you doing?
I was just walking by.
Why don't you help her study?
No way. She's too stupid.
And I'm the one who'll suffer
if she makes the top 100.
I see.
So it's complicated.
Not at all!
Kotoko.
Sorry.
I...
get so sleepy
when I look at mathematical formulas.
Kotoko!
Don't go to sleep!
What should I do?
Dinner.
I can't believe it.
What a tutor.
I'd better get going.
How far did you get?
We solved one problem.
In three hours?
Yes.
How many pages?
From here...
to there.
I can't let you waste more time.
It looks like you're in trouble.
I'll teach you.
But I'm not very smart.
You'll get frustrated.
I'm used to teaching kids like you.
The answer is...
2xy (3x - 2y...
close parentheses?
Correct.
Wow! I did it!
Hey!
Naoki? Yuki?
Was I sleeping?
Stop bothering my brother.
He's taking the National Medical
Board Examination soon.
What are you gonna do if he fails?
I'll teach you.
We have one week until final exams.
I'll tutor you after school until 9 pm.
Really?
What's going on?
Yuki is tutoring Konomi?
Thanks to you!
I don't know what's going on, but...
You got your foot in the door!
Now kill two birds with one stone!
Love and exams!
Yes!
You're starting to talk like mom...
What?
Nothing.
I'm feeling really fired up!
How exciting!
Yuki's study sessions continued...
Hey!
Correct.
Really? Wow!
We did it!
Next!
Yes.
- 2y = 0.
y + 3 x (- 2y + 3).
Excuse me.
And today is the final day.
Konomi, Yuki. How about some tea?
Thank you.
How is it going?
Fine, thank you.
Yuki's a tough teacher.
Is he mean to you?
Oh, no.
I can't help it if she's stupid.
Don't say that!
Konomi, don't take it to heart.
Yuki may say that...
but boys are always mean
to girls they like.
Is that true?
Her? No way!
There he goes again.
Tadaa. Look at this.
What's that?
Open it.
These pictures...
Mom took them. Aren't they great?
Look how he's staring at you.
Don't be so stubborn, Yuki.
Just admit that you like her!
You look so cute together!
May I keep these?
Of course!
I'll keep them for good luck!
Thank you!
Are you kidding?
It's bad enough I have to tutor her.
You took pictures as well?
I...
I'm not your plaything!
You all make me sick!
I... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Konomi!
What are you doing?
Yuki.
You're a mess.
Why?
I promised.
I'd tutor you every day
until 9 p.m. for a week until the exam.
It's still 7:30.
Don't try to break my promise.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
And...
You forgot something.
For good luck, right?
Thank you!
Let go!
Look!
All right.
This one, too!
Let go. We're going home.
That's enough, already.
But your mom asked me to.
It looks like Yuki may take
the same path as me.
Poor guy.
What poor guy?
Do you have your papers?
Your pencil case?
Yeah.
Calm down.
I'm the one taking the test.
I know, but...
Can't I go with you to take your test?
No.
Naoki, what if...?
What if what?
What if...?
You fail...
that means we can graduate
together next year.
It'll be fun! So don't worry!
I don't intend to.
See you.
You can do it, Naoki!
The results of the National Exam
are going to be posted today.
Stop pacing back and forth
like a bear in a cage!
But!
The results will be posted
in one minute! I can't stay still!
Calm down, Kotoko.
Relax! Breathe in and out.
It's 2:00.
How was it? Did you pass?
I...
No!
It's okay.
You have a long life ahead.
What's the rush?
If you stumble once or twice...
Are you kidding?
So...?
Congratulations, Naoki!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Let's celebrate!
Congratulations, Naoki!
Naoki is going to be a doctor!
Kotoko!
Excuse me.
Mr. Irie!
It's not a bad offer. Think about it.
I will.
Well...
What shall I do?
Oh, yes!
We'll have his graduation party
at home!
Sounds good!
I want to invite lots of people
so please invite your
nursing school friends.
Oh, okay.
Yuki, please invite Konomi.
Why should I?
Because Konomi is your friend.
She's not my friend.
What do you mean?
She made the top 100
in the final exams!
Ninety-seven.
What?
That's wonderful!
It's decided then!
I was a good tutor, that's why.
I see.
I felt the same way with Kotoko.
It's a big deal for someone
in Class F to make the top 100.
The power of love is amazing.
I told you! It was my tutoring.
The hardship of studying
was overcome by spending
time together and fostering love!
Now you and Konomi
have a special bond.
Kotoko! Shut up!
But at the end of the day,
you wanted to be friends
with Konomi, too.
I said...
When is Naoki's graduation?
March 20th.
I see. So he's going to be a doctor.
He's going to speak
on behalf of the graduates.
Right, Naoki?
What's wrong, Naoki?
What?
You're speaking at
the graduation, right?
Yeah.
I knew it!
I'll bring my video camera!
Yuki is graduating, too.
Maybe I should buy a new one!
Kotoko.
I have something to tell all of you.
What? You sound so serious.
I met with my professor today.
I'm thinking of working
at a hospital in Kobe.
Kobe.
I thought you were going
to work at Tonan Hospital.
That's what I thought at first,
but I want to explore
some specialized fields
But...
The hospital in Kobe
is very specialized.
But! But...
Kobe is so far!
It's 6 hours there and back. How...?
Commuting is unreasonable.
Then...
I'm thinking of moving to Kobe.
Naoki! Are you serious?
Yeah.
I've already been invited
by a doctor in Kobe.
I'd study there for a few years
and then return.
Naoki! Then...
I have to find a school in Kobe!
Do I have time?
You should stay.
I'll go on my own.
You should stay here
and continue your studies.
I don't want to be apart!
Study here for a year
and come after you graduate.
No! I don't want to be
apart for a whole year!
I'm not that smart!
What if I don't graduate next year?
Then, it will be longer!
Kotoko.
We'll be apart for too long!
I can't do it!
Do you expect me to wait
until you become a nurse
and then go to Kobe?
How could you say that, Naoki?
Think how Kotoko feels.
You're husband and wife!
Yeah.
You shouldn't be apart!
Don't just think about yourself.
I know.
You don't know.
You wouldn't understand.
Because I love you way more
than you love me.
You wouldn't know
how I feel.
How hard it would be
to be apart from you!
Because
you
would be totally fine without me.
When you made your decision
you never
even thought about me, did you?
I'm the only one that would miss you!
Kotoko.
What should I do...?
What should I do? What?
I'm making it hard for him.
I'm failing him as his wife.
I know. I know it.
But... But...
I don't want to be apart.
Kotoko.
You didn't eat dinner again?
No.
But I'm sleepy.
Kotoko.
Good night.
Welcome home.
Thanks. You're still up?
Do you have a minute, dad?
How's Kotoko? Is she still upset?
Yes.
I was prepared for a bad reaction, but
when I actually see her like this...
She's crazy about you, that's why.
Dad.
I'm thinking of taking
Kotoko to Kobe with me.
Naoki... But...
If we find a nursing school now
she might be able to transfer.
But...
she won't know anyone
in a strange, new city.
Will she be able
to settle down and study?
I'll probably be so busy myself...
I wasn't confident
that I could think about
her well being, too.
I want her to become a nurse.
I thought
it may be better for us
to spend a year apart.
Naoki.
She
doesn't seem to realize
that I love her.
Naoki.
Representing the undergraduates,
Takayuki Miura of the Medical School.
Address by Naoki Irie
of the Medical School.
Yes.
Farewell address.
When I look back on my life
at Tonan University,
many unforgettable memories
come to mind.
How did I feel watching Naoki
at our high school graduation?
Jinko, Satomi and Kin-chan were there.
Naoki refused to give me his button.
But I still feel the same way.
I love Naoki!
All I know is one thing.
That I love Naoki.
Representing the graduates
of the Medical School ...
Naoki Irie.
That's one thing
that will never change.
This is the engineering campus
he attended as a freshman.
Yuko Matsumoto was here, too.
Did you decide on your electives?
No, not yet.
And the Tennis Club.
We played a doubles match.
Smooth.
The cafeteria where we ate lunch
and Naoki fought with Kin-chan.
What's with these portions?
Got a problem with it?
Kin-chan?
The medical lecture hall.
I used to watch Naoki from here.
There he is!
His aura outshines everyone else.
Yes!
I won't be seeing him here anymore.
Naoki.
Naoki!
What?
You're so loud.
How did you...?
I thought you might be here.
I have to talk to you.
It's probably better to talk here.
About Kobe.
I...!
I...
I'll become a nurse in one year.
Then I'll go to Kobe.
I promise! So...
Wait for me.
Don't
cheat on me.
Don't get mad
if I call you every day.
And...
And?
On my breaks
I'll come
Someone might come.
I don't care.
This is fine.
I'll see you off at the station.
That's okay.
You might stop the bullet train
if you come to see me off.
No I won't...
But...
maybe it will be easier
to say good-bye here.
Yeah. See you.
Call me when you get there.
Sure.
Your lunch.
I'll buy one!
Shin-Kobe is one station
after Okayama. Don't miss it!
You mean after Shin-Osaka.
Can I go now?
Sure.
How about a good-bye kiss?
Just joking.
Study hard.
You too, Naoki!
Yeah.
You can do it, Naoki!
You can do it, Kotoko.
We can...
do it.
Next Episode
Ep.12 "...and Love in KOBE"
How much bandage do you need?
I haven't talked to Naoki
in three days!
1,000 yen that she'll go to Kobe
within a week.
5,000 yen that she'll leave tomorrow.
I did it...!
There he is!
I'm feeling more energized
every minute.
He might start feeling single again
and spread his wings.
I found you!
Kotoko.
The mother and daughter
are named Shiina.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2