When I wake up, Naoki is lying next to me.
I'm so happy.
Am I the luckiest girl in the world?
We've been married
for two and a half years,
but my love for Naoki
sets new records every day.
Morning.
Your face is all swollen.
It's not a pretty sight.
Never mind what he just said.
I love him!
Good morning!
Good morning, Kotoko.
It's spring break. You should sleep in.
I'm still a housewife.
Oh, my!
My mother-in-law is so sweet.
Morning, honey. Morning, Kotoko.
-Morning.
-Good morning, Dad.
-How about some coffee?
-Thank you, Kotoko!
So is my father-in-law.
Kotoko! You washed my shirt
with my ID book in it!
Oops.
This won't fit into my pocket anymore.
Let's skip over him.
-Morning.
-Morning!
-Kotoko, can I have some coffee?
-Sure!
And... And...
the best husband in the world.
I thought my happiness
would last forever...
until...
Oh, I forgot to tell everyone.
Rika is coming
to live with us for a while.
-Rika?
She's back.
Yes, after seven years!
Who's Rika?
That's right. Kotoko hasn't met her.
She's Naoki and Yuki's cousin.
She's super brainy and beautiful,
unlike you.
She used to come over all the time
until their family moved to America.
Why is she coming to live with us?
Her family is moving back in May,
but Rika starts school in April
so she's coming back to Japan
a little early.
She's going to stay with us
until her family arrives.
So, Rika's coming back.
I thought Yuki hated girls,
but he looks so happy.
Speaking of Rika...
She used to win all those piano
and cooking competitions.
She's really a nice, cheerful girl.
She was talented,
ever since she was young.
So, Rika is like a perfect girl.
She's the complete opposite of you,
Kotoko.
Think of her as a younger sister.
Sure!
These are so heavy. My hands...
I'm almost home.
Oh, no!
-I'm sorry!
-No, it's my fault!
-Excuse me.
-Sorry, thanks!
Were you coming to our house?
Are you Rika? You're Rika, right?
No, I'm not.
Sorry.
Thanks.
-I'm very sorry.
-No.
Are you Yuki's friend?
No.
Excuse me!
Wait a minute!
I'm home.
Hi there.
-Watch where you're going.
-I was.
-You ran right into me.
-Sorry.
That girl was about Yuki's age.
-Naoki.
-Yuki.
-Yuki, when I was outside--
-Naoki! Rika's here!
Hey, Rika!
Wow... she's so cute.
Naoki!
You're more handsome than ever.
And you're more beautiful.
Wha...? What...?
What's going on?!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
Thank you for having this dinner for me.
HERE COMES A CUTIE LITTLE VIXEN!
I'm glad to see everyone is well.
Today, we're celebrating
Rika's return to Japan
and her staying with us for a while.
Cheers!
-Thank you.
-Welcome home.
Cheers!
Thank you. Thank you.
Nice to meet you, Kotoko.
Same here.
You start school tomorrow, right?
At St. Sumiregaoka Academy.
St. Sumiregaoka Academy?
That super selective school?
I lived nearby the school.
You don't attend a school like that
just because you live nearby.
You practically aced
the entrance exam, right?
Aced the exam?
You could learn something from Rika.
I think Kotoko is way
more capable than me.
Kotoko? More than you?
It's easy to ace a test.
It's nearly impossible
to win Naoki's heart.
Oh, my! She may be right.
Naoki is so stubborn.
We couldn't believe that
Naoki got married!
He had no interest in girls.
Kotoko, you must be incredible.
I worked pretty hard.
You pursued Naoki, right?
Yes, that's right.
I knew it. Otherwise...
If I only knew, I would have reserved you
before I left for America.
I know they're cousins,
but she's hanging onto him way too much!
Come now, Rika.
Naoki is a married man. Leave him alone.
Let's eat my lasagna before it gets cold.
There it is!
I love your lasagna!
Here you go.
That...
sounds like a real problem.
Really?
She's a fresh, young, high school student.
-Plus she's got beauty, brains and a body.
-Yes.
And... they're cousins
who grew up together.
They have a history
that you can't compete with.
She may embrace him...
and intimately call him "Naoki!"
What a formidable enemy.
Enemy?
Yes, enemy!
For you, and for me.
But, I don't think she has
romantic feelings for him.
Of course she does! What are you thinking?
We're talking about Naoki Irie!
-Really?
-I'm sure of it.
This parfait is delicious!
She's definitely cheerful
and seems like a good girl.
I feel a little left out, that's all.
Like I'm alienated.
I see.
Your biggest obstacle is...
his family.
-What?
-His family was always on your side.
Now they're all on her side.
Don't exaggerate.
You don't have the luxury
to be so magnanimous...
while everyone adores Rika.
Naoki...
could be taken away.
No!
And you'll be totally forgotten.
Moto-chan!
Thanks for dessert.
Kotoko!
Rika.
So may guys tried to pick me up already.
Pick you up?
Guys here are so immature.
Oh, really?
Including the boys in my class.
Hot guys are non-existent here.
I guess...
I grew up with Naoki
so my standards are high.
You can't compare them to Naoki.
Kotoko.
Can I...
have Naoki?
Why not?
Can I have him?
Rika, you must be...
You should have seen your face!
I was joking!
Joking. Joking, huh?
I can't let her get to me, but...
Who could that be? Mom?
Kotoko!
Rika! What is it?
Let's take a bath together.
Rika, I'd rather not.
Why not? We're both girls.
Well... I guess.
What... a... body.
Kotoko...
were you the one who proposed?
Oh, no!
Why do I always react to her?
I have to remain calm!
Be bold and confident!
She's just a high-school kid,
and I'm Naoki's wife.
Can I ask another question?
What?
Is Naoki... a good kisser?
Why? I don't know.
I wouldn't really know.
I've only kissed Naoki and...
Oh, really?
Then you wouldn't know.
I've had several boyfriends in America.
We kissed a lot.
No... I'm starting to feel faint.
I think I'm done.
But... the best kisser I've ever known...
is Naoki.
Naoki... is... a great kisser.
What... did she just say?
You're so lucky you get
to kiss him all the time.
I'd like to kiss him just one more time.
But there are all kinds of kisses.
Like smacks on the cheek
when you're small...
I was in fifth grade
and Naoki was in high school.
It was on the lips, of course.
What?!
I think it was the first kiss
for both of us.
Liar!
Kotoko.
Naoki's first kiss wasn't with me.
It was with Rika.
Kotoko!
Someone... tell me it isn't true.
Naoki. Naoki.
Naoki.
Kotoko... I'm going out with Naoki.
What? Naoki is married to me!
But we make a better couple.
And I kissed him first.
Right, Naoki?
Yeah... I guess so.
We were each other's first.
Leave her, and let's kiss.
Okay.
No!
It was a dream.
I overslept!
Good morning, Kotoko.
Are you feeling okay?
You fainted yesterday.
You should sleep in.
I borrowed your apron.
You like omelets, right Naoki?
Shall I make you one?
-Sure.
-Me, too.
Okay! Leave it to me.
Rika, don't worry. I'll do it.
But I make a better omelet.
How do you know?
Just go back to sleep.
What's wrong, you two?
I'll make it!
You want to know about Rika?
You must know about her.
Well...
We were like siblings
ever since we were small.
Does Rika...
like...
Naoki?
Who knows?
But... I like her a lot.
So, I asked her to live with us.
And she said to me...
"If I marry Naoki...
I can be your real sister."
Marry...?
If I really wanted her to be my sister,
I would have to help her
get married to Naoki.
I remember promising her that.
Kotoko.
Can I...
have Naoki?
She's been in love with Naoki
all this time.
Is she really in love?
Okay.
This time...
You're up early, Kotoko.
You, too, Rika.
What's this breakfast?
They made it together.
You girls are so nice.
-Morning.
-Naoki!
Naoki!
This is really good. Try it.
A special breakfast. Try it.
I can't eat so much this early.
What? Please.
I made it just for you.
Oh, well.
Which one first?
Mine first.
It's bad.
Try mine.
-It's good.
-You've always liked omelets!
Don't give up, Kotoko!
This is awful.
Kotoko, coffee.
I'll get you some coffee.
No.
Kotoko makes good coffee.
I'll make some right away.
Kotoko.
Rika, you'll be late for school.
I...
I love Naoki.
I've loved him way longer than you.
Give him back.
What?
She's serious.
If I didn't go to America...
he would have never married you.
How would you know?
Because... Naoki was in love with me.
We exchanged passionate kisses.
He held me tight.
It was so romantic.
So what?
I don't know how Naoki felt then...
because all I could do
was watch him from afar.
But... little by little, he noticed me,
and he asked me to marry him!
Little by little?
You forced yourself on him!
No, I didn't!
What is this?
Who do you think you are? How stupid!
Give it back! Give it back!
You're in your own little world.
It's so stupid!
That's enough!
Rika!
Naoki!
It hurts.
Let me see your leg.
Naoki... I didn't mean to...
You should know better!
She's just a high-school kid!
What's wrong with you?
Can you stand?
I'll bandage it at home.
It wasn't like that.
Naoki carried Rika away. Far, far away.
Kotoko?
We brought home your drunk daughter.
Oh, you're Kotoko's friends.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
Excuse us.
She said she couldn't go home
after what she did to Rika.
She's been crying since this morning.
We went drinking to cheer her up.
I can't drink any more.
Get off of me. You're heavy.
What the hell?
Naoki!
Sorry to trouble you, Kikyo.
Don't mention it.
He called me by my name!
Come on. Let's go.
No!
You... You...
You don't like me anymore.
I'm an immature, violent girl.
Your eyes are telling me you're disgusted!
You're absolutely right!
I'm totally disgusted.
Let me down!
Be quiet!
But, Naoki, you like...
You like Rika more...
Rika... Rika more than me.
You...
Is Kotoko sleeping?
Sorry about this morning.
I don't want your apology.
You...
shouldn't provoke her like that.
-What? I never--
-Good night.
It's ready! Hurry, before it's burnt!
Eat up!
Naoki, I picked out the good ones.
Thank you.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good.
Everything tastes good outdoors.
Don't eat too much, now.
Don't worry!
Kotoko, can you bring me a beer?
Yes.
I'll go with you.
Kotoko.
When did you fall in love with Naoki?
In my freshman year in high school.
So, 8 years ago.
That's pretty long.
But I've loved him since I was 2.
So, 15 years.
Rika...
you asked... for Naoki back.
Where's the beer?
Oh, no.
But... I can't do that.
Never.
I see.
But that's just your opinion.
I wonder how Naoki feels.
What if Naoki says he prefers me?
Then give him back to me, okay?
Fine. Ask him, then.
I see.
Did you hear that, Naoki?
Most of it.
I've always loved you.
I don't understand why you love Kotoko.
I'm a better match for you.
So, why did you marry Kotoko?
Do you know how shocked
I was when I heard?
Then...
Then... you shouldn't have gone
to America!
How can you be apart so long
from the one you love?
It couldn't be helped!
I was in fifth grade.
I had to go with my parents.
It doesn't matter!
I could never stay away
from the one I loved.
If it were me...
I wouldn't have gone to America!
I'd stay near him,
even if he didn't love me!
You may have loved him longer than me...
but you'll never love him as much as I do!
So...
I don't know how Naoki feels...
but that's how I feel.
So...
Kotoko!
That's why.
That's why... I fell in love with her.
Unlike you... she can't do anything right.
But I love her power.
More than me?
More than you.
I see.
Maybe Kotoko...
wouldn't have gone to America.
Probably not.
Look at your face.
Why are you crying?
Because... what if...
it's over between us?
I have to find the strength
to go on living.
Go on living.
Can you?
No.
When did I ever give you reason
to doubt me?
I never have.
I chose you. Have more confidence.
Rika.
Naoki didn't like Kotoko at first.
She turned this house upside down.
But...
before he knew it, he fell in love.
Traitor.
Traitor!
You promised me...
that you'd help me become your sister.
That you'd help me get married to Naoki.
It's all your fault!
Stupid Yuki!
Stupid! Stupid!
Sorry.
Sorry...
Rika.
Uncle, aunty...
thank you for having me.
We'll miss you.
We felt like we had two daughters.
-Come back anytime.
-Of course.
Next time I'll bring a boyfriend
that's better looking than Naoki.
Good luck finding one.
Oh, you two.
Rika.
See you.
This kind of reminds me
of that other time.
Other time?
The day I left for America.
The day we had our first kiss.
So, it was a goodbye kiss.
Should I do it again to show you?
No! No! No!
That's what happened seven years ago.
Sorry. I may have dramatized a bit.
Dramatized?
Actually, I forced myself on him.
But it was still a kiss.
So, that's how it was.
Here.
For me?
I guess I'll have to accept you
as Naoki's wife.
See you!
-Take care.
-See you.
-Bye-bye.
See you, Rika!
Bye-bye!
She's so loud.
Bye-bye, Naoki.
I'm the person who understands
Rika's feelings the most.
The next time we meet...
I'm sure we can be better friends.
Right, Rika?
NEXT EPISODE:
NAOKI, COUNTING ON YOU FOR KOTOKO!
You like Yuki, don't you?
His cool eyes.
I'm rooting for you!
Next week is the anniversary of
Kotoko's mother's death. I'll go with you.
You don't have to!
-Are you hiding something?
-You'll see soon enough.
Thank you for this unbelievable reception.
But my name is misspelled.
The characters are wrong.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2