I passed!
Yes!
Congratulations!
Naoki, I want you to be the first
to see me...
as a nurse!
I wanted to tell you
the minute I found out.
We can finally work together.
You studied hard all year.
Naoki!
You look good in that uniform.
Thanks.
4 MONTHS LATER
Hi, everyone.
No!
It's Kotoko!
What do you mean by "No!"
as you see me coming?
What are you trying to do?
To take a blood sample.
Oh, God. From... From who?
Mr. Harada and Mr. Kimura.
It's me!
Come on. Let's do it.
You have no idea what it's all about
since you joined us here today.
-What a treat for your first day here.
-What?
That nurse is named Kotoko Irie.
You'd better watch out for her.
Just watch.
Are you afraid of a little shot?
You're just like a kid.
Give me your arm, please.
Do you prefer right or left?
Don't screw it up.
Leave it to me.
Let's start with the tourniquet.
Squeeze your thumb tightly, please.
Okay, now.
Let's make those veins pop.
Ouch! Ouch!
Now some rubbing alcohol.
Okay.
It'll feel a little cold.
Now, this may sting a little.
That's weird. Blood isn't coming out.
Don't worry.
Narrow veins perhaps? That's strange.
Okay.
Wait a minute, please.
Okay. Let's try again.
What?
Something's not right...
This usually doesn't happen.
One last time.
My arm will be full of holes!
What are you doing, Ms. Irie?
Nurse Shimizu.
Let me do it.
Thank God.
Mr. Kimura was a rare example.
How about Mr. Harada?
Please, don't! No!
Wait, Mr. Harada!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
FLOWERS AND STORMS
Out of the question!
How long have you been a nurse now,
Ms. Irie?
Two... Two months.
I told you to call someone
after failing two tries.
I'm sorry.
You're not a trainee anymore.
And yesterday, you also did...
That's my patient calling.
How can I help you?
What? Okay. Got it.
I have to run, Nurse Shimizu.
Mrs. Irie!
She's only so quick
when she needs to be.
Take care.
Kotoko.
Moto-chan.
Nurse Shimizu chewed you out again?
Cheer up.
You must be used to
getting scolded by now.
It's not that.
I worked so hard to become a nurse.
I thought I could finally
work with Naoki.
I cried tears of joy.
But look what happened!
They told me there were
no vacancies in Kobe.
Could that be possible?
Naoki and I are still apart.
I can't believe it!
How could I be happy?
I guess...
divorce may just be a matter of time.
Stop it!
It can't be helped.
At least you were assigned
to Tonan University Hospital.
I guess.
Marina and Funatsu ended up together
in the Cardiovascular Unit.
Tomoko is in Surgery Unit 2,
of course.
Keita is in Orthopedics.
And you and I are in Surgery Unit 3.
We're all here except...
Naoki isn't here!
When will I ever get
to work with Naoki?
I thought I could finally
become a help for him.
God is so unfair.
Ms. Irie.
You look depressed.
Did you mess up again?
Dr. Nishigaki.
This nurse here...
...turned her patient's arm
into a pin cushion.
That's not necessary.
How terrible.
I'll teach you how to give injections.
Maybe during a night shift?
No, thank you.
How about a date, then?
Dr. Nishigaki!
I'll have you know
I'm a married woman.
So I heard.
You don't look it, at all.
I heard your husband
is a very capable intern.
Is he better looking than me?
Of course.
That's hard to believe.
But if he's not here,
he's not a rival, is he?
If you get lonely without him,
don't hesitate to call on me.
-I will not!
-I will.
How about lunch, Dr. Nishigaki?
Oh, Ms. Tanaka.
Sure.
New hairstyle?
You noticed.
Of course I did.
I never miss one single change
in a beautiful woman.
You look fantastic.
Really? You're such a flirt.
It's gonna be a long lunch.
What a player. He gives me the chills.
But Dr. Nishigaki is good-looking.
I would fall for him.
What do you mean?
He's such a player.
And he's a brilliant surgeon.
He's 29 and single.
I need eye candy. Especially
since Mr. Irie is not around.
Don't you agree?
Not at all.
Okay, you're right. He is good-looking.
And he might be a good doctor, too.
But...
But! He's totally different from Naoki!
Naoki is a doctor of principle.
He would never be tempted
by a sexy nurse or a patient.
Not even by you.
Speaking of not being
tempted by women,
Dr. Daijamori is principled, too.
Please. Don't even try to compare them.
That doctor isn't...
What?
I'm supposed to take...
Dr. Daijamori's patient
to the MRI Room at 11:00.
He'll blow up even if you're
a minute late. He's such a stickler.
And the time is...
It's 11:15.
No!
Ms. Irie! No running in the halls!
I'm sorry.
Hey!
I heard from Nurse Shimizu
that we have a problem.
In just one day, we've had claims
from Dr. Ezaki and Dr. Daijamori,
and even from patients.
You're making too many
fundamental errors.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Irie.
You submitted a request to be
transferred to the hospital in Kobe.
-Yes.
-Because your husband...
Dr. Irie is working there?
Yes. I...
I want to work with Dr. Irie.
That's all very well.
I believe married couples
should be together.
But! Do you think you're ready?
Dr. Irie has been so brilliant
ever since when he was a medical student.
He must be making his marks over there
right now.
You want to be a good partner
to Dr. Irie, right?
Yes.
But as it stands, you will not only
make a poor partner...
You will be a burden on Dr. Irie!
A burden... on Naoki.
You know...
What's wrong, Kotoko?
We haven't seen you in a while.
Why are you so down?
Really, Kotoko. What happened?
You finally became a nurse.
I was looking forward to
being nursed back to health
by Nurse Kotoko.
I'll take care of you, Kinnosuke.
-Idiot, that was my fantasy.
-Well, discard that fantasy.
-What for?
-I can be a nurse, too.
-You can?
-I can.
-Prove it.
-Okay.
You two get along so well.
Why don't you get married?
Yeah. Tell him that, Kotoko.
Let go of me.
You can work together...
and be together forever.
I'm so envious.
You miss Irie. Is that it?
It's not good to be apart
from the man you love.
I gave up going home to England.
You're right.
To be honest,
I want to be with Naoki every day.
But they say I'm not ready.
I'll just be a burden on Naoki.
They're right.
I mess up all the time.
I've been a burden on doctors
and patients all the time.
They're scared of me.
At this rate...
I won't be able to assist Naoki.
I'll just get in his way.
-Kotoko--
-No, Kotoko.
Don't be so negative.
Where is the Kotoko that inspired me
in matters of love?
The Kotoko I know
is not weak and negative.
The Kotoko I know...
would trample over flowers and storms
to pursue Naoki.
That's the real Kotoko.
-Flowers and storms?
-Yes.
-Trample over?
-That's right.
You're right.
All I can do is try my best
to overcome my challenges.
If I just stand still,
I'll never reach Naoki.
That's the spirit, Kotoko.
-Chris.
-That's the real Kotoko.
I'll do it.
You're so resilient.
Trample over flowers and storms.
Mr. Yokoi's IV is done.
I'm going to distribute the lunches.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Did you change Mr. Yamagishi's sheets
in Room 203?
-I'll do it right now.
-I did it already.
What?
I'll be going now.
What's come over Ms. Irie?
Who knows?
Do you have a dream?
-For the future?
-Well...
As for me, my husband is a doctor,
so, that's why I became a nurse.
-Dear God, dear God.
-It'll just be a little prick.
Dear God, dear God.
Mr. Hasebe in 216 complained
of post-surgical pain at 1:00 p.m.
I gave him an IV drip.
Okay.
Excuse me.
There you are, Ms. Irie.
I'm sorry. Did I mess up again?
No. This time, it's good news.
There's a vacancy.
We heard back from Dr. Irie's
hospital in Kobe.
Let's get the paperwork done
for the transfer.
I'm sure you want to go right away.
Me? At Naoki's hospital?
Yes! You endured
a long, long separation.
And you've shown
great improvement lately.
Please keep it up and support Dr. Irie.
Thank you, Nurse Hosoi!
Hospital in Kobe?
So, you're leaving us.
Maybe we'll all live a little longer.
Hey.
But we'll miss you.
And your loud voice.
Good luck with your husband.
And injections.
I'll miss you all, too.
There you are, Ms. Irie.
We're doing our rounds.
Oh, yes.
Let's take a look at your scar.
Thank you.
-It's healing very well.
-That's good.
-Minimal scarring.
-Good.
Alcohol.
I have to tell Naoki.
Is he gonna be surprised?
Alcohol.
Alcohol!
Oh, yes.
Sorry.
Stop daydreaming.
Who are you to say?
You're only an intern.
What...? What are you doing here?
I've been transferred to Tonan
University Hospital Sugery Unit 3.
I'm Naoki Irie. How do you do?
Irie...?
Are you Kotoko's...?
Then...
Naoki, that means you and I...
Can finally work together.
Kotoko.
Naoki!
We've come such a long way.
Memories flash through my mind.
I...
What I want to do most...
is to help you do your job.
In other words, to become a nurse.
Naoki is here.
This is exactly what I've been dreaming of
all this time.
--committed to my care.
I'm thinking of working
at a hospital in Kobe.
It's been so long.
Hey. We're in a hospital.
Is that your husband?
Yes. This is my husband.
Good for you.
Yes.
From today, he and I
will take care of you all.
But aren't you going to Kobe?
So, we're going to be apart again.
-No.
-I guess it wasn't meant to be.
Well, do your best in Kobe.
Are you done?
Let's continue our rounds.
Nurse Hosoi!
Please cancel my transfer!
I'm home.
Ready?
Welcome home, Naoki!
This is wonderful.
It's been so long. Right, Kotoko?
Yes.
Naoki.
You left Kotoko all alone
for a long, long time.
Please take good care of her
from now on.
Do you hear me?
Mom.
Naoki is back home.
Now our family is all together.
The two of you, and our family,
will all be happy.
Yes.
Let's have a toast. Over there.
And don't forget about my grandchild.
Tonight is Naoki's
welcome-home party.
Drink up.
Thank you.
I'm sure I'll be very busy,
but Kotoko and I will do our best.
Okay.
Well, Naoki, welcome home.
Cheers!
Now for the food. Let's go get it.
Welcome home, Naoki.
You've grown up, Yuki.
Really?
He's already grown
10 centimeters this year.
Good thing you're taller than Konomi.
Shut up, Kotoko.
Why? I'm happy for you.
Sorry, but...
Naoki.
Welcome home.
Thank you for letting me come today.
How is school going, Konomi?
I'm still struggling.
Yuki gets mad at me all the time.
Are you and Yuki getting along?
He still tutors me.
We go to the movies, too.
With Yuki, huh?
What are you telling my brother?
Hey, Kotoko. We're here.
Naoki. Welcome home.
Let's eat.
My glasses are slipping.
So, you're a teenager, huh?
Kin-chan.
-What?
-The monkey...
You did this.
You'll catch cold, Naoki.
Are you tired?
Everyone's having a great time.
My life in Kobe was so quiet.
Living alone...
Everyone's so happy you're back.
They can't help but celebrate.
Mom, Dad, even Yuki.
He talks big, but even Kin-chan.
My Kobe transfer has been canceled.
Now we can finally live together.
I'm so very happy.
It's so noisy back here.
I really feel like I'm home.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Naoki.
Now we'll be together forever.
Mr. Kimura in 215 is going to have
an intestinal polyp removed tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Mr. Yokoi's stiches come out today.
-So cool.
I could look at him
in his doctor's coat all day.
I'm so happy.
You'd better watch out.
I think I underestimated him.
Dr. Nishigaki, you're Naoki's...
Dr. Irie's medical advisor.
How can an intern be more popular
than his advisor?
-That's not the issue.
-Dr. Irie.
How was Mr. Ito in 202?
I was watching his progress on primperan,
but his condition hasn't improved.
And? Then what?
How should we proceed?
We should identify which side
of the intestine we should resect
by using an enema.
You're spot on.
It's no fun being your medical advisor.
Kotoko. He'll cheat on you in a minute
and make you miserable.
You should break up with him
while you can.
Then...
you can go out with me, huh?
Dr. Nishigaki.
This is Mr. Tsuda's pre-op chart.
You can't even take a joke.
You're assisting in Unit 2. Be ready.
Yes, doctor.
I'm back.
Ms. Irie!
Where have you been all this time?
You've been slipping again
since Dr. Irie has been back.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if you're ready
for this responsibility.
What?
From today, you'll be assisting
in actual procedures.
-What?
-This is your first time, right?
It's a simple procedure today.
Don't worry, I'll be there, too.
Yes.
Assisting. Could it be?
You're assisting in Unit 2. Be ready.
Yes.
My first time as an assisting nurse.
I might work with Naoki.
Do you know what you're
supposed to do?
Be sure to review it.
Nurse Shimizu?
Who's the attending doctor?
Doctor...
What are you doing here?
My name is Irie. I'll be assisting.
Give me a break.
Is she going to be of any use?
Okay, let's start.
We have a very risky assistant today.
So, be extra careful.
Please keep the sanitized and
unsanitized instruments separate.
-Yes, doctor.
I can't screw it up.
I practiced this a hundred times
during training.
I'll surprise Dr. Daijamori.
I can do it, Naoki.
Scapel.
Yes.
Oh, no.
I'm starting to sweat.
Gross.
-Gauze.
-Yes.
Why are you wiping yourself?
Give me the gauze.
Oh, sorry.
No. Don't faint.
-Pean.
-Yes.
-Hurry up. Pean.
I got it. Here you go.
You...
You caused another commotion?
I... I'm sorry!
The procedure was completed
and Dr. Daijamori's injury
turned out to be minor, but seriously...
This was another fundamental error
on your part.
I guess you weren't ready.
It was my mistake.
Night shift?
You're on night duty, too.
Yeah.
You want some caffeine?
Yes.
I...
The stabbing incident?
I heard you made a grand debut.
I'm so depressed.
I injured the hand of a surgeon.
It can't get any worse.
I could have placed
a patient's life at risk.
My own carelessness scares me.
I don't want to be a burden on you.
So...
I'll be sad if we're
in different departments, but...
I thought I'd request a transfer
to another area.
Like dermatology or ENT.
I'd better go. Thanks.
This is Irie.
I see. I'll be right there.
An emergency?
Three people were in a car accident.
Three people?
No other hospital would take them.
I'd better go.
I'm coming, too.
Dr. Irie, take this patient to the ward.
He's stable now.
I'll see him after I operate.
-It's a femoral compound fracture.
-Yes, doctor.
Let me know if anything happens.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
I guess he's going to be fine.
Why is his blood pressure dropping?
It might be a ruptured femoral artery.
Kotoko, call Dr. Nishigaki!
Okay.
Dr. Nishigaki.
The patient's blood pressure
is in the 50s!
His femoral artery...
What...?
Dr. Nishigaki! Hello? Hello?
He said to wait. He can't leave
the operating room right now.
It's too risky to wait.
But...
The artery needs to be sewn up.
I'll do it.
But, Naoki, you're just an intern!
-Dr. Nishigaki told us to wait.
-We don't have time.
But there will be consequences.
I'll take responsibility.
-No. Let's wait for Dr. Nishigaki.
-Kotoko.
-Yes.
Put on a gown, now.
Assist me.
But, I... I can't.
I'll mess up again and you'll be...
Are you going to abandon this patient?
But...
If you don't do this now,
you'll never move forward.
If you can live with that,
go to dermatology or ENT
or wherever you want.
Forget it. I'll call another nurse.
Wait!
I'll assist you.
I want to save this patient.
Good for you.
I'll be assisting Naoki.
I'm not scared.
Not at all.
Naoki must be scared.
With no attending doctor...
The fiasco with Dr. Daijamori
is still fresh in my mind.
But I have to support Naoki.
I can't be a burden.
-Scalpel.
-Yes.
-Gauze.
If anything goes wrong
because of me...
I'm scared.
Everything will fall
on Naoki's shoulders.
-Tweezers.
-Yes.
-Kotoko, vitals.
Blood pressure 50-30. Heart rate 300.
You mean 160?
-Forceps.
-Yes.
I have to be strong.
I can't be a burden.
-Forceps.
-Yes.
I'm sorry.
My mind blows up. I can't think.
The patient, Naoki...
It's all my fault.
What should I do?
NEXT EPISODE
EP.14 "STAND UP FOR LOVE"
Get up.
-Just listen to me.
-What are you doing?
I decided to do it. Kotoko, go.
I can't let her do this by herself.
Forceps. I'm closing it up.
Prepare the saline.
It is unprecedented.
Who will take responsibility?
-Do you have a boyfriend?
-I don't.
Why are you acting like my girlfriend
when you're not?
Sorry.
What's wrong?
I was waiting for you.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2