Ta-da!
"Congratulations..." You passed?
I, Kotoko Irie, passed the examination
to transfer to the nursing school!
And for my reward,
a dream date with Naoki.
Couples who ride in these boats
are destined to part ways.
What?
What do you want to do?
We're already on the boat.
Why didn't you tell me
before we got on?
I would never have--
This is the kind of date
you envisioned, right?
You and me... on a boat.
Naoki, how did you...?
I'd never agree on a date
exactly as you planned it,
but you stayed up all night
planning it.
The least I could do was
make part of it come true.
What do you want to do?
Believe in a stupid jinx
and get off the boat?
Naoki...
Or...?
TONAN UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL DEPARTMENT
A white lab coat!
Hello.
This is my first step
to becoming a nurse!
And...
our departments are right next
to each other.
There it is!
"202, Department of Nursing."
Okay!
Good morning!
Who's that?
Oh, yeah. I don't know anyone here.
Plus, everyone is three years younger
than me.
Excuse me.
Thank you. Thank you.
Are you new here?
She's so cute!
Yeah. I transferred
from the Literature Department.
You must really want to be
a nurse to transfer midway.
Yeah. I guess.
I'm Tomoko Ogura. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kotoko Irie. Same here.
Good morning.
Today is the first day of a new year.
This year, you'll get
some practical experience as a nurse.
You will work in groups of five.
I expect you to work as a team.
I'll read the names now.
-Group? Naoko Saeki.
-Here.
It's finally started. Wait for me, Naoki!
I'm going to be a nurse
that you can be proud of!
-Scalpel.
-Yes.
-Wipe my sweat.
Good work.
Thanks to you, Dr. Irie,
the surgery was a success.
Thanks to my capable nurse.
I'm not really...
I hope you'll continue to support me.
Of course!
Kotoko Irie.
Ms. Irie?
Kotoko.
Yes! I vow to support you!
Daydreaming in the first class
of the year?
You'd better shape up!
I'm sorry.
We're both in Group 2.
Really?
Thank goodness!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
I'll introduce you
to the other members.
EXTREME!? MATES IN WHITE COAT
Everyone.
This is our newest member.
She's so beautiful.
They're kind of intimidating.
This is Kotoko Irie.
How do you do? I'm Kotoko Irie.
I transferred to the nursing school
to follow my dream.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Marina Shinagawa.
So, what's your dream?
Well...
Do you have your eye on a guy
in the medical school?
You do?! Me too!
I'm going to marry a doctor
and become rich!
Marina! Purge that foul idea
from your head!
You're tainting a sacred profession.
I like rich, intelligent men.
I want children with superior DNA.
People like you are the bane
of the medical field.
Shut up! We're not all fanatics like you!
You're so dispassionate!
You're too passionate!
Calm down, both of you.
Don't mind them.
They're always like this.
This passionate guy is Keita Kamogari.
I'm going to be
the best nurse in Japan.
I'll do whatever it takes.
So noble for someone so young.
Hey...
You're not related
to that other "Irie," are you?
What kind of reaction is that?
Are you... a man?
How rude. I'm a woman at heart.
I'm Motoki Kikyo.
You can call me Moto-chan.
Moto-chan?
You're not related to Irie
in the medical school, are you?
-Irie in the medical school?
-What?!
Don't you know
the super-elite Naoki Irie?
Naoki Irie... I've heard of him.
Right? He's a total hottie
as well as a genius!
You'll never find a man
so close to perfection.
He's so good-looking!
And so intelligent!
That's right. Moto-chan started
a Naoki Irie Fan Club.
I'm a member, too.
He meets all my criteria.
Wait a minute.
Criteria?
Is that how you see Mr. Irie?
You're the same!
I'm not so calculating.
My feelings for him are pure.
Give up. It's hopeless.
What did you say?! All is fair in love!
But...
isn't Naoki Irie married?
How do you know?
A rumor! I heard a rumor.
Can you believe it?
He forsook me and got married.
Rumor says his wife was
his classmate in college.
It's unforgivable.
What sort of selfish girl
would monopolize him?
Only a beauty and a genius like him,
of course!
I'd love to see her face.
NURSING PRACTICE ROOM
Let's take your blood pressure.
Let's visit Mr. Irie at his house today.
I'm in! Are you, Tomoko?
Moto-chan, you succeeded
in finding his address.
Of course.
As a president of the fan club,
I want to check out his wife.
What...?
They're coming over?
What should I do?
I'm Naoki Irie's wife!
But if they find out,
I'll be ostracized.
For the next three years,
I'll have to pretend
I don't know him.
Poor me.
Hey! Isn't that enough pressure?
Look. My arm is turning purple.
Don't be mad. It's not good
for your blood pressure.
Who's making me mad?!
It won't happen again.
I didn't want to be in your group.
That's funny...
Ow! Stop, stop, stop!
Are you trying to stop my circulation?
But you don't have a pulse!
Your...
stethoscope is backwards.
Is that intentional?
Sorry! One more time--
Enough! What if I was a real patient?
Don't get so mad!
Everyone makes mistakes.
But you've made three already.
I think it's four.
Six, to be exact.
Your intentions aren't serious.
That's why nothing is sinking in.
My intentions are serious!
I want to support Naoki!
Why would you support Mr. Irie?
Because...
I'm...
I'm Naoki Irie's wife!
What utter nonsense!
You're hilarious!
Don't laugh!
Okay, okay. Talk is for free, right?
Then I'm Naoki Irie's wife, too.
But it's true!
Excuse me.
Mr. Irie!
Kotoko.
You forgot this.
Mom said to give it to you.
See you.
Mr. Irie!
Ko... to... ko...
I told you it was true.
Didn't you say, "I've heard of him"?
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to lie.
I was trying to find a way...
Now I'll be a pariah.
You don't need to apologize.
We're not mad at all.
If you're his wife, we still have hope.
I thought he was so inaccessible,
but this means we stand a chance!
Right?
What does that mean?
Naoki!
-Mr. Irie!
-Naoki!
Now I can proudly say
that I'm Naoki's wife.
Watch carefully.
All done.
You can do it, Kotoko.
Got it.
I bonded with my group members,
and I was enjoying
this challenging, yet fulfilling time.
But the biggest challenge
was still ahead of me!
The injection spot is
three fingers below
the central deltoid,
so right around here.
Oh, no.
I hate shots more than anything.
A green light comes on
when you've hit the right spot.
The sight of... blood!
Is that clear?
Let's practice administering injections.
You'll have an exam next week.
If your entire group gets it right,
you can go to lunch.
Okay.
Let's be the first to finish!
Let's go.
This feels so realistic.
Let's get this over with
and go to lunch.
-Lend me your arm, Keita.
-What?
Wow, your arm is pretty muscular.
Can you do it?
Of course. Who wants to go first?
Can I go first?
Sure.
Aren't you scared?
Not at all.
Hey, wait up!
-The syringe.
-Yes, ma'am.
How was it?
Tomoko passed.
You're good at it, Marina!
I did it!
You're the last one, Kotoko.
Okay.
Concentrate!
Yes, sir! Here I go.
That's my shoulder!
-The fake one!
-Oh, yeah.
-Can you do it?
-No problem.
Who gives shots
with their eyes closed?
But I'm scared to look.
Take it out of the arm!
Not done yet?
We're the only ones left.
I'm starving.
This time, for sure.
Hey! How many times
do I have to tell you?
Pinch the arm
and stick the needle in!
I know, but this device
doesn't like me. Sorry.
How many times
do I have to say it?
We're always in last place,
thanks to you.
If you're really sorry,
arrange a med school mixer
and invite Mr. Irie.
But...
I can't believe it.
-Naoki!
-Mr. Irie!
Kotoko.
If you can't handle this,
I hope we never work together.
I doubt she'll even pass
the national exam.
Do something about it.
At this rate,
she'll never become a nurse.
"Never"?
You're a genius, right? Do something.
I'm not going to become a doctor
for her sake.
If she doesn't have what it takes,
so be it.
It has nothing to do with me.
But she's your wife.
Why don't you do something about it?
Sorry for intruding.
He's so cool.
What's his problem?
Don't you feel anything from this?!
Why'd you marry him anyway?
For his looks? For status?
Calm down, will you?
It's fine... because it's true.
He's always like that. I'm used to it.
Naoki doesn't baby me.
That's not what I mean!
Married couples...
should encourage each other
and help each other.
There's so much more to it!
They should work together!
With encouragement...
I think Keita really idealizes marriage.
Anyway, I'm relieved.
Mr. Irie doesn't seem
to love you that much.
No! He does!
Am I really cut out to be a good nurse?
And...
We're always in last place,
thanks to you.
If you're really sorry,
arrange a med school mixer
and invite Mr. Irie.
I'm sure Naoki won't go to a mixer.
This onion... is making me teary.
What's wrong, Kotoko?
Are you crying?
Becoming a nurse isn't easy.
I empathize.
You're doing something challenging
you've never done for Naoki.
You're so devoted, Kotoko.
I'll tell you something
to make you happy.
Dad has some land up in Hokkaido.
There's a village without a doctor.
Working in a big hospital is nice,
but wouldn't it be fun to run
a small clinic together?
Just the two of us?
Yes!
The villagers will be so grateful,
and you can gaze
upon the stars at night!
Oh, my God!
That's enough.
I didn't know you were home, Naoki.
I guess you didn't notice,
so immersed in your fantasy.
Who'd run a clinic with a nurse
that can't even administer a shot?
Kotoko is trying her best
to juggle housework and schoolwork.
Tonight's dinner is your favorite,
beef stew.
I'm making plenty
so we can eat it again tomorrow.
I won't be home tomorrow.
Eating out?
The guys at the medical school
are going drinking.
You never go on group outings!
How many of you are going?
Six or seven?
Where?
Shibuya.
Oh, Shibuya!
Which restaurant?
How should I know?
I didn't arrange it.
We're all here at 6:59 p.m. Let's go.
Welcome!
I'm Funatsu.
I have a 7 p.m. reservation.
We've been expecting you,
Mr. Funatsu.
Your guests are waiting.
They're in the back.
What a coincidence!
Aren't you med students
at Tonan University?
We're second-year nursing students!
Is it okay if we join you?
Sure! Right, guys?
It's more fun with girls in the mix.
What a coincidence, huh, Irie?
Kotoko!
Naoki! What a coincidence.
Coincidence? You planned this.
It's a coincidence!
Is that why you called me last night?
I knew it was strange when you asked me
where we were going.
Shall we sit down, everybody?
Come on. Let's sit down!
Here you go, Mr. Irie!
Thanks.
-Here you go.
-Thanks!
You're so thoughtful, Marina.
I do it out of habit, I guess.
So feminine!
So fake.
She never acts like this with us.
She's the type that changes
in front of men.
Thank you for waiting.
This is our famous sizzling steak.
Looks good!
Tomoko, you're so good with knives.
I bet you cook all the time.
I don't enjoy cooking.
I enjoy cutting meat.
That's why I chose nursing school.
So I can cut, cut, cut away!
But nurses don't use scalpels on people.
That's true.
Really?!
I'll never wield a scalpel?
So, I had a scalpel custom made
for nothing?
She seemed so angelic.
Never judge a book by its cover.
-Mr. Irie! You're too close!
-And you're heavy!
Heavy? Are you kidding?
He looks like he's having fun.
Letting pretty girls serve him!
It looks like your husband
forgot he was married.
He's always popular with girls.
Mr. Funatsu,
it's a good opportunity for you
to talk to some girls. Lighten up!
I have no interest in such things.
Don't be a prude!
Look! Cute girls left and right!
Mr. Funatsu!
Here you are! May I sit next to you?
I... suppose.
My name is Marina Shinagawa.
Nice to meet you.
I've always wanted to talk to you.
Do you have a hobby?
Reading medical books.
What do you do on your day off?
I read medical books.
-So, you never go out?
-Sometimes.
Where do you go?
I visit parasite museums
and mummies around the country.
I see.
See you later.
-Wait, wait, wait!
-What?
Stay a little longer. He's just shy.
Are you kidding? I like smart guys,
not mummies!
There she goes...
She's not right for you anyway.
Shall I introduce you to someone else?
How about that girl?
She looks like your type.
So? So? So?
Miss Marina.
I like Miss Marina.
But you acted
so disinterested just now!
I always act like that
in front of girls I like.
Feel my wildly beating heart.
Oh, my God!
Was it love at first sight, Mr. Funatsu?
Hey, Kotoko!
What now, Marina?
Mr. Funatsu will always be lacking,
compared to Mr. Irie.
He'll always be Number 2.
Damn it!
It's always the same!
Irie this and Irie that.
Irie has a good-for-nothing wife!
Listen, Marina Shinagawa!
I will beat Irie and become Number 1.
Take back what you just said
and go out with me!
-Did you hear me?!
-Okay. Calm down.
Keita Kamogari!
What?
You know...
I always wanted to tell you this.
Despite my appearance,
I'm three years older than you!
Three... Three! Got it?
So?
So...
show me a little respect!
You're always yelling at me.
That's cold!
What are you doing?!
It's cold. It spilled.
You spilled it, you mean.
I'm sorry.
Wipe me up.
Done.
You're clumsy and you never learn.
If you want to be respected,
act your age.
Huh? What did you say?
Ow. That hurts.
Hey.
Hey!
Don't fall asleep here.
Kotoko's fast asleep.
Ko-to-ko.
It's no use. She's dead to the world.
Shall we call Mr. Irie?
Never mind. I'll take her home.
I didn't drink, and I drove here.
But shouldn't we leave Kotoko
to her husband?
What for? He's having his own fun.
Did Kotoko fall asleep?
Mr. Irie! Yes, she did.
Sorry, I'll take her home.
Hey, Kotoko!
Let's go.
Kotoko, let's go home.
He said, "Let's go home!"
Never mind. I'll drive her home.
Who are you?
Keita Kamogari,
from the nursing school.
Your wife is always causing me trouble.
Sorry about that.
I'll get her home safely.
Why you don't go back
to your harem?
You have no interest in her.
Shut up.
Whether I'm interested in her
or not is none of your concern.
Stay out of it.
What...?
Shots!
Who cares about stupid shots?
I'll master it right away...
Are you up?
It's Naoki!
Let's go, Kotoko.
Okay!
You're such a baby.
Mr. Irie.
Kamogari...
Don't talk about Kotoko
as if she's yours.
What's come over you, Keita?
You were so confrontational.
I don't like him... Naoki Irie.
Naoki...
What?
Naoki!
She's talking in her sleep.
Shots...
Dreaming about shots?
Keita Kamogari...
Me again!
I'm cursed.
What are you talking about?
It's not a real shot.
She's going to use the fake arm.
Idiot!
It's a fake arm, but the hand
holding the needle is shaking.
You have no idea how scary that is.
Don't worry, it'll be fine!
I practiced a hundred times with a doll!
Leave it to me!
You have 15 minutes. Begin now.
Okay, first...
Pinch the arm and grab the muscle.
Okay.
Ow. That's my arm.
Sorry.
-Calm down.
-Right.
Okay. Ready?
Yeah.
Ow! Ouch!
-What are you doing?
-I poked myself.
You're not even wearing gloves.
Kotoko!
-Hey!
-Kotoko?
Kotoko!
Are you all right? Get up!
She's out cold.
I'm taking her to the health office.
-Thanks.
-Do you need help?
No. I can handle it.
Move!
Move it!
Out of my way!
Move!
Wasn't that Kotoko?
I wonder what happened.
And who was that?
Doctor! A patient!
No one's here.
She looks so peaceful.
Makes me want to faint.
You keep falling asleep on me.
What do you think you're doing?
You, again.
I haven't done anything.
Are you kidding me? With her?
It didn't look that way to me.
So, she fainted
and you carried her here?
Thanks for doing that. For her.
But I'm here now.
Go back to your training.
I was about to go anyway.
Kamogari.
I know that you're aware
that she and I are married.
Don't try...
anything with Kotoko.
I would be...
I just realized.
I'd take better care of Kotoko than you.
I'd love her more than you.
Is that right?
NEXT EPISODE
"A GENIUS AND JEALOUSY"
Naoki and I are going on a trip alone.
-I don't remember saying I'd go.
-Let's all go have fun!
Irie!
Naoki!
He's so nice.
And you're so cold!
You don't stand a chance!
Why don't you go home
with Kamogari, then?
Why did it turn out this way?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
I was serious when I said that.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2