Excuse me, madam.
Madam.
Something to drink?
Oh, yes.
-Are you okay?
-Yes. Excuse me.
We have coffee, Japanese tea,
and orange juice.
Then, coffee...
Coffee please!
Certainly, madam.
Here you are.
Why are you speaking English?
Oh, dear, I didn't know you're awake.
We're going to Okinawa,
You don't need English.
'Cause this is my first time flying.
When it comes to flights,
it's "Attention, please! Coffee or tea?"
You're carried away.
Of course I am. It's our honeymoon!
Yes, we're on our honeymoon...
to Okinawa!
And sitting here next to me...
I have dreamed of having
for a long time... Irie-kun!
What?
We really are married now.
I just realized it.
How many times you have
to look at those pictures?
I'm gonna take a nap.
Are you sleeping?
It's our honeymoon.
My mom's set up our wedding and
this honeymoon without asking me.
I'm tired.
Are you on honeymoon?
The girl who laughed at me earlier.
-Yes.
-So are we! Right?
Hi.
Oh, did your husband fall asleep?
Poor you, it's your
long-awaited honeymoon.
I'd never fall asleep
and leave Mari alone.
You have such a sweet husband.
'Cause Takumi is madly in love with me.
Madly in love...
The day Mari joined our company,
I felt, "She is it!"
A boring office romance.
What do you mean "boring?"
And... you are?
I'm, Kotoko. Iri...
I'm Kotoko Irie.
-Your husband proposed to you?
-No! Never! No way!
What?
For us, I'd say...
I was the one who tried
to hit him like crazy.
TONAN HIGH SCHOOL
ENTRANCE CEREMONY
It was love at first sight
all the way back
to the Entrance ceremony.
I love you.
I don't want it.
Please take it as your home.
I'm the eldest son, Naoki.
Nice to meet you.
Will you keep distance from me?
I hate stupid girls.
Kotoko.
What?
"You may not know me, but I know you."
"I was attracted by you giving a speech
at the entrance ceremony."
I'll...
I'll stop loving you.
I'll see if you can do that.
Serves you right.
Yuki! Yuki! Hold on!
Papa! Are you all right!?
I'll protect my dad's company.
This is Mr. Oizumi,
the chairman of Hokueisha.
How about having
a marriage interview?
I'll snatch Kotoko away from you.
I'll let you forget that bastard.
No! Stop! Irie-kun!
You love me!
You'll never love anyone but me.
How could you be so confident!?
Yeah, you're right! I can't help it!
But you don't even love me!
You don't even...
I love you so much.
Serves you right.
So...
My 6 year-long one-sided love
finally ended up with our marriage
and here we are.
You were quite patient, Kotoko.
Oh, my, what am I...
So you came from behind to win.
Yeah, maybe.
So you pushed him down
into the bed? Right on!
No way! We are yet to go
that far...that far...
He went to bed first last night
saying he's tired...
Wait, so you mean...
You're kidding!
You haven't slept with him yet?
I haven't seen a couple
like you guys before.
But... aren't you anxious?
What?
I would be shocked if my partner
wouldn't want me as a woman.
I'd come to think I'm not
attractive to my partner.
Well...
Are you guys okay? Please don't
end up being "Narita divorced."
It's not Narita. It's Haneda. My bad!
Narita... divorce...!?
I feel I'm a bit tired.
Takumi, give me a massage.
Yes, I'm willing to!
Na... Narita divorce...!?
How dare she says that to me
on my first day of honeymoon!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
What's up?
My sunglasses.
LOVE IN OKINAWA
Sunglasses?
I thought you're night-blind.
Night-blind people feel brightness to.
Let's see...
Wait till we get to the hotel.
I wanna wear them right now.
It doesn't open.
Yeah, right.
Gosh, maybe the lock is broken?
You don't wanna break that.
It's open, Irie-kun!
You wear that?
No! I never wear
this kind of swimsuit!
I wonder who would wear
this kind of showy stuff.
That's mine!
Is that... mine?
I'm so glad that we're staying
at the same hotel!
Why in the world do we have to stay
at the same hotel with this slut!?
Hey, why don't we have
some food together after this?
Irie-kun! Let's go to our room!
Excuse us, please.
So finally, we're just two of us.
Watch out!
I'm sorry! Are you all right?
Got hurt?
I'm fine.
Go... Minam?
Are you Go Mi Nam of the A. N. JELL?
Kang Shin-woo... Jeremy...?!
Yap, we are.
-I'm Go Mi Nam.
-Kang Shin-woo.
Jeremy.
Oh my gosh! It's A. N. JELL!
Popular band from Taiwan!
From Taiwan?
I'm a big fan of them!
Sorry for the trouble.
We're okay because
you stopped this quickly.
Please ask them why they're in Okinawa.
You do it.
But, I don't speak their language.
Come on.
Why are you guys in Okinawa?
To shoot a music video.
Okinawa is awesome!
What? What did they say?
They're here to shoot a music video.
Really! That's so cool!
Have a nice trip.
Bye-bye.
Best wishes.
Wow, thank you!
Bye-bye!
-Let's go.
-Gotcha!
Fantastic! How fantastic!
White beach and blue sky!
Okinawa! We're in Okinawa, Irie-kun!
Calm down.
What a gorgeous bed!
I can roll over and over!
Hey, look, Irie-kun!
Wait. Tonight I will be in this bed...
with Irie-kun...
I will be unified in love with Irie-kun.
Irie-kun...
Yeah?
I'll do my best to become
a good wife, so...
So, please don't give up on me.
You were caught up with
A. N. JELL a few minutes ago.
What?
Nothing.
I don't expect you much.
Just stay as you are.
Stay who you are.
Hello?
Hello? Naoki? It's me! Mari!
Naoki, Naoki! Kotoko!
Over here!
We kept seats for you!
How dare she repeats
his name like she's dating!
Naoki! Right here!
We got seats for you guys!
Hi.
We can drink here at the pool!
Naoki, let's go to order!
-Okay, then let me...
-Sure.
Please excuse her,
I guess she likes Naoki.
Hey Takumi! ...is it right?
What kind of disciplines
are you giving to your wife!?
If you know what's going on,
stop her! Aren't you her husband?
Yeah, but my love was one-sided
for a long time,
I barely got to her heart.
Why are you being so nervous!
You guys are married you forget?!
It's vice versa!
Stupid Kotoko,
it's funny you say that.
I think I just heard
a voice sounds like Yuki.
I guess those two get along well.
Maybe, we should make out, too!
She is clinging on Irie-kun!
Are you all right?
I will bring you a towel immediately.
What the heck!?
Hey, watch out!
Good work! Ms. Blond!
Mari, are you okay?
Are you okay, Mari?
Damn!
It was my mistake.
Wait a minute, those people...
...are from a foreign country!
Wow, so Naoki is a future doctor?
No, I'm just aspiring to be a doctor.
But you're aspiring, that's awesome.
I'm quite sure Irie-kun will soon
get into some medical school!
'Cause, no matter what,
he got 200 on IQ test!
I heard you two got married after
Kotoko's impetuous approach.
Impetuous...
Yeah, because Irie-kun is like one
who lives in another world.
You two are married, and
you still call him "Irie-kun."
-So you're still not that close to him.
-Mari!
Well, I've been used to this way
for years!
Just that much of drink.
Kotoko, we're back in our room.
Hey, Kotoko.
Honey, we're back in our room.
Can't help it...
Irie-kun...
I love you...
DAY 2
It's Shisa! So cute!
-Let's take a picture with this!!
-No way.
Let's ask somebody
to take a picture!
Let's see...
Excuse me, could you take
a picture of us?
Thank you! I beg your kindness!
Irie-kun!
Get more closer to each other!
Say, "Chinsuko!"
-Thank you very much!
-Okay?
Yes, this is great! Thank you!
I've seen those guys...
Oh, at the swimming pool!
They were at the swimming pool
yesterday! What a coincidence!
No wonder! This spot was
recommended on a guide book!
It was so much fun! I'm starving.
Let's eat!
Oh, what a coincidence!
Can we have lunch with you?
Excuse me!
-Having a good time today?
-We just saw the Eisa show.
Cool! We'll go see it after this!
Excited, Takumi?
Did you enjoy it?
Yes, we did!
Say, "Cheese!"
DAY 3
Wow! How colorful these fishes are!
Irie-kun, a coconut crab!
Do you think this tastes good?
Excuse me! Can I have this?
Let me take you to the second floor.
Naoki! This way!
Hurry, we got seats for you!
Hurry, Naoki!
DAY 4
Naoki!
Hurry, Naoki! This way!
Can you see me? Hurry up!
I'm waiting for you!
Naoki!
Why the heck does
she always gets in the way?!
DAY 5
Voila! This is the main-temple,
a Ryukyuan castle long ago.
1, 2, 3... 3 dragons!
I wonder why it's not Shisa!
A bright red castle!
Naoki, what's your favorite color?
DAY 6
Oh, my gosh...
Why didn't I notice...?
Today's our last day in Okinawa!
It's the last chance tonight.
We're heading back
to Tokyo tomorrow.
But, we haven't had any progress
in our relationship.
It's all because that couple
bothers us every day.
They invite us for some a drink
every night.
Same as mine.
So we got married around
the same time.
You have two lines of fate!
Another round!
I know I'm carelessly drinking
over my capacity.
Thanks to all that, we're still
far away from romance.
Please don't end up being
"Narita divorced."
What if we'll end it up with nothing?!
My dear Kotoko! I expect you a lot!
For mom's sake, and for my sake!
I'll never go back to Tokyo
without any progress!
Tonight!
We will definitely have
a true bridal night!
Wow, it's a whale shark! So huge!
Tonight, I will definitely...
Look, Irie-kun!
What a beautiful chapel!
Good smile both of you!
Okay, are you ready?
Say, "Cheese!"
Okay, let's take another one.
Looks good! Say, "Cheese!"
And another one. Say, "Cheese!"
Now, sir, please put your hand
gently on your wife's shoulder.
Looks great! Good smile, madam!
Sir, give me a smile! Smile, please!
Say, "Cheese!"
Lucky us, we could have
our photo without reservation.
It reminds me of
our wedding ceremony!
I'm never gonna do this again.
Thank you so much.
No problem. We were expecting
another couple for a photoshoot so.
A couple...?
I guess they're here!
This way, please.
You two were here?
We met again.
You know each other?
Yes.
Naoki you look so cool!
I bet it's 'cause you're tall!
Don't we look like a perfect match?
How about taking pictures
of Naoki and me?
No, I think not.
Kotoko, I'd lend you Takumi.
What do you think, Naoki?
Sorry, we need to go now.
Souvenirs, right?
Y... yes.
Let's go, Kotoko.
Yes.
Wait for me, Irie-kun!
What happened?
Please help Mari.
She said her stomach
has suddenly hurt.
Why don't you take her to hospital?
It's weekend,
and probably it's too late.
Then, call an ambulance!
She doesn't wanna make this serious.
It'll get better if I keep lying down.
Oh, it hurts!
Mari! Are you okay? Are you okay?
Naoki!
You said you wanna be a doctor, right?
Could you take a look?
No way! Though he aspires
to be a doctor, he is still...
Okay. I'll take a look.
-Does she have nausea?
-No.
-Fever?
-Not particularly.
Let me check your pulse.
Naoki, is Mari going to be okay?
Where does it hurt?
Let me see your stomach.
No, Irie-kun! Don't touch her!
Hey, I think we should call
an ambulance.
It depends on her condition.
Then, what about our dinner?
This is not the time for that!
No! Don't touch her, Irie-kun!
Don't touch another girl!
That's enough!
You married a guy
who's gonna be a doctor!
You better be aware of that.
Irie-kun.
Are you always gonna be that way
when I see patients?
I don't wanna deal with that.
If you don't understand,
I can't be with you anymore.
Naoki, you're going too far...
Kotoko!
You don't have to go after your wife?
Your wife's all right.
I assume she's got mild food poisoning.
Pharmacy is still open,
some stomach medicine will do it.
Thank you so much.
Takumi, go buy it for me.
Yeah, sure. I'll be back soon.
-You should go find your wife.
-Takumi, hurry up!
Yes, then...
So, I'm off.
Naoki, you have a cold heart.
Because you have your partner...Kotoko.
Or you don't love her...?
Don't you have a stomachache?
I made it up.
What?
'Cause I wanted to be alone
with you, Naoki.
I heard you guys haven't done
anything sexual yet.
Well, it's understandable.
You don't feel like it with Kotoko, right?
I fell in love with you
at the first sight.
I wish I had met you before she did.
Then, both of us didn't have
to marry a wrong partner.
It's not too late.
Shut up.
What?
Even if I'd encounter you 100 times,
I would ignore you every time!
What...
Do not compare yourself with Kotoko.
Oh, my, I forgot my wallet.
What happened, Mari?
Naoki seemed angry.
I'm not gonna forgive him.
He fooled me.
Mari?
I'll definitely break them up!
He didn't have to be that mean!
-Don't you dare!
-That's my word for it!
How dare you do that to me!
We're finished! We're over!
You're right!
We started off by my one-sided love!
But, now we're married,
we're together in the same place!
You're my wife!
Don't give your heart to the other guy!
Did you get it?
Yes.
I'm so terrible...
I feel so embarrassed,
I wanna kill myself.
Thought I understood Irie-kun's
ambition to become a doctor.
Where am I?
I guess I'm totally lost.
I don't remember how
and where I came in from.
I left my wallet at hotel.
Feels like I strayed
into a savage place
I'm gonna be kidnapped!
If I get kidnapped, maybe
I could never go back to Irie-kun!
Irie-kun, help me!
Irie-kun!
Irie-kun, I love you!
Narita divorce!! No!!
What is she doing?
Irie-kun!
I thought I will never see you again!
I thought you will never find me.
Everything is okay.
He thought you were a lost
elementary school student.
An elementary school student?
So, he is not a bad guy?
Anyway, apologize.
Thanks for coming.
Your scream was real loud.
'Cause...
Narita divorce... how classic.
or we say, Haneda divorce, right?
I'm sorry.
I was jealous.
Having being selfish,
I was such a scumbag.
You fool, I really worried about you.
Splendid!
I was right buying this
high-sensitive camera.
What a feeling of this chaotic
anger swirling inside of me...
was turning into something
warm and sweet like a candy.
It took so long to get here.
Yeah, but I was okay.
I was happy just staying
by your side.
I'm not okay.
If there was a way to measure
my happiness...
I must've been the happiest one
of all in this world today.
I'll never forget
what happened today.
Never.
Time flies in the blink of an eye...
I'm so sad. I already miss there.
We couldn't spend much time
alone together.
It tastes good!
Really?
Mari, your turn.
What happened to those two?
They are the ones
who put us in trouble!
It's good for them.
Well, you're right. But...
What?
Nothing.
Our stay was short,
but it brought us sweet memories.
Sorry for making you wait, Noriko.
Irie-kun and I finally
met your expectations.
-It's sweet.
-Tastes good.
That was fun!
Let's go again someday.
Yeah, someday.
Next time, we'll be all alone and...
Naoki-san!
Mr. Kanamori...
Welcome home, Mr. Irie.
And Mrs. Irie.
Mrs. Irie...!
What are you doing here?
I came to fetch you.
Fetch us?
What is it? Did something happen
at work while my dad was away?
Your father was away?
It's not for me to say.
Aren't we going home?
Where are we headed, Mr. Kanamori?
We'll be there shortly.
Shortly?
NEXT EPISODE
EP.02 "MY MARRIAGE STILL ON HOLD?!"
You're not officially married?!
I'm not ready to register our marriage.
I don't understand Naoki at all.
It's fine.
There must be some reason.
Tennis warrior Koto-rin!
What a useless bride.
Don't play with her heart!
What are you men thinking?
I don't want to see him.
This isn't a marriage!
Then leave.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2