I'm going to study hard
and when I graduate,
I want to be a nurse.
I know you'll say it's a job
that involves life and death.
But I really believe in this.
So...
I want to be a nurse.
What do you think?
If I tried to stop you,
you wouldn't listen.
So...
give it a try.
Kinnosuke...
I'm running out of time.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
EXCITING! MY FIRST DATE
You came.
Congratulations, Matsumoto.
Congratulations!
I heard you're transferring
to the nursing school.
How did you know?
It's a well-known fact.
You're still pursuing Naoki,
even in the medical field.
That makes it sound like
Naoki is my only motivation!
Isn't it?
You, too?
Well, I guess...
So, how did you do on the exam?
Ta-da!
"Congratulations." You passed?
I passed the highly competitive
nursing school examination!
That's right! I did it.
I passed the nursing school
entrance exam!
I don't think it's the best thing
for people but...
I guess congratulations
are in order.
I share your concerns, but...
Naoki!
Oh, well. Good luck, nurse.
You're graduating!
Take care!
Thank you! You too.
You're leaving us.
Bye-bye!
Satomi!
Jinko!
Are those your friends
bawling their eyes out?
Actually... neither of them
are graduating.
They flunked?
Satomi hardly attended an elective
class which turned out to have
strict attendance requirements.
Jinko turned in her brother's homework
instead of her dissertation by mistake.
It sounds unreal, but it's true.
So, they flunked together?
Yeah.
They both had job offers and
their boyfriends had graduated.
Your friends are incredible.
I can't bear to watch.
Don't act as if you're above it all.
You would have flunked, too.
Naoki!
Good thing she got into
the nursing school...
I thought I had just enough
credits to graduate
but I made a slight miscalculation.
You shouldn't be laughing.
I can't believe you passed the test.
You can't even count
your credits accurately.
Are you cut out to be a nurse?
I'll be more careful!
God...
All three of you
are unable to graduate.
It's not an easy task.
I'm actually impressed.
How rude.
At least you can all
stay in school together.
You got your dream job.
Yes. I'll be working in the IT industry.
My intention is to work hard
and find the best man out there.
I want to avenge myself.
Here comes your best man
carrying a bouquet of roses.
Out of the question!
Naoki.
Thanks to you, I enjoyed college life.
Become a good doctor, okay?
Thanks.
Miss Aihara.
I had fun with you, too.
Don't hold Naoki back, okay?
I hope you make a good wife.
Thank you! And good luck in IT!
See you.
Hey, Matsumoto!
Congratulations on
joining the ranks of society!
There's nothing between us now.
This is for you.
That's very nice of you,
but I have a party to attend.
Matsumoto! I'm going with you!
Matsumoto! Wait for me!
Kinnosuke will never
have feelings for me.
Kotoko... you're still his only love.
That's not true.
He's just embarrassed.
I'm sure he thinks about you.
Oh, Kotoko.
I...
have to return to England.
What?
But...
if Kinnosuke asked me to stay...
I...
Chris...
What? A birthday party?
You've never had one before!
So, we decided to throw you one.
But my birthday is December 29th.
That was three months ago.
Oh, yeah... You're right.
But it's the three-month anniversary
of your birthday!
That's so embarrassing.
I feel like a VIP.
That's it! VIP! VIP! VIP!
Really? Okay.
If you want to throw me a party,
I'd be glad to attend.
Yes!
Happy birthday, Kin-chan!
Well, well, well.
Thank you very much.
You're 22 years old!
A long journey. How time flies!
Which is it?
But in my case...
I only get better with time.
Not to brag, but...
Okay, it's time to light the candles.
Wow! What a huge cake!
Chris made it with TLC.
Oh, is that right?
Do you like it, Kinnosuke?
I'm not really into sweets.
And these English cakes
are kind of over the top.
Kin-chan!
Wow! What a feast!
-Right?
-Go on, eat up!
Thank you.
Delicious! Did you make the meat
and potatoes, Kotoko?
Nope. Chris made it.
Is it good, Kinnosuke?
I'm so happy!
Maybe it was a fluke.
Let me try the other dishes.
Here I go.
Oh, my God! This is terrible!
What is this?
See? This is more like it.
Kin-chan. I made that.
What?
You should appreciate Chris.
She dedicated these past six months
to becoming a traditional
Japanese girl for you.
Kinnosuke... here.
It's your birthday present. Open it.
Wow! A sweater!
It says, "Kin!"
And I made a matching one.
It says, "Kuri!"
I'm not that good at knitting,
so it took me a while, but...
I put my heart and soul into it.
They're amazing!
Maybe I'll try knitting one for Naoki.
Chris, teach me!
I'm not a good knitter!
But it's made with lots of love.
Did you hear that? Love!
Kin-chan's embarrassed.
Oh, my God!
Just say you're happy!
Shut up!
Kin-chan...?
I've said it a hundred times.
I love Kotoko. She's my only love.
I don't have any feelings for you.
Kinnosuke...
What is this?
Who would wear such a lame sweater?
You...
should hurry up
and go home to England!
Fine!
Chris...
Your wish will come true.
I'm going home.
What is she so mad about?
How stupid.
You're stupid!
Chris is leaving! Don't you care?
You're overreacting.
She's going home to England!
Next week!
Chris didn't want to leave.
She tried so hard to win your heart.
You may not feel the same way,
but you didn't have to be so hurtful!
You're terrible.
You all came.
Thanks!
You've taken such good care of me.
Chris!
Chris.
Take care!
Kotoko, I'll miss you.
What are you doing?
Sorry!
What's going on, Kinnosuke?
You're so fidgety today.
I know why!
Chris hasn't been here lately.
I guess she gave up on you.
We haven't seen her for a while.
She used to come every day.
I kind of miss her.
Huh?
Boss, aren't you a little
too old for her?
Idiot! She's like a daughter to me.
She...
She's leaving.
Leaving?
Boss!
Boss...
Sorry, but I need to go!
-Go where, Kinnosuke?
-Hey, Kinnosuke!
We're super busy today.
Hey! Put away the dishes!
Damn it.
Damn it!
I promise to write!
It's almost time.
Can't we wait just a little longer?
I think Kin-chan will be here soon.
It's okay, Kotoko. I'll be fine.
Kotoko, you really did a good job.
But what if
he's on the Narita Express now?
Just a little longer.
Thank you, Kotoko. But I give up.
But... But...
Thanks to Kinnosuke,
I had so much fun in Japan.
Will you tell him that?
Chris.
See you!
I'm going! Bye!
Chris!
But to be honest,
I was hoping he'd come.
I wanted to...
see him for one last time.
Bye-bye.
Chris.
He didn't come.
Let's go home.
Chris!
Kin-chan?
Kotoko? Where's Chris?
Kin-chan, Chris is...
In the bathroom?
Is she in the bathroom?
You came, Kin-chan.
So, you really do care.
But Chris is already...
Kotoko...
Sorry!
Kin-chan...
Chris!
Where are you?
I came for you!
Come back!
You're too late. She already left.
Really?
Chris!
Idiot.
Why didn't you wait for me?
I came here for you.
I wore this lame sweater for you.
I went all the way home to get it.
Look at me!
Kin-chan.
If he came a little earlier...
He's too late.
I'm starting...
to like you a little bit.
Stay in Japan, Chris.
Is that true?
Yes! So, come back!
Chris...
Hi, Kinnosuke.
If that is your wish.
Chris?
But, Chris, your plane.
Oh, the plane. I first got on...
but right before it took off,
I saw a glimpse of
Kinnosuke's face and...
Oh, Kinnosuke. I'm so happy!
You wore my sweater. I'm so happy!
I meant to return it to you.
Don't be silly.
Kinnosuke!
Wait, wait, wait. Chris!
Kotoko. Help me, Kotoko!
What's the problem?
That's enough! Get off me!
I think spring has arrived
for Kinnosuke.
What is this? A fashion show?
Actually, I'm going
on a date with Naoki!
Oh, how nice!
Come to think of it,
you've never been
on a real date with Naoki.
That's right.
Congratulations, Kotoko!
Before the nursing exam, Naoki said:
"If you pass the test,
I'll take you out on a date."
That's what he said!
Sin(theta) = minus the root of 16/25.
So, this becomes minus 4/5.
Therefore, the tangent(theta)...
What?
Naoki...
What is it?
If I pass the test,
will you take me on a date?
What are you thinking?
I'll be way more motivated
if there's a reward in sight.
And we've never been
on a real date.
We're always together.
But we've never gone out on a date.
We went to Odaiba.
I was following you and
Matsumoto on your date.
That's right! You took
Matsumoto on a date!
But not your beloved wife.
Isn't that strange?
I want to know what it's like
to go on a date with you!
Please, please...
All right! All right.
So, get back to your study.
Really?
Yes! I'm going to do it!
Memorize what?
I said...
I'm so proud of Naoki!
We've been so busy.
It's been hard to find a free day.
But it's tomorrow!
-Tomorrow?
-Yes!
So, you were choosing a date dress.
Yes!
How fun!
My heart is fluttering!
Mine, too!
Thank goodness you passed the test.
Naoki will be a doctor
and I will be a nurse.
I'm one step closer to my dream.
How wonderful!
You must have studied very hard.
It wasn't that bad. Actually...
it was quite easy.
Really?
Naoki!
Oh, Naoki.
Quite easy?
Well...
Welcome home, Naoki.
Naoki, speaking of our date...
Ta-da!
What is this?
I stayed up all night making this.
I hope our date tomorrow
will follow this itinerary.
All night? Good job, Kotoko!
Naoki is such a lucky guy.
You should be using your time
to study nursing instead.
Oh, my.
It's a secret. Top secret.
-Good morning, Naoki.
-Morning.
Naoki, you're still here?
Still here?
Your date is today.
What are you still doing here?
Kotoko already left!
We're supposed to meet at noon.
Oh, it's a little early, then.
Her head is in the clouds.
What is she thinking?
Leaving so early...
I don't get it.
Why should we meet somewhere
when we live in the same house?
Yes! The best spot!
Let me review the itinerary.
Eleven-thirty a.m.
Naoki arrives at our meeting spot
30 minutes ahead of time.
I'm way too early.
Naoki is waiting for me.
He looks a bit nervous.
Twelve-o-five p.m.
I arrive just a few minutes late!
Sorry. Did you wait long?
No, I just got here.
I'm really sorry.
You're here now.
That's all that matters.
Naoki.
This is it. This is it!
Okay!
I wish he'd hurry up.
He knows it's today, right?
He never picks up his phone.
What if something happened?
An accident? Oh, no!
If something happens to him, I'll...
What are you doing here?
Naoki!
We're meeting on the bridge, right?
Naoki, thank God you're safe!
I can't let on that I was
watching from here!
Did you just arrive?
What a coincidence!
Why...
did you leave the house
two hours early to hide here?
I'm busted.
It was you who told me to be here
at the bridge at noon.
I don't get it.
-Well...
-Let's go.
Not a very good start.
No! Our date is only beginning!
Our dream date. Let's go!
I prefer an action film.
I already bought our tickets.
Ta-da!
Eternal Love. It's supposed
to be so romantic!
Naoki...
Here are our seats.
Is he going to...
hold my hand?
Naoki...
Kotoko.
Wake up.
But, Naoki...
The movie's over.
Let's go.
I wanted to enjoy
the beautiful outdoors with you.
I heard that couples that
ride the boats in this park--
Let's ride the boat, Naoki!
Hurry!
Excuse me. Can we rent a boat?
That will be 400 yen.
-Okay.
-Wait a minute, Kotoko.
I'm going to buy some drinks.
Now?
We can drink them on the boat.
Sorry. I'll be right back.
Okay.
Naoki!
Where is Naoki? How far did he go?
Kazuhiko, what's wrong?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Kazuhiko... are you okay?
What's wrong? Kazuhiko!
-Kazuhiko...
-What's wrong?
My son... he suddenly...
Are you all right?
He can't breathe!
Can I loosen his buttons?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-Are you okay?
-Kazuhiko...
-Kotoko!
-Naoki!
What happened?
I don't know.
He started coughing
and couldn't stop.
Does your son have asthma?
I don't think so.
Let's lay him down on the bench.
He'll breathe easier
if he's sitting up.
Hold him up like this.
-Call an ambulance.
-Okay.
Can you suck on this?
Hello? A 5-year-old
is having trouble breathing.
You'll feel better.
Do you? Kazuhiko!
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
I want to play basketball next year.
You'll have to work hard, then.
Okay!
Thank you so much.
How is he?
The doctor is with him now.
His condition is stable.
I don't know how to thank you.
Not at all.
The doctor said it's a good thing
we brought him in quickly.
That's good...
What did he say it was?
He thinks it's bronchial asthma.
I see.
He's been coughing a lot lately.
I thought it was a cold...
Asthma is sometimes
triggered by a cold.
It's easy to control with medication.
It's a very treatable condition,
so, don't worry too much.
Oh... okay.
He's going to be a doctor.
Oh, is that why?
Thank you very much.
I was a bit shocked just now.
What?
You're usually so cool, but you
really empathized with his mom.
Of course.
I know, but...
But...
What?
You...
were like a real doctor.
Idiot.
There are a lot of sick kids,
aren't there?
Yeah.
But...
when you become a doctor,
you can help them.
It's not that easy.
When you become a doctor,
you'll save many children's lives.
You'd better hurry up.
You'd better become a nurse, too.
Don't worry! I'll be
a bona fide nurse in three years.
You have to pass a national exam
to become a nurse, you know.
Another test?
Wait, Naoki.
You were a pretty good nurse today.
They're already closed.
Yeah.
Oh, it's you!
Is it too late to rent a boat?
He saw everything, didn't he?
He let us take the boat
because we helped that boy.
Yeah.
This is a little different
from the date I imagined.
I had all these grand plans in my head
but it's no fun when things go
exactly as planned.
As long as I can be with you...
I'm happy.
What?
Didn't you know?
Couples who ride these boats
are fated to part ways.
What?
The goddess of this park...
is a jealous spirit that
likes to break couples up.
-Oh, my God!
-Don't stand up!
You mean you knew that?
What do you want to do?
We're on the boat already.
Why didn't you tell me
before we got on?
I would never have...
This is the kind of date
you envisioned, right?
You and me, on a boat.
Naoki, how did you...?
What else?
Holding hands at the movies.
Me arriving 30 minutes early.
Naoki, did you know everything?
I wonder.
I can't believe it!
When did you read my plan?
I'd never agree on a date
exactly as you planned it,
but you stayed up
all night planning it out.
The least I could do was
make part of it come true.
What do you want to do?
Believe in a stupid jinx
and get off the boat?
Naoki...
Or...?
NEXT EPISODE
EP.05 "EXTREME!? MATES IN WHITE COAT"
This is my first step
to becoming a nurse!
Nice to meet you.
You're not related to
that other "Irie" are you?
Member 1071 of the club.
I'm...
I'm Naoki Irie's wife!
Arrange a medical school mixer.
I'll take her home.
Who are you?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2