We're really married!
On your honeymoon?
Naoki-san!
What's with the "Naoki-san!"?
Sorry very much.
Those people look familiar...
Say "Cheese!"
Naoki-san!
Hurry, Naoki-san!
Why is she pestering us
day after day?
It hurts!
Where does it hurt?
Don't touch her, Naoki!
Don't touch another woman!
That's enough!
You married a man
that's going to become a doctor.
I'm so terrible...
I thought I understood Irie-kun's
ambition to become a doctor.
You're so cold.
I don't blame you,
with Kotoko as your wife.
I bet you don't even love her.
If I met you a hundred times,
I'd ignore you every single time!
I was worried about you.
That was fun!
Let's go again someday.
Yeah, someday.
Next time, we'll be all alone and...
Naoki-san!
Mr. Kanamori...
What are you doing here?
I came to fetch you.
Did something happen at work
while my dad was away?
Your father was away?
It's not for me to say.
Where are we going, Mr. Kanamori?
We'll be there shortly.
Please go in.
Where are we?
Please.
Welcome home!
Come in, Naoki!
You, too, Kotoko! Come in!
Thanks, Kanamori.
You must be exhausted from your trip.
-You, too, Mom.
-What?
What are you talking about?
This house...
This is our new home for both families!
Our old house
would have been too small
once the babies arrive.
So we took the plunge
and built a new one!
We'll be staying with the Irie's again.
Guess what. I have my own room!
It's too early to think about kids.
Anyways...
What is this?
How embarrassing! I love it!
Is this Okinawa? How did you...?
Still don't get it?
These people followed us to Okinawa.
What?!
The blond people...
...that were hugging!
Take it down.
I know how you feel, Naoki,
but it's a nice photo.
You're a good photographer, Mrs. Irie.
Thanks!
She took enough photos.
Take it down! What will people think?
They'll think you have a happy marriage.
This is the living room. Like it?
It's so spacious!
Look, Kotoko! Look!
Come on, everyone! This way!
Ta-da! This is the kitchen!
Come on in!
This is your bedroom.
What a gorgeous bed!
And this is the nursery.
Like it?
Lovely! Adorable!
It's true.
Me and my dream guy, Naoki Irie,
are married.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
MY MARRIAGE STILL ON HOLD?!
Okay...
I'm up...
It's my first day as a wife.
My beloved husband is next to me.
Naoki is still fast asleep.
From now on, I can see
his adorable face every morning...
I'm so happy!
And for my perfect husband,
I'll make the perfect breakfast!
A traditional Japanese breakfast
of miso soup with tofu, grilled fish
and a rolled egg omelet.
That sounds good.
Oh, yes. And fermented soy beans.
Then I'll see him to the door and...
Wait! What?
Oh, my God!
Good morning, Kotoko.
You didn't have to get up.
I... I'm sorry.
Never mind. It's fine.
First the wedding, then the honeymoon.
You must be exhausted.
If you know what I mean.
What an useless bride.
My poor brother
married a sloth.
He must be regretting it.
I'm sorry...
By the way, where is he?
Who knows? He's gone to work.
What? No way!
Naoki!
Thank God you're still here.
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
The alarm clock went off so early.
I was looking forward
to a nice breakfast.
Married life...
What a good wife I have.
I... I...
I promise. Tomorrow...
I'm kidding.
I don't expect anything from you.
That's kind of depressing...
I'm going.
Wait a minute, Naoki.
Aren't you forgetting
something important?
What?
A kiss when your new bride
sees you off!
How can I?
With a camera in my face?
Will you do it without the camera?
Give me a break!
We'll decide how to live our lives.
Leave us alone.
If you think you can do it all
on your own, you're mistaken.
You seem to be forgetting
the most important thing
in a new marriage.
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
We took care of that
on our honeymoon...
Registering your marriage!
You forgot, right?
I can't believe it.
You still haven't gone
to the ward office...
How could you have forgotten?
You mean it's not official?
We're not legally married?
That's right.
So my name is still Kotoko Aihara?
We have to go to the ward office
right away and...!
No need to panic, Kotoko.
Look! Registration forms!
And in case you make a mistake...
I got multiple copies!
I've already signed them as your witness.
Wow, so many... Thank you.
Thanks, but...
I'm not ready to register our marriage.
I have to think about it.
I'm putting it off for now.
B... but Naoki! Wait!
That's not acceptable!
Yo!
If it isn't the newlywed, Kotoko!
How's married life?
Don't fool around too much now...
Who thought you'd actually
rope Irie into marriage?
It's a miracle. There's hope
for me and Matsumoto!
You're no longer Kotoko Aihara.
You're Mrs. Irie.
I'm still...
...Aihara.
What was that?
I'm still Kotoko Aihara.
What? Still Kotoko Aihara?
You're so loud!
But didn't you get married?
I went to your wedding.
It's not registered yet.
Are you saying Irie doesn't
want to make it official?
I don't understand Naoki at all.
What are you men thinking?
Calm down, Aihara. No, Irie?
Aihara? Irie?
He wants to avoid a messy divorce.
Matsumoto.
He thinks of everything, doesn't he?
What?
In other words, you're on probation.
If he deems you unfit as a bride,
he'll leave you.
N... no way!
I guess that means
I still have a chance.
Right, Miss Aihara?
Hey... Hey, Matsumoto!
It's the reception desk.
There are people here
who claim to be your friends.
Who are they?
They won't say. They said
you'll know them when you see them.
Never mind, then.
Okay! I'll tell you!
It's Aoki from Tonan University.
Aoki? Who's Aoki?
Whatever.
Let them through.
I'm Aoki from the Anime Club.
I'm Akagi.
I'm Kimura.
Anime Club?
That's right.
What does the Anime Club want with me?
We were totally shocked!
You're the President-to-be of Pandai!
Right?
Actually, we created something
that will greatly benefit your firm!
A masterpiece 18 months in the making!
Wanna see it?
Not really.
But you'll want it so badly,
you can taste it!
Yeah! We heard you married
Kotoko Aihara.
What is it?
Wanna see it?
Fine. I'll take a look.
If you promise to leave afterwards.
Yes!
Tennis warrior Koto-rin!
What is this? A computer game?
Bingo!
You're brilliant!
See? Isn't Koto-rin adorable?
Not really.
-Koto-rin?
-Bingo!
Hello? Naoki?
Kotoko?
What happened? Busy at work?
I won't be coming home tonight.
I won't be coming home for a while.
NEXT NIGHT
He didn't come home the next night...
2 NIGHTS LATER
Or the next night...
3 NIGHTS LATER
Damn!
...and the next night...
He didn't come home.
Naoki...
There! Done!
Hi there, Naoki...
I love you!
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm here to see the secretary
to the president, Naoki Irie.
Let me check.
Thanks.
And you are?
His wi...
You can tell him it's Kotoko.
Miss Kotoko?
Yes.
How pitiful.
I can't even say I'm his wife.
You brought me lunch?
How thoughtful of you.
Come. Let me give you a hug.
Naoki!
You're such a good wife.
Let's go register our marriage.
Miss? Miss!
Yes?
I'm very sorry, but Mr. Irie
can't see you now.
Sorry. I can deliver your package
to him, though.
Yes, please.
Okay.
He refused to see you?
That's bad.
You haven't registered your marriage
and he hasn't been home in two weeks?
And he refused to see you?
It doesn't sound work-related to me.
Could it be... another woman?
Hold on, Jinko!
Is it true?
Kin-chan!
You haven't registered your marriage?
Irie hasn't been coming home?
Is he making you miserable?
Well...
I'm sure there are reasons.
Where are you going?
Are you kidding?
I'm going to clobber him!
Hold on, Kin-chan!
Irie! Where are you?
Where's Irie?
Come out, you!
Irie!
What's all this noise?
You... What are you doing here?
Why haven't you registered
your marriage?
Why aren't you going home?
Why are you avoiding her?
Are you preparing to break up with her?
I... was ready...
to keep my mouth shut
as long as she was happy.
I entrusted Kotoko to you.
Or so I thought!
But you're already making her cry!
Do what you want,
but don't play with her heart!
This is between Kotoko and me.
Stay out of it.
What?
How many times do you
have to make her cry?
Hey you! Cut it out!
Let go of me!
Wait! Wait!
Kotoko...
He's not at fault. You are!
You don't think of me as your wife!
I'm the only one who gets excited.
I'm the only one who feels insecure.
This isn't a marriage!
Then leave.
It's not official yet anyway.
How can you say that?
Hey! Kotoko!
I guess she needs me.
I win!
Kotoko!
Kotoko.
Aren't you supposed to be at home?
It's time to make dinner
for your husband.
It's fine.
Naoki isn't coming home.
There's nothing for me to do.
Kotoko...
Big-mouth Kinnosuke
told me what happened.
I'm not telling you not to fight.
But...
A man's workplace is a battlefield.
You go to his office and pick a fight
just because he's working hard
and not able to come home?
That's no reason
for a wife to demean her husband.
It's pitiful.
Stop thinking only of yourself.
Put yourself in his shoes.
Excuse me, boss, but Kotoko
is not the one to blame.
Kinnosuke!
It's Irie's fault.
You should have seen him.
I'm so disgusted.
Stay out of it! This is between
a man and his wife.
But boss!
Shut up and go back to work!
Come on, Kinnosuke.
Yes, sir.
But...
try to understand Kotoko's feelings, too.
Naoki must have his reasons.
You should believe in him.
If you don't, who will?
Hey, Aihara!
Stop daydreaming! Say something...
Say something, damn it!
I believe in him...
I believe in Naoki.
But I want to see him.
I want to see you, Naoki.
Kotoko!
Naoki!
Naoki? It's him!
Come here, Kotoko!
We need to go. Hurry!
Okay. But I need to change first.
Never mind. Come as you are. Hurry!
Okay!
What happened, Naoki?
Naoki...
Naoki?
Where are we going?
You'll see.
Everything is ready.
Okay. Let's get started.
Prepare to begin.
They're here, everyone.
Mr. Naoki Irie has arrived!
What?
First, a statement from Mr. Irie.
Kotoko, wait here.
This press conference
will be streamed live globally
over the Internet.
Hey! Kotoko!
Kotoko!
Dad!
I'm glad you made it in time.
What's going on? What is this?
Naoki hasn't told you anything?
Members of the media,
thank you for coming. I'm holding
this press conference to announce
Pandai's new online game.
I'm Naoki Irie, in charge of design.
Mr. Irie, you're a trendsetter
in this industry...
Naoki was designing an online game
that Pandai is going to distribute.
-An online game?
-Right.
It would normally take months...
No, over a year to complete.
But a small team put it together
in a matter of weeks.
It's quite an accomplishment.
He was up all night, every night
to complete it.
I'm surprised he's still standing.
He didn't wanna have to rush.
What's more,
I told him to contact you
and invite you here.
He insisted on going to get you...
himself!
-Really?
-Yes!
Naoki...
And now, I'd like to introduce
the design team and title character.
The title character was designed by
the Anime Club of Tonan University!
Whoa! It's the seniors!
We love you, Koto-rin!
-Koto-rin?
-What?
What's that?
The title of the new game is
"Tennis Warrior Koto-rin"!
Koto-rin...?
It's Koto-rin!
Oh, my God...
What? What is it?
And now, the inspiration
for Koto-rin herself!
Koto-rin a.k.a. Miss Kotoko!
It's Kotoko!
What? Kotoko?
What? It's Kotoko? Why?!
Miss Kotoko, please come forward.
Yes!
Thank you...
I'd like to introduce my wife,
Kotoko Irie.
Say something.
Okay...
I'm...
Kotoko.
I'm honored to be
the wife of this very smart man.
Thank you very much.
Was that weird?
Yes.
Kotoko.
Long time, no see.
Naoki!
It was embarrassing...
But I was really, really happy!
Are these new?
Sorry! I bought new ones.
Why?
I used the old ones to make this.
Because... you didn't
come home for a while.
I was lonely.
This is you.
Looking at it cheered me up.
I quit my job today.
Really?
I still have to train my successor
but I'll be back at school next month.
So you can study to be a doctor?
Finally.
That's great!
Do you think that game will be a hit?
Of course.
I ate your omelet,
complete with eggshells.
What? Eggshells?
I'm so sorry.
I missed you, Naoki.
Sweet dreams.
1 MONTH LATER
Look! Look!
Naoki's game is in the paper!
What?
Oh, my gosh! Koto-rin is a huge hit!
"Unprecedented level
of excitement and realism!"
He did it!
Let's go.
Okay!
That's right!
Naoki is going back to school today.
Have a nice day!
Thank you!
I need to make a stop first.
The ward office?
Naoki.
What's that?
Now it's your turn.
Okay!
Don't mess up.
Okay...
Hey.
Why did you write "Irie"?
You mean I'm not Kotoko Irie yet?
I should have known...
Mom is always prepared
for these things.
That's fine.
Can you fill in this part, Mrs. Irie?
Mrs... Irie?
This part here.
Mrs...?
Mrs...
Hey!
Now... I'm finally officially your wife.
I knew you'd be anxious,
but, as a man,
I wanted to get my dad's
company back on its feet
before we got married.
But then my mom
went ahead and arranged
the wedding reception and all.
It ended up taking a long time.
It was fine. Because I believed in you.
But you came barging
into my office with Kinnosuke.
That was...
But now you're my wife.
And now you're my husband, Naoki!
Wait for me, Naoki!
As of today, I'm finally Kotoko Irie!
NEXT EPISODE
EP.03 "HELLO BABY?!"
My name is... Christina Robbins.
I want to find my ideal boyfriend
in Japan!
No!
Kotoko, you're pregnant!
What?!
Naoki's mom is tweeting it
all over the place.
Grandpa?
Have you seen a doctor?
Not yet, but mom said...
Let's go.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2