Your basic training starts on Monday.
I have some handouts
from Tonan University Hospital.
I'll distribute them now. Here.
I hope there are some
good looking male patients.
What if I fall in love
with one of them?
Hurry!
At last! I wonder what kind
of patients we'll get!
I want Nurse Kotoko!
Leave it to me!
Naotaro, you have to cooperate.
But I... I...
Sounds good.
My...
You're like a granddaughter to me.
Oh, Grandma Naoko.
But it can't all be so good.
I don't want your pity!
I know I can't walk anymore.
Stupid!
Weakling! I know you can do it!
Nurse Kotoko...
We'll work hard...together.
Kotoko is in dreamland again.
Hey, Irie! Come back!
I'm sorry...
No daydreaming during training.
Yes.
The printouts I gave you
outline the case histories
of patients in the orthopedic department
to which you are assigned.
Read them over carefully
so you can manage them properly.
Yes!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
RIVALRY WITH GRANDMA TOYO
Good morning. I'm Head Nurse Hosoi.
Good morning.
Over the next two weeks,
these trainees will be training
in the orthopedic wing.
If you have any questions
ask these veteran nurses.
Yes...
Gosh! I'm so nervous.
We're going to make our rounds.
I'll introduce you to the patients.
Akiko.
Nurse Saeki. I'm going to rehab.
I'd like to introduce you to someone.
This is Kamogari.
He's training with us for two weeks.
I'm Keita Kamogari. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
This is a good opportunity.
May I take her to the rehab center?
Oh... well, please do.
Thank you.
Shall we go, Akiko?
Yes.
Are you cold?
I'm fine.
Shion, this is a trainee, Motoki Kikyo.
He's going to be with us for two weeks.
A guy?
He doesn't look like it. Whatever.
Shion? Where is Shion?
Mr. Aoki.
You're perfect.
You'll get used to it.
She'll make a great figurine.
I fell off my bike.
My face got all bloody.
Nurse Yamamoto,
may I change his bandages?
Oh... you want to try?
May I see
your open wounds?
Good morning, Mrs. Yoshida.
I brought a new trainee.
This is Ms. Irie.
She'll be helping us for two weeks.
My name is Kotoko Irie.
I'm pleased to meet you.
I can't be remembering
trainee's names.
I bet you can't even change a bed.
Not what I expected!
God!
That sassy little brat.
With a name like Shion?
All he does is eat snacks,
the little piggy.
Anime freaks are just as bad.
They talk about anime
for one hour straight.
You could teach a class
on anime in two weeks.
My patient is nice.
Mine, too.
What's wrong, Kotoko?
You look faint.
So...
...there's a patient, Mrs. Yoshida.
She's incredible.
She called me eight times
this morning alone!
Eight times?!
I massaged her shoulders,
back, arms, legs.
I made her a cup of tea.
And another. And another.
Then massaged her shoulders and back...
Ms. Irie. Good job this morning.
Thank you.
Mrs. Yoshida is at it again.
Oh... bullying the trainees.
Sorry you had to take all her calls.
She'd just yell at me if I went.
Watch out. The previous trainee
lost confidence and quit.
What? She quit?
I'm starved. What are you eating?
What are you eating, Irie?
Naoki...
It's Mr. Irie! He's so cool!
I examined a patient
with him the other day.
Oh my god, really?
See that guy?
He's an intern named Naoki Irie.
Isn't he handsome?
That's right. He's our idol.
He's still a student, but he's so smart.
He's more capable than
most of the doctors here.
Oh... you trainees.
Don't even try to get his attention.
Should you try to go over our heads,
you know what will happen.
Hey!
How did your training go?
Have you met Mrs. Yoshida yet?
Yeah.
I think you'll make a great pair.
No...
Well, good luck.
Wait a minute...
Hey! What was that?
Why was Mr. Irie talking to you?
Before me, even!
You just got here.
What are you to him?
Well...
Spit it out!
Explain yourself!
I...
Kotoko is Mr. lrie's wife.
What?!
I can empathize.
We felt the same way.
Are you kidding?
I heard he was married,
but to that plain Jane?
I don't get it.
I can't help it.
That's just fine.
I'm sure Mr. Irie's wife
is an exceptional nurse.
She won't need any guidance from us.
Should we leave Mrs. Yoshida
in Mrs. Irie's care?
That is...
- Great idea.
- Yes!
Let's eat! Let's eat!
Excuse me, nurses...
Kotoko... good luck!
Excuse me... excuse me!
Excuse me...
Thirty-five, 36...
You rang, Mrs. Yoshida?
You're late.
You should be here in 15 seconds!
But this is the 12th call!
What's wrong now?
Turn on the TV.
Your remote is right here.
My hand hurts.
I can't press the button.
It's a button. Just press it.
And you have two hands!
Use your other hand!
What?
You!
How can you be so cruel
to a bed-ridden, old lady?
You're full of energy!
You're just spoiled!
You're a terrible girl...
A demon... demon...
What is it? What happened?
Nurse Hosoi...
What is it, Mrs. Yoshida?
This trainee is terrible.
She yelled at this poor, old lady.
Ms. Irie! Come with me!
You'll be all right.
Five floors...
Why can't trainees use the elevator?
Two more floors to go...
Okay!
Here you go.
Not this one!
I said the one
with chocolate crunchies!
Where are my crunchies?
They don't sell crunchies. Who cares?
Chocolate is chocolate!
Are you stupid?
Chocolate without crunchies
isn't chocolate!
Get out of here! Buy me another one!
Now I made a mistake.
Please take care.
I'm back...
Good job, Ms. Irie.
Let me sit down...
There it is! Mrs. Yoshida's
22nd call of the day.
What?
Hurry up!
Yes...
What's wrong?
What now, Mrs. Yoshida?
Come over here. Hold this!
-Hold it up.
-Okay.
Today is a very important day.
Mrs. Yoshida, the doctor is here.
Oh, no!
Okay! Go!
Ready!
This...
-Leave it there!
-Yes.
Naoki...
I endure all these hardships
for moments like this...
Grandma Yoshida. How are you?
Are you feeling a little better?
Actually, I'm aching all over.
And this trainee is totally useless.
Go easy on her, okay?
May I check you?
Oh, but...
I prefer Dr. Irie.
Mrs. Yoshida!
But I've been waiting all day
for Dr. Irie to come.
Mrs. Yoshida...
I told you a hundred times.
Interns can't...
No! Not you!
I would never let you touch
this precious body.
Dr. Irie, please.
Does she...
I'll make a special exception.
Go ahead, Irie.
Yes.
She has a thing for Naoki?
Let me take your pulse.
Sure.
Doctor...
Is my pulse fast?
Yes. Maybe just a little.
It's because I'm thinking of you.
Then it must be temporary.
What is this conversation?
Mrs. Yoshida really likes Mr. Irie.
She's fine.
Good.
Mrs. Yoshida,
you know Mr. Irie is married
to this trainee.
Wha...?
You must be joking.
Don't kid an old lady.
How could Dr. Irie be married
to this foolish trainee?
Right?
It's true.
Now the bullying will never stop.
Was your name Kotoko?
Yes...
I'm sorry I was so hard on you.
Yes.
If Dr. Irie chose you,
you must be a good girl.
From now on,
I'll entrust my care to you!
Grandma... Yoshida!
Okay. Take care, Mrs. Yoshida.
Let me check your pulse next time.
Okay.
Kotoko.
Yes?
As a gesture of peace,
let's share a snack together.
Really, Grandma?
Just a moment. I'll make some tea.
Oh, no. Allow me...
Never mind! Sit down.
This is super delicious.
Go ahead! I'll be right back.
Grandma...
Looks good!
This is it...
The reason I became a nurse.
I'll never forget
this day!
Ms. Irie!
Nurse Hosoi! Look at this.
What in the world are you doing?
You take sweets away from a patient
and make her serve you tea!
-No, it's not...
-Don't lie!
Mrs. Yoshida just came crying to me.
She said you were bullying her!
Nurses should not receive gifts
from patients.
But look at you!
I've seen all kinds of trainees
in my time
but never someone like you!
Ms. Irie! Are you listening?
You did a great job in rehab today.
Thanks to you, Keita.
At this rate,
you'll be walking in no time.
Keep it up!
I'll do my best!
This isn't how it's supposed to be.
Grandma Toyo, what's this?
More to the right.
Go.
Grandma Toyo isn't my only nemesis.
You're too rough!
And you're doing it all wrong!
Follow the manual.
This nursing plan is terrible.
Rewrite it.
I'm sorry.
What part...
Think for yourself.
Remake the bed. This is too messy.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe you're a housewife.
The hospital is full of enemies.
Someone...take my blood pressure...
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
You're Akiko, right?
Shall I push you?
How long have you been here?
Two months.
You were in an accident, right?
You're Keita's patient.
Keita seems to be interested in rehab.
But I don't know when
I'll be able to walk again...
Maybe never...
Don't be so pessimistic!
Keita will be sad.
Kotoko...
How do you feel about Keita?
Keita?
No, nothing.
What is it? Tell me...
Stop it!
I'll be fine!
Maybe patients just don't like me.
Naoki!
A nice photo, right?
Why do you have a picture of him?
Lookie here.
I have plenty more.
No!
I don't even have a photo of Dr. Irie.
Can I reprint some of these?
No way.
I'm secretly admiring
Dr. Irie from afar.
What?
Why would I give one to his wife?
Dr. Irie!
Please... stop...
My chest...
My chest hurts.
What's wrong, Grandma Toyo?
Someone! Call a doctor!
Doctor! Doctor!
Have you seen a... A doctor!
What did you say? Just hurry!
Wait...
Grandma Toyo! I brought a doctor!
What happened? What's going on?
What are you all doing here?
Grandma... What about your chest?
Who said I had chest pain?
My heart aches for Dr. Irie
is what I said.
I didn't ask you to make
a huge deal out of it.
That's terrible...
I was so worried. You tricked me!
Are you calling me a liar?
You can't tell the difference between
a broken heart and chest pain?
And you call yourself a nurse?
I'm not a doctor. I'm a radiologist.
I'm sorry!
Can I leave now?
I'm really sorry.
You...
Ms. Irie, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
In an emergency,
you have to stay calm.
You should have taken her pulse
and checked her symptoms.
You said she tricked you?
Yes...
Come with me!
Yes, ma'am.
Hey.
Naoki...
You caused another panic?
I'm losing confidence.
I'm doing my best
but Grandma Toyo
doesn't appreciate it.
I actually got mad at her.
She doesn't take me seriously at all.
It's pitiful.
I'm exhausted...
Are you going to quit?
That's one solution.
I've been meaning to tell you that.
You want to be a nurse
because I'm going to be a doctor.
Maybe that's not enough of a reason.
Look at you. You're at your limit.
If it's too hard for you,
you should quit now.
Ms. Irie.
I want you to stay away from
Mrs. Yoshida's room from now on.
You can't let a patient control you.
You need to spend time
with other patients, too,
or you won't get any training.
It'll be easier for you.
She's a little too challenging
for a trainee.
But...
I don't want it to end like this.
Grandma Toyo.
Are you sleeping?
What?
Starting tomorrow...
I won't be in charge of you anymore.
I wanted to say goodbye.
I guess you and I just didn't get along.
I wonder why.
It makes me sad.
Sorry for being such a nuisance.
Can't you even look at me
to say goodbye?
Are you crying?
What is it...?
Oh no! You have a fever!
This is nothing...
Why didn't you call me
when you're feeling sick?
You call me for silly things,
but not when it counts!
Are you stupid?
I'll never be indebted to you.
Too late!
Wait, okay? I'll go call a doctor.
Wait for me!
She's coming down with pneumonia.
Give her oxygen.
Yes.
She may have actually
been in pain this morning.
If only I had taken her vitals
like Nurse Hosoi said...
Your mother isn't doing too well.
She has a high fever and...
Hello?
How was it?
They won't come if it's just a fever.
Really?
They said to call if it gets really bad.
I can't believe it! It's their mother!
That's terrible...
It's not uncommon.
People don't want to take care
of the elderly.
They treat hospitals
like senior homes.
They haven't come once
since you've been here, right?
You're right...
She gave you a hard time...
but maybe she's just lonely.
Veteran nurses know
how to handle her,
but you react to everything she says.
It was probably fun for her.
Nurse!
Can I stay with Mrs. Yoshida tonight?
Don't worry. I've already
prepped the night nurse.
-But...
-In any case...
Trainees can't do the night shift.
But!
Those are the rules.
-Nurse Saeki.
-Nurse Hosoi.
What did Mrs. Yoshida's family say?
They're not coming.
That's a problem.
If only there was someone,
like a friend...
We could ask them to stay with her.
Right?
A friend...
Does that mean...
Ms. Irie, what are you doing?
Training time is over.
Hurry up and change.
Yes, ma'am...
What you do after hours
is up to you.
Just don't let it interfere
with training tomorrow.
Excuse me!
Naoki.
How is she?
Her breathing is erratic.
Her fever is still high.
If only I could...
You did everything you could.
You have to trust in
her own strength to recover.
All you can do is stay by her side.
Okay.
I'm going home.
Thanks for dropping by.
Kotoko...
Hang in there.
Thanks.
What's wrong, Grandma Toyo?
Are you in pain?
That's right...
You have neuralgia.
I hope this helps.
It's no fun when you're so quiet.
Did you husband look like Naoki?
There aren't many people
who are as handsome...
Maybe we have the same taste
in men.
Get off me!
Wake up already!
What kind of nurse falls asleep
on a patient?
What about your fever?
What fever? I never had one.
It's down...
Your fever is down! Thank goodness!
Let go of me!
I'm so happy.
The other day...
I was rude to you. I'm sorry!
Were you? I forgot.
Marina told me that
Keita had feelings for you and...
And I...
Marina? That big-mouth.
Does that mean you like Keita?
What? I...
I see.
Keita is a nag, but he's a good guy.
I'm rooting for you!
Kotoko...
But what about your feelings
for Keita...
Oh, no.
Actually I'm married to Dr. Irie.
What? Really?
We just got to know each other, Shion!
It can't be helped.
Life is full of goodbyes.
Work hard and become
a good nurse, bro.
I'm not a bro! A sis, maybe!
Thank you, Mana-rin!
Mana-rin?
From now on, Mana-rin,
and Koto-rin will be our top
two figurines!
Sorry.
Please forget about me.
I'm sorry!
Thanks to you, my bandages
were removed,
but I fell down again.
I'm over here.
I'm so pitiful...
Don't worry.
But can I see your wounds again?
So I can remember them?
Akiko, today is my last day.
Thanks for everything.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
You'll be fine.
I'm sure you'll be able to walk again.
I have to say goodbye
to Grandma Toyo.
It was an eventful two weeks.
I'm kind of sad...
But I have to part with a smile!
Okay!
Grandma Toyo...
Wait a minute!
Why are you taking a photo with Naoki?
With his arm around you?
Shut up! I'm his special patient.
No fair!
Nurse Igarashi,
can you take one of me?
What? You're still in training!
-Please?
-No.
-Make an exception?
-No!
Let me borrow your camera then!
I think you chose a good one.
Right?
She's a little dense,
but she has guts.
Say, "cheese!"
NEXT EPISODE
EP.09 HERE COMES A CUTIE LITTLE VIXEN!
-Rika is going to live with us.
-Naoki!
What is this?
I would have reserved you
before I left for America.
I feel a little left out, that's all...
What a little nasty cutie honey.
You have a strong marital bond!
That's right!
I'm Naoki Irie's wife!
Naoki is a great kisser.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2