I'd like to introduce my wife,
Kotoko Irie.
MARRIAGE LICENSE APPLICATION
Oh!
Now it's your turn.
Okay!
Now, you're my wife.
It's our last semester
as college students.
9 MONTHS LATER
It's kind of sad.
I won't be at school
that much this term.
I'm pretty busy, too.
I work at a fashion magazine,
but all I do is run errands.
Our editorial department is
preparing for its year-end show.
I wish I could relish
the last few months of student life.
Both of you are so busy
with your internships.
I guess we won't see
too much of each other.
We have job offers,
but we're still on probation.
But not you, Kotoko.
Your husband will be a doctor
with lifetime employment!
-What a catch!
-So lucky!
Yeah...
Tonan University.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
HELLO BABY?!
Is this right?
Shouldn't I be looking for a job?
What do I want to do?
Excuse me.
I don't understand English. I'm sorry.
Oh, no!
You're welcome. I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry, too.
By the way, hello.
What is the Literature Department?
I wonder.
Oh, I made a mistake.
"Where" is the Literature Department?
Oh! Where!
I'm going there, too.
Together please, we go.
Oh, okay! Thank you!
She understood me!
My name is Christine Robbins.
I went from England.
No, came! I came from England.
I'm 19 years old.
Please call me Chris. Okay?
Oh, okay! Chris!
I came to Tonan University
to study for six months.
I'm here!
My name is Kotoko Irie.
I'm 21 years old.
Kotoko! Okay. Nice to meet you, Kotoko!
Same here!
TONAN UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL DEPARTMENT
Oh! Your darling is a doctor?
A fledgling doctor.
I wonder where he is.
Oh, well. I'll ask.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Do you know Irie, a senior here?
Irie? Naoki Irie?
Yes! The genius!
I knew it! He's famous.
And you are...?
His friend. Or should I say, his wife!
There! I said it!
You...?
Is something wrong?
I was curious to see what kind of girl
captured Irie's heart.
You're not exactly what I imagined.
What kind of chuckle was that?
Like something's stuck in his teeth.
How rude.
Kotoko?
Chris!
Is she an exchange student?
Oh, yes.
Hi, I'm Seiichi Funatsu.
I'm a medical student.
I'm one of the top students here.
If you don't mind, I'll show you around.
I would like to see
if my English skills are world class.
Thank you, but I'll pass.
You're not my type.
My standards are high.
You're not even close!
For that reason, I'll pass.
Not even close?
That bad?
Your standards are high.
What are you doing here, Kotoko?
Naoki!
What do you want?
Oh, yeah!
This is my classmate Chris.
She's an exchange student.
Chris, this is my husband, Naoki.
How do you do, Chris?
We were talking about going
to my dad's restaurant tonight.
Do you want to join us?
Is it okay if I join you?
What's wrong, Chris?
Shall I translate?
Is it okay if I join you, as well?
Oh!
Please do! Yeah! I'll eat you up.
Chris.
Is Naoki Chris' ideal boyfriend?
Maybe you should focus
on studying instead of playing.
I appreciate your concern.
But going out won't affect my grades.
You can rest assured in your 2 spot.
Wh--? What?
You won't be resting
on your laurels for long!
I'll beat you at the upcoming
dissertation presentation
and go to the conference!
Who's that?
Funatsu.
Never mind. Leave him alone.
I'll join you after I'm done.
Okay.
JAPANESE CUISINE
"AIHARA"
Looks delicious!
Eat up. Don't hold back.
Thank you, Kotoko papa.
Naoki is joining us later.
Okay.
Delicious!
Chris is adorable.
Sigh...
I have a bad feeling about this.
I finished prepping
for the banquet, boss.
Okay.
Kotoko! I missed you!
Naoki!
-Welcome.
-There he is!
Good evening.
Shoot. Naoki's here too, huh?
Hurry and break up. I beg of you.
Who's this blond?
Chris, I thought you were...
She's a quiet one.
Don't you speak Japanese?
Hello. I love Kotoko.
Kin-chan. This is Chris.
She's studying at Tonan for six months.
Chris, this is Kinnosuke Ikezawa.
Call him Kin-chan.
He used to be my classmate
but now he's a fabulous chef.
What's wrong, Chris?
Kotoko, I have to be honest.
I found my true love.
I never felt this way before.
Kotoko, you may not like
what I'm going to say.
You mean...
But please! Let me say it!
The man I love is...
No! Naoki is my husband!
Hey.
What?
No way.
Oh, Kinnosuke!
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Oh, my love, are you okay?
Thanks for helping us out, Naoki.
I hope I was of some help.
You saved the day.
That Kinnosuke. We're so busy
and he goes and faints.
He looks so happy.
Poor guy. It's my fault.
I can't believe he fainted from a kiss.
He looks so cute. Kinnosuke!
Do you really think so, Chris?
Of course! Is it a problem?
Oh, no! As long as it's
good for you, it's fine with me.
You're the problem, Kotoko.
I couldn't tell you
because you're my friend
but friends don't keep secrets
so I'll tell you.
You have bad taste in men.
I knew it when I saw Naoki.
You have no idea
what handsomeness means.
What? Are you kidding?
You're the one that has no idea!
Love is blind.
But I have perfect eyesight.
Kinnosuke is the best!
Kinnosuke wins the gold medal!
Kin-chan is so ugly!
Naoki is looking 100 times better!
That's because you have bad taste.
I think I'll get married to Kinnosuke.
I've decided. It's definite!
You're the one that's blind!
I can't get up in the middle of this.
A FEW WEEKS LATER
What?
You'll be gone for three days?
I'm going to a conference in Kobe.
What?
Does that mean your dissertation
was selected at the presentation?
-Yeah.
-Wow, that's great!
You're amazing, Naoki!
It's no big deal.
But it is! You're amazing.
You're on a different level.
Speaking of levels...
What about Funatsu?
Oh, him.
I object!
Why wasn't I chosen?
This is a conspiracy!
My dissertation was clearly superior!
Naoki, you must agree with me.
My essay was superior.
Be a man and admit it!
Okay.
Right?
I understand.
You finally admit it?
You really love staying at 2.
-Calm down!
-Irie!
Let go! Let go!
Irie! Let go!
-Don't touch me! Let go!
-Calm down!
Naoki is a genius.
It's a shame.
He'd make a good surgeon.
Is Funatsu that capable?
No one can wield a scalpel like he can.
Not even you?
I wonder...
He's that good, huh?
If only his personality
wasn't so warped.
I'll be so lonely
without you for three days.
It's just you and me again.
-What's wrong?
-Well...
My stomach's been
feeling funny since lunch.
You probably pigged out again.
You always think the worst.
You have a slight fever.
Open your mouth.
Lie down and pull up your shirt.
Are we playing doctor?
Feeling sexy?
We're not playing anything.
Hurry up.
Okay.
You'll keep me company
while he's away.
"I'm here for you."
Okay! I'll stay with you.
Jinko! Satomi! You came to visit me?
What a gorgeous room.
-How are you feeling?
-I'm still a little nauseous.
Naoki is gone anyways,
so I'm taking it easy.
I'm not surprised.
The way you attacked
that buffet yesterday?
Eight pieces of cake?
I didn't tell Naoki that part.
We brought fruits. Want some?
Thank you! I was craving
something refreshing!
-Is there grapefruit?
-Probably.
Did you just say grapefruit?
Yes.
You feel nauseous, right?
And you're craving something sour?
You have a slight fever?
How about your period?
I think it's been coming a bit late...
Oh, my God!
Kotoko. You're pregnant.
What?
I knew it, I knew it. Those symptoms!
Kotoko? Really?
I don't know. But...
Remember!
Do you remember having "relations?"
Well, I guess we could have...
I was waiting for this day!
Kotoko and Naoki's baby!
It's a dream come true.
But, Mom.
Listen to me, Kotoko.
I've had two children.
I know about these things!
Where is Naoki at a time like this?
What bad timing!
Oh my, God! I have to tell Dad!
And your dad!
I want to tell the entire world!
Calm down, Mrs. Irie!
Me? Pregnant?
Naoki and my baby? In my stomach?
Congratulations, Kotoko!
That's great! Congrats!
It doesn't feel real... Does it?
Are you in here, baby?
Kotoko!
Are you pregnant?
Is it true, Kotoko?
I haven't seen a doctor yet.
There's no doubt. I'm a veteran.
Go to the doctor with Naoki.
Right, grandpas?
Grandpa...?
Grandpa.
Congratulations, Kotoko.
Congrats.
Congratulations, Kotoko!
Please take care of yourself.
Hello, Miss Aihara.
Matsumoto.
I heard you're pregnant.
Congratulations.
Who told you?
Didn't you know?
Naoki's mom is tweeting it
all over the place.
What?
Now you have a legitimate excuse
to withdraw from academic life.
Good luck. Guess what.
You're full of surprises!
See you.
The tweet about the pregnancy
is spread worldwide.
It's not a joke.
Even the professor
congratulated me. In class!
I don't even feel pregnant.
I don't know what to say.
Why? It's happy news.
Yeah.
Look how tiny these are.
This is a birdie print.
Diaper covers are
so much cuter nowadays.
And look at this! Angel wings!
How adorable!
Mom, there's so much pink.
Of course! Because I want a girl!
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
I'm home! This is heavy!
Right this way, please.
Kotoko, look at this!
I know it's a little premature, but...
I couldn't help myself. Baby stuff!
You too, Dad?
You too, Mom? What a coincidence!
Thank you for your help.
Look! Look!
This is a car. Vroom, vroom!
This is a plane. Whoosh!
Dad, this all looks like boy stuff.
Well, I guess.
It's our first grandchild.
It has to be a son.
Are you kidding?
It'll be a girl, of course!
A boy.
No, a girl.
A grandson first.
No, a girl!
-A boy!
-It has to be a girl.
-I'm sure it's a boy.
-But I want a girl.
Look at them, all worked up.
-A boy.
-No, a girl.
-Boy.
-I said a girl!
Kotoko!
Eat this. It's from my restaurant.
A special congratulatory
feast for the baby.
Eat it!
Dad.
-Don't hold back. Eat!
-But...
I forgot the chopsticks!
I think it's a little early...
I'm starting to feel pregnant.
Me and Naoki's baby...
I'm sure it'll be adorable.
How will Naoki react
when he comes home tomorrow?
Will he be happy?
TO NAOKI, RING THE BELL TWICE.
FROM MOM
-There he is!
-It's him!
-Hurry!
-Okay.
You, too, Kotoko.
Congratulations!
What is this commotion about?
Want to know, Naoki?
I would love to.
Kotoko, go ahead. Tell him.
Welcome home.
Thanks.
You said "um" three times.
Okay.
Oh, sorry.
I think I'm...
What did you say?
I think I'm pregnant.
Yes!
Are you sure?
Probably.
-Have you seen a doctor?
-Not yet, but Mom said...
Let's go.
Go where?
HOSHIGAOKA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Aren't you embarrassed
to be in a place like this?
No.
I'm going to be a doctor.
The smell of hospital is rather calming.
Naoki...
What did you think when
you first heard about the baby?
Mrs. Kotoko Irie? Please come in.
Yes!
I'm going.
I'm sorry! Really sorry!
So you're not pregnant after all.
No, I'm not. I'm sorry!
I made a big, big mistake.
The doctor said it was just indigestion,
and the period will start soon.
God.
You should have checked
with a doctor first.
I'm sure my mom
blew things out of proportion.
But I made her so hopeful.
If you're not pregnant,
you're not pregnant.
What else can you say?
But...
I can't believe it wasn't a baby.
What's wrong?
Are you depressed?
Naoki.
You'll catch a cold.
I'm fine.
My stomach is weak,
but my body is strong.
But I'm stupid.
You're right.
You're supposed to disagree!
How can I disagree?
Naoki...
I like looking at the sky with you.
I hope we'll always
look at things together.
Yeah.
I've...
...been thinking
about this for a while.
I know I take things
too lightly sometimes.
I don't even know if I deserve
to do something like this.
Do what?
I...
...was thinking about
what I wanted to do most.
You may think it's a stupid idea but...
I...
What I want to do most
is to help you do your job.
In other words, become a nurse.
After seeing the doctor
and nurse today,
I'm now so sure.
I'm going to study hard
and when I graduate,
I want to be a nurse.
I know you'll say it's a job
that involves life and death.
But I really believe in this.
So...
I want to be a nurse.
What do you think?
What do I think?
I hope you realize that
people's lives will be in your hands.
One mistake could be fatal.
I know. I thought about that.
It's not like working part-time.
It's a big decision.
I know! I'm not taking it lightly.
Doctors and nurses
have to want to help people.
Do you really want to do that?
I want to help you!
I want to be useful to you!
If I become a nurse and help patients,
I can help you with your work, right?
Then, I'll do whatever
it takes to help patients.
This one thing I can assure you
that I really want to do!
You're incredible.
Naoki?
If I tried to stop you,
you wouldn't listen.
So...
Give it a try.
Naoki...
You'll have to transfer
to the nursing course first.
If you pass the exam,
then we're talking.
The transfer exam...
So I have to pass the exam...
Of course.
Okay! I'll do it!
At the hospital today,
you asked me what I thought
when you told me you were pregnant.
Yeah.
And when I came home,
you first told me you were pregnant...
...to be honest,
my mind went totally blank.
But at the hospital,
I was thinking while
you were with doctor for checkup.
I did have a feeling that you weren't.
But if
you really were,
in those few, short minutes,
I felt like a parent.
How did it feel to be a dad?
I liked it.
Me, too.
I kind of
want a baby now.
Should we make one?
Naoki...
Me, too.
For the short time that Naoki's baby
was in my heart,
I was the happiest girl in the world.
So,
one day,
I hope I'll see you again.
Our baby!
I don't understand this at all.
Kotoko, let's go.
Naoki!
I'm stuck here. Can you help me out?
Why me? I thought you were
going to manage on your own.
Let's go.
Just a little!
A little.
I'm busy, too.
Why don't you get it?
I told you about it just seconds ago.
Did you?
Apply this formula here!
What formula?
Naoki...?
You have to think for yourself.
What?
You look cute when you're mad.
Unbelievable...
That's cute, too!
Stupid!
Sorry.
Time passed as he scolded me
day after day.
TONAN UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF NURSING
TRANSFER TEST SITE
I'm so nervous.
Nerves won't help you at this point.
Forget about it.
I know, but...
What I'm worried about is...
What?
...whether or not you'll
remember your ID number.
Of course I'll remember that!
Oh!
Oh, my God! My ID card!
You left it on your desk.
Thank goodness.
Are you going to be all right?
Of course! I'm a good test taker.
Leave it to me!
Naoki.
I love you.
Okay!
Let's go for a drink.
My treat tonight.
Really? Thanks!
Kinnosuke.
I was waiting for you. Let's go home.
Chris!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
My heart still belongs to Kotoko.
I can't change how I feel
just because she got married.
Anyways, you're a young lady.
You shouldn't be out
by yourself at night. It's dangerous!
I know but...
You're such a pain. Just this once...
Sorry Chris!
Kinnosuke is busy tonight.
Let's go drink.
Let's go, Kinnosuke! Let's drink!
See? I'm busy tonight.
Kinnosuke...
Stop being a pest!
Be careful and go straight home.
Kinnosuke!
Yes!
Kinnosuke...
I'm running out of time.
Happy birthday, Kin-chan!
NEXT EPISODE
EP. 04 "EXCITING! MY FIRST DATE"
-I have to go back to England.
-Don't go, Chris.
-I wanted to see you one more time.
-Damn it!
"If you pass the transfer exam,
I'll take you on a date."
That's what he said.
Couples who ride these boats
are fated to part ways.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
What do you want to do?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2