Naoki.
Oh yeah.
He's gone.
How are you, Naoki?
Have you adjusted to life in Kobe?
Congratulations, Naoki!
You passed the National Medical
Practitioner's Qualifying Exam.
It's not a bad offer. Think about it.
I'm thinking of working
at a hospital in Kobe.
You should stay.
I'll go on my own.
You should stay here
and continue your studies.
I...
I'll become a nurse in one year.
Then I'll come to Kobe.
I promise!
So...
Wait for me.
You can do it, Naoki!
It's been 2 months since
you left for Kobe alone.
You can do it, Kotoko.
We...
can do it.
I...
don't think...
I can make it.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
...AND LOVE IN KOBE
You've really been spacing out lately.
Way more than usual, to be exact.
Are you and Naoki all right?
We're doing great!
Of course we are.
She's getting teary-eyed!
This is pretty severe.
Why don't you just go see him?
Or else we'll be the ones to suffer!
I'm fine! Naoki and I
share a strong marital bond.
Without their wives around,
men feel like they're single again,
and spread their wings.
He is a man, after all.
If a beautiful nurse or patient
made a move on him
he probably wouldn't mind.
If you won't go to Kobe
maybe I should go and make a move.
Don't say that.
I said, we're fine!
They're terrible! All terrible.
I'm desperately trying to suppress
my overwhelming desire
to see him.
While they just chat about
everything I'm trying to forget.
Of course, I want to
see Naoki
and kiss him and have him
hold me tight.
No, that would be too much to ask.
I just want to catch
a glimpse from afar.
To see him.
Just a glimpse from afar.
That's right!
I did it...! How bold of me.
But just one glimpse from afar.
If it's just a glimpse.
I haven't broken my vow.
Because...
Because I...
I need to recharge myself!
So this
is where Naoki lives!
I'm breathing the same air.
Dr. Irie!
Dr. Nomaguchi wants
to speak with you.
He's in the outpatient
consulting room.
-Thanks.
-Excuse me.
There you are! Naoki!
I'm feeling more energized
by the minute.
Now I can return to Tokyo and...
It's Dr. Irie!
I swear, he's such a hottie!
The hottest intern, for sure!
I wonder if he's married.
Yes, his wife is right here.
I heard he's single.
But he's so eligible.
He probably doesn't need a girlfriend.
Hey...
Maybe I'll make a move.
Impossible. Too much competition.
I know of at least 10 girls
who are after him.
So I'd be 11.
Oh my God.
It's fine.
This happened all the time in Tokyo.
Maybe I should go home
while I'm still recharged.
Move it!
You're standing there like an idiot!
Who is this girl? She sounds like
a Kobe-version of Yuki.
I have to be firm with kids like her!
You should apologize
when you bump into someone.
Please apologize.
Idiot!
The little brat!
Mom. She looks like a snake!
Nami!
I'm sorry. She has such a foul mouth.
Her mom is so young and pretty.
Go!
Sorry I called you a snake.
How adorable. Never mind.
You look more like a clown.
Nami!
Exactly like a clown. Exactly!
Wait! Don't run.
It's Dr. Irie!
No running in hospitals, Nami.
Yes doctor.
You know who I just saw?
A lady who looked just like a clown.
A lady who looked like a clown?
I would've liked to see that.
I wonder where she went?
Hello, doctor.
Hello. You're here today.
What? Do they know Naoki?
What are you doing, Nami?
I'm sorry, doctor.
She's such a rascal.
Mom takes forever with her make-up
whenever she's going to see you.
What are you talking about?
For real! Mommy's in love with Dr. Irie!
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Irie. Do you have time
to see me today?
Of course.
Five p.m. at the Central Park, then.
Okay.
What?
Another date with my mom, Dr. Irie?
I guess.
Naoki.
It's getting dark. Why...?
What am I doing here? This is pitiful.
Dr. Irie's late.
But I have to find out what's
going on between them.
I can't go home yet!
Here he comes!
-Doctor.
-It's Dr. Irie!
Sorry I'm late.
Thanks for coming.
Naoki.
Let's go on the slide, Dr. Irie!
Nami!
It's right over there.
Nami, go buy some juice.
I guess I'm a third wheel.
I'll leave you two alone.
How rude.
Don't leave them alone!
What's happening here?
What? This must be
some kind of mistake. Right?
Naoki.
Found you!
Dr. Irie! Over here!
Hurry! The clown lady..
Be quiet! He'll see me!
Kotoko.
What are you doing?
Oh, no!
The mother and daughter
are named Shiina.
The daughter, Nami, is my patient.
I'm not her attending doctor, but...
She seems so healthy.
It may seem that way now, but...
She has a congenital heart disease.
She's already had strokes in the past.
Her heart...
She had one surgery
when she was 5.
But the heart is a complex organ.
She needed another surgery
once she got a little older.
Her attending doctor and I
think that now is the best time.
But...
Nami lost her father two years ago.
Nami is scared that...
this surgery might take her life as well.
Her mom is worried, too.
I was trying to advise them ...
I see. I...
Wait. Are you going to
be a pediatrician?
Didn't you know?
No, I didn't.
I thought you were going
to be a surgeon.
I want to study pediatrics.
This hospital is really
excelling in that area.
At first, I was considering
being a surgeon, but...
What do I really want to do?
Why did I want to become a doctor?
When I asked myself that...
the answer came quite easily.
The reason you wanted
to become a doctor?
Never mind. It's nothing.
What? What? What?
It's a secret. Let's go to sleep.
I want to know! Please!
Good night.
Naoki, a pediatrician.
Yes.
Sounds good!
I'm going.
Sorry I can't see you off.
I'll be fine. I'm totally energized.
I'm sure everyone is worried about me.
Good luck on your internship.
It's the clown lady!
She's with Dr. Irie again!
Were you together since yesterday?
Nami.
What is the clown lady to you,
Dr. Irie?
Nami!
I highly doubt it, but I have to ask.
Is she your girlfriend?
I wouldn't say girlfriend.
Nami. Don't be rude.
She's not.
I knew it! I knew that was impossible.
Watch what you say!
I'm really sorry.
She's my wife.
No.
It's true.
It's not true. I don't believe it.
Nami.
Because...
You're going to marry my mom!
My mom is way prettier.
She's a super cook.
And...
Nami.
I can't do that.
Stupid!
Nami, don't run!
Nami!
Nami?
Nami
must be scared. Her dad died
and now she's sick, too.
That's why she wishes
you were her dad.
She looks up to you.
Don't worry. The surgery is in 3 days.
I'll convince here before then.
I'll do whatever I can, too.
Me, too! Leave it to me, Mom!
I'll convince Nami to have the surgery!
What are you talking about?
Aren't you going home?
I can't leave at a time like this!
You should go home.
But I'm partly responsible!
You're too direct when you
talk to little kids, Naoki.
You have to take their feelings
into consideration.
Mrs. Shiina, don't worry!
I'm going to be a nurse.
I decided yesterday that
I'm going to be a pediatric nurse!
You can't do that.
Why don't we give it a try?
Yes!
The situation calls
for desperate measures.
Yes! I am very desperate!
That's not what she meant.
Over the next 3 days, I'll focus all
my energy on convincing Nami!
I want her to get better
as soon as possible
and give up on marrying Naoki!
Tadaa! I'm here to visit...
Nami?
Wrong person.
What are you doing here?
Nami!
I thought I'd bring you some flowers.
But I got the wrong patient.
Do you like flowers?
No!
-But I brought them.
-I said no!
I love roses, but...
Here again?
Here again.
That's a fox.
It's not a dog?
No! A dog
barks like this.
How?
This is how you make a barking dog.
I ended up staying in Kobe.
Two days passed
with no progress whatsoever.
It's you again.
I bought some sweets.
Let's eat them together!
Are you ready to have surgery
and get better?
Are you ready to break up
with Dr. Irie?
Sorry, no can do.
What's with the accent?
I can't believe you got
Dr. Irie to marry you.
I'll give you credit for that.
Well he's only human.
He couldn't resist my charms, I guess.
I take it back.
Give me back that credit.
I'm kidding! Well...
It was a long hard road
to win Naoki's heart.
I bet it was.
It was love at first sight in 10th grade.
A confession of love in 12th grade.
A lot happened and we ended up
moving in with his family.
What? That's too easy! No fair!
I guess you can call it fate.
Fate...
Our love just gradually blossomed
after that.
But you must have had rivals.
Dr. Irie must have been popular.
Yes. Fierce rivals.
But all along, I sent
powerful laser beams of love
in his direction.
No one could compete with that!
That must have turned people off.
But I'm confident that
I love Naoki more than anyone else!
When you get a little older,
you'll fall in love with a handsome guy.
You'll have to get stronger
so you can persevere, like I did!
Then you'll find a boyfriend
like Naoki, too.
Nami.
You're using your mom as a decoy.
You're the one that's in love
with Naoki, aren't you?
What are you saying?
I'm doing it for my mom.
That's okay!
Naoki is like Superman.
He'll always come to the rescue.
He's an intern, but everyone knows
of his superpowers.
He'll come to your rescue, too.
You believe in him, don't you Nami?
Yeah
But even if I have the surgery
and get better...
Dr. Irie is still your husband.
And I'm sure you'll never give him up.
Isn't there someone else
that looks just like Dr. Irie?
That would give me hope.
Nami!
I have an idea.
You'll have the surgery? Really?
Yes! I'll go for it!
Really?
That's good!
Good girl, Nami. Thanks.
Okay! Leave it to Dr. Irie and me!
Right, Dr. Irie?
Yes.
What made you change your mind?
She promised me
that after my surgery...
Right?
Right!
What are you scheming now?
What? Me? Nothing.
It's our little secret!
Yup ...
Thank you so much.
We'll start as soon as we're ready.
I don't know what you did,
but thanks.
Dr. Irie.
What? Are you scared?
Don't worry. It will be over
before you know it.
I'm not scared at all.
Because I trust you, Dr. Irie.
Thanks.
Why did you want
to become a doctor?
When I was struggling,
unable to decide what I should do,
someone told me I should
become a doctor.
I thought, "Maybe so..."
Was it her?
I'm sure she doesn't even
remember it.
Is Nami.
She's fine!
Thank you!
Thank God.
Sorry I broke my vow.
But I'm well suited to be
a pediatric nurse, don't you think?
Oh, yeah.
Nami asked me to give you this.
Nami! How is she doing?
Great. Kids are so resilient.
That's good.
What did she write?
"Kotoko. I'm getting
stronger and stronger every day.
I'll see you in Tokyo soon.
If you break your promise,
I'll kill you.
Nami.
Scary.
What did you promise her?
Well...
What? Tell me.
Actually...
You promised to set her up with Yuki?!
But! But...
She wanted someone just like you,
but I wasn't about to give you up.
Nami said, "I'll have the sugery, then."
So...
I thought, "Yes!" and...
then it was too late to turn back...
And...
You promised her that?
Idiot! You liar!
How can you make promises
that you can't keep?
What am I going to say to Nami?
Well, so...
I thought the genius Naoki
would think of a plan ...
I have no plan.
What about Konomi?
You set her up with Yuki, too!
I know. I feel awful about that.
But I thought Nami
would forget by now ...
This isn't how I wanted to part.
See you.
Thanks for seeing me off.
Why do I always, always
mess things up.
Pass the National Exams in one shot.
Naoki!
I...
I'll do my best!
Wait for me, Naoki.
I'll become the best nurse in Japan!
A nurse worthy to work by your side!
The seasons came and went.
Summer passed.
Then autumn passed.
Is the long, long winter
ever going to pass?
Okay!
2 WEEKS LATER
NATIONAL EXAMINATION RESULTS
NATIONAL NURSING EXAMINATION
RESULTS
It's 2:00 p.m.
Hurry up, Kotoko!
No! I can't do it!
Hey.
Hey, Kotoko!
It will be fine, Kotoko.
You studied so hard.
But mom, my test ID was 794.
That stands for "cry." It's bad luck!
Really? Oh, my.
Okay. 794.
I'll look for you.
I passed!
Me too!
Moto-chan, Marina, Keita
and Tomoko.
You all passed.
I passed!
Yes!
Congratulations!
You did it, Kotoko! By miracle
or by coincidence, you passed!
It's a miracle! Kotoko passed the
National Nursing Exam in one shot!
Are you sure Naoki didn't
take the test for you?
You're so mean!
But you'd better study five more years.
For the patients' sake.
-You have a point.
-We're in sync!
Dads! You, too?
But...
Now, we're all nurses!
Yeah.
I did it!
Let's celebrate!
Yes!
The long winter is finally over.
And spring finally arrived at my doorstep.
But...
This is a voicemail box.
After the beep, leave your name
and a brief message...
He's not picking up!
Why?
Are you on night duty?
I passed the Nursing Exam!
I don't want to leave that on voicemail.
Right.
I'll go to Kobe and...
tell him myself. Yes!
Will you be okay, Kotoko?
Do you remember the way?
No worries!
Naoki, I want you to be the first
to see me
as a nurse!
It's cold.
Why is this happening to me?
I made it on the last train, but ...
I have no idea where I am.
I don't have a map or a cell phone,
so I can't call him.
It's cold.
Is this really happening?
Oh, well.
I guess I'll be like
that drunken old man.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm not used to this kind of thing.
I don't know the rules ...
This may be an imposition,
but can I sleep here tonight?
I'm sorry if I'm bothering you.
I've never slept outdoors before.
Don't mind my clothes.
I'm not into cosplay or anything.
There's a story behind this.
A long story.
Can I tell you my story?
You can go to sleep.
I'll just talk by myself.
My husband
is a brilliant doctor working
at a hospital here in Kobe.
I've been studying and studying to be
a nurse in Tokyo. And finally, today...
Now it's yesterday...
I passed the National Nursing Exam!
And I wanted to tell Nao--
My husband in person so
I jumped on a bullet train to Kobe.
I wanted to surprise him,
so I wore this nurse's uniform.
But someone got sick on the train
so I got off at Shin-Osaka
and helped him find an ambulance.
By then, the train had left
and my coat was still on it
along with my cell phone and map.
I shook it off and got on the next train,
but it didn't stop at Shin-Kobe.
It's like a nightmare.
Hey!
You don't have to laugh. I...
That must have been rough.
Hi.
How can I go to sleep?
You talk so loud.
I had 3 days of non-stop surgeries.
I wanted to surprise you, but...
You did, believe me.
Why... Why are you sleeping here?
Mom called me at the hospital.
She said you were headed over here
and I should pick you up
because you'd get lost for sure.
But I never thought
you'd get on the wrong train.
Why don't you ever call
before you come?
Because you never
answer your phone or voicemails.
I wanted to tell you the minute
I found out
We can finally work together.
You studied hard all year.
Naoki!
You look good in that uniform.
Thanks.
So I got off at Shin-Osaka.
I heard already.
And I left my coat and cell phone
on the train!
I heard already.
I was telling that old man.
And in Okayama.
Your story was better before.
I know.
I asked which way to Shin-Kobe
and they said this was the last train.
I heard already.
I didn't know which platform
was for Shin-Kobe and...
I asked the station staff...
NEXT EPISODE
EP.13 "FLOWERS AND STORMS"
They told me
there were no vacancy in Kobe!
Ms. Irie.
I'll teach you how to give injections.
-Gauze.
-Yes.
You'll be a burden on Dr. Irie!
The real Kotoko
would trample over
flowers and storms
That's right. All I can do is try.
We can finally work together.
I'll be right there.
The artery needs to be closed.
No! Let's wait ...
Kotoko!
Put on a gown, now!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2