Chris was splattered with hot oil?
If anything happens to Chris, I...
Her burns have
penetrated the inner skin.
Oh...
Regarding scarring...
How's is it?!
Some of it might stay.
Naoki!
What's wrong, Naoki?
What's all this, Kotoko?
Naoki has a long surgery tonight.
I thought I'd bring him
a nutritious meal.
Naoki!
You just finished your surgery!
I wanted to bring you
something nutritious...
...that will give you stamina...
Ouch...
Naoki...
Naoki?
Naoki!
No!
Naoki! Naoki!
Naoki!
Naoki! Open your eyes!
Kotoko!
-What's going on?
-Moto-chan...
I just heard at the nurse's station...
What happened?
Naoki...
Naoki fell from the stairs...
trying to break my fall...
What if he dies...?
Come on. Calm down.
What did the doctor say?
Dr. Nishigaki just told me
to get out of the room.
He wouldn't let me in.
Naoki is unconscious.
He hit his head...
Oh, my God! It's my fault...
What if he dies because of me?
-I... won't...
-Kotoko!
Calm down.
You're a nurse, aren't you?
You can't panic like this.
You're Dr. Irie's wife.
You have to be strong!
Dr. Nishigaki is one of
the best doctors here.
Okay...
Please, God!
Save Naoki...
Please save him!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2
TEARFUL PROPOSAL
Ouch...
I remember...
...Kotoko and food...
So, my leg...
...is broken.
You're up, Naoki!
Thank goodness!
You know,
you broke your leg yesterday.
I can see that.
You were sleeping all this time.
You're here to take
my temperature, right?
Oh, yeah.
Put this under your arm.
May I see your arm?
I have to draw blood
and give you two IVs.
What's the diagnosis?
Simple fracture of
the lower right leg.
It's terribly swollen,
so, until it goes down
you'll be hospitalized
with mandatory bed rest.
In addition, fatigue-induced
anemia, sleep deprivation,
and malnutrition...
It's overwork.
Lack of sleep, overwork,
malnutrition, anemia.
He's not unconscious.
He's fast asleep.
There's nothing wrong with his brain.
He'll recover in two months.
Kotoko?
You didn't pass out
because you hit your head.
It was overwork.
Overwork?
It's my fault! I tired you out!
Kotoko.
You became anemic
and broke your leg
all because of me!
So... so... so...
I want to take full responsibility
and take care of you.
I'll be your legs!
Hey...
It's my duty as a nurse
and your wife!
Open wide.
Come on! Open wide!
I said I can feed myself!
You just broke your leg!
Don't push it!
It's my leg that's broken.
Patients must listen to the nurse.
Open up. Come on!
I got that! Nice shot!
Mom!
I brought your stuff.
Konomi.
-You came.
-Yes.
She insisted on coming.
You asked me to come with you...
Shut up!
Just admit it!
Naoki, you're so lame.
Falling down the stairs.
Mom, I'm the one that fell
and Naoki tried to--
Catch his beloved wife!
Where's your triple-flip landing?
I'm not a circus act.
Oh, my God!
So, it's true!
We heard and came running!
Chris. Kin-chan.
You tried to save Kotoko
and got hurt instead.
How unfortunate.
How lame, Irie!
You should be ashamed!
Okay, Naoki. Time to draw blood.
Wow!
It's Nightingale Kotoko.
Okay.
Draw my blood, too.
Let's see you at work, Kotoko.
Here we go.
Give me your arm.
Aren't there any other nurses?
Why? I'm right here.
Okay.
First, some alcohol.
It'll feel cold a bit.
Okay.
Just a little prick.
-Here!
-Ouch!
Huh? It's not going in. I'm sorry.
The needle is supposed to
go under the skin!
Sorry. One more time.
This time... Here we go.
Don't maul me!
There! Success.
Success?
How long did that take you?
I was so nervous
drawing your blood.
What if I failed?
Don't worry. You did.
The IV is next.
The needle is already in!
I'm not your pin cushion!
Oh, yeah.
Oops.
So, Naoki's hospital stay began.
I'll peel an apple for you.
It's okay. Just leave it.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
What beautiful weather...
Isn't it nice outside, Naoki?
The birdies...
Kotoko! Watch out!
Sorry, Naoki. I wasn't looking.
Don't get so mad.
Let's move on!
I'm focusing all my energy on
taking care of Naoki, but...
I'm a failure as a nurse and wife.
NAOKI IRIE
Okay.
Good morning!
Morning.
Blood pressure: 104 over 76.
Sorry I woke you up last night.
It's fine.
I'm used to it.
You were on the night shift.
Are you done now?
Yeah.
Can you put this on my desk
before you leave?
Okay. I'll put it on your desk.
Thanks.
Okay!
MEDICAL OFFICE
Excuse me.
Hi, Kotoko.
Oh.
Naoki asked me
to put this on his desk.
It's right there.
How is he?
He's doing better.
Irie is so lucky to have such
a cute wife to care for him.
You're just saying that
because it's true!
Sorry!
Where's a rag?
Looks like it's okay...
It's legible.
I'm sure once it's dried out...
Right?
Right.
NEXT DAY
Good morning, Dr. Irie.
Here's your breakfast.
Thanks. What's up with you
for getting this to me?
Kotoko is blocking all the other nurses
from entering your room.
No one can come near you.
Really?
By the way.
Kotoko's not here yet.
That's unusual.
In that case, let me feed you.
Hold it right there!
I'm Naoki's private nurse!
That's my job!
Such a commotion for
first thing in the morning.
I'll take care of him today.
Open wide, Dr. Irie!
My hands are fine.
I wanted you to eat this.
Tada!
It's so garlicky!
Fried cutlet
with garlic scrambled eggs.
Fried chicken
and garlic barbeque meat.
Okra salad.
Sticky stuff is good for you.
For breakfast?
You couldn't eat my meal
the other night.
Actually, that was the reason
you broke your leg...
But I'll make you breakfast
every morning.
Every morning?
Yes! I bet you can't wait!
Ms. Irie! Are you still
dilly-dallying around here?
Nurse Shimizu...
I know you're his wife,
but finish your duties first!
You deliberately missed
our meeting, too!
You're supposed to change
Mr. Sakamoto's sheets!
I'm sorry...
-Go!
-Yes.
See you later, Naoki.
How powerful she is.
Do you have a minute, Irie?
What is it, Dr. Kato?
It's about Mr. Kusakabe's surgery.
He has esophageal cancer,
so, I think esophageal resection
and restoration would be appropriate.
Oh, I see. Yes.
I'm sorry I can't operate
with this broken leg.
No, you need the rest.
And...
I wrote down some notes
on the surgical procedure.
They're on my desk.
That will be helpful.
On your desk, right?
Yes, on my desk.
Huh? On your desk...
Dr. Kato?
It's midnight.
I'm sure Naoki's sleeping.
I'll just take a peek at his face.
He's sleeping well. How cute.
Good night, Naoki.
You scared me. Were you up?
I wanted to ask you something.
What?
What is this?
This should dry it out quickly.
It will dry on its own.
But I want it to dry nicely.
I see.
Okay...
This is...
What did you try to do?
I wanted to be of use to you.
Don't do anything
I don't ask you to do!
Thank God I remembered everything.
Never touch a doctor's desk!
It could be a matter of life or death!
I'm sorry!
I never thought this would happen.
I wanted to ease your burden,
but I spilled coffee on it.
Caused a lot of trouble for Dr. Kato, too.
All I did just made more work for you.
I love you, but...
I love you so much, but...
But I keep getting you tired
and even injured.
I'm bad luck for you.
No matter what...
...I'll always...
...be a failure as your wife.
Then that wouldn't be just about you.
Me, too.
I couldn't even catch you.
Look what happened to me.
But...
I failed as your husband.
Naoki...
I should have caught my wife
and made a triple-flip landing.
While I've been here,
I realized how patients feel
and how hard you work.
A nurse and her patient...
This...
...is kind of sexy.
Naoki's leg was healing nicely
thanks to the power of my love.
-Proposal?
-Shh! Don't talk so loud!
I'm not even talking loud.
Listen, Irie...
When you...
...proposed to Kotoko,
what did you say?
I don't really want to know...
...but you can tell me if you want to.
Well, it was the day
she rejected you.
Huh?
On the spur of the moment,
in front of family.
I said, "I'm marrying her."
-Mr. Aihara, I need to talk to you.
-You should change your cloth first--
I would like to...
To marry your daughter.
Naoki!
On the spur of the moment?
Without asking Kotoko first?
I didn't need her approval.
I knew she'd say yes.
What an ego...
Did that help?
Hell no!
Forget it!
Kin-chan!
Kin-chan! What's happening?
He's going to propose to Chris.
I see.
What...
What?!
Really?
Wow, Kin-chan. Finally...
He's going to propose to Chris!
She'll be so happy.
They can be happily married.
Just like us!
I have to check it out!
There they are!
What do you say, Chris?
I...
...can't marry you, Kinnosuke.
What?
Did you just say "you can't?"
Yes.
You can't marry me?
Sorry, Kinnosuke...
Forget...
...about me.
Chris!
Why did you refuse
Kin-chan's proposal?
Kotoko...
You love him so much!
You were waiting for this!
Kotoko, I need a favor.
What?
Do you have plans
to break up with Irie?
Huh?
No! Of course not! Are you kidding?
Will you break up with Naoki
and marry Kinnosuke?
Huh?
Kinnosuke is a better cook
and he's very kind.
And he's a total hunk.
You should remarry Kinnosuke.
Wait...
Kinnosuke has always loved you, Kotoko!
Chris!
Will you do it?
I couldn't stand it if Kinnosuke
married anyone else.
It would be best
if he married you, Kotoko...
Chris...
This was unexpected.
I know.
Chris won't tell me
why she turned him down.
I'm so confused.
He must be even more confused.
Poor guy.
She's hiding something.
JAPANESE CUISINE
AIHARA
Kinnosuke, do the prepping--
Aren't you done yet?
Forget it, boss.
Ever since he went to see Chris
yesterday, he's been useless.
What?
See?
What the hell happened, Kinnosuke?
I bet Chris turned him down.
Chris turned him down?
I'm not sure, but...
Oh...
Bingo...
What?
But Chris was totally
in love with him...
But I know how she feels.
I could never understand
why a cute girl like her
would go for a guy like him.
You're right...
And Kinnosuke was so cold to her.
He was taking her love for granted.
You're right.
What if...
...another guy showed her
a little kindness?
Another guy? Kindness?
Someone who could
fill the void in her heart.
Chris would change her mind.
Chris? Change her mind?
Shh! Boss!
Never mind, Kinnosuke.
He always blows things
out of proportion.
Why would Chris ever change her...
Kinnosuke?
-Kinnosuke... Kinnosuke!
-Hey, Kinnosuke! Hey!
Look what you did, boss!
Who, me?
Want some sweets?
Thank you Mrs. Abe,
but I'm not really hungry right now.
Come on. Have some with me.
I can't eat it all by myself.
Just one, then.
It's good.
See? Sweets always make you happy!
Mrs. Abe...
Mom.
Oh, Yuichi!
I happened to come nearby, so...
But isn't it a workday?
Yeah.
I just dropped by to see you...
Yuichi! What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Isn't she cute? Chris is from England.
My name is Christine Robbins.
Your mom has been so kind to me.
Oh... well...
If you're on your way out,
will you go buy candy
from downstairs?
Sure. On the first floor?
I'll show you where it is.
What?
I wanted to buy a box
of tissues anyway.
I was shocked.
I went to see my mom and...
You didn't expect to see a blondie?
Well, that, too, but...
I never expected to meet
such a lovely girl.
Thank you.
It's nice to hear
a Japanese man say that.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
Of course you do.
Boyfriend...
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I just remembered something...
Um... are you all right?
That's my Chris!
You made my Chris cry!
Who are you...?
You little pretty boy...
You stole my Chris away
and made her cry!
Kinnosuke!
Chris...
Excuse me.
Kin-chan!
I...
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry!
What got into you, Kin-chan?
Never mind my stupid son.
Stupid son?
We all know how much
Kin-san loves Chris.
He came to see her every day!
He must be busy. It's not easy to do.
Unlike my stupid son.
Ouch!
I'd better get going, mom.
Work hard!
I'm really sorry!
It was totally my mistake.
I thought your son...
...was Chris' new boyfriend.
If Chris loved someone else,
I'd have to give her up
and wish for her happiness.
But I had to see
what kind of guy it was...
Love someone else?
But you found someone new.
That's why you turned down my proposal.
Proposal?
No! I don't love anyone else!
Then why?
What don't you like about me?
I love you, Kinnosuke.
I always dreamt
that you'd propose to me.
You took good care of me
when I burned my leg.
Of course!
Just because I love you!
I'll be scarred for life,
but you still proposed.
I was so happy!
Then why?
Yeah! Why did you reject his proposal?
Because...
You're feeling pity for me.
Pity?
You're so sweet. You know no one
will marry a scarred woman,
so, you said that
you have to take care of me.
I never...
I know you don't really love me...
-I don't want you to marry me out of pity.
-Stop that!
Who said anything about pity?
Your burn is nothing between us!
No matter how bad it is,
it will never gets in our way!
But you proposed so suddenly...
I see.
Will you believe me
if I'm scarred like you?
Kin-chan!
Kin-chan...
Let's bring some tea to Dr. Irie
while Kotoko's not around...
Where's the kitchen?
Who is that?
Give me that!
No... Don't...
There you are!
Kotoko!
What are you doing, Kin-chan?
I'm going to burn my leg!
Don't! You'll burn yourself!
-No!
-That's hot!
Leave me alone Kotoko!
I'm going to be just like Chris!
Sorry, Kinnosuke!
I waited for so long.
You finally proposed to me
and-- And...
I refused. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Chris...
How could I spend my life
with someone out of pity?
Everyone besides Chris knew
that Kin-chan was crazy about her.
Kinnosuke...
What?
Propose to me again.
I want to answer you properly.
Oh, my.
Here comes a proposal!
Propose to her properly.
Wait a minute...
With all you old ladies around?
Old ladies?
Don't be shy, Kin-san!
Be a man!
Propose to her!
Kinnosuke...
Well, then...
Let's get married, Chris!
Yes, Kinnosuke...
I love you so much!
I'm so happy!
A kiss! A kiss!
Nice try, Kin-chan!
My blood pressure goes up!
A Kansai-style proposal.
How passionate!
Congratulations, Kin-chan! Chris!
Congratulations!
Thanks!
According to Naoki,
Chris misunderstood
about the scarring.
There won't be any scars left.
That's how Kin-chan and Chris
vowed to get married.
And the day we long awaited for...
Congratulations on your recovery!
Congratulations!
What's all this about?
I always wanted to do this.
Like you're a celebrity.
Congratulations, Kotoko.
Now you can relax.
The power of love healed him.
Well, maybe...
The days at the hospital
deepened our bond.
Now that Naoki is fully recovered,
maybe we'll go to a hot spring
for some romantic time alone--
Kotoko! He's going!
Wait, Naoki!
I have lots of work piled up
and patients to see this afternoon.
Sorry you had to take part in this.
No problem.
But Naoki!
He and I are back to business again!
NEXT EPISODE
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
FINAL EPISODE
EP.16 "BEST BIRTHDAY GIFT EVER"
MISCHIEVOUS KISS 2