Don't be so arrogant.
-Irie.
-Sorry, I got to go.
I'm running with Irie.
It's like a dream.
I'm saying that
being in the same house
with you
doesn't bother me.
Does that mean you...
don't hate me?
You're hard to deal with,
but I don't hate you.
No, I'm against it.
Kotoko's finally back, but now
you're moving out?
Why don't you try it.
Thank you.
I'm going now.
Naoki, take good care
of your health.
Eat enough vegetables. Also...
I know, I know.
See you later.
Augh!
He really left.
Irie has moved out?
He's renting a place
and he'll work for his living expenses.
Where is Irie now?
I don't know.
How about his part-time job?
What kind of job does he have?
I don't know that either.
That sounds like you guys
are complete strangers.
Hey Kin-chan, what's this?
It's a celebration gift.
Irie moved out, right?
What's better to celebrate?
I won this battle.
Irie must have given up
on the Kotoko finally.
Wait, Kin-chan.
You don't know anything about
how Kotoko feels.
What are you doing here?
Just go away.
Kotoko, I'm on your side.
I'll eat this.
Kin-chan doesn't know anything.
I think what Kin-chan's saying
is right.
Satomi.
Because Irie is a man, too.
If he had any feelings towards
Kotoko,
he wouldn't have moved out
of the house.
See, look at Kin-chan.
People want to be close
to who they love.
Right after he said
he didn't hate me,
he moved out of the house.
Is he trying to avoid me?
What's Irie's true feelings?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
TONAN UNIVERSITY SCHOOL
OF SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING
WHEN YOU GIVE UP ON YOUR LOVE
You still can't stop coming here
to spy on him.
Because I can see him only
at college.
Kotoko, you're so stupid.
Yeah, she really is.
Why am I stupid?
-S.T.U.P.I.D, stupid.
-Right.
S.T.U.P.I.D?
Stupid!
-Stupid, stupid.
-No, I'm.
Hey, you're Irie's.
Hello.
Too bad. Irie already left.
He went to work.
Oh, what kind of a job did he say?
We asked him too,
but he didn't tell us.
Irie is somewhat secretive.
Sorry that we can't help.
I see.
Are they twins?
They must be brothers.
No, twins.
No way. Are they twins?
Go for it.
Kotoko Aihara.
The feelings of the balls.
One who's lazy at picking balls
get her regular position
taken away.
Remember that.
-You!
-Yes.
Be clear if you're hot or cold.
You're in the tennis club, right?
Gather the balls.
You guys are members, right?
He's not going to come.
You try it!
I'm sorry to serve you
things like these.
My wife has errands
and she's not here.
No, it's delicious.
Really? Eat them.
Thank you for the dinner.
What's up, Yuki? You haven't
eaten much.
I have no appetite.
Oh...
you don't?
If that's the case,
this will happen.
I wonder if Yuki misses Naoki.
Even though he gave me
a cold shoulder
and being sarcastic,
I was with him all the time.
The distance between Irie and I
will get farther and farther.
Kotoko-chan.
Yes.
Kotoko-chan, Kotoko-chan.
I found out.
What?
"What?" did you say?
Of course where Naoki works.
How did you?
It's impossible for him to have
a secret against me.
I wonder who you are.
Anyway...
you and I
should go to his work
and spy on him.
I will.
I'll come too.
Yuki, were you listening?
More than Kotoko,
I'm worrying about my brother.
I want to see him too.
Okay. Then,
let's spy on him
with three of us.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
Let's do it!
We'll make it happen.
All right.
Ricotta cheese pancake
with bananas and...
the drink is...
Original blend tea.
Okay.
-Low-- Low fat milk.
-What?
-Yes.
What? What?
-I'll take over.
-Thanks.
He's so cool.
That's my brother all over.
Excuse me.
Waiter, over here, please.
Yes. Ready to order?
Not you,
but the other guy over there.
Excuse me.
Hey, waiter, over here.
What would you like?
-What will be good?
-I'll take this one.
Do something with your obvious
disguise, mom.
How did you know?
I don't understand your nerve
to think that it's a disguise.
Because, not only where you work,
but also your address is
kept secret from us.
I'm working now so stop having
a private conversation.
Is your order two coffee
and one orange juice?
I'll be back.
Why?
-I don't see my brother.
-What?
He might have gone
to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
Where's Naoki Irie?
Irie is done with his shift today.
He left without saying
anything to us?
He didn't give us
his new address.
Mrs. Irie, let's go home.
I'm happy with seeing Irie
doing well.
You're right.
Kotoko.
Look at that.
NOW HIRING
PART TIME WAITRESSES
Mrs. Irie, I'll work here.
That way I'll be close to Irie.
Great idea, Kotoko.
Yes.
Excuse me, I'm applying for
that job.
NOW HIRING
PART TIME WAITRESSES
-This way, please.
-Yes.
Manager.
Another applicant
for the part time job.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just hired this lady.
Ms. Matsumoto.
Wow, what a coincidence, Kotoko.
How did you know that
Irie worked here?
I was told
by him.
He did?
Mrs. Irie.
Kotoko, how was your job interview?
I didn't make it.
A girl who was in Engineering
with Irie applied for it earlier.
So she was hired.
It's probably...
that girl.
Yuko Matsumoto.
Mrs. Irie, when did you...
I told you. The one who controls
information
controls the world.
She's fairly good looking
and has a nice figure
and must be kind of smart,
but she is out of question.
She's not for Naoki.
Do you think so?
Of course. She must know that.
That's why she got into
his work
and is trying hard to sell herself.
I was going to go into
where he worked too.
Anyway, you're the best fit
for Naoki.
I, who raised Naoki,
am saying that so it's true.
A girl like her.
You can just kick her out.
Mrs. Irie.
The knife.
This one?
I was filleting a mackerel.
A mackerel.
Yuko Matsumoto works
at where Irie works?
Not only that, she heard that Irie
was working there from Irie himself.
But why? The Engineering guys
were saying that.
We asked him,
but he wouldn't tell us.
Irie is somewhat secretive.
Right.
He was hiding about his work
to his mom.
However, he told Yuko Matsumoto
about his job.
I understand that.
When someone changes his way
of living,
there's some kind
of motivation.
See, when Kotoko started tennis,
you were influenced by Irie, right?
That means
the reason for Irie to start
living by himself
is Yuko Matsumoto?
No way! Because Irie told me that
he doesn't hate me.
I may sound cruel,
but not hating you
and loving you are totally
different. Do you understand?
Irie has been hating women.
If that kind of a guy
falls in love with someone.
If something big like that
didn't happen,
he wouldn't have decided
to leave his comfortable home.
I agree.
AIHARA
WE'RE GETTING READY
What's wrong?
It's rare for you to come here
on your own.
I wanted to eat the food you cook.
You used to come and eat here often
when you were little. There.
Wow, looks delicious!
Kotoko, since you're here
let's eat together.
Kinnosuke, you are eating
with me in the back.
-Why not?
-Just come.
Thank you for this meal.
It's delicious.
I know.
About Naoki, right?
Iri-chan said there was nothing
to do with us,
but he moved out right after
we came back.
I was wondering too.
I wonder Irie hates me
more than I think.
What are you talking about?
You are the one who decided
to keep on going no matter what.
If you've decided once,
do it without complaining.
That's what you've decided.
I got it.
I came here because I really
wanted to eat your food.
It's the best.
Thank you for the meal.
See you, Kotoko.
I'll come back soon again.
-Chef.
-Yeah.
Aren't you little harsh?
What?
Kotoko is suffering now.
She's not a little girl anymore.
It's not something that parents
have a say on it.
I will help her
when she's really in trouble.
So that I can protect her,
I can sit here and wait until then.
That's what parents are all about.
Don't worry about us,
but you should establish yourself
soon to make your parents proud.
Yes.
DAIKANYAMA STATION
Okay... go.
-I'll help you.
-Thank you.
I'm going to wait outside
until he's done working.
Pokey poke, turn around
pokey poke, turn.
There he is.
Okay.
Is he waiting for somebody?
It can't be.
Sorry for having you wait.
No.
It's on the corner over there.
Have you been there?
No.
Their pasta is really good.
Salads are good as well.
I see. Irie is riding a train
to go home.
I got it. He's okay.
He's going home.
How long is she going to be
with him?
Irie, do you like amusement parks?
Yeah, but I don't go there often.
I see.
Is Irie's apartment
close to Matsumoto's?
Did he start living by himself
so that he can live close to her?
No, It's close
to Tonan University here.
It's normal for him to rent a room
close to school.
What would you like for dinner
tonight?
I haven't thought about it.
Well, then...
how about beef stroganoff?
-Sounds good.
-Let's go.
Beef...?
Beef... teck apple... geoise.
She's going to cook that one?
No, no, no.
MATSUMOTO
Matsumoto?
What? They live together?
Eat it up.
Good morning.
What happened, Kotoko?
Nothing.
But your face.
I couldn't sleep very well
last night.
You're stupid and look
like a monster now.
My brother is not going to
like you being like that.
Stop it.
Thank you for warning me.
I got to be careful.
What?
Well,
I'm going now.
Wait, Kotoko.
What about breakfast?
Is she going to be okay?
They live together?
I didn't know that they were
that serious.
Well, but...
it can be false information.
You may have misunderstood
something.
I waited in front of the house
for three hours.
Three hours?
I'm impressed with your
determination.
Irie never came out of Matsumoto's
place the whole time.
It would've been little too long
if he just took her home.
They're living together for sure.
If he lives in her home, her parents
must be accepting him.
It makes sense that Irie didn't tell
his new address to his mom.
A college student moves out of his
house and live with a girl's family.
He can't say that.
Kotoko?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I have to go to class.
What?
Kotoko.
Hey Irie.
Long time no see.
I felt like sweating a little.
Oh, today...
Aihara is not here.
She's not feeling well.
So she's absent.
Really.
Her tennis skill hasn't improved,
but her body is sturdy.
She has never missed practices.
Irie.
Let's practice together
over here.
Sure.
Later.
Brother.
-Hey. Are you doing well?
-Yeah.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I wanted to see you
after a long time.
Besides I'm wondering about
how it's like at home.
Speaking of which, there's something
wrong with Kotoko.
Her? What's wrong?
I don't know.
She looks pale and dazed.
She doesn't eat much either.
When I tease her,
she has no response.
It's not fun at all.
It's just like
pushing a curtain,
an Iron clamp on Tofu.
Nails into rice bran.
There, there...
Chinese and Western. I got
desserts too.
If there are this many choices,
you'll be able to eat something.
Kotoko. Don't hesitate.
Eat them up.
These are from Kin-chan and us.
How long are you frowning
like that?
You have to take nutrition
or new love won't come.
I understand that you're
broken hearted.
He's not the only guy.
Right. Look around.
A nice guy is
right in front of you.
Kin-chan, stop selling yourself
for now.
Right. Mr. Kin-chan acted
too quickly.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Kotoko.
Start from something
you can eat.
There, there.
Thank you.
But...
I really don't have an appetite.
So please...
you guys eat these.
Kotoko, are you okay?
Are you okay? Kotoko?
There.
I won't forgive Irie.
-Where are you going, Kin-chan?
-Of course, to see Irie.
I'll show him.
Listen. You're a part-timer,
but a faculty of this college.
If you hurt a student,
you'll be fired from the cafeteria.
You can't be close to Kotoko.
Just hold your emotion now.
We'll take care of Kotoko somehow.
Right. You're right.
-Let's eat. We'll eat now.
-Let's eat.
-You need some sugar.
-Sugar? I need more mustard.
-I think it's sugar.
-Give me some dessert, then.
Kotoko.
Kin-chan went to get his car.
Doctor, how's Kotoko doing?
She's got fatigue
and lack of nutrition.
She'll be better once she eats
something easy to digest and rest.
I called her family.
You both should go home.
Thank you, doctor.
Thank you.
But considering her fainting in
this degree,
she must have had something
that shocked her mentally.
Shocked her mentally.
That guy. I won't forgive him.
Naoki Irie.
Is Naoki Irie here?
Move over. Get out of my way.
Hey, come with us.
I have something to tell you.
Who are you?
We were in the same high school.
Even though you got 200 IQ,
you don't remember us?
I don't remember something
that's a waste.
He's so annoying.
I remember.
You have same level brains
with Kotoko.
Jinko and Satomi?
The other way.
-I'm Jinko.
-Satomi.
What do you want?
About Kotoko.
Right.
Aren't you too cruel?
Lately,
Kotoko's been hurt
because of you.
-Because of me?
-Do you think we don't know?
About you living...
with her.
Poor thing.
Kotoko followed you
and Matsumoto.
She saw it with her own eyes.
In front of her house,
she waited for three hours.
Although you know Kotoko's feelings
towards you,
you moved out of the house
and are living with someone secretly.
It's so cowardly.
Don't leave her in limbo.
If you are a man,
tell her straightforward.
Should I tell her straightforward?
Consider the way to deliver it.
Right.
If you learned how to love,
then now you understand
feelings of a human
a little bit, right?
Anyway, don't make Kotoko
suffer anymore.
I won't
tell you to stop loving Matsumoto.
But at least
if there's no chance,
I want you to lead her to
give up on you.
Please.
Anyway,
that's what we wanted
to tell you. Bye.
Bye.
I see.
AIHARA
Here we are.
Are you okay, Kotoko?
I'm okay.
Sorry, you have to go to work.
See you later.
Kotoko.
I'm right here for you.
Kin-chan.
Always, anytime,
I'll be close to you.
I'll be right here.
So...
That's all.
Get well soon.
Kin-chan.
Sorry.
It's not the situation
for you to apologize.
Then...
Eat well and go to bed early.
Does that mean that
you don't hate me?
You're hard to deal with, but...
I don't hate you.
How long are you frowning?
You have to take nutrition
to find a new love.
I understand that you're
broken hearted,
but he's not the only guy.
Kotoko.
I'm right here for you.
What am I doing?
Kotoko, are you okay?
Shall I drive you to school?
I'm really okay.
I'm going now.
Enjoy your day.
I have to pull myself together.
I have to become okay for real.
Any more...
I can't cause trouble for everyone.
All right. I'll cheer myself up.
Yeah.
Good morning.
Wait.
Come with me.
How do you like your new place?
It's nice. It's big, so...
Of course, it's such a mansion.
It must be big.
How are you doing with meals?
I eat at a cafe or have something
made for me.
As I thought.
Listen.
I think it's wonderful
to fall in love.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I've been
in unrequited love with you.
It may have been a nuisance
to you, but...
I could accomplish things
because of that.
If I stayed as I was,
I may have not been able
to get into Tonan University.
I know that
it might be nothing for you,
but it was a big deal for me.
Summarize what you want to say.
I mean...
If you have somebody you love,
I want to be happy about it.
Of course I'm disappointed,
but if you like Matsumoto
and she likes you,
then if you live happily together then
I'm good with it.
I'll back you up.
Naoki.
Who is she?
Is this...
Kotoko Aihara?
How do you know my name?
That's what I thought.
I recognized you because you're
just like what I've heard.
You look unintelligent and clumsy.
How rude!
Who's saying stuff like that?
Naoki and my sister.
Your sister?
Is your sister possibly...
Right. It's me.
Yuko Matsumoto?
I'm Ayako Matsumoto.
Senior in high school.
Didn't you hear about us
from Naoki?
Then maybe I can tell you.
Naoki comes to our house and...
I know.
He lives together, right?
I wish you every happiness,
Matsumoto.
What are you talking about?
Naoki is tutoring me at
our house.
He's tutoring?
I'm applying for Tonan University
next year.
So my sister introduced him to me
and three times a week,
Naoki is tutoring me.
It's a good part-time job
at the Matsumotos.
Meals are included.
Beef strongano... beef sto--
What?
How do you know?
Beef stroganoff.
What's wrong with her?
Is she crying?
Are you okay?
She's little different, you know.
Anyway, Naoki and sis, why don't you
tour me around the college?
I came here for that today.
So, what did you say?
You approve that Matsumoto and I
live together.
You are going to back us up, right?
No, no, no.
I'm taking back what I just said.
I'm strongly against it.
You're so loud.
I moved out to be
all by myself.
Why do I even bother living
with someone?
See you, Kotoko.
Alrighty!
Matsumoto.
Matsumoto, Matsumoto.
Hey, you guys. Here's a racket.
Matsumoto.
Hey where's Yuko Matsumoto?
Where did she go?
Irie.
He wasn't living with Matsumoto.
What?
Do they live together?
That Irie guy...
-I won't forgive him.
-Mr. Sudo, wait!
No. Irie is still free.
He has been and he will be.
He's been free the whole time.
So you too
should be happy.
I don't know what you're
talking about,
but good for you.
Congrats.
But...
why did Matsumoto tell me that
she heard about his job from him?
What?
I'm the one who told her about
Irie's job.
I'm the one who introduced
that restaurant to Irie.
What? Does that mean that
Matsumoto lied to me?
How did you know that
Irie works here?
I was told...
by him.
Okay.
I see.
You're a man, too.
You're "him" also.
Are you sure you're okay?
I don't know what you're
talking about.
I'm okay.
Mr. Sudo. I'm hungry.
Can you buy me some food?
Why is that?
Why do I have to buy you food?
Why don't you buy me every
once in a while.
No way. I have no money.
I entered there.
To the store that had a lot of hats.
In the end, I misunderstood
that they lived together.
I'm so glad that it was
a misunderstanding.
But if so,
why did Irie start living
by himself?
It's okay.
-I see. It's okay, huh?
-Yes.
Are you sure?
Of course.
I think it's good.
I'm going now.
Are you sure you'll be okay
just the two of you?
We'll be okay. It's only one night.
-What's wrong?
-Yuki, hang in there.
He needs an operation.
I'll find Irie and take him here.
Matsumoto may know something.
We'll get there no matter what.
You should have told your contact
number to your family.
I was a nuisance to you today.
-Where's Kotoko?
-She's maybe at...
-Naoki's place.
-Do you want to take a shower?
What am I thinking in this crisis?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION