I am Kotoko Aihara of Class F.
Could you please read this letter?
-No thank you.
-Rejecting Kotoko? I will punish him.
This means a war.
When you move, luck may turn
in your favor.
A shooting star?
It got hit by a shooting star?
I ended up living with a family of my
dad's best friend.
-But it turned out...
-What's wrong with you, Kotoko?
Hi, I am--
It turned out to be a family of Naoki
Irie, whom I really liked.
Tell no one that we live together. Do not
talk to me at school at all.
You don't need to humiliate me that much.
I don't like a stupid girl.
I will beat Naoki Irie with term-end
exams.
-Give it to me.
-We have a week until the exams.
-Help me study.
-Kotoko may be
much more awesome than I think.
I can't believe it. 100th?
I suspect that her new house holds some
secrets.
What is this?
Do you live at Naoki Irie's house?
-Aihara.
-What?
Just come.
Our secret of living together was out.
Everybody in our school is gossiping
about us.
What are your friends thinking?
Since you like me, it would be okay for
you, but this bothers me a lot.
Do not disturb my life anymore.
I...
am crying? Why?
Since Irie had rejected me flatly,
I didn't think that I would care how
he treated me anymore.
Then why am I crying?
After all...
I think I still love him.
Kotoko, you are so late.
-I was worried about you.
-Sorry.
I should have called you earlier.
I'm really sorry.
This is the first love letter
I wrote in my life.
But this love letter has no reader.
No thank you.
I know he is a jerk, but...
I still love him. Why?
Hey, take a bath.
I'm coming in.
My mom wants you to take a bath.
Dear Mr. Irie.
I am Kotoko Aihara of Class F.
You may not know me.
But I know you well.
I've been in love with you for two years
since the entrance ceremony.
I felt like I was struck
by a shooting star
when I saw you for the first time.
This special feeling
has stayed in my heart.
I love
you.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
MORNING COFFEE
IS THE AROMA OF LOVE!?
Good morning.
Good morning, Kotoko.
You overslept as usual. Why don't you
wake up early to help her?
-I'm sorry.
-Don't worry.
Neither of my sons will help me at all.
-Have breakfast.
-Okay.
Bon appetite.
Hey, Kotoko.
Can you leave school early today?
Sure, but why?
I want to pay them back
for their kindness.
I would like to cook dinner
for them tonight.
-So I want you to help me.
-I see.
That's right.
Your restaurant is closed today.
Mr. Aihara, don't be bothered.
I just want to show you my appreciation.
Ai-chan is a great chef, so I can't wait.
Right, Naoki and Yuki?
You are right.
I'm done. See you, everyone.
-Have a great day.
Kotoko, you have to leave, too.
What?
You have bread crumb on the face.
What was that?
HIGH SCHOOL AFFILIATED
TO TONAN UNIVERSITY
-Stairs.
-Watch your step.
You are in my way.
To be honest, this is very annoying.
This is for you.
I am protecting you from Irie.
What?! Irie?
I will be fine.
He doesn't like me at all.
He told me unequivocally
not to talk to him at school.
Clear.
-Roger.
-Look.
Is that the girl who lives at your place?
What are they doing?
I don't care.
Spy on Irie's house?
You are nuts, Kin-chan.
But you two are also curious about them,
aren't you?
Well, I guess.
That's the house.
Huge!
Walk stealthily. Walk stealthily.
If Irie finds us, he will be mad.
Here she is.
-Kotoko!
-Yes.
-Can't see anything.
-The cap is on.
Wow. Everything looks so delicious.
Very impressive, Ai-chan.
Wait. What is this?
It is deep-fried tofu I made.
It may not look good, but it is delicious.
-I don't want it.
-Me, either.
Naoki and Yuki, watch your mouth.
You two are rude.
Let's have a seat.
Damn you! You refused Kotoko's
homemade dish?
Calm down, Kin-chan.
They may see you.
Then I will eat Kotoko's dish.
If I eat it, you two can eat it, right?
This is terrible.
I knew it.
No, no. This is delicious.
Iri-chan, be honest. That's okay.
She has never been good at cooking.
I can't believe that she is my daughter.
I must wonder whether someone
will take her as his wife.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't worry.
We like her. We will take her.
What did she just say?
I'm saying that you should marry Naoki.
No! I'm against it.
It's not your decision.
It's my life. Don't play with it.
Really? I really think that Kotoko
is your type.
Am I?
No way.
You are not my type at all.
I don't want to marry you, either.
Good. I'm glad that Kotoko said that.
Is that so? Then why did you give me such
a passionate message?
"How do you do, Irie?
I am Kotoko Aihara of Class F.
You may not know me, but I know you
well.
I have been in love with you, since--"
How dare you?
-What a jerk! Did you see my letter?
-You wrote it to me, didn't you?
-You don't need to memorize it.
-That's not my fault.
How dare you say it in front of everyone?
Wait. What's going on?
Kotoko, you mean you have been in love
with Naoki?
Did you hear that?
Tell it to everyone.
I wrote a love letter.
Is that true?
Then my fantasy
can be a reality.
But that was before
we started living together.
-Right now I'm not--
-Don't say that.
You may fall in love with him again.
What do you think, honey?
Well, if you two like each other,
I'm fine.
Hold it!
Open it!
Who are those kids?
Kin-chan?
Kotoko, open the door.
They are my classmates.
What the hell are you doing here?
Sorry, but Kin-chan really wants to know
how you are doing here.
Coming in?
Irie is a man, whether he is
a genius or not.
Who knows if he may get interested in
you in the future. See. I was right.
I will punish him for what he said.
-Who the hell are you?
-What?
Hello, everyone of Irie Family.
How do you do?
I am Kinnosuke Ikezawa aka Kin-chan.
I'm Kotoko's classmate.
It means that you are dumb, too.
-What did you say?
-Watch your mouth, Yuki.
Kotoko and I are in an intimate
relationship.
Kin-chan, stop your nonsense.
Kotoko, you are very popular
among boys, huh?
-That's right.
-I'm really sorry.
That's why I don't want you
to flirt with her.
Marriage? It's not funny at all.
Understand, Mr. Irie?
You never know.
What do you mean by that?
Our feelings are complicated.
I don't like her today,
but I may like her tomorrow.
What? After all, you like Kotoko,
don't you?
Who knows. But remember
that she likes me, not you.
I'm going to my room, so have fun.
What was that?
What did he mean by that?
Could it mean...
Do I have a hope?
Is that what he meant?
In the meantime, our last summer break
is about to begin.
I wish I can make some wonderful
memories during the last summer break.
But we have to prepare
for the college entrance exam.
-I know that, but...
-I know what you mean.
All we do during the break
is our homework? It's sad.
Kotoko, you are a lucky one.
You can be with him all summer long.
Nothing will happen.
Who knows.
He was so passionate the other day.
He was just carried away by the argument.
You may be right. He didn't even
touch the dish you cooked.
That's because I'm not good at cooking.
You are missing the point.
Men can't resist a dish
cooked by women they love.
It doesn't matter how terrible it is.
That's right. You live with him.
You can find a way to make him
appreciate your cooking.
That could be
the best memory of your summer.
My homemade dish, huh?
I'm so worried.
But I can't spy on their house every day.
On the other hand, Irie
can be with Kotoko during the break.
It's true that women tend to fall in love
with someone close.
Shut up! You are not helping.
Bro, don't give up.
You should stay close to Kotoko
as much as possible.
FIRST DAY OF SUMMER BREAK
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Kotoko, you don't have school anymore,
do you?
Well, for some reason,
I have to go to school.
Why? This is summer break.
Well, because... What can I say...
-Yuki, answer the door, please.
-Okay.
Yes?
Hi, Irie Family!
Good morning.
I'm here to pick up Kotoko
for mandatory summer school.
Mandatory summer school?
But you ranked 100th
in the last exam.
That was the term-end exam.
I didn't do well with the mid-term.
I wonder how bad your grade was
before the term-end exam. You are dumb.
Shut up.
See you later.
All the students from Class F are here.
This looks like a regular class.
Listen up. Let me be clear.
You all are on the borderline
between going on to
Tonan University or not.
Including Aihara, who ranked 100th in the
term-end exam.
That's why I want you to work hard
in summer school.
So-called "summer school of hell"
starts now.
Keep in mind that this summer
is a crucial time.
Now we have to forget about making
good memories of summer.
Our memory of the last summer in the
high school will be homework only.
This is exactly what Kotoko predicted.
C'mon. This is not that bad.
You can spend the entire summer
with Kin-chan.
That will be a great memory of summer.
Eat it.
Kin-chan, sense the mood.
You are not the one whom Kotoko
wants to spend the summer with.
But she can't spend time with Irie,
because of summer school.
Wait. But I saw Irie today.
Don't say that, idiot.
What? Irie? Why? No way.
Is Irie taking summer class?
No. Look outside.
Right. Irie is a de facto member
of the tennis team.
De facto? What do you mean?
He is asked to play for the team
only in an important tournament.
I see.
Right. The national high school tennis
tournament is coming up soon.
What?!
I thought he was super smart,
but not athletic.
It's not fair.
He is a perfect guy
except his personality.
He makes me sick.
He didn't tell me
that he was coming to school today.
He still has no interest in you.
That's good.
Our feelings are complicated. I don't like
her today, but I may like her tomorrow.
Lost in your thought,
while staring at him?
What? Not at all.
No weight training, no running.
But can he still win a game?
That's not what a good team player
should be.
Let's get back to work.
Let's study hard.
Mars, the red planet,
has fascinated people
from the earliest time.
Ancient people identified
it with the god of war...
Understand? First of all...
He is so cool,
whether he is a jerk or not.
He will get tired after the practice.
If I cook something special for him,
it may make him feel better.
That could be a good idea.
Aihara.
-Kotoko Aihara!
-Kotoko.
-Yes.
-Read the next paragraph.
What?
-Run 10 laps for punishment.
-10 laps?
Run faster.
One more lap, Aihara.
Sorry about that. Not on purpose.
Isn't summer class over yet?
None of your business.
I just wanted to run.
Aihara! No time for a lover's quarrel.
Here you go. Did you get sunburn?
You have a PE class, too?
-Well, this is...
-Kotoko didn't listen to the lecture.
So she was forced
to run round the schoolyard.
How do you know that?
Set a thief to catch a thief.
Thief? What do you mean?
You don't even know the phrase?
What a shame!
Yuki, stop teasing her.
It's summer. It's not bad to get sunburn.
You are right.
We usually go vacationing in the mountains
or beaches during the summer.
-But not this summer. Too bad.
-What?
Didn't Ai-chan tell you that?
What happens is,
we are going to Kyushu to attend
our middle-school reunion.
-Is that so?
-So no family vacation, right?
Why don't you go to Kyushu
with your husband?
I can't leave you guys here.
-I'm sorry.
-Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for the meal.
I will help you.
Thank you, Kotoko. Can you wash dishes?
-Sure.
-In the meantime,
I will prepare your box-lunch
for tomorrow.
I really appreciate your kindness.
Since you leave early,
I must prepare it at night.
Mrs. Irie.
Can you teach me how to cook someday?
I can, but you have a father
who is a professional chef.
That's true, but I want to master
a taste of mom's home cooking.
You want to learn recipes
of the Irie Family, don't you?
Tell me. You are still in love
with my son, aren't you?
-How do you know?
-I can tell it.
I really want you to marry him.
So you can be my daughter.
I won't make a good match for him.
When I got married,
I was 19 years old.
I'm not bragging,
but I had a plenty of suitors.
All of them were rich and handsome.
Among them, he is not handsome as you
can see. And he is much older.
Back then, he just started his business
and was poor.
My parents were against
my going out with him.
But you chose him. Tell me why.
He is the most sincere person I ever met.
And a more serious person
than anybody else.
On top of that, he really cares about me.
He didn't care about the social standing
of my family or my look.
He really loves who I am.
Kotoko, you remind me of him.
SEVERAL WEEKS LATER
Congratulations!
Let's make a toast to Naoki winning
the national high school tournament.
Cheers!
Have a seat and eat.
Naoki, you are very impressive.
You are not only smart,
but also good at tennis.
Besides, you have won the title
three straight years, right?
You are juggling so many things.
Very impressive.
It's easy. If you study the opponent
and calculate his move,
you can tell where the ball is heading.
See. He is not a lovable type.
He is very smart. That's all.
He takes after Iri-chan in that, even
though they don't look like each other.
I wasn't that smart when
we were in the middle school.
-Really?
-I wasn't that smart.
-It was the good old days.
-Yes.
I'm looking forward
to the reunion tomorrow.
This is the first time I go back to Kyushu
for a long time.
I imagine that everyone has changed.
I wonder if Hiromasa
will come to the reunion.
THE LAST DAY OF SUMMER BREAK
See you soon.
-Have a great trip.
-Bye.
-The red shirt suits you well.
-Don't make me self-conscious.
Have a safe trip.
They are like kids who go on a picnic.
Since my dad has been busy,
he can't go back to Kyushu often.
I'm sure that he is very excited.
Hello, this is Irie residence.
What? Really?
I will be right there.
-Oh, my goodness. What should I do?
-What happened?
Your grandma got hurt.
It's not serious, but she must stay
in the hospital tonight.
So I must stay with her
at the hospital tonight.
-Do whatever you need.
-Thank you.
You two take charge
of the house today. Okay?
Sure. What? Two of us?
I will take Yuki. You two
have school tomorrow. That's why.
Understood. I'm fine with that.
Get ready quickly.
It means that Irie and I
are alone in this house.
It makes me very nervous,
but this could be a great opportunity.
-Let's go, Yuki.
-Okay.
This is it! Finally I can cook for Irie.
This will be the best memory of this
summer.
"Bifteck en...
Bour...geoise."
This is it.
What the hell is this?
Hi, Irie...
What is that?
Bifteck en Bourgeoise.
Oh, no...
Don't you need to check the recipe?
I already did. I've memorized it.
It smells nice.
And how is grandma doing?
Aren't we going to see her?
It's a long story, Yuki.
They don't know
how to deal with each other.
I want to make them get closer.
Since their fathers are out,
I want them to have an intimate moment.
But you said that grandma got hurt.
Of course, I made it up.
It was a sales call.
My acting was very convincing, wasn't it?
What? I'm going home.
I see. Then you don't want this?
Wow. This is exactly like the photo
of the cooking book.
Bon appetite.
Contrary to my plan,
we ended up
eating Irie's homemade dish.
But I'm having a wonderful dinner
with Irie.
We are like a newly-wed couple.
I'm sorry that you had to cook.
Then I want extremely sweet dessert
from you.
Hey.
You should wash the dishes at least.
And clean up the kitchen.
Okay. You do your homework now?
Can we do that together?
Homework? I finished it all
on the first day of summer break.
On the first day? Wow.
Don't tell me that you
haven't touched it yet.
Well, you are right about that.
It would take you a week to finish it
even if you work day and night.
Good luck.
Oh, no, what should I do?
It's already 10 o'clock.
It took so long to clean up the kitchen.
Let's do it.
I don't understand it at all.
Let's take a look at English.
It should be easy.
I have to study until the end.
What a terrible summer break it is!
I managed to fill something in questions
of Classics, World history and English.
But I still have Mathematics and
Physics. I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry, God and Buddha.
I feel like a criminal
who is cornered by the police.
Let me see...
your answers.
Safe.
Where is Irie's notebook?
Where is it?
Here you go.
Mathematics and Physics.
I will borrow these.
What the hell are you doing? Sneaking
into someone's room during the night?
Nothing. I have to go. Good night.
Don't you wish!
These are...
I know what you are doing.
-You want to come into my bed, don't you?
-Stop. What are you doing?
You sneak into a boy's room. What
else do you expect?
Relax. I won't let you down.
Won't let me down? You mean...
We are the only ones at home tonight.
-But...
-Your friends were right.
Even a genius may turn into a beast.
No, stop it.
I like you.
But we are not ready for this.
We should have
a platonic relationship first.
Platonic relationship? Really?
I see. It means that you still love me.
You weren't serious?
Relax. I am not interested in you at all.
I will tell everyone that Irie
tried to assault me.
Go ahead.
Everyone has already been gossiping
about us. It won't change anything.
-You win.
-Hey.
You forgot something.
I don't need...
The same formula applies
to number three. Try it.
Can I just copy your answers?
It wouldn't help you at all. Just do it.
After all, my memory of the summer
is doing my homework.
I didn't get what I hoped for.
But I am so happy now.
I wonder why.
-Focus. Do it now.
-Okay.
Well, this one is...
We ended up staying up all night.
To show you my gratitude,
I will make breakfast for you.
No, thanks. I don't want to have a
stomachache on the first day of school.
-Coffee.
-What did you say?
Make coffee for me.
Okay.
Here you go.
Good morning, Irie.
We were up all night together.
I couldn't make special memories
during the last summer break
of high school.
But I will never forget the aroma
of this morning coffee
which I shared with Irie.
The written oracle said that I would have
the best of luck.
NEXT EPISODE
Of course, Naoki Irie's dream school is
Tokyo University, right?
Why do you want to go to a college?
You are taking the standardized college
admission test, right?
I will accompany Irie to the gate of Tokyo
University.
-Oh, no, I slipped.
-Don't tell me this medicine is...
Naoki, throw it up.
Don't tell it to Kotoko, no matter what.
What happened, son?
I didn't get the name.
I think you will stick to her forever.
It was the most nerve-racking moment
in my life.
Good-bye, Irie.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION