I'm Kotoko Aihara from class F.
Would you read this?
-I don't want it.
-How could he brake Kotoko's heart.
He's challenging me.
It's okay.
I'm giving up.
When you change your home
your luck will change too.
Something good will happen to you.
Wait, wait.
Can you hear a weird noise?
Is that a shooting star?
Has it gotten hit by
a shooting star?
This is Iri-chan's home.
After an unexpected turn of events,
I started living at my dad's
best friend's house.
My name is Kotoko Aihara.
But that house turned out to be...
-What's wrong, Kotoko?
-Sorry to greet you late.
He's the boy who I admire:
Naoki Irie. It was his house.
Don't tell anybody that we live together.
Don't talk to me at school either.
You don't have to say that much.
I don't like stupid girls.
How humiliating.
I'll get my own back on him
for sure.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
The bad season has come.
LOVE EXAM
Okay, this is
the schedule
for the first trimester finals.
-What?
-Quiet.
Excuse me.
What's wrong, Aihara?
Do you have a stomachache?
I have a question.
In English that you teach,
have you decided on the range
of questions?
-What?
-Does it cover lesson 3 or 4?
She's gone nuts.
She's too serious.
Be quiet.
Let's go home, home, home.
What's going on, Kotoko?
You're different.
I can't forgive Naoki Irie.
-Good. Well said.
-So I'll do it this time.
I'll beat Naoki Irie on the finals.
You're laughing at me too.
You know,
Irie is always number one by far.
Not only that he's also number one
on the national test.
He's not the guy who you can beat.
-Right.
-Absolutely not.
Then I'll put my name
on the bulletin board.
On the same list as Naoki Irie
I'll put my name on it.
You're going to be in top 100?
No way. We're in class F, remember?
Right. Stop kidding
and let's go eat something
to give us energy. Let's go.
No.
History is there to change.
I'll get to the top 100
and put my name on
the bulletin board.
I'll change the history of class F.
Excuse me now.
What's going on with Kotoko?
-Here they come.
-Looks good.
-There they are. Thank you.
-Oh, it looks delicious.
Let's eat.
The skin's got nice texture.
As expected, Kin-chan.
I can trust you only
when it comes to food.
What do you mean by only food?
Master, you've got a great review.
-Thank you.
This week's special,
Colombia is great as well.
Kotoko should have come with us.
Right.
What made her decide to be
in top 100 on the test?
Speaking of that,
don't you think that she's a little weird
after she moved?
You don't know what kind of area
she lives, right?
She said that she was able
to walk to school now.
That means... in Setagaya?
Shibuya?
It could be Meguro.
See, it's suspicious.
There's no way that she can live in
that kind of upscale neighborhood.
Because she's living lent-free.
Didn't she say that it was
her dad's friend's house?
-Right.
-Is that a true story?
She might be
treated badly in that house.
She says she's studying,
but the truth is,
she's being a maid and worked hard.
There's no such things
in these modern times.
Right. You freak.
He's a freak, right.
It's so funny. Isn't he a freak?
You're so stupid.
Something is fishy about it.
Thank you for this food.
Anyway...
Ai-chan's store re-opened, right?
What a great news, Kotoko.
Yes. Thanks to you all.
Thank you so much.
Not at all.
What kind of rice is this, honey?
This is not rice,
but it's a kind of pasta.
You're right.
He's so handsome.
You like it, huh?
I don't like stupid girls.
-Thank you for the meal.
-You don't have to hurry up and eat.
I'll have finals soon.
I have to study.
Excuse me now.
Wow, she's so motivated.
Easy Math II Workbook
I don't know where I don't understand.
I'll study English first.
English.
Okay, it starts from here.
I should have listened better
during the class.
Okay.
I...
D...
Well, this is...
With this pace,
it'll take 100 years
to be in top 100.
-Kotoko.
-Yes.
-May I come in?
Would you like to take a break?
Wow, thank you.
Help yourself.
Here they are.
Thank you.
-There.
-I'll eat them.
It looks so good.
It's delicious.
I'm happy, too.
I wanted to do something like this.
I've been dreaming of it.
How about Irie?
Because he doesn't study.
What? Irie doesn't study?
How about now?
He went to bed already.
Irie is really a genius, isn't he.
I don't know if it's a good thing.
-Why?
-I can't explain it really well,
but if he stays like this, I feel like
he'll lose something important.
Irie is going to be okay.
He has such a wonderful family.
Thank you.
I know.
-Listen, Kotoko.
-Yes.
Do you want to see
the album of when he was little?
I want to see it.
Wait right here. I'll bring it for you.
The album...
Irie is asleep now, huh.
Here it is.
Let's see.
This is it.
Great.
My photo technique is a pro level.
I like it a lot.
But there are only few recent ones.
He doesn't like to get pictures taken.
Yuki copies him
and doesn't want it either.
I miss it.
Irie has been a good looking boy
since he was little.
I remember this.
Receiving kind words
from upperclassmen
filled me with deep emotion.
He's so little.
Who's this girl?
This is Naoki.
No way!
Isn't he cute?
I wanted to have a girl,
so I believed that the baby
would be a girl.
So I bought only girl's clothes.
Then I got carried away.
There was a time like this.
You're the first one to tell about this.
I never told Yuki either.
Naoki told me never to tell him.
Keep it secret between us.
Yes.
Then...
I'll give this to you for keeping secret.
Really? Thank you.
So cute.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Have a seat.
Good morning.
What's up, Kotoko?
Are you sick?
Nothing.
You must have studied so much
that you got crazy.
People fight meaninglessly.
The American Civil War, 1861.
People freed slaves.
People freed slaves, 1863.
1863, 1863...
Emancipation Proclamation.
1863, Emancipation Proclamation.
People freed meaningless slaves.
Kotoko, you're serious about it,
aren't you?
People freed slaves.
The next one, Suez Canal, 1869.
Hey Kotoko, where do you live now?
Suez Canal...
1869, Suez Canal.
She's gone crazy for sure.
Suez Canal, 1869.
Ms. Aihara.
Naoki Irie.
How could you come to see Kotoko?
Ms. Aihara, can you bring your bag
and come with me?
Yes.
Her bag?
Bring it with her?
-Why?
-What?
It couldn't be. That Irie guy
changes his mind and he might
tell her to go out.
No way.
Wait for me.
What is it?
This...
My mom switched accidentally.
-Right.
-Stuff like this,
if those idlers in your class see it,
it'll be a disaster.
They just exchanged something.
What does that mean?
There are so many things
that are inconveniencing me.
It's confusing when we're
in the same school.
Exactly.
You might accidentally wear
my uniform to come to school.
Why do I wear your uniform?
You grew up wearing skirts, right?
What are they talking about?
I can't hear anything.
Hush. They'll find us.
Ta-da!
Why do you have that?
Your mom gave it to me.
-What's that?
-Hold on.
Hush.
My mom did.
-Give it back to me.
-No way.
-Give it.
-No.
You've been bullying me.
It's my turn now.
A genius has a weakness also.
Is she trying to threaten me?
I can give it back to you.
But I have a condition.
For a week until finals,
teach me to study.
Teach?
You?
How about this.
You make me get into top 100.
Then I'll return this photo to you.
-No, thanks.
-Why not?
The important thing is to sense
if possible or not.
By Philip Chesterfield.
Phi...Chi... What's that?
It means that it's a waste of time
to challenge something impossible.
It's impossible to put an idiot
like you into top 100.
-Then I'll show this to school.
-Wait, wait.
I got it.
I'll teach you for a week at night
starting today.
-All right.
-However...
I'm going to be strict
to achieve the goal.
Top 100 is usually filled
with classes A and B.
It's a miracle to put you in there
as a class F student.
See you this evening.
-Kotoko, are you okay?
-Kotoko.
Did he do anything to you?
What were you talking to Irie?
Nothing.
Okay.
I'm going to study hard. Yeah.
Eat them up.
Yuki, don't leave anything on your plate.
Right. Kotoko,
kids' jobs are to eat.
-Eat well.
-Yes.
Eat this Daikon.
It absorbs the flavor, right?
It absorbed the flavor very well.
Irie and I, two of us are
going to study together.
Kotoko, I'll make a snack for you
again tonight.
Thank you.
Mom, make two snacks, please.
Bring them to Kotoko's room.
Two?
Are you studying?
Right.
That's not fair.
Help me study too, brother.
You are okay.
-Let's start.
-Yes.
Thank you for the meal.
Come on in.
So, what do we start with?
What's the subject that you're bad at?
-Math, I think.
-Let's do that, then.
Okay. Math...
Math is...
What section?
Isn't the section same as yours?
I don't know.
The section is...
Where is it?
Here it is.
Until page 40.
Then the questions will be...
This and...
How do you know?
These are just summaries.
How do you study usually?
I remember it when I hear or read once.
I'll give you some questions.
You solve them.
You'll score 80 percent
if you can solve this.
What are you listening during class?
I want to see inside of your brain.
Sorry.
I wonder what's going on.
Naoki is studying with someone.
What made him change his mind?
I wonder if Kotoko is greater
than I thought she was.
In this short time,
-she changed him this much.
-Yeah.
That can be a good change for Naoki.
-Really? Do you think so too?
-Yeah.
Let's keep watching them.
Schedule
Do you have a tape?
Here.
You have to strictly follow this schedule.
Keep your notecards when
you're in bathroom or taking a shower.
Spartan!
Evil!
There's no time to chit-chat.
Let's review math formulas today.
It's after midnight, though.
N equal three.
And parenthesis
X minus, plus...
Minus five parenthesis, so...
"Until this point" is?
So far.
"Different way of saying" is?
In other words.
-On purpose?
-What?
-On purpose.
-On purpose?
Well...
Intentionally?
Intentionally.
I did it!
Phi... Phi... Phi...
Phi... Philip Chesterfield.
THE NIGHT BEFORE FINALS
I made the practice test. Solve them.
English
Great. I can come up with answers
left and right.
Do it quickly.
You have other subjects too.
Yes.
When you apply it here,
this becomes four.
What's the square of four?
-Sixteen.
-Right. So square root of 16 is...
So,
X equal square root of 1/2.
Okay. I did it.
Are you asleep?
Irie's
sleeping face.
I got you snacks.
Good morning.
I made coffee. Would you like a cup?
Here.
I'm leaving now.
Kotoko, wait.
Here.
What's this?
Don't open it, yet.
After the test result comes out
and if you're in top 100, you can open it.
This is the lucky charm until then.
To Kotoko
Lucky Charm
Thank you.
You're overreacting on just finals.
Thank you so much.
-I'm going now.
-Okay. Have a wonderful day.
I did this.
I know differentiation.
Correlation is done.
Next,
Cosine is good. Sine is good too.
Double angle is good to go.
Okay. Perfect.
At school,
I was told not to talk to him, but...
Thank you.
Good luck.
You may start now.
I don't know this.
What do I do?
This is the same problem
as Irie came up with.
So as this one...and this one,
and this one.
Answer the questions below.
THREE DAYS LATER
We're done.
Let's go have some fun.
Good idea.
Me too, me too.
Let's go.
I'm not going to let you go.
-Let go.
-No, I won't.
You haven't cared about me lately
so I'm not letting you go today.
I give up.
Hey, where are you going?
Let me handle it. Let's go.
Yeah!
Why?
Isn't she the girl who had crash on you?
She's with another guy already.
It's none of my business.
I see. By the way...
Class A is having a get together
at a coffee shop too.
Do you want to come?
Well,
I guess you aren't coming.
No, actually I'll come today.
What? Really?
Isn't it the first time for you
to do that in these three years?
I thought it would be good sometimes.
Let's go. Hurry.
Number one is Irie.
He's got perfect score.
You're the second place again.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
Naoki Irie
Good for him.
Congratulations on your first place.
You've got the perfect score.
You, too, did it.
What?
Haven't you seen it?
No way.
The 100th place?
The 100th Place? No way.
Irie, I'm in the 100th place.
I did it. I'm so happy.
We did it.
That's not it.
Give that thing back to me.
This one, right?
Don't take it out in public.
Besides, I tell you again,
but don't talk to me at school.
Hey Irie.
The important thing is to sense
if it's possible or not.
If it's just difficult,
you only need to persevere.
Perseverance it is.
What?
Spirit and perseverance
will get the better of the latter.
You know it, too.
The rest of some Chesterfield's quote.
Of course.
Irie, thank you.
My name is on
the same paper as Irie is.
I did it.
That's her. Ms. Aihara in class F.
The girl in the middle.
She's in top 100.
Great.
She's the brightest one since
class F started.
Really.
You finally became famous
on something good.
We're proud to be with you.
You're smiling too much.
I feel so good.
It's suspicious.
It's completely suspicious.
I knew it from the beginning.
In her new home,
there's some kind of secret.
-See you.
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
-Stay safe.
Bro, don't we stand out even more?
Idiot, it's important to go
with the looks first.
-Right.
-Okay.
-Let's go now.
-Yes.
The sunset
feels so good.
It's done.
That's it.
In this kind of upscale neighborhood
is not where she can afford.
She must be worked hard as a maid
by some rich guy.
-Right?
-I agree.
-Poor thing.
-She is.
Bro, look.
Irie.
What's Irie?
It says Irie here.
-Irie?
-Yes.
-What's this then?
-Family.
It means Irie Family.
Irie Family?
Irie?
Well, but,
a last name like Irie
is all over the country.
-Right.
-I agree.
-You're right.
-I think so too.
No kidding.
Bro, over there.
It's Irie.
Let's hide.
-Where?
-Over there.
No...
No way.
It can't be.
Bro!
Tonan University Senior High School
-Good morning.
Kotoko!
Kotoko.
Kotoko, Kotoko.
Kotoko, the house that you live...
Is it Naoki Irie's house?
What?
There's no way.
But I saw you go into his house
with my own eyes.
Gintaro and Dozo are witnesses too.
-I did see it.
You must have had a dream
or something.
Because how can I live with Irie.
-But we saw it, didn't we?
-No!
-Oh, my.
-I saw it.
-Dream? No way.
It can't be. It's a dream.
Dear Kotoko, lucky charm?
Don't say things like that.
-It's not a dream.
-It's not a dream, right?
Wait a minute.
What's this picture?
What?
Is this a two-shot with Irie?
Wait, Kotoko. What does this mean?
I'm sorry.
As I thought,
you're living at Irie's house?
Well, but it's not something
that you're thinking about.
Well, both dads are best friends
and our house was broken, right?
So until we find a next house,
we're staying with them. Yeah.
That means the test this time...
Did Irie teach you?
No wonder.
I couldn't get your good grade
this time.
-That's what was going on.
-He made Kotoko make the 100th.
Irie is a genius for sure.
I'm relieved. It must have not been
Kotoko's own ability.
Wait, everyone. That's too harsh.
I got it.
Okay.
But these two have good vibes.
When they live under
the same roof...
Stop saying such stupid things.
I want to know.
That's never happening.
Because Irie is ignoring me.
He hates me.
Kotoko, poor thing.
Jinko.
But I don't like such a cold person.
I'm okay.
But I'm told
not to tell anybody
about living together, at school.
Everyone, please keep this secret
for now.
Okay. Count on us.
-Right everyone?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
You are so kind.
These two have good vibes.
Aihara.
-What?
-Come with me.
We're not supposed to talk
at school, are we?
Extra! Extra!
Naoki and Kotoko are living together.
A big scoop on Naoki Irie
and Kotoko Aihara.
Extra!
Those two.
Jinko and Satomi are...
What are your friends thinking?
-Take one.
-Please do.
-Please.
-Take one.
Hey, did we do the right thing?
Trust me. We have to clear the decks
for her love.
Well said, Jinko.
It's the scoop between Naoki Irie
and Kotoko Aihara.
Irie.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You wrote me a love letter
so you wouldn't mind it
to get rumors like this,
but it's a nuisance to me.
Don't put me off
from my pace anymore.
I...
am crying. Why?
Home cooked meal, huh.
NEXT EPISODE
If she stays like this,
will she be able to get married?
It'll be nice if Kotoko is Naoki's bride.
What's this?
Marriage is out of question.
Say that clearly.
-What did you do to me?
-It's terrible.
You can't lose.
You have to beat Irie
to be with Kotoko all the time.
I don't know people's mind.
Even if I don't like someone today,
I might like her tomorrow.
What are you doing?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION