Is it true that you will meet a
prospective marriage partner?
She is a granddaughter of the chairman
of a big corporation.
Ruin his formal meeting?
She wants
to proceed with this arrangement.
I thought that I was
getting closer to Irie.
So I still can't believe it.
Kotoko is my dearest.
You played with her feelings.
I can't forgive you.
Then what are you going to do?
I will steal Kotoko from you.
No. I mean I will protect her from you.
Do whatever you want.
Next Sunday,
-do you want to go out with me?
-Okay. Let's do that.
Irie and I are about
to go our separate ways.
I must wonder what kind of future
is awaiting us at the end of the road.
Good morning.
Kotoko has a date today.
Date?
She went out, dressed up nicely.
Do not bother us.
You have someone whom you want to
marry. Then you know how I feel.
Just like you care about that woman,
I care about Kotoko.
I've never seen Kotoko
so heartbroken.
Really? Who dares go out
with such a woman?
Naoki, are you sure about this?
Son.
Sorry.
I have some documents to read
by Monday.
What is he thinking?
I love it.
I really like the car chase scene.
It was so cool.
Today is a day to release our stress.
Let's go to a video arcade.
I'd love to.
Let's have fun.
Let's go crazy.
Let's do it, Kotoko.
-I'm ready to serve the country.
Something is coming.
Go, Kin-chan.
Good. I got it.
One more time.
I didn't expect to have so much fun
with Kin-chan.
It allowed me to forget about Irie,
even though it was only for a while.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
You had a date with Kin-chan?
GOODBYE, IRIE
Kin-chan and I have been good friends
since we were in the high school.
But this is the first time
we went out together.
And?
And how was the date?
Kin-chan is not good enough, huh?
That's not what I mean.
I enjoyed it
more than I expected.
I was having so much fun
that I felt that time flied.
And?
I had so much fun today. Thank you.
Me, too. I don't know when was the last
time I had so much fun.
See you.
Kotoko.
Can you go out with me again?
I will find some other places
you would enjoy.
You don't need to take it seriously.
Just think of it as a casual date.
When you want to have fun, call me.
Sure.
Let's go out again, Kin-chan.
-Kotoko?
To tell you the truth,
I've agreed to go out with him again.
That's a quick development.
Finally you've become
a normal college student.
It's not like that.
A date? A party? Whatever.
Have a seat, Kotoko.
Listen, Kotoko.
If you can forget about the heartless
Irie even for a moment
and enjoy your life.
Satomi.
You don't need a boyfriend.
Do not make a snap judgment
about a boyfriend.
Just have fun
with Kin-chan or any other boys.
That's right. Find something to cheer
you up. That's what you need right now.
"Kin-chan or any other boys"'?
I feel bad for Kin-chan.
Listen.
If you really feel that way,
even a little bit,
it means that
you like Kin-chan.
Is that right?
You care about him.
We call it "love."
What do you think? You love Kin-chan?
Well... I'm not sure about that, but...
Kin-chan is
a good guy.
Come on.
Finally you realized that?
What a brilliant performance!
Yes.
I love Stravinsky.
It tells me something about you, Naoki.
He changes his compositional style
in every work.
That's why they call him "Chameleon."
I think you also have
such a mysterious side in you.
I am attracted to you by that.
You overestimate me.
But I was really upset.
Did you see the person
sitting in front of us?
As soon as the performance started,
the person fell asleep.
It was obvious that the person was dozing.
I can't believe it.
It was one of the best seats.
Why are you smiling, Naoki?
Nothing.
Let's go.
This restaurant
only plays opera music.
Do you like opera music?
Of course I do.
I like Tristan.
Tristan, huh? That's a good one.
I'm home.
You are so late.
I told you that I would be late,
because of a date with Sahoko.
I know that. But how long
did the concert last?
We had a dinner together after that.
I told you about that, too.
I hope that Sahoko and you
didn't do any indecent things.
Indecent things?
What are you talking about?
I'm not a teenager.
We are dating with marriage in mind.
You can imagine whatever you want,
but keep it in mind.
But I have not approved
of your marrying her.
Remember what my father said.
"It's your choice whom you want to marry."
When he said that, you agreed with him.
I did, but...
I had Kotoko in my mind
when we talked about that.
Anyway,
regarding my marriage,
I will make a decision by myself,
no matter what your opinion is.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm home.
Kotoko, you are late, too.
Did you have a date, too?
"Too"? It means Irie had a date?
We went to a concert.
I see.
What? I didn't have a date.
I forgot to tell you, but I started
helping at my father's restaurant.
Helping at his restaurant?
You want to be a chef like him?
No. No way I can become a chef.
I'm glad to hear that.
I don't want to see customers
having a stomach ache.
I know I can't cook,
but I could be some help
in serving the food.
So I'm learning.
Kin-chan is also working there
and is helping me.
It sounds like a date.
I don't know about you, but I wouldn't mix
business with relationship.
How about him?
What are you talking about?
Apologize to Kin-chan.
See. I was right.
Even if that's so,
it's none of your business.
That's true.
I have no interest at all
in your relationship.
Calm down, the both of you.
Wait.
This sounds like
a lovers' quarrel.
No, it's not.
No?
I don't need dinner tomorrow night,
either.
Going out again?
None of your business. Good night.
Kotoko...
I have to prepare for tomorrow's classes.
So please excuse me.
And I have dinner at the restaurant
every night from now on.
Good night.
It's over, honey.
Naoki holds on his course
to marry Sahoko.
Kotoko is dating
with a chef apprentice Kin-chan.
And, since she is helping
at her father's restaurant,
the boy and Kotoko will get closer.
Well...
I got a call from Kanamori yesterday.
According to him,
Chairman Oizumi wants to have
a formal engagement ceremony
as soon as I leave the hospital.
You are doing great.
You may be able to go home soon.
-Really?
-Yes.
You have been doing great.
Thank you for performing
such a successful surgery on me.
But you have a dream to be a doctor.
It is not a long-time dream.
Are you giving up your dream?
You want to talk to me?
Yes.
You know that I'll be discharged
from the hospital this weekend. Right?
Yeah.
My heart is not in a good shape, is it?
I have to have a surgery soon.
Am I right?
I know that, even though you guys
are keeping it from me.
I can tell it from your mother's attitude.
I will return to the company
before having surgery.
I want to settle
all the issues my company is facing
before having surgery.
But stress
will worsen your heart condition
if you return to the company.
But I cannot allow you
to marry someone
whom you don't even love.
"I don't even love"?
You have no idea how I feel.
Listen, Naoki.
You are my son.
Your happiness is more important
than my business. That's why--
That's enough. This is my life.
I will make my own decision.
So, Father...
Take care of yourself.
That's all you need to do.
Focus on your health.
MEDICAL IMMUNOLOGY
Kotoko, this goes to Table Number 3.
Sure.
I take this, so you serve the dish.
Thank you, Kin-chan.
They look like a good couple.
Hey, everyone. Daddy is home.
I'm home.
Yeah!
Hey, Yuki.
-Nice to see you at home.
-Thank you.
Are you ready?
-Mr. Irie!
-Iri-chan.
Honey!
Just kidding.
As you can see, I feel great.
I've made a full comeback.
You scared the hell out of us.
I'm sorry.
Mrs. Irie, it tells you that he is fully
recovered.
Let's celebrate it today.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Here you go. Enjoy.
-Wow.
-Looks great.
I made all your favorite dishes.
I'm so happy.
I was tired of hospital meals.
You are not fully recovered yet.
So do not smoke. No alcohol.
No sweets. No greasy food.
Don't say that.
I went through weeks of tasteless meals
in the hospital.
That's not the point.
Well, your son is right, honey.
No excessive eating.
Okay.
Now let's start the celebration.
Get your glass.
Can we have your words first, honey?
My sudden hospitalization
caused you so much trouble.
I'm really sorry.
Thanks to your support,
I got better enough to come home.
I'm so grateful.
Cheers!
Everyone, eat.
I will enjoy Ai-chan's signature dishes.
-Bon appetite.
I want meat.
Then I take fish.
Oh, no, I can't grab it.
Home sweet home.
It's nice to have a meal
with all the family together.
Family is the best.
What? Visitor?
This is strange.
I didn't invite anyone to this party.
It's my guest.
Who did Naoki invite?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Chairman Oizumi.
Hi, Mr. Irie. I'm glad to see that you
came back home.
Since Naoki invited us, we are here
to celebrate your recovery.
Thank you for coming all the way.
-I really appreciate your kindness.
-You look great.
Naoki.
I told you that this would be a party
only for family members.
That's why I invited them.
Father, this is Sahoko Oizumi.
Very nice to meet you.
Please sit here.
Kotoko, move.
Please have a seat.
-Please sit down.
-Thank you.
-You sit here.
Honey, take this.
This is my wife.
You may have met her before.
That's Yuki, Naoki's younger brother.
How do you do?
Mr. Irie.
We want to celebrate
your recovery together.
This is for you. I hope you like it.
What is this?
Wow.
Here you go.
This is so delicious. Sahoko,
did you make all of them by yourself?
Hope you like it.
I like it? I love it.
Seasoning is perfect
and accentuates the flavor
of each ingredient.
This is one of a kind.
Come on, honey.
Your praise is over the top.
Don't make Mr. Aihara feel bad.
He is a professional chef.
Wow.
You cooked it without sugar
and animal fat, didn't you?
That's right.
I hear that Mr. Irie had a heart problem.
What a thoughtful lady you are!
This is so delicious.
This is brilliant cooking.
Chairman, this is my friend Aihara.
He owns a very popular Japanese
restaurant.
I see.
A professional chef is eating
my dishes? I'm embarrassed.
You shouldn't be. You could offer
these dishes in a restaurant.
You substitute sweet drink for sugar, huh?
You are absolutely right.
Where did you learn such a classic
cooking method?
My mother taught me. That's all.
Then your mother must be
up with the professional chefs.
I should learn it from you.
This is unbelievable.
It's so delicious.
Right?
So you must be Mr. Irie's best friend.
I should have introduced myself first.
I'm Aihara.
Mr. and Mrs. Aihara are nice to invite
me to this family party.
I'm sure you are like
a family member to them.
And is this your daughter,
who lives with the Irie family?
Nice to meet you. I'm Kotoko Aihara.
It's nothing.
I hear that Mrs. Irie adores her.
That's why I have been curious.
Grandpa, you are staring at Kotoko.
It's rude.
You are right.
You are so cute
that I couldn't take my eyes off.
Thank you for your compliment.
Kotoko, can we talk privately?
I've wanted to have a talk with you.
Sorry about my grandpa.
His attitude was rude.
Don't worry about it.
To be honest with you,
both my grandpa and I
are jealous of you.
Why?
That's because you have lived
with Naoki for more than two years.
-Yes.
-Besides, Naoki's mother loves you.
That's why I envy you.
Well...
Sahoko.
Why do you like Irie?
On that day, my grandpa
wanted to talk to me
about something important.
It turned out that it was about meeting
Naoki as a potential marriage partner.
Are you okay?
He was such a gentleman.
And he was kind.
I fell in love with him
at first sight.
I didn't even dream that I would meet him
as a potential marriage partner.
So I was stunned
when I saw him in the formal meeting.
I thought that it was my destiny.
I also fell in love with Irie
at first sight.
TONAN HIGH SCHOOL
ENTRANCE CEREMONY
I had a crush on him
for two years since then.
After a strange turn of events,
we ended up living together.
But I never thought that
it was my destiny.
Nothing happened between
the two of us as time passed.
I wish I could have had
such a romantic encounter.
You wish you could have had?
I mean I wish I can have
such a romantic encounter.
To tell you the truth,
I was going to turn down the meeting.
I'm still in college and I thought
I was too young to marry.
But my grandpa convinced me
to meet him anyway.
Then it happened.
I never imagined this to happen.
You never know what happens next.
I agree.
But
I'm
scared.
Why?
It seems to me that Naoki
is trying to be nice to me
and I feel distant from the real side
of him as he does.
Sometimes I don't understand
what he is really thinking.
I'm losing my confidence.
It's very strange, isn't it?
It's because
you really love Irie.
It's not strange at all.
If you fall in love with someone,
that's how you feel, isn't it?
Even though you are determined
to pursue your love,
a trivial thing
could destroy your confidence.
Sahoko, you are beautiful and elegant.
If a perfect woman like you
loses her confidence,
it could happen to anyone.
Even if you are depressed,
you can be so happy
and feel walking on air
when he is nice to you just once.
And you believe in your chance
and become the happiest person
in the world.
But
you will get scared right away
if he gives you the cold shoulder again.
Such a cycle repeats forever.
No matter how determined you are,
you cannot avoid
emotional ups and downs.
Kotoko,
you have been in love with someone.
I can tell it.
That's not true.
I can tell that...
...Irie...
...really loves
you.
He is totally in love with you.
How do you know that for sure?
How do I know?
I cannot answer that.
But I think that I am right about that.
So don't worry.
-I'm sorry to disturb your family party.
-Don't be.
Mr. Irie,
take care of yourself.
As soon as I return to my office,
I will pay you a visit.
First we will have formal
engagement ceremony.
-Is that right, Naoki and Sahoko?
-Yes.
I appreciate your help.
Mr. Irie, let's discuss the date later.
Sure. Thank you for coming today.
Let's go, Sahoko.
I will take a walk with Naoki
before going home.
Naoki, you don't mind?
Of course not. I will take her home.
Thank you.
Good-bye, everyone.
Good-bye.
You want to go?
Sure.
I'm so tired.
They violated our territory.
I should sprinkle salt for purification.
Honey, calm down.
Are you sure about this?
It's Naoki's decision.
We can't do anything.
Kotoko, do it tomorrow.
You must be tired, too.
I'm not sleepy yet,
so I will finish the dishes.
It was a busy day. You must be tired.
You can go to bed now.
But I feel bad for you.
Don't worry. I can finish it quickly.
Kotoko.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I kept telling you that
you would be our daughter-in-law.
But it didn't go as I expected.
I tried to help you two get closer.
But at the end
it hurt you.
I feel very sorry.
That's not your fault.
I'm still hoping that
you will marry my son.
Thank you.
You really love me, huh?
I'm so honored.
You are
like a real mother to me.
You will be my mother from now on,
no matter who Irie will marry.
Kotoko...
You mean it?
I'm home.
It took you so long, huh?
Where are my parents?
Already in bed?
Yes.
I see.
Good night.
Hey.
Sahoko is a nice lady.
She is pretty and a good cook.
That's not what I meant.
After we talked, I'm convinced that
she really loves you.
Now I understand
why you are totally in love with her.
You find a good guy. Okay?
AIHARA
IN PREPARATION
Good morning.
You are the only one?
Where are Kin-chan and Mr. Odawara?
They are out for shopping.
I see.
Then I will do the cleaning.
Hey, Kotoko. You have a moment?
We need to talk
before the restaurant opens.
Dad, what do you want?
We must leave Irie's house.
I'm sure you realized
everything yesterday.
Naoki is serious about the marriage.
If that's the case,
it's awkward for us to live with them.
The Oizumi family doesn't like you
to keep living with Naoki.
You should step aside.
That's why we should move out.
An old house? A small house?
I don't care.
I guess you are right.
I know it's so hard for you.
I'm not cool.
I promised myself not to give up on Irie
no matter how hurt I got.
Despite that...
It's important to know when to quit.
Naoki may be impressed
if you give up in a dignified way.
I hope you will forget
about Naoki soon.
How many times have I wished
upon a shooting star?
But I must
stop doing that.
Honey, don't make such a sad face.
I can't help it.
He will be engaged formally.
This is the worst day of my life.
Come on, honey.
I don't mean to depress you more,
but remember that we still have a wedding
ceremony and a wedding party.
Don't tell me that.
I'm going to cry.
I'm sorry.
Father and Mother, it's time to go.
Right. Let's go.
Mother.
Fine.
Hello, Kotoko.
Good morning, Kin-chan.
Good morning.
-Shall we go?
-Yes.
Let's begin.
Please accept it.
I will accept it with great humility.
I will keep it
forever.
I will accept it with great humility.
I will keep it forever.
What do you want to eat?
What do you feel like right now?
How about Okonomiyaki?
Yes, your Okonomiyaki.
I haven't eaten it for a while.
You like my takoyaki, too.
Right now Irie is...
Kotoko?
Are you okay?
Why am I not?
Where do you want to go today?
I would like to go
to a video arcade again.
I want you to grab a stuffed animal
for me.
It's so cute with a red hat.
Let's get married.
Will you marry me?
How did you know that I wanted this?
I told you.
I know what you think.
Ms. Kotoko Aihara,
will you marry me?
Did Kin-chan propose to you?
Kin-chan is a better match for you than
Irie.
It is my dearest Sahoko's wedding.
I can't back out now.
Let's run a restaurant together to serve
the best home cuisine.
That is my dream.
I have endured a one-sided love
for many years.
I'm tired of the hopeless love.
I will leave the house.
Everything is about to end.
You two are a perfect match.
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION