Are you okay, Yuki?!
The surgery should be done immediately.
Your brother fell sick!
Don't you think you're too selfish?
Know that it's important
to communicate
your feelings to the people around you.
Thanks, Kotoko.
Graduating university and taking over
my father's business
are things my parents
are expecting me to do.
Brother...
Of course, things were happening
without my knowledge.
I assumed that
there was no progress
with my relationship with Irie.
And as days went by,
Yuki's surgery was a success,
and by the time he left the hospital,
it was New Year's Eve.
For couples,
it was the extremely anticipated
Christmas season.
But for singles...
You're welcome.
Hey there, young man!
Will you refill my water, too?
You only ordered coffee and water.
How much longer are going to sit here?
Wait! Actually...
Irie, I was wondering what you were doing
on Christmas Eve.
Are you coming back home?
Work.
Hey.
Since he's working at a cafe, there's
no way he can take off Christmas Eve.
Are you working that day, too,
Ms. Matsumoto?
Yup!
I'm going to work hard with Irie.
We have many reservations that day.
Then I'll make a reservation, too!
Oh, would you like to?
Our cafe will only be serving
full course dinners that day.
It's exclusive to couples, too.
Dinner for two?! And 20,000 yen?!
There's no way...
It's fine!
If I don't get to spend it with Irie,
I'll spend it with my friends!
Kotoko?!
Kotoko!
Hey, Jinko! Satomi!
So, about Christmas this year...
Actually, I wanted to introduce you
to someone today.
-Introduce me?
-Yup.
There he is!
Huh? What?
-Hey, do you have a minute?
-Sure.
Hey, come with me!
Let me introduce you.
My boyfriend Narasaki is in a band.
I'm Narasaki, nice to meet you.
My boyfriend is Ryo Takamiya.
He studies law.
Nice to meet you, I'm Ryo Takamiya.
Boyfriend?
Both of you?! How? When?!
I wanted to introduce you to him
before Christmas, no matter what.
Oh, I see.
Congratulations to both of you.
Thanks!
So, right before my first Christmas
as a college student,
I faced a dire situation where I was
the only one who was single.
I have a feeling this is going to be
the worst Christmas ever!
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
MY BOYFRIEND IS SANTA CLAUS
Oh, dear... Oh, dear...
How melancholic.
Kotoko!
Hey, Kin. Aren't you working?
Don't slack off.
I'm almost done.
But, anyway, I heard Jinko and Satomi
have boyfriends now!
Well, it's true...
That means that they'll be
spending a passionate
Christmas Eve with them, right?
They're spending Christmas with their
boyfriends for the first time, of course.
This...
is serious!
That means you're going to be...
alone, Kotoko.
Please don't remind me.
Aren't you lonely?
Aren't you sad?
So, I have a special plan for you, Kotoko.
There you are!
Jinko?
Kotoko, I need to talk to you!
You can't spend Christmas Eve
with Narasaki anymore?!
But this was going to be
your first Christmas Eve together!
I know, right? But Narasaki's like:
"I'm going to play in a Christmas show.
Christmas is the day of love.
As a musician, I have to spread the love
to the world that day."
Can't you see him after the show?
The show's going to be in Sendai,
not Tokyo.
It ends late, too.
There's no way
he can come back that night.
But he's working towards becoming
a professional musician, right?
You should support that.
I understand that! But...
I wish he would spread the love to me,
not just the world!
Do you understand?
-Yeah. Eat up.
-So, you're going to eat?
I'll eat away the pain!
There you are!
Can you believe this?! Ryo...
Ryo... Ryo...
He told me
he can't spend Christmas with me!
Satomi, you too?!
No way!
Ryo said
he really can't take the day off
from work.
He said it's because he wants
to buy me a present.
But what we crave is their heart,
not material things!
Exactly! Guys really don't understand
how girls feel.
I want to be with him that night,
no matter what!
Why can't he understand that?!
Seriously!
All right!
Let's forget about the guys
who don't understand us!
This Christmas,
let's have fun with just us girls!
I'm in!
But are you sure, Kotoko?
Yeah, isn't Irie coming home
for Christmas?
Actually, he can't get out of work either.
Yuko Matsumoto is working with him, too.
-The worst!
I think I'm dealing with the worst case
of a guy who doesn't understand
a girl's feelings.
Though, I'm not even Irie's girlfriend.
That doesn't matter!
Men can never be trusted!
Exactly! You can only believe
your girlfriends!
Put your hand out, girls!
Let's swear that the three of us will
spend a fun Christmas together!
Agreed!
Betrayal is not an option!
Yes!
Hey, hey, hey! Wait a minute!
How about me?!
Uh-oh! Now you're scaring me!
You can't just put me in the same category
as some other guy.
If you're having a party,
count me in, too, will you?
I'll prepare a Christmas feast for you,
how about that?
I won't betray you.
Let's make it
a fun night together!
Together... Together...
Together...
What's wrong?
Kin, I know you're training, but you're
in the food and beverage industry.
Yeah, how about Aihara?
Exactly. There's no restaurant that'll
allow you to take Christmas Eve off.
What?
Wouldn't they end earlier, at least?
Your reservation is confirmed.
-Thank you very much!
-Spending Christmas with Kotoko!
Christmas with Kotoko!
Aren't you excited for Christmas?!
-Let's see, two, four, six, ten...
-What?
No way! The tables...
and counters are all completely reserved!
Of course, it's Christmas Eve!
The first rush starts at 6
and the second starts at 8!
Recently, there's been many walk-ins, too.
It's going to be busy!
But isn't Christmas a Christian holiday?
Why would you eat
Japanese cuisine that day?!
But it's something
we should be grateful for.
Since the boss is leaving around 9,
we're going to be
the only two working.
Why? Where's he going?
He said he has something important.
Probably some party.
Party?
Must be a Christmas party!
A Christmas party?!
Oh, my God!
That's right!
His company's celebrating
its 20th anniversary.
So, that's why, on Christmas Eve,
we're having a party
at Hotel Prince!
Is that so?
Congratulations!
Why, yes. Oh?
My dear.
My, my.
I wouldn't be here
without everyone's support.
It's a way to express my gratitude.
And to top it off,
Kotoko's father said
he'll come by after work, too!
He said that?
Yup. Among the party attendees
are good customers of Aihara.
And there's a lot of people
I want him to meet at this party.
So, I'm hoping
you can come, too, Kotoko.
That sounds wonderful!
Christmas at Hotel Prince?
Right?
Let's swear that the three of us will
spend a fun Christmas together!
Agreed!
Betrayal is not an option!
Yes!
But I'm sorry.
I already have engagements that day.
Engagements?
Is it with a man?
Kotoko!
Are you seeing someone besides my son?
No way! It's not that.
I already promised Jinko and Satomi.
I would've loved to go
since you invited me, but...
Well...
can't you do anything about those plans?
There's no way out of it this time.
It's a long story.
I see.
Well, that's unfortunate.
But there's nothing we can do about it.
Hey, Mom, how about brother?
He's coming to the party, too, right?
Actually,
he can't go either.
What? Are you serious?
He said he had to work at the cafe
on Christmas Eve.
Oh, man. That's a drag.
I know.
I can't believe he's missing
his father's company party.
Well, this is rare.
You never ask to meet
at places like this.
-Ginger ale, please.
-Yes, right away.
So, what did you want to talk about?
You heard about my company's
anniversary party from your mom, right?
I want you to attend.
Please.
I know your ulterior motive, Dad.
You want to introduce me
to the guests
as the company's successor, right?
But I...
still haven't decided whether
I'm succeeding your company.
I understand that.
But will you please attend,
just this once?
Don't worry about what's to come.
It'd be great if you made an appearance.
Please, just this once.
SANSEIDO USED BOOKS
-MEDICAL INTERN
-DIAGNOSTICS, EMERGENCY
You can do anything, Irie.
You'll invent different types of medicine.
Become a doctor and cure all illnesses!
-He's up early.
-Yes, he is.
Irie, why are you here?!
What?
I can't come back to my own home?
No, it's just been a while.
But why did you decide to come here?
I'm here to get my suit.
-Suit?!
I can't attend the party with jeans.
You're going to attend
our Christmas Eve party?!
Work's letting me off early,
but I'll be late.
I won't stay long either.
Yes! Brother's going to be there, too!
Thank you! Father will be
very happy about this!
So, Irie's going to the party after all...
That means if I attend,
I'll be able to spend Christmas with him!
It's a hard decision,
but betraying my friends
for this chance is forgivable, right?
I would love to attend the party.
Heard you can't go.
You're spending Christmas
with your usual girlfriends, right?
Well, you know, so...
That's disappointing. It would've been fun
if you were there.
Irie, um, I...
Yes, I know!
Will you please convince Kotoko
to attend, too?
Well, there's nothing we can do about it.
You made your decision already.
But still.
I'm sure your girlfriends
would betray you in a heartbeat.
It's Christmas Eve!
No, their friendship is special.
Isn't that right, Kotoko?
Sure, well, but...
Are you sure about that?
Brother.
Let's get you that suit!
The one you wore for your graduation!
Irie, you're such a bully!
But, oh, well...
I promised I wouldn't betray them.
Christmas
Look at that!
So, the cake is going to be
the exclusive Shibuya one, right?
I'll order one for us.
-I'm so excited! It looks so good!
-I know, right?
Going to the party with Irie...
Kotoko?
-Kotoko?
-Kotoko! Are you there?
-Yes!
Look at this!
They look delicious!
I'll prepare the chicken.
I'll bring games.
Of course,
Christmas is all about presents!
-Yes!
-Yup.
They're both really looking forward to it.
This was the right decision.
White Christmas, yeah!
CHRISTMAS EVE
-Looks good!
-All right!
Are you all ready to go?
Yes!
Oh? Where's Naoki?
He's coming directly from his job.
Mr. Aihara will also come a little late
from his restaurant.
I see, then we're all ready.
Let's go!
Yes!
Kotoko, are you sure about this?
Even my son made arrangements to attend.
Yes, but unfortunately, I already made
a promise to my friends.
But, anyway, thank you very much
for letting us use your place.
Jinko and Satomi were ecstatic!
Really? I'm glad it worked out.
We're going to be late tonight.
So, I'm grateful that you and your friends
will be here at our place.
Recently,
it may be because it's the end
of the year,
there's been thieves lurking around!
So, it's safer if you girls are here,
having a blast.
-Yes, thank you very much.
-My pleasure.
Well, it's still regrettable
that you can't come with us,
but have fun with your friends!
I will!
Let's go already!
All right, let's go.
See you later!
Irie in a suit...
He must look so handsome...
Party, huh?
Will you dance with me?
It would be my pleasure.
No, don't do that!
It's totally girls' night!
Girls' night with Jinko and Satomi
Over there.
How cute!
Christmas is so fun!
This is too long.
How long is this thing?
I didn't expect this to happen!
There!
What should I wish for...
as a Christmas present?
MERRY CHRISTMAS
All set!
I was supposed to be working with Irie.
It wasn't supposed to be like this!
Merry Christmas!
But what a coincidence.
I didn't expect you to be working here
on Christmas.
So, what do you think?
Can I take you out for dinner
after you're done?
But you're already eating.
For two.
Excuse me, Miss Waitress.
May I get more water?
Waitress! Waitress Matsumoto!
May I get some water?
I wish I was waiting
for Irie to come over right now.
They must be here soon.
Hello, Jinko? What's up?
I'm sorry, Kotoko!
Narasaki's show in Sendai got canceled
due to the snow.
So, he hitchhiked back
to Tokyo to be with me!
He hitchhiked back
since the trains weren't running!
I can't leave Narasaki here
and go to the party.
Will you please let me choose
my man over us, just this once?!
Got it. I'll let Satomi know, too.
It's fine!
It's an unforeseen circumstance.
Tell Narasaki I said hello.
Well...
I'll just have a blast with Satomi, then.
Hello? What's up, Satomi?
Sorry, Kotoko.
Ryo was lying about having work today.
He just came over with roses
without notice!
He was planning to surprise me all along.
He made reservations at a restaurant
way in advance.
It's one of those "surprises," right?
So...
I feel really bad, but...
I understand.
I'll spend Christmas with Jinko, then.
I'm so sorry.
I'll treat you guys next time.
Don't worry about it. Have fun.
Thanks!
They betrayed me after all!
If I knew this would happen,
I should've attended the party, too!
Oh, yeah, I should head over there now!
Jinko and Satomi got last-minute plans
with their boyfriends, so...
now I'm here.
I told you so.
You can't trust your girlfriends.
Betrayed by your friends?
How stupid are you?
That's not very appealing to my brother.
No, no, no.
No, that's not good.
It'll look too bad.
Thank you very much!
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Yes, you got it!
There's one more reservation to go.
-We can handle this.
-Yes.
But I've never seen the restaurant get
that packed before.
We got to be grateful for Christmas!
-They're here.
-Welcome!
Welcome!
Thanks.
This is a star-rated place.
While preserving tradition,
they're known for their unconventional
neo-Japanese cuisine.
Really?
You have such refined taste, Ryo!
-You're so cool!
-Thanks.
Satomi?!
Kin, what are you doing here?
Oh, was this Kotoko's father's restaurant?
It's your friend's place?!
I'm impressed, Satomi.
You got me there.
Satomi, didn't you have plans
with Kotoko?
Where's Kotoko?
Sorry, Kin.
My boyfriend surprised me with plans.
-I'm Ryo Takamiya.
-Is Kotoko alone right now?
She's with Jinko.
I'm sure they're having a blast by now.
I see.
Wow, that looks delicious!
Veggie and tiger prawn tempura.
I would never think to have
Japanese food on Christmas.
-I know.
-I think it's great!
Jin--
What was that?
I'm helping
with Narasaki's show right now.
Aren't you supposed to be
at the party with Kotoko?
Actually, Narasaki surprised me today.
Kotoko should be with Satomi right now.
All right then, have fun.
Merry Christmas.
Love, love, love
Lust, lust, lust
No, this is love, love, love
Love, love, love
But still,
I'm sure your girlfriends
will betray you in a heartbeat.
It's Christmas Eve!
Lust, lust, lust
Love, love, love
Christmas
With Irie
I'm hungry.
Jinko and Satomi were supposed
to bring the chicken and cake.
So, I only prepared snacks.
INSTANT NOODLES
Salt ramen, huh?
It's Christmas Eve!
What is everyone up to?
Is that so?
On Christmas Eve,
couples enjoy dinner together.
But are some of us
spending Christmas alone right now?
I'm sure you're out there.
You should ask yourself whether
you have a horrible personality.
But Christmas sure is a fun holiday!
I'm all about it!
My brain explodes since it's too much!
Hilarious, right?
What do you think?
But anyway...
This is sad.
Sad and alone...
Isn't it fun?!
How's that?
Please, tell me.
What was that?
Recently,
there's been thieves lurking around!
Could it be?
No.
It's possible, since...
the Iries are rich.
What should I do?
Oh, yeah!
Thief!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?
Irie?!
Sorry. Are you okay?
You look so handsome.
What?
Well, because...
you were getting hit in the head
while looking so elegant.
Plus,
it's your own home!
You're the one who did it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, man...
Sorry about that.
I got scared of the sound of the locks.
I thought you were a thief.
I accidentally tried to open the door
with my apartment key first.
You hit me so hard.
I'm sorry.
But what happened
to your father's party?
You didn't go?
I went.
But I left in the middle of it.
I got bored saying hello to the heads
of the companies he works with.
Father must be so mad right now.
But, anyway, how are you?
Weren't you having a party
with your friends?
Well, actually, both Jinko and Satomi...
got last-minute plans
with their boyfriends.
What loyal friends.
Don't mention it.
What's this smell?
This?
Chicken!
Did you bring that for me?
Of course not.
I got hungry.
You can't really eat
at a buffet party.
I only ate instant noodles myself.
Well, what a night.
Well done.
-Let's close up and leave!
-Yeah.
Can I ask you something?
I want to try something out.
-Will you let me stay a little longer?
-Sure.
Thank you very much.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, KOTOKO
I'm having dinner with Irie
on Christmas Eve!
Oh, yeah.
I set it up for Jinko and Satomi.
Doesn't it feel like Christmas now?
Does it?
It's my...
first one since becoming a young adult.
Since...
my mom passed away
when I was young,
my dad was always busy
working at the restaurant
until midnight on Christmas.
Well, I went to parties with friends,
but...
I never actually spent
a Christmas with family before.
Even if it was just a coincidence,
this was the most
Christmas-like Christmas
and I got to spend it with Irie.
It's a dream come true.
I think this is the best
Christmas present I've ever received.
Love, love
Love, love, love
-Satomi.
-Yeah?
Merry Christmas.
-No!
-It's real!
Welcome, can I help you?
-The Santa!
-What? Oh!
They're over here.
-There?
-Yes!
It's right over here.
There it is!
That was the last one,
you made it!
All right!
I'm going to go buy a cake.
We have to have cake on Christmas!
What a waste if we don't!
I'm sure they'll have it
at the convenience store.
I brought one.
The cake.
Merry Christmas!
No way! Are you serious?
It's a present from Santa!
Of course not.
Then, you got this?
Who else?
You knew I was going to be home,
so you got this for me?
You're excessively self-conscious.
A girl at work begged me
to buy the last cake because
she couldn't leave until it sold out.
Wait for me, Kotoko,
I'm bringing you a feast!
Merry Christmas!
Then let's make a wish.
-That's for birthdays.
-What?
Was it?
It's a surprise!
Thank you, Irie.
Whatever, it wasn't meant for you.
But this cake is the size for two.
It's a coincidence.
You get the Santa, Irie.
I don't care.
It looks dark in there.
Hey, let's make a wish anyway.
Come on.
Then... you do it.
Are you sure?
-Are you getting married into the Iries?!
-Oh, stop it!
Congratulations on entering
your second year of college!
A new rival enrolled in our school!
You have to fight now.
Kotoko, I think you'd make a fine wife.
You would be the ideal bride!
I've had enough!
That's why I don't want to be here.
Irie!
Why didn't you tell your father?
Don't tell anyone yet.
You want to be happy
with the one you love.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION