Now...
Naoki Irie and Sahoko Oizumi's
engagement is arranged.
I'm happy for it.
I respectfully accept it.
I will keep this promise forever.
Miss Kotoko Aihara.
Will you marry me?
You were proposed to by Kin-chan?
Come this way.
Sit down here.
So, what did you tell him?
I haven't said anything, yet.
What are you going to tell him?
I... I don't know.
I like Kin-chan a lot,
but we've been friends.
I understand.
I think for you,
Kin-chan suits better than Irie.
To be honest.
-Satomi.
-Think about it.
Irie has been suggestive to you
and he even kissed you.
Then he engaged
with a different girl easily.
Being your best friend,
I can't forgive him.
Right. During all that,
Kin-chan has been
in love with only Kotoko
the whole time.
You've said that
when you're with Kin-chan,
you have fun.
I get that you admire Irie
who has something
that you don't have,
but the person you can stay
together with longer,
the person who makes you happy
for the rest of your life,
is a guy like Kin-chan.
That's what I think.
It makes women happier
to be loved than to love.
Take this chance
to consider Kin-chan seriously.
Here's the sake for you.
All right.
You're cheerful as always.
Thank you.
I wish a cheerful guy like you
were in my restaurant.
-No, no.
-I own
a Japanese restaurant.
-Where?
-I'm not telling you.
-Tell me.
-Do you want to know?
If Irie learns that I was proposed to
by Kin-chan,
what would he think?
Would Irie
be surprised even a little bit?
Or...
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
You've decided to contribute
to us in a great amount.
Thank you so much.
MIRACLE OF A SHOOTING STAR
Stop being so formal.
We'll be a family soon.
Let's help out each other.
Thank you so much.
So, what will be
the day of wedding?
-Please decide as you wish.
-Okay.
Chairman.
Actually, my father will
be having heart surgery
this year.
Naoki.
You told us that we'd become
a family.
So I don't want to hide anything.
Naoki.
What a guy.
Therefore,
I'd like the wedding to be after
the surgery,
next year, if possible.
I see.
It's my precious Sahoko's wedding.
We might need that much time
to prepare.
It's the June bride, isn't it?
Then it'll be around this time
next year.
-I see.
-Okay.
Does he still have time?
Chairman, your next appointment
is getting close.
Oh, all right.
See you then.
It's like a dream
to become family
with a guy like you.
Thank you.
We're home.
Welcome home.
I'm tired.
You're not 100 percent, yet.
-You'd better rest now.
-Yeah.
Naoki.
Thank you.
But,
are you sure
it's okay with you?
You understood that when you
met Sahoko, don't you?
Why would I complain
when I get to marry a girl like her?
You're right.
Naoki is
really marrying that girl.
We can't go back anymore.
Miss Kotoko Aihara.
Will you marry me?
Marrying Kin-chan, huh?
I can't picture myself.
-Yes.
-Kotoko, may I come in?
Yes.
What is it, Dad?
Kotoko.
Can you take a look at this?
-Is this the new house?
-Yeah.
How do you like it?
It's bigger than before.
It's a little far from the station,
but the rent is reasonable.
Didn't you tell me that you
didn't like this kind?
You said you liked
a single-family home.
Owning a single-family home was
a promise that I made with your mom.
But it's impossible to get one
right now.
So we'll go with a rental for now.
If you marry a man,
I'll aim for owning
a two generation home with him.
Of course, if there's a guy
who wants to marry you.
Dad.
Will you be happy
if I marry Kin-chan?
Is anything going on
between you and him?
-I'm just asking.
-Oh.
Kinnosuke, huh?
Well, he sure is
talented when it comes to cooking.
He's warmhearted and caring.
So honest and sincere.
If he marries you,
I'll have a successor
for my restaurant.
I'll be happy about it.
I agree.
But you don't have to force yourself
to marry him.
Your feelings are the most important
thing to me.
If you love this man the most
and he'll make you happy,
then the restaurant
has nothing to do with it.
Don't turn around yet.
-After you get up there.
-Okay.
Not yet.
-Not yet.
-Yes.
Here we come.
One, two, three, ta-da!
Amazing.
Kotoko, look.
It's so beautiful.
How about that, Kotoko?
Let's go.
I know the best seat.
The special seat for you.
There, there.
There, there. This way, this way.
See?
How about this?
Take a look.
How do you like it?
It's huge.
It's so cool.
It's impossible to block this.
I'm
telling you that I don't mind
being in the same house with you.
Does that mean that
you don't
hate me?
You're hard to deal with,
but I don't hate you.
Kotoko.
Rainbow Bridge is over there.
Hey, Kotoko.
Kotoko.
Sorry, nothing.
I know. You must be hungry.
Shall we go eat something
before we go play?
When you're hungry,
you can't fight the battle. Right?
You're right. Let's go.
-Let's go then.
-Yeah.
Rainbow Bridge looks nice.
What's wrong, Kotoko?
That's Irie.
That's okay.
Is the girl next to him his fiancé?
She looks so much like
a high-class girl.
Is this Kotoko?
Oh, Sahoko. Nice to see you again.
What a coincidence.
Are you on a date too?
She's my fiancé, Sahoko Oizumi.
How do you do?
I'm Sahoko Oizumi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kinnosuke Ikezawa.
I'm a cook at Kotoko's dad's
restaurant.
Wow, you're the successor
of her father.
No, no. I'm still in training.
What made you come here?
Actually, we're going to an art
exhibition in Ginza.
But Naoki suggested to stop by here
before that.
He said that there was
a great place.
You said that you wanted to go
to a place that had an open feel.
This is the place
that he came with me.
He takes Sahoko here.
For Irie,
the first date with me
was nothing.
It was something
that he didn't care about.
Right. If you don't mind it,
Kotoko and Kinnosuke
should come with us.
Francis Bacon's
early works will be...
-Be... Bacon?
-Be... What?
We'd rather have
sausage than bacon.
You shouldn't force them, Sahoko.
Even if you invite them there,
it'll be painful for them.
They have their
-own level.
-Wow.
Level? What do you mean, Irie?
Right. Do you want to tell us
that we're stupid?
Am I wrong?
Naoki?
Let's go, Kin-chan.
Let's do something
that suits our level.
Kotoko.
Sahoko, please enjoy bacon
by yourselves.
We'll eat sausages until we're full.
Excuse me now.
Kotoko.
What a great couple
you guys are.
Thanks a lot.
What's wrong, Naoki?
Saying harsh words like that
to Kotoko
is unlike you.
Is it unlike me?
Don't worry.
I won't say stuff like that to you.
Sahoko?
Naoki, you're
good at your job
and you know everything,
but you don't know
your true feelings.
I'm going home today.
It's so irritating.
Are you okay?
-About what?
-I mean...
About what?
Nothing.
Eat a lot of sausages.
I guess you're eating them already.
-Ai-chan.
-Mr. Aihara.
Are you sure you're moving out?
Yes.
We don't mind it at all.
No, no.
Naoki is getting married.
It's about time.
Everything is going to be over.
AIHARA
Good job, guys.
Thank you.
I'm visiting this regular customer.
-Take care of the rest of it.
-Yes.
See you later.
Tomorrow is the day off.
I've worked hard this week.
-Bro.
-Yeah.
We'll do the rest of it.
You can go home now.
Are you sure?
I'll be leaving then.
Have a nice night.
You've worked hard this week.
Yeah.
Hey, Kotoko.
-Do you have any plans for tomorrow?
-No.
I don't have any.
Do you want to go out?
No.
Why don't we have a study
meeting here?
Study meeting?
You must be getting
used to it here,
but you don't know the basics
of Japanese cuisine and things, yet.
I want to start making
a full course meal plan by myself.
As you taste test my food,
we can study about it together.
Sounds good. Let's do it.
Good idea, isn't it?
Okay, let's do it.
Sure.
-I'm home.
-Oh, Naoki.
You are late tonight.
But
Kotoko is not home, yet.
Is that right?
I wonder if she's cleaning up
at the restaurant.
She's been late these days. No.
She's later than usual today.
Maybe she's going out with
Kin-chan some place.
Possibly
she may not come home tonight.
Good night.
Hey, Naoki.
The Aiharas are
moving out of here.
Are you sure
it's okay with you?
Aihara said she'd be missing
practice today.
Is that right?
Even though you live in the
same house, you don't know
anything about each other.
I'm busy at work
and I'm going home late every day.
See you later.
Hey, Irie.
I heard that you were getting
married. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Long time no see.
-How are you?
-Good.
Even though you broke my heart,
I'm doing well, as you see.
Are you going to quit school?
Probably.
I don't like her.
A girl who can't complain
is boring.
It's just like you.
If you become somebody
else's man,
stay as a cool Irie yourself.
See you then.
Naoki Irie. Why are you here?
Is it bad for me to come here?
I'm taking a leave of absence,
but I'm still registered here.
Well, Kotoko is not here today.
Too bad for you.
I didn't ask you that.
She'll be at the restaurant
by now.
Restaurant? Isn't it closed today?
Wow, you know well.
But on that day off
she purposely goes there
and studies together with Kin-chan.
Studying together?
That's more like an excuse
and Kotoko is trying to answer
to Kin-chan's proposal.
Proposal?
You didn't know that?
Kin-chan proposed
-to Kotoko.
-Jinko!
Let me say it.
Someone is
marrying for political reasons
with this high-class girl.
Kotoko was depressed
in the beginning.
But later, she found
a true love.
-Right, Satomi?
-What?
Right. Right.
Money, social standings,
or a title has nothing to do with.
It's true love for her.
Right.
We're going on a date now.
Excuse us, now.
Going on a date with my true love
makes me
so happy,
even if it's a low budget one.
Right.
-Excuse us.
-Good bye.
-Feels so good!
-Jinko, your leg.
I'm feeling so good.
But Kotoko
never said that she'd answer
his proposal.
Was it okay to tell him
that kind of made-up story?
Because I was frustrated
that I had to say that.
It'll be a good opportunity
for that cold-hearted guy.
You're right.
You're right about it.
I feel so good.
There.
Beautiful.
It doesn't look like potato stew.
Japanese cuisine is not only
for your tongue,
but also for your eyes.
It's important to arrange it
beautifully.
Please try it.
Yes. Thank you for the meal.
Potato.
It's the first time for me to eat
a potato stew this good.
Isn't it good?
Sophisticated Kaiseki
is good,
but I want to cook
a homemade meal
that everybody knows.
Potato stew, Kinpira,
and fried tofu.
I want to open a restaurant
that serves that kind of food.
I think people's sense of taste
is rooted at home.
Using the best ingredients
and making the best homemade meal.
I want people to know
the wonder of it.
I want to make it a homely
atmosphere.
A kind hostess is there
who everyone loves.
We run the restaurant together.
Kin-chan.
Listen, Kotoko.
Your answer from the other day,
can you give me it now?
Sorry.
Can you give me a little more time
to think about it?
You can't forget about Irie,
can you?
-It's not that.
-Then what?
My feelings have been
towards you this whole time.
Can't you look to the future?
Why do you like such
cold-hearted guy?
-Kin-chan.
-I'll make you forget
that guy.
Stop! Irie!
Sorry, Kin-chan.
I see.
You still like
Irie.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Damn it!
I'm the worst.
I made Kin-chan expect a lot.
I was being suggestive to him.
And the word that came out
of my mouth was
Irie's name.
I thought about it.
I was troubled about it.
Then I gave up on him.
After all
I still love Irie.
I don't know
what to do anymore.
Hey.
Irie. Why?
I'm here to
pick you up.
Picking up?
Me?
Were you with him?
Who?
Ikezawa.
Right.
I heard that you were proposed to.
I'm quite popular, you know.
What did you tell him?
Whatever I told him
is none of your business.
You're
getting married with Sahoko.
You're right.
I'm
moving out.
My dad and I have decided.
And then
I'll marry to Kin-chan.
Then I take over my dad's
restaurant
with Kin-chan.
Do you love him?
Kin-chan has been
liking me ever since we were
freshmen in high school.
Do you fall for the guy
if he says he likes you?
So what? Something wrong?
I've been in one-sided love
for many years
and got tired of not
being successful.
You just think about Sahoko.
Forget about me.
You love me.
You can't love
anyone else but me.
How come you're so confident?
Right. You're absolutely right.
I can't do much about it.
Because you don't like me.
You don't...
Don't you ever say that
you like somebody else but me.
This kiss is
the second time.
It's the third time, right?
What?
You don't have to count anymore.
We'll miss you.
We'll come visit you.
They're home.
Naoki, Kotoko.
What made you so wet?
I'll bring towels.
No, I have something important
to tell you before that.
You stay here too, Mom.
Mr. Aihara, I have to talk to you.
You should change before that.
With Kotoko...
Please allow me to marry
your daughter.
Irie.
Are you serious, Naoki?
I am.
I've finally figured it out.
I want to
marry Kotoko.
Of course it's not right now.
I have to have the Oizumis accept it.
When the company recovers
and the business goes back on track.
But
the person who I want to be with
for the rest of my life
is nobody else but her.
I can't think of anybody else.
Mr. Aihara.
Would you accept it?
Naoki.
She's a girl who can't do much.
I know.
She's not smart.
She can't cook.
I know.
She's careless,
jumps to conclusions,
and makes lots of mistakes.
I know.
However...
She's cheerful
and spirited.
She's earnest and very precious.
I know.
Naoki.
Please take good care
of Kotoko.
Yes.
Okay, Kotoko?
Kotoko-chan!
How long have I been waiting
for this day!
Dad.
I'm sorry for being selfish.
This will make
it difficult for Chairman Oizumi
to contribute to Pandai.
I'm causing a big loss.
You're right.
For Pandai, this is
a very serious issue.
Honey, leave that subject alone.
No, as a president of Pandai,
I can't allow this selfish act
of an employee.
Mr. Irie.
Even so,
if you want to marry
Kotoko no matter what,
I have a condition.
You have to
quit Pandai.
Honey.
Then you go back to college
and study to become a doctor.
Dad.
Do you think you were hiding it
from me?
Don't underestimate your parent.
I've already known about it.
Pandai is
the company that I made.
I'll properly reestablish it.
I'll talk to Chairman Oizumi.
So you should
follow your dream.
Together with Kotoko.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
But what's going to happen
to your company?
I'll do it.
I'll take over Dad's company.
It's going to take a while
so Dad has to work hard until then.
So you can be a doctor.
I'll do that then.
I'm counting on you, Yuki.
How wonderful. It's so great.
This will make everything
work out.
We'll
become a real family.
Anyways, you guys go change.
Right? Let's have a toast.
Get changed and let's have a toast.
I'm scared.
When tomorrow comes,
you might turn back
to old mean Irie.
Do you want to sleep
together then?
I didn't mean that.
Are you sure that I'm the one?
Yeah.
I love you, Irie.
I know.
More than enough.
But
I didn't know you liked me.
You got me.
I love you.
When is the closest Sunday
that's the most auspicious day?
Hey, Mom, are we there yet?
We're almost there.
Why do we have to go early
in the morning on Sunday?
Sorry, Ai-chan.
It's okay. I don't mind.
Anyway, Mrs. Irie,
where are we going?
Wedding.
What?
Over there.
It can't be.
Of course it's Naoki and Kotoko's.
What?
Hey, I didn't hear that.
Because
I didn't tell you.
Well, but
are we really having a wedding?
It's not, like, just looking?
It's the surprise present for you.
Ta-da!
Congratulations on your wedding.
Aren't you all surprised?
Okay, everyone, stop dozing
and go get dressed. Hurry up.
There you go.
I've never thought that this day
would come.
It's just like a dream.
Yuki.
-Fair feathers make fair fowls.
-What?
You don't know English
that's this easy?
You're stupid after all.
What does that fair something mean?
Fair feathers make fair fowls.
Beautiful feathers
make birds beautiful.
It means anybody will look decent
when wearing a beautiful dress.
You're making fun of me.
I'll tell you something good
as a wedding gift.
Come close.
You're looking sharp.
You're always perfect
when it comes to looking good.
Ikezawa.
Kotoko
is mine.
I would say
Kotoko has bad taste
in choosing a man.
Make Kotoko happy.
I won't forgive you if you
make her cry even for a little bit.
Yeah.
You can't let your guard down.
I'm always waiting for her.
Right.
I shook his hand.
Come round, Naoki.
Right, Naoki.
-That's a good one.
-You look sharp, Naoki.
Being forced to do this
is irritating.
But you look beautiful,
so it doesn't matter.
Honor her, comfort her, and help her.
As long as you both shall live.
Keep yourself unto her.
The groom
may lift her veil.
Now, you may kiss your bride.
Hey, Irie.
You've been in love with me,
haven't you?
What?
Don't get carried away.
I heard about our second kiss.
Yuki told me secretly.
That rascal.
You've been crazy for me.
Oh, my God!
I've never seen an ideal Japanese
woman
like her before.
It serves you right.
I can't win
over you.
This is how
I changed my name
from Kotoko Aihara
to Kotoko Irie.
Congratulations.
Is that a shooting star?
In this daylight?
The possibility of a person getting
hit by a shooting star
is one in ten billion.
Meeting you
is a miracle even rarer than that.
Try not to overwrap.
Say cheese.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION