The love letter that I wrote for
the first time in my life.
The love letter that would never
been read.
Terrible! Did you read my letter?
Kotoko, why don't you be Naoki's bride?
Marriage is out of question.
You don't know about people's minds.
Even if I don't like her today,
I might like her tomorrow.
Wait, what are you doing? Wait!
Don't worry. I have no intention of
going out with you.
Did you make fun of me?
My memory of last summer vacation
in high school is nothing special.
But I'll never forget the aroma of
the coffee that I had with Irie.
Time flies by and the season
changed from summer to fall,
then fall to winter.
I made it to get promoted to college.
But the relationship between Irie and
I stays the same.
And nothing has progressed.
So cute. You look good in kimono.
I choose navy blue this year.
It was yellow last year.
Jinko, Satomi!
-Wow!
-Happy new year.
Happy new year, Kotoko.
Wow, you're wearing a kimono this year.
Mrs. Irie helped me to get dressed.
Cute. You look good in it.
-Thank you.
-Jinko, did you put on some weight?
Stop it. I'm conscious of it.
When I think about being free
from studying to enter college,
I get a big appetite for
Christmas cakes and
-the new year meal.
-I can relate to you.
Isn't it nice that all of us are
promoted to Tonan University?
Right.
We'll be college students in spring.
-Let's make this year a great one.
-Yes.
-Shall we go now?
-There's a line there.
-It's amazing.
I wish I have a wonderful college life.
I wish I have a boyfriend this year.
Kotoko is serious, isn't she?
It's obvious that
what she's wishing, isn't it?
Hey, let's draw a fortune.
-This one.
-I'll take this one.
Which one should I pick? This one.
Great! I got the excellent luck.
-Me too.
-Me three.
Three of us got the best one.
-Wait.
-What?
"The person who you've been waiting
for is coming. Look forward to it."
-Oh!
-You did it!
-What am I going to do?
-Let's see mine.
"The person is not coming, but you'll
hear from him." What does that mean?
-He's not coming again.
-"If you desire, he won't come."
Bro.
About this.
Don't you ever tell Kotoko.
-But--
-I'm telling you.
I'm telling you not to.
Bro.
Congratulations!
To celebrate Kotoko's promotion
to university, cheers.
Cheers!
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Kotoko.
Let's eat, everyone.
Thank you, everyone,
for doing this for me.
I thought Kotoko was still little, but now
she's going to be a college student
this spring.
Your mom in heaven must be
very happy for you.
-Dad.
-Sorry.
Naoki, you have to do well on the
entrance exam like Kotoko.
He's different from a fool like Kotoko.
He'll pass Tokyo University no problem.
Yuki.
Oh, right.
Here, Irie, this is for you.
I was able to be promoted to college
because you helped me study.
It's just a small token of appreciation.
How wonderful. Why don't you open
it up and show us?
What's this?
It's a head massager.
Irie is taking an entrance exam for
Tokyo University.
So, I thought you had more to study.
It looks like a whisk. It's old man stuff.
-Hey, Yuki.
-Why don't you try it out, Naoki.
-Right.
-I'm okay.
Besides, let alone Tokyo University,
I haven't decided to go to college.
Yuki, why don't you show that to me?
How do you use it?
-On your head.
-On my head.
No. Irie who's genius to get into
Tokyo University for sure may
not go to college?
What does he mean?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
CHOCOLATE IS LOVE AMULET?!
-Your mouth.
-What a big mouth!
Aren't we in heaven for not having
to study in the third trimester?
-We sure are.
-Hey, look, look!
What a view!
We're having fun,
but class A is studying so hard.
-Isn't it strange?
-The Center Exam is getting close.
However, only Naoki Irie is relaxed.
I can't believe it. He's reading a
book that has nothing to do with
-the entrance exam leisurely.
-Hey.
Is Naoki Irie's first choice school
Tokyo University?
Let alone Tokyo University, I don't
know if I would go to college.
Kotoko. Kotoko?
I'm not sure.
I think he'll go if he passes.
What are you saying?
Irie will get in for sure.
Kotoko, you'll miss him when you
two go to different colleges.
But it's for Irie's future.
-I'll support him.
-Not quite, Jinko.
-Was I? Really?
-Mrs. Irie.
-Yes.
Can I possibly borrow your
sewing supplies?
Of course. Hold on a second.
Yes.
It got crooked.
You're okay. Do it slowly.
Is that lucky charm for Naoki?
Thank you, Kotoko.
The person who thinks about his
college exam the most is you, I think.
It's not true that
Irie's not going to college, is it?
I don't think he doesn't
want to go to college, but maybe
his dad's expectation is too high.
He graduated from Tokyo University,
so he wants Naoki to
go to the same college and
have him take over his business.
But being expected to do well might be
a burden on Naoki.
THE NIGHT BEFORE
THE CENTER EXAM
Yes.
Do you have time?
Here.
Tomorrow is the Center Exam.
So, you're taking the exam, right?
I sent an application.
I'm glad to hear.
I understand if you have some
other college in mind.
But if you go to Tokyo University,
your parents will be happy.
I'm always causing trouble for my dad.
I envy you for having many chances
to make your parents happy.
That's all.
You--
What will you do at college?
What will I do?
I will study, and make friends
and things like that.
Are you taking the trouble to go there
to study that you don't even like?
I don't get it. Why does everyone
want to go to college so bad?
Colleges must exist
for people like you to study.
But I never thought that
I wanted to go to college.
I don't have to be taught in college.
If I want to study, I can do it myself.
That's not all, right? You can get a
certificate for what you want to do.
Then what do you want to do?
I don't know what it is yet.
The time you spend in college is
the time to search for it.
To search what you want to do
in the future.
You shouldn't keep your brain to yourself.
You have to contribute to
Japan's development.
You're amazing.
I've been thinking about it.
But why can you be determined
so much?
Even though you're working so hard,
why can't you do it?
I'm so impressed.
What's that? Are you being sarcastic?
I feel like you're the one to be envied.
I'll leave early tomorrow
so I'm going to bed now.
Good night.
I'll put this on then.
Perfect. Good luck.
Naoki is late.
Is he trying not to take Center Exam?
He'll be all right. He knows how you feel.
But he's stubborn once
he makes up his mind.
-What?
-Good morning, Naoki.
Nice morning, isn't it? Here it is.
-Your lunch.
-Thank you.
-What's wrong, Naoki?
-I feel a little hot.
-It seems like I caught cold.
-On an important day like this?
Oh, my! Got to make
the egg and sake drink.
No, green onions are better
for his throat.
-Medicine, medicine!
-Did we have Nukamiso?
It's okay. I'm going now.
-How about breakfast?
-I have no appetite. This is good.
-What?
-Irie, Irie.
Take this medicine. This works well.
That should work.
Just in case, does this medicine
make you drowsy?
"After you take this, avoid driving."
Throw it up. Get it out, Naoki.
I'll hold him so you put your fingers in.
That's enough.
I'm going now.
Irie.
Is he going to be okay?
-Good morning.
-Good morning. Hey--
Is that lucky charm handmade?
Did the girl who live with you
make it for you?
I'll throw it away once
I get to the venue.
No way. Poor her.
I kind of like her.
Excuse me, I'm getting off.
Thank you so much.
What's wrong, Irie?
That girl.
The lucky charm got stuck between
the doors. Pull it off.
Hey, it's not moving at all.
Irie, hurry.
Watanabe, you go ahead.
How about you?
I'll take care of this quickly.
Sorry, I'll go ahead.
-See you at the venue.
-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, the elevator has stopped.
Hey!
Good. It took you a while.
I was scolded by a station staff
for a long time.
It sounded like there were lots of
pranks to stop elevators.
I was blamed to be the suspect
on all the incidents.
I'll listen to you later. Let's go inside.
By the way,
what happened to that lucky charm?
It's so strong.
Isn't it bad luck?
Right.
I'll take it off.
It came off easily.
Irie!
-Someone fell off from the stairs.
-Someone.
Is anyone there?
Take both of them to
the nurse's office. Right now.
What a scary lucky charm!
Sorry, I'm late.
You're the student who fell from
the stairs. Hurry. 30 minutes left.
Yes.
It happened then.
Thank you.
Hey, Irie. I'm hesitant to ask you,
but how did you do?
I didn't see most of the problems
and answered with imagination.
You must have made it happen.
Good luck!
That girl.
What's up?
Is your lunch made by that girl?
You better not eat it.
You don't want to get diarrhea.
If these work for you.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Hey, this is an unsolicited advice.
But you should throw that
lucky charm away.
It was gone when
I noticed at nurse's office.
That's good.
The misfortune has gone away then.
Ten more minutes left.
It was a disaster, wasn't it, Irie?
It makes you just about average
after these kinds of accidents.
I guess I'm not comforting you.
Hey, you.
It was a disaster, wasn't it?
Thank you for helping me.
No broken bones,
but you have to rest for a while.
Yes. Thank you.
So, I think it was yours.
But a lucky charm was left on a stair.
I put it in your chest pocket.
It was handmade so I thought
it must've been important.
I hope it would bring you luck.
I'm envious.
I feel like you and that girl will
stay together forever.
Stop it.
It's about time for Naoki to come home.
But he's late, isn't he?
That's him.
Naoki, what's wrong? What happened?
-I fell.
-What?
It's still a bad injury.
The lucky charm didn't work.
No, it worked really well.
What do you mean?
Never mind. I'm going to bed.
Brother.
-I failed Center Exam.
-Me too.
I have to go for private schools now.
Irie will be fine. He's a genius
who's the top of the nation.
I don't think that applies at this time.
Kotoko, Jinko.
Did you hear that?
Irie is applying to Tokyo University.
You're kidding. Where did you hear that?
There was a rumor in the teachers' office.
Among other applicants,
his grades are superior.
What a genius!
Wait, Kotoko. How come you're crying?
Well.
I'm so happy.
I'll go and tell Irie congratulations.
-She's got a passion of youth.
-Yeah.
He was injured badly.
But he made it happen.
The person who I adore is really cool.
I wonder if that lucky charm
had helped him a little bit.
I can apply to Tokyo University
thanks to your lucky charm.
Thank you.
Watch out!
Are you in class A?
Wait, what's wrong?
Do you know the Center Exam results?
Did Irie fail Center Exam as I thought?
What are you talking about?
Irie is all right.
He'll be able to
apply to Tokyo University.
What? Amazing. With that condition?
That condition?
It was terrible.
I've never seen Irie being like that.
Even if it was because of
that lucky charm.
-That lucky charm?
-Shoot!
-Wait, what do you mean?
-Nothing.
-Never mind.
-Tell me.
Stop it. I'll tell you.
I'll tell you, so--
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have to take an exam
for my first choice, Waseda University.
Your destroying power is so amazing.
-Destroying power?
-We can laugh about it now.
But horrible things happened that day
with your lucky charm power.
His injury and all was because
of my lucky charm.
I...
put Irie through a great deal of
trouble.
I pray for Irie to get accepted to
Tokyo University.
I pray for Irie family's dream
to come true.
Congratulations on your acceptance
to Tokyo University
This is going to happen for sure.
It's a little early.
But the day after the exam
on St. Valentine's day,
I'll give it to him.
And the day of the destiny has come.
I'm leaving now.
You all don't have to see me off.
I'm worried about you.
I can drive you there.
I'm okay. My leg is healed up.
-I'm going now.
-Stay safe.
Have a nice day.
It was terrible.
I've never seen him like that.
Even if the lucky charm caused it all.
Kotoko?
I'll go see Irie off until he passes
the Tokyo University gate.
I don't want anything to happen.
See you later.
See you.
It's so obvious that you're following me.
I thought I would see you off
by the Tokyo University gate.
Whoa, I slipped.
I'm sorry to say that
in front of a test taker.
Why is a banana peel here?
Ouch.
Everyone looks smart.
Aren't you walking a little weird?
Do you think so? It's normal.
You look pale too.
I'm just nervous.
Why are you being nervous?
I'm the one who's taking the exam.
What should I do?
I've never had this kind of pain
in my stomach.
No, I have to see Irie go through
Tokyo University gate.
I can't make him worry
about me until then.
Hey, are you sure you're okay?
Of course. Good luck on your exam.
See you later.
Bathroom.
What's wrong? Anybody?
Are you okay? What's wrong?
-She just collapsed.
-Are you okay?
-Hang in there.
-Excuse me.
Hey, are you okay?
Excuse me, hospital.
Where's a hospital?
There's one over there.
Irie.
Go take the exam.
Irie, you'll be late.
Take the exam.
Mr. Irie, Mrs. Irie, and
Yuki, all of them are
cheering for you.
-Kotoko.
-Kotoko-chan.
Kotoko-chan.
Dad.
Mrs. Irie, Mr. Irie.
I--
Why am I here?
Kotoko, are you okay?
You had appendicitis,
but the antibiotics are working now.
-You can go home today.
-You'll be okay, Kotoko.
How about Irie?
He wasn't here when we got here.
I think he went to Tokyo University
right after he called us.
He must be taking the exam by now.
I'm relieved.
It's my fault if he can't take the exam.
I worried that if his life
would be ruined.
Kotoko-chan.
When you're suffering like this,
you're worrying about Naoki the most.
What about me?
Naoki, didn't you go take the exam?
Since I was hungry, I went out to eat.
How about the exam? Tokyo University?
Tokyo University? I didn't take the exam.
How can it be? No way.
Iri-chan, Mrs. Irie, and Naoki,
I'm terribly sorry.
Ai-chan.
Because of my daughter,
your son went through such a trouble.
Hey, get up. Not taking the exam is
what Naoki did with his own will.
Right. Besides even if he got into
Tokyo university,
I would have been disappointed
if he didn't help Kotoko.
-However--
-She's right.
It was the destiny.
-It's okay, Ai-chan.
-Please get up.
Because of me,
Irie's family is facing the worst time.
Everyone in the Irie family
Everyone in the Irie family,
thank you for taking care of me
until now.
Good bye, Irie.
I can't put you through trouble anymore.
I'll...
live my life somewhere where
you can't find me.
Where should I go?
It's cold.
Do you want to hold
a hot can of coffee, then?
Irie.
Why?
No reason.
I couldn't fall asleep,
so I'm taking a walk.
It's warm.
Don't stop me. I can no longer--
I'm not stopping you.
Goodbye, then.
Are you leaving because
I didn't go to Tokyo University?
I think I'm a bad luck for you.
Not only Tokyo University,
but also the Center Exam--
I heard it.
From Watanabe in class A.
Maybe...
I'm someone who's awful for you.
Probably.
Nothing good happens when I'm with you.
My pace of life gets
messed up all the time.
A rumor was spread at school.
I was forced to teach you to study.
It affected
my college application in the end.
I'm the worst.
But...
it was kind of fun.
It was the first time in my life
to feel so anxious.
It was the first time for me
to feel anxious about my test result.
It was a crazy experience.
How about Tokyo University, though.
I tell you, but it's not your fault
that I didn't take the exam.
If I went there after
I dropped you off at the hospital,
I would have made it in time.
Then why?
You said that the college was the
place to decide what you do.
It has been fun to be around you
to feel anxious about things
that it may not be a bad idea to
get promoted to stay at Tonan.
I've been wondering what I would do
after I go to Tokyo University.
You mean you chose the
same college because I'm going?
I don't mean that.
But--
You can go now. Take care.
Wait.
Well, may I stay at the Irie residence
for little longer?
-I won't cause you trouble anymore.
-Stop lying.
There's no way you won't cause me trouble.
You're right. Then I'll promise you
to have an exciting life.
You get carried away easily.
Hey, it's St. Valentine's Day, today,
isn't it?
So, what? Are you giving me
a chocolate or something?
I'm sorry.
Were you counting on me?
I wasn't.
There it is.
It tastes bad.
Congratulations on your acceptance
to Tokyo University
White Valentine's day.
My feelings towards him was
fruitless this year.
But someday I hope...
my feelings towards him...
get accepted.
First kiss.
NEXT EPISODE
The couple that kiss on the graduation day
will stay together forever.
Let's make it the best graduation
and the party.
Kotoko, am I not good enough?
It's not like I don't like Kin-chan.
I'm going to kiss Kotoko tonight.
If it's a dream,
why don't you go to sleep?
Are you going to like me?
She's noticed
who treats her the best.
What a cold blooded guy!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION