-How's my father's condition?
-If he keeps on overworking,
-he might have a heart attack.
-I'll do it.
I'll protect Dad's company.
If Irie feels helpless
and needs assistance,
I'll do whatever I can,
-if there's anything I can do.
-If it stays this way, Pandai might
be merged into them. Right now,
we need huge
financial assistance.
This is Chairman Oizumi and his
secretary, Yokoyama from Hokueisha.
About finance, I'll be discussing
with you,
instead of my father.
Dad's condition is not that great.
If I take over the company...
everything will work out.
What an honor for us to receive
a visit
-from you. Thank you so much.
-Not at all.
I had some business to take care of
in this area also.
Are you alone today?
I wanted talk to you
in person today.
To me?
Naoki, would you like to have an
arranged marriage meeting?
I'm hesitant to ask you while
Mr. Irie is hospitalized,
but I have a granddaughter.
She's the same age as you and goes
to University of the Sacred heart.
That's the most prestigious school.
What do you think, Naoki?
How about seeing her once?
You're young. I know you can't
give me an answer right away.
Discuss with your parents and
give me an answer in a few days.
We'll discuss about the investment
after that.
-Sorry for the surprise visit.
-No problem at all.
Then Naoki, think about it
really well.
Yes. Thank you.
Naoki.
This will be a good deal...
for the company also, right?
-What do you mean, Naoki?
-Honey, calm down.
However...
having a marriage meeting with
the granddaughter of Chairman Oizumi?
What's going on?
Nothing.
Could it be that it's for
the financial assistance?
Since we came here without
telling them,
-will Dad be surprised?
-What do we do?
-Will it be bad for his heart?
-What are you talking about?
He'll get so much better to get rid
of the disease when he sees you.
Don't underestimate
your parents.
I...
never wanted to sacrifice you...
to save the company.
He's right. Marrying her is
out of the question.
Marrying? My brother is?
I'm proud of myself to make Pandai
big in one generation.
So, don't be so considerate
for me.
Marry a person you really love.
I like her.
When I saw her picture,
she was my type.
Brother.
-Are you serious?
-Yuki.
Are you really marrying her?
Because....
Kotoko! Mr. Aihara too.
Irie.
Is it true that you're having
a marriage meeting?
Yeah.
This Sunday.
Since my dad is like this,
it's not a formal one,
but we're having lunch together.
I want you to come, Mom.
Be ready for it.
It can't be.
Irie is having an arranged
marriage meeting.
I can't believe it.
What can I do?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
Is Irie having a marriage meeting?
With the granddaughter of his
business connection.
CROSSROADS OF LOVE
-It's a political marriage, isn't it?
-Does that still happen these days?
I don't know.
Irie said he liked the girl.
Sorry, I gotta go.
Is Kotoko okay?
She's not okay. How many years
do you think she's been
in one-sided love with Irie?
Right. But I can't
believe that Irie is
-having a marriage meeting.
-I won't forgive Irie.
You're right. How much does Irie
have to trifle with Kotoko?
It's more like Kotoko is being
trifled by herself.
But how about Kotoko's feelings?
She's been...
devoting herself to Irie, but...
he's having a marriage
meeting with someone else?
Kin-chan?
It sounds like you want Kotoko
and Irie to be together.
I didn't say that.
I just want Kotoko to...
be smiling. That's all.
If I take over the company...
everything will work out.
But you have a dream to become
a doctor, don't you?
I had that dream only a short
time ago.
Are you giving up?
Irie.
That time...
I thought we were together
at heart.
I broke it.
Are you okay, Kotoko?
Oh, no! You're bleeding.
It looks painful.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
It must've been because of
Naoki's marriage meeting.
That Naoki.
His bride should be...
you. I'm not changing my mind.
This is what Irie has decided.
About that, I can't believe that
what he said was
his real intention.
It's the same thing
with the company deal.
Of course I've been
thinking that It would be great
for Naoki
to take over Pandai.
But looking at Naoki work there
makes me think that
something is not right.
I don't feel like it's what Naoki
really wants to do.
I think Naoki feels responsible
for his dad becoming sick.
That's why he's sacrificing himself
to save the company.
But would he marry for that reason?
It's once in a lifetime thing.
He's the kind of a boy who's determined
once he makes up his mind.
Therefore, I...
-thought of a good idea.
-Good idea?
Irie is having a marriage meeting,
isn't he?
She's the granddaughter of
the chairman of Hokueisha.
-Chairman Oizumi's?
-Do you know him?
Of course. Don't you read
newspapers?
He's a bigwig in the business world.
He influences politicians.
He's the big boss of
Japanese business.
I never knew that she was the
granddaughter of such great person.
I heard that she's been going to
Sacred Heart since kindergarten.
She's real high-class.
Irie said that he liked her right
away when he saw her picture.
She must be beautiful.
I don't like it.
Think about it. Why is Irie being
taken away by this new perfect girl?
-I don't get it.
-Well...
I think Mrs. Irie will do
something about it.
What? Mrs. Irie?
What do you mean?
Oh, who? Me?
-No, nothing.
-There must be something. Tell me.
So, it's a secret. The operation for
Mrs. Irie to ruin the meeting.
Ruining the meeting, huh?
-You guys haven't improved at all.
-So what?
However...
I'll join you this time.
THE DAY OF THE MARRIAGE MEETING
This way, please.
Oh, Naoki and Mrs. Irie.
-I've been waiting for you.
-Thank you for waiting.
Sorry that we're having this while
Mr. Irie is at hospital.
It's just me and my granddaughter,
Sahoko today.
The formal meeting with Sahoko's
parents will be
after Mr. Irie gets better.
We'll set it up another day.
I wonder if that day would come.
Mom.
One, two.
One. two.
Why do I have to dress like this?
Don't complain. In order to sneak
into the garden
...without being suspicious,
this was the only way.
That way.
What kind of a girl is Chairman
Oizumi's granddaughter?
-She doesn't seem to be there, yet.
-Really?
Sahoko is getting ready now.
She'll be here soon.
-I'm sorry, I'm late.
-Sahoko. We've been waiting for you.
You're the person...
Are you okay?
Do you remember me?
I don't forget a beautiful
lady like you.
Wow, it wasn't the first time
for you to see each other.
That makes it easy. Here, Sahoko,
Have a seat.
Hey, What are you doing?
Stay alert. Give me that.
So what? Even if she's kind of
pretty, she may not be smart.
Right. Let's go closer and
listen to their conversation.
-Crawl forward! Let's go.
-Are we really doing that?
I can't do it.
-What's your hobby?
-I'm not good at anything.
Cooking, sewing, and crafting.
-I'm boring.
-Oh, you're right.
Boring.
-Mrs. Irie, good job.
-Hush! They'll hear us.
It might sound strange for me
to say it as her grandfather...
but she's very graceful.
She's like...
an ideal Japanese woman
in this modern days.
That's great. I like a lady
who's graceful.
Oh, my! Ideal Japanese woman?
So old-fashioned.
No wonder you don't have much
youthfulness.
Well, what are your interests,
Naoki?
Well, I read often.
-Also I play tennis a little.
-What do you mean by little?
I heard that you won
many competitions.
-Wow, wonderful.
-I'll teach you next time.
-What?
-I'm happy to hear.
But I'm bad at it so you might
get tired of me.
-I think he will.
-Mom.
Actually, Naoki is very mean.
He looks down on the person who
can't do it after he teaches once.
He shows it outright too.
Oh, good job, Mrs. Irie.
I think she's the one who's
being outright.
You're good at academics and sports.
You're good-looking too.
Naoki, you must be popular.
-Not so much.
-Yes, he's very popular.
Don't worry.
He's never dated a girl.
-You're conservative.
-Yes. He's very conservative.
He refuses to accept the love letter
right in front of the girl.
Even if a girl confesses her love to
him he refuses in front of everyone.
He's really conservative.
Is that story all about you?
You're really being hated,
aren't you?
But compared to a man who makes
himself available to everybody...
it's much better to be cold.
Exactly. You don't have to worry
about him cheating on you.
It wasn't like he didn't know
any women.
To be honest, Naoki has lived...
with this girl...
...who's his age for nearly
three years.
Give me a break. She's not staying
with me, but with our family.
-It's the same thing.
-Mr. Oizumi, there's a reason.
Right. We might accept your
precious granddaughter.
She has to know our situation.
We have a girl who lives under
the same roof.
It's an unmistakable fact.
Even if he's conservative,
he's a young man.
I can't guarantee that
-...nothing has happened.
-Sahoko.
Shall we go to the garden?
-Oh, good idea.
-Just Sahoko and I.
Sorry that we didn't notice.
You both go together.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Oh, my back.
I'm sorry. My mom was being
rude to you.
No. Your mom must like...
that person.
The girl who lives
with your family.
She's the daughter of my dad's
best friend. We're family friends.
That's why my mom said
things like that.
But the person who likes her is...
not me, but my mom.
I want your mom to like me.
Before all that I have to be liked
by you.
Does that mean that you
like me?
Ever since I first met you
in front of the elevator.
What a coincidence.
It's the same with me.
Wow.
How irritating! What's that mood?
-You, how about the first operation?
-All right.
We'll move from here.
The secret weapon of our first
operation is this sprinkler.
We'll turn it on when they
pass by here.
Her kimono will be soaking wet.
She just has to go home.
-Isn't it too easy?
-It's better to be simple. Let's go.
There are Bonsais that are more
than 500 years old.
-That old?
-Ready?
-Right now.
-Yes.
It's nice weather, isn't it?
I feel like playing in water.
Why?
I'm glad to know that you have
that kind of personality.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're so slow.
They've passed it already.
Give me that.
Why? That's odd.
-It can't be.
-What's going on?
This switch doesn't work at all.
What?
A sprinkler must be malfunctioning.
Let's go.
Yes.
Stop it.
No!
Why do I have to go through this?
Stupid.
We pull ourselves together and go
with the second operation. Let's go.
My eyes. Ouch.
Your tricks are really like
elementary school.
-But they're gross, aren't they?
-They are.
Let me show you.
When that Sahoko girl passes through
there, I throw this at her.
She'll scream and fall into
the pond.
It serves her right.
-Am I doing too much?
-Give me a break.
You're too soft as always. That's
why Irie doesn't care about you.
-I can't argue with that.
-I'm the same way, though.
Look, there they are. Hurry.
Hurry, they'll pass by again.
-I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
-Hurry!
We did it!
You're okay since I'm with you.
Oh, did someone fall into the pond?
It looks like they're custodians.
They must be cleaning the pond.
Let's go.
What a water disaster you had,
Kotoko.
I got a punishment
since I tried to be mean to such
a beautiful girl.
Sahoko, huh?
She surely was kind of beautiful.
Mrs. Irie, when did you...?
But she's not his type at all.
Naoki needs excitements
in his life.
With a perfect and
quiet girl like her,
he'll soon feel like something is missing.
I can see that clearly.
But they seemed to be...
interested in each other
very much.
Besides, my evil-mother-in-law
tactics worked well too.
Chairman Oizumi must be
furious by now.
To the family that has this kind of
mother-in-law, he won't send
his precious granddaughter.
They'll decline it for sure.
Here it comes. It's the sound of
the phone
to tell us their refusal.
I'm coming.
Hello, this is Irie.
Chairman Oizumi.
I'm sorry for my mom's behavior
today.
Is that right? It's okay with me.
Please take care of it.
How was it? Did he decline?
Sahoko likes me...
-he wants to go forward with it.
-What?
So, I asked him to go forward
with it.
-Naoki.
-She's the person who I like.
So, don't get in a way of us
like that anymore, Mom.
-You too.
-What?
-It was so obvious.
I'm sorry.
Naoki is serious about it?
I can't believe it.
Sahoko calls him often...
...and they go on dates many times
a week.
Mrs. Irie is irritated that Irie
comes home late.
-We can't do anything about it.
-Are you giving him up?
Because I can't win against
Sahoko Oizumi.
But if Irie is taken away
from me...
it would've been better if
it was done by you.
Because if it's you, Irie will
regret it in the future.
He'd think that he should've
chosen Matsumoto.
I'm being made fun of, aren't I?
I feel like I lost without a battle
against Sahoko.
In that sense, I have to
acknowledge your effort.
Even though it's waste of your time,
you keep on going.
You makes me laugh.
Leave me alone.
I know. He kissed you, right?
That was just...
Good luck.
What was that?
Could that have been a cheer?
I'm back.
Yes.
I can do that.
See you tomorrow.
Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Do you have a date with Sahoko?
I'm just wondering.
Sorry. It's none of my business.
It's at Omotesando.
It's the party of this artist's
exhibition who he's a patron of.
Are you following me again?
Pretending to clean
the bathroom at the party venue.
Kin-chan.
How about that.
Looks good, huh?
-Eat this and cheer up.
-We told him
that Irie started dating the girl
he had a marriage meeting with.
You're right.
It means...
he's dating her.
Okay. Eat it.
-Here it is.
-I'm borrowing this.
Let me try some.
If you eat it with a frown,
my cuisine will taste bad.
Kotoko, cheer up.
You should feel better about a cold
guy like Irie to marry soon.
He's right.
I tell you.
I know that it's all in
my mind, but...
lately...
I was feeling like
I was closer to Irie.
So, I still...
can't accept the reality.
I know. I thought you two were
inseparable and would be
together.
Jinko, that's a cruel comment
for her now.
Irie is doing well with his marriage
meeting girl.
You are right.
It's a different circumstance
this time.
Because an arranged marriage is
between
families.
It's not like he can quit
when he gets tired of it.
Irie knows it and is going forward
with it, I guess.
You're right.
-Let's eat.
-There. Eat it.
-Living is about eating, right?
-Cheer up. Eat a lot.
Sweets are especially good.
-All that artwork was amazing.
-Did you think so too?
The party was very nice and I felt
the artist's personality.
You must be hungry since it was
a standing party.
-Would you like dinner somewhere?
-I'd love to.
I know. There's an Italian
restaurant that my grandpa likes.
If it's Mr. Oizumi's favorite,
I can trust it. Let's go.
Naoki is late, isn't he?
I'll go take a look.
It's okay. It's dangerous for a girl
to go out this late at night.
But I don't feel like I can
go to sleep.
I'll go for a walk and get a juice
from a convenience store.
Kotoko-chan.
No matter what she says,
she still cares about Naoki.
Hey, good-looking.
Did you just have a date with that
high-class girl?
Wait, dude.
What are you thinking about Kotoko?
-It's none of your business.
-It is my business.
You've been suggestive to Kotoko,
haven't you?
Kotoko is a precious person
for me.
The feelings of my precious
person...
were being trifled with.
How can I keep myself quiet?
What are you going to do, then?
I'll take Kotoko away from you.
No, I'll protect her.
So, don't get in the way.
If you have a girl who wants to
marry you, you should know that.
If that girl is important to you...
Kotoko is important to me.
I can't watch Kotoko suffering
like that anymore.
What do you say?
Irie, say, "Kotoko likes me."
You've said that before.
Please.
Do as you like.
Yeah. I'll do as I like
just as you told me.
So, don't interrupt me
anymore.
It's a promise between men.
Are we done for sure this time?
Giving up on Irie is...
impossible for me.
Brother.
Are you really marrying that
girl from the marriage meeting?
-What do you want to know?
-Answer me.
I think that's what's
going to happen.
Do you really like that girl?
-What's the matter, Yuki?
-Give me your honest answer.
Because...
Because the girl you like is...
Kotoko, isn't it?
Because in that hospital room,
you...
-kissed Kotoko.
-I'll let you meet Sahoko soon.
She's beautiful and I heard that
she was a good cook.
I'm sure you'll like her.
She's suitable for me.
Everything will work out.
-Hey, good morning, Kotoko.
-Good morning, Kin-chan.
-Are you going to the cafeteria?
-Yeah.
Today's special is chicken katsu.
You like it, don't you?
I'll give you a big portion
secretly, so come.
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey, Kotoko.
This Sunday...
can we go out if you have time?
I got movie tickets from a customer
at Aihara.
So, I thought it might be
good for refreshment.
It's an action movie, so you
might feel refreshed.
-You can't go with me, I guess.
-I will.
I will. Let's go together.
I mean... It's going to be a date.
-Are you sure?
-With Mr. Irie's issues,
you've been helping me.
Let's go on a date to
thank you for it also.
See you later, then.
I heard the president would be
discharged next week.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Also about the arranged marriage
meeting...
as soon as president becomes
stable,
you'll have dinner with both
sets of parents.
Then you go from there.
That's what they want to do.
That's okay with me.
Please take care of it.
Thank you, Naoki.
Chairman Oizumi will promise us
huge financial assistance.
Our company will be secure then.
Irie and I are...
starting to go on a different
route from each other.
Beyond that...
what kind of future is waiting
for us?
-Let's get married.
-What?
We're dating with marriage
in our minds.
I'm different from someone that I
don't mix up work and love.
-It depends on the person.
-It was fun. Time flew by.
-I'll decide my life by myself.
-I wanted to talk to you, Kotoko.
-We have to move out of Irie-chan's.
-You too, find a nice guy soon.
I decided that I would keep loving
Irie no matter how hard, but...
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION