The couple that kisses
on the graduation day
will stay together forever.
Look over there.
Kiss?
First kiss.
Among those three years,
this last year was the most fun for me.
For the past 18 years for me,
this last year was the most suffering.
You and I aren't good at studying,
but we can find something
that we're good at.
If I find it
and succeed in it,
would you fall for me?
She finally came to realize
who treats her the best.
Kin-chan, we're here.
Irie and Kotoko are meant
to be together.
-Stop kidding.
-You cold-blooded guy.
You love that cold-blooded guy,
don't you?
I...
...kissed with
Irie, didn't I?
You come with me.
What now?
I'll
stop loving you.
You are going to forget about me.
Why don't you try, then.
I'm sorry.
I've been embarrassed
since that day that
I couldn't follow my heart.
It was a dream.
Since that day, I wake up
with this kind of dream.
However
let alone the second kiss,
but the relationship between Irie
and me hasn't progressed.
The short spring break is over.
Irie and I
are college students starting today.
Tonan University
The day of the entrance ceremony
-Hey.
-Yes.
How long are you going to follow me?
Are you going to the School
of Science and Engineering?
Right. I'm at the School
of Literature. See you.
So you end up coming
to the school of Engineering
to spy on Irie?
Kotoko, you haven't progressed
at all since high school.
It's such a stable quality of Kotoko.
There are only men in the school
of Science and Engineering.
That'll keep Irie away from ladies.
Kotoko, you're safe.
Kotoko, look at her.
Who is that pretty girl?
Amazing.
In the men-dominated campus,
it looks shiny around her.
Irie.
Naoki Irie.
Have you decided on electives?
No, I haven't.
What should I take?
Whoa! Hey, Jinko, Satomi.
What do you want?
The desks
of the Engineering department.
I was wondering how they'd be like.
-She's hopeless.
-Right.
Is she your girlfriend?
No way.
No way?
Even though we kissed,
does he still say "no way"?
What's going to happen
to my college life?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
He kissed you?
You both are too loud.
How can I not be loud?
RIVAL APPEARS!? HARDSHIP OF LOVE
That Irie kissed you?
His attitude didn't seem
like that at all.
I know.
It serves you right.
I don't understand what Irie's thinking.
Stop being so weak-spirited.
You dedicated your important
first kiss to Irie.
Right. You have to stay strong.
We're college freshmen.
Besides it's springtime.
It's time to meet new people.
If you don't do anything,
Irie will be taken by that pretty girl.
Aihara
Welcome.
Ai-chan, here we are availing
ourselves of your kind offer.
Tonight is the cerebration of Naoki
and Kotoko's college entrance.
-Please, take a seat over there.
-Thank you. Let's sit down.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Here.
It's a nice restaurant with good taste.
Isn't it? Ai-chan told me that
this paper is the best quality
washi paper.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You can't make a mess.
These chopsticks
are the best quality too.
You can't make it dirty.
I can't eat anything, then.
I'll use my hands.
Welcome.
Kin-chan!
Guess who.
You have a different aura.
I couldn't tell at all.
You look better this way.
Well, thank you, madam.
How come you're at Aihara?
I'm aiming at becoming a chef
and being trained at this restaurant.
I see. Kin-chan,
you've been good at cooking.
From the professional's view,
my cooking is nothing.
But I'll try hard and get better
than your dad
then I'll become the best chef
in Japan.
I'll never lose against you.
I'll become an accomplished chef
and earn lots of money,
then I'll come get you,
so be ready for it.
Kinnosuke, how long
are you chit-chatting?
Yes. Sorry. I'm coming.
Kotoko, serve these for me.
Okay.
This is so uneven
that we can't offer it to customers.
-I'm sorry.
-Give it to me.
-Fold them nicely one by one.
-Yes.
Yes.
Thank you.
It was delicious.
-Kin-chan.
-Yeah.
You found your way to take.
How wonderful. Work hard for it.
Yeah. You work hard at college.
I will.
Jinko and Satomi are.
Cut it like pushing out
with the blade.
Yes.
It's still too thick.
It's your turn for the bath.
Well, Irie.
What?
Well...
the lady at the School of Science
and engineering.
-Yuko Matsumoto?
-What?
You remember her full name
already?
I never forget when I hear it once.
Well, I'm wondering
if Ms. Matsumoto
has a feeling towards you.
What? Are you jealous?
It's not that.
You're right.
Matsumoto is definitely pretty.
She's got a nice figure.
She's also smart. She told me that
she made it to the 5th in national.
Why is that kind of person
in our college?
Who knows.
Maybe she has other goal.
Now...
weren't you going to forget about me?
Right.
Our relationship is serious enough
to kiss.
Can't you forget about me anymore?
Is this going to be
the second one?
I'm being made fun of.
Irie doesn't
think anything about kissing me.
How humiliating.
That girl's name is Yuko Matsumoto?
Beautiful and smart.
She's just like a female version
of Irie.
They're kind of suited
for each other.
Don't say such ominous thing.
You have to face the reality.
That girl is targeting Irie
without a doubt.
Kotoko, you're in a big crisis.
Let's eat and cheer up.
What will I eat?
Lunch A
Kotoko.
-Kotoko?
-Huh?
Haven't you ordered, yet?
Well, I was in a daze.
-Sorry.
-What are you doing? We'll go now.
Let's see. Lunch A is a hamburger.
Lunch B is fried shrimp.
Can't you think unless
you say it aloud?
Lunch A for me.
Well, I.
There's no lunch F here.
Lunch A for me too.
Two lunch A's.
What's this difference?
What is it, customer?
Are you complaining?
You're complaining about my fair serving.
What a nerve you have.
Kin-chan?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Haven't you found your way
to take?
You work at my dad's restaurant,
right?
Right.
At night at your dad's place
and during the day I work
at this cafeteria.
The taste that's affordable
for students,
the taste of the high-end restaurant
can be learned. Nice, huh?
Besides I have to save Kotoko
from the evil right there.
How about that, Mr. Genius?
Too surprised to speak, huh?
I'm impressed.
How can you decide your life
around a woman?
No, I can't.
What did you just say?
You two enjoy yourselves now.
He must have scared of
Mr. Kin-chan's power of love.
Right, Kotoko?
In a way, Kin-chan is right.
Humans tend to be conscious
about opposite sex who's close.
Kotoko, you should learn
from Kin-chan.
Right. Even though you're in the
same school, Irie is in Engineering.
You're in Literature.
The campus is different.
It's not going to be the same
as high school.
Yuko Matsumoto, who's in the same
school has far more advantage.
Moreover, she's a beautiful girl
with a nice figure.
No.
Hey, there you are, Irie.
-Hello, Mr. Sudo.
-Hey.
Who's that dude?
I don't know.
Upperclassman? Or a professor?
You know why I'm here, right?
Why don't you join our club?
I have no intention on
joining a club.
Don't you say stuff like that.
You and I know each other since
elementary school, don't we?
I'll be waiting for you
after school.
Okay?
Right?
Adios!
Kotoko.
You've got a chance.
Join the same club as Irie.
Then even if your school is different,
you can be close to Irie all the time.
Right. It's your chance
to get rid of Yuko Matsumoto.
I see.
I'll do that.
-I'll take your shrimp.
-Okay.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Irie, are you joining a club?
What kind of a club
are you joining?
I'm not telling you.
Why not?
Because you might join with me.
Well.
That's not.
-He read your mind.
-That's genius all over.
I'm not giving up. Good!
Good!
That guy with the mustache
said he'd be waiting for him after school.
If I follow him I'll know
which club that is.
Anyway, there are so many
different clubs.
Which club is Irie joining?
Oh, that one.
I want to join you.
Anime Club
Anime club?
Well... is Irie here?
Irie?
Who is that?
Isn't that a guy who just came in
and left?
Excuse me now.
Brass band members wanted.
No experience necessary.
You're late.
I told you to go together.
That's just what you said by yourself.
Okay.
But we're going to join the same club
so may as well, right?
Same club?
Let's go in.
All right.
Excuse me, I want to join too.
Well, who are you?
Do you have an invitation?
Well, I don't have any invitation,
but I really want to join
the tennis club.
When I'd enter Tonan University,
I definitely wanted to join this club.
I was yearning for it.
Please consider me.
Isn't it great, captain?
We welcome passionate people.
What's your name?
Kotoko Aihara.
Kotoko-chan, come on in.
I'm in charge of freshmen, Sudo.
We're having a welcome party
for newcomers. Join us.
-You're over here.
-Right.
I'll give you a rundown.
If you have questions ask Sudo.
I'll tell you anything except for
my cell number. It's 0120.
-How do you like it?
-Wow, great!
Can I wear this?
I'm so happy
that you're playing tennis.
I was a pretty good player
when I was young.
-You were?
-I was.
It's me who taught Naoki tennis
for the first time.
Look, Naoki.
Isn't Kotoko's clothes adorable?
How do you like it?
I don't think you should go
by the looks.
Aren't you guys doing well?
Because you and Naoki
are joining the same club.
You both must be in love.
Not at all.
-Irie is popular.
-He is?
Mrs. Irie.
Does Irie like beautiful
and smart woman?
Is there such a girl for him?
Wow, Naoki is popular
than I thought.
Even though he's so unfriendly.
You'll be okay.
Go over to the school
of Engineering
and keep working on him.
No matter what kind of woman
comes by
you're the best for Naoki.
I don't know.
I've been living with both of you
and kept watching you so I know.
Do your best.
Yes.
Hold the racket. Strike a pose.
You look good.
Do it. Right.
Receive. Good. It's this next.
Do like this.
All right. I'll get my love
with this energy.
You look good, Kotoko.
What are you doing?
Serve.
Good job, Kotoko. Nice!
Okay, freshmen.
It's the first day today
so we'll have tryouts.
It's just to see your skills.
-Do your best.
-Yes.
What? I didn't know
that there was a tryout.
You'll match with Sudo who's a Junior
and in charge of freshmen.
I'm Sudo. Good to see you guys.
Good to see you.
I'm relieved that it's Sudo.
You don't know anything, yet.
What do you mean?
He seems to be changed.
Let's start with Wada.
Me first?
Did you think I'd start from the top
of the list? Loser!
I'm the guy who's unpredictable.
Wada.
Come to the court.
Why are you idling there, Wada.
-Attack with your whole body.
-He's called as the Evil Sudo.
More.
Next, Yada.
-Come in.
-Yes.
Sudo has been known
for his personality change
when he held a racket
ever since he was in
an elementary school.
Although he's usually peaceful.
Next.
Miyamoto. Come on in.
yes.
Matsumoto is on fire.
She was in the best four in women's single
when she was in high school.
Her grades are good also,
so she could have gone
to any college if she wanted to.
The tennis club in Tonan
is prestigious.
How do you know that?
She asked me when we were
applying to colleges.
I've known her since freshman in
high school at national competition.
When I was a freshman
in high school,
Irie didn't know me.
I was just watching him.
That means Ms. Matsumoto
has longer history with Irie.
I feel like I'd lose.
Okay, Matsumoto. As expected.
Great job.
Thank you.
Next.
Naoki Irie.
Come in.
Yes.
Finally, the day has come.
Yes. Please don't be too hard on me.
Like I'm not going to be hard on you.
Irie is fantastic.
Okay, that's it.
Irie, move out of the court.
Wait, Irie. One more time.
Sudo.
It's a tryout today.
No, one more time.
Amazing, that Naoki Irie. As I heard.
Look at Sudo's expression.
Irie made him mad.
The next one will face that rat.
Next, Kotoko Aihara.
Come in.
Don't walk slowly.
Wait!
It's the first time for me
to play tennis.
Shut up. Here I come.
What's up with her?
Wait, don't run away.
Hold your racket.
Open your eyes.
Here's another one.
Oh, my gosh, Aihara fainted.
There.
Are you okay, Kotoko?
Kotoko is so lame as usual.
Yuki.
Kotoko, why don't you take a break
from practice tomorrow.
Freshmen are not allowed
to miss practices.
I'll be okay.
I'll get used to it soon.
You're a girl. Don't kill yourself.
Yes.
Do you have any other scratches?
I think I'm okay.
I'm a little sore, though.
Aihara
We're getting ready
Chef, what should I do with these?
Wash and peel them.
Yes.
Hey, Kinnosuke.
You work at college during the day, right?
Yes.
How's Kotoko doing at college?
She hasn't changed since high school.
She can't be the same.
She's in a good age.
Well...that.
Boyfriend or somebody?
If that's your concern,
I'm watching her not to get a bad one.
Then how about Naoki?
Chef, don't worry.
I'll always protect her
from his evil hands.
Besides, at college,
they go to different buildings.
Compared to high school,
the distance between them
seems to be way farther.
It shows that justice will conquer.
Hey, Kinnosuke...kun.
-Yes.
-Can you deliver a message for me?
Kotoko, is your face okay?
Ouch, it hurts!
I heard that the tennis club in Tonan
is seriously athletic.
They're so strict
that most newcomers quit.
They end up with a couple
of them left every year.
Kotoko, are you sure you can
keep going?
It's for me to be close to Irie.
I'll do my best.
Quit it now.
Kin-chan.
Kotoko Love
Kin-chan, It's not fair that only
Kotoko gets it.
Do you have a problem?
I'll give you a hip shake.
It's Kin-chan special.
Hey, Kotoko.
Quit tennis.
You don't have to injure your pretty face
to do stuff like that.
Since I joined, I want to try hard.
It's not good to give it up
in the middle of it.
My dad taught me that.
Kotoko.
How courageous!
Oh, now I remember.
I have a message from your dad.
Come to Aihara tonight.
Why?
I don't know. He said he wanted
to discuss something with you.
-Eat it.
-Sure.
Let's eat.
You guys are eating too much
during our talk.
Stop kidding. You ate "Love."
You ate my love.
What are you doing.
Don't be so slow.
Yes.
Lower your hip more.
You guys are lacking motivation.
This tennis club doesn't need
that kind of a guy.
Quit now.
-Do you want to quit?
-No.
Right? A river is flowing.
A forest is alive. We all are.
-Alive.
-That's right.
Time for a break. A break is over.
Listen.
There's no time for you to rest.
-Next, 100 sit-ups.
-Yes.
-Answer me.
One...
Together. One.
Is this tennis club?
It's all conditioning.
Besides,
Irie and Yuko Matsumoto,
who joined together, aren't here.
What's going on?
One.
Oh, my!
Sorry, Kotoko.
Could you throw it to me?
Wait.
There.
Hey you.
How come you're hitting balls
even though you're a freshman?
How about conditioning?
Oh, you didn't know?
Tonan tennis club goes
with players' abilities.
If one passed the tryout yesterday,
even a freshman can get priority
to practice on the court.
Is that right? Then is Irie there?
Irie is even more special.
He'll come whenever he feels like
and to the tournament.
That was his condition to join here.
Does that mean that he won't come
to the practice?
Why did I join the tennis club for?
A little bird told me that you lived
in the same house as he does.
However, you don't know much
about him.
I guess that's the kind of relationship
that you have.
Aihara,
what are you goofing off for?
As a punishment,
you'll run 100 rounds on the track.
-It was a great meal.
-Thank you.
Oh, Kotoko. Welcome.
Hey, Kinnosuke, when did I tell you
that you could leave your spot?
-You got lots of dishes to do.
-Sorry, bro.
See you at school, then.
What's wrong, Kotoko?
I'm just sore.
Anyway, what do you want
to talk about, Dad?
-I'm going to use the private room.
-Yes.
Are you okay?
Looks delicious.
I'm going to eat now.
It tastes much better after
working out.
You're not good at ball games,
are you?
You're not interested in it.
Why do you play tennis?
Is that because of Naoki?
Why are you being serious
all of a sudden?
Listen, Kotoko.
It's been almost a year since
we started living with Irie family.
I thought about many options,
but keep depending on Irie
family's kindness is not good.
Iri-chan and his wife
take good care of you.
To be honest,
I thought about you and Naoki
being together
in the future... possibly.
Dad.
However.
After watching you guys for a long time,
it doesn't seem like Naoki's feeling
is towards you at all.
Then it's not going to work.
With me again,
let's go back to live just two of us,
okay, Kotoko?
Of course I want to consider
your feelings too.
But I found a good property nearby.
So please consider my feelings too.
For me,
it's hard to see your heart broken.
But if I
leave Irie family now,
the contact with Irie
will be gone for me.
What are you dazing about?
Irie.
Are you going home now?
Where have you been?
It's none of your business.
What about you? You're late.
I was at my dad's restaurant.
-Your dad's restaurant?
-Yes.
I wondered
if you went to see that guy.
That guy?
No, never mind.
I was told that my dad
found a good property.
What?
Our new house.
He hasn't made a contract, yet.
See, my dad and I
are at your house
for almost a year, right?
So my dad thought about this
and that.
That's why.
Are you leaving my house?
If that happens...
Will you miss me?
Irie?
It's more like I can finally go back
to my regular life.
I don't know.
I don't know
how Irie feels.
What...can I do?
I gave up on Irie.
NEXT EPISODE
You're kidding!
We'll match with doubles.
You team up with Kotoko Aihara.
-No kidding.
-Don't get in my way.
Accomplishing something together
might change Irie's mind.
The reason why you try hard
on tennis is because
-you want to be with Irie?
-We'll definitely win.
-You got it?
-Being a nuisance to your love
won't make you feel bad at all?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
It's all over.