I'm going to the party, too.
I heard that you couldn't come.
Your girlfriends will be with you
for Christmas, right?
Let's make it a fun night together.
Listen, I want
to introduce someone to you.
Boyfriends? When did you both...?
I was betrayed after all.
If I knew this would happen,
I would've gone to Mr. Irie's party.
Around this area,
I heard burglars were prowling.
Burglar!
You bastard, bastard, bastard!
What are you doing?
Weren't you going to have a party
with your friends?
There is one.
The cake.
Even though it was a coincidence,
my first Christmas-like Christmas
was spent with just Irie and me.
It's like a dream come true.
Wait for me, Kotoko.
I'll bring you dinner.
It's really like Christmas.
What's going on? It's dark in there.
The Christmas Eve
that I spent with Irie was
so much fun for me, but...
it was just a special treat.
My relationship with him
hasn't changed at all.
The seasons have passed
and the year has changed.
Another spring has come.
We've become sophomores in college.
Tonan University is
welcoming new freshmen.
I'm the tennis club's 54th captain,
Sudo.
Now,
from a freshmen representative
with a bright future,
I'd like to receive
an address.
Go ahead.
I started law school
at Tonan University this year.
I'm Ayako Matsumoto.
I was the winner of last year's
national high school competition
in the girls' division.
My goal in college is to win
a national championship.
And also...
to steal Naoki's heart.
Please guide me.
What do you teach your sister?
That's what I want to know.
Well, this newcomer is with us, too.
We're sophomores now.
It feels awkward to be called senpai.
Right. I still can't get out
of the mindset of a freshman.
What are you reading so earnestly,
Satomi?
Ah, well, I'll start...
working as an editorial staff member
for this magazine tomorrow.
What?!
We have to start thinking
about finding employment, right?
I've been wanting to work
in an editorial department
for a women's magazine.
I've been visiting them often
to sell myself,
and I finally got accepted.
Great! That's awesome, Satomi.
They told me that I would run errands
and serve tea first.
But I feel like I've finally toed
the line.
I'll work hard.
What are you going to do
in the future, Kotoko? Maybe...
marrying into Irie family
as soon as you graduate?!
No way!
I've never thought
about my job specifically.
It's about time to get started
and get things going for you.
Right. You're being too passive.
We'll be job-hunting next year.
You have to research it
and get things going.
I'm aiming for record labels
and music production companies.
Are you influenced by Narasaki?
In the beginning,
I just wanted to support him,
but I got interested
in indie music more and more.
The band that'll be known worldwide...
I want a job discovering that band.
I see.
My dream for the future will be...
It's not that.
Your mind is easy to read.
Before I knew it,
everyone started chasing their dreams.
I...
What's my future dream?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
BEYOND EACH DREAM...
We're gonna throw a promotion party
for you and Naoki.
Is Irie coming home that day?
Of course.
There's no party
without the main guest.
It's been a while
since Irie came home.
Right? I can't wait.
Kotoko, you've got to take action.
It's a new semester.
At college,
you've got a newly arrived rival.
You can't let your guard down.
Mrs. Irie, when did you...?
She's kind of cute,
and her tennis skill might be better
than her sister, but...
My goal in college is to win
a national championship.
And also...
to steal Naoki's heart.
She's totally unacceptable.
She's the type
that doesn't take challenges well.
If anything happens,
she'll take up with another man.
No matter what happens,
you're devoted to Naoki.
She doesn't possess
that same stubborn will power.
Should I take that as a compliment?
Work hard, Kotoko.
You're a sophomore.
You'll be 20 this year.
You're not a child anymore.
To become a family in the future,
we'll make a big step this year. Okay?
-Yes.
-Okay!
Mr. Irie, thank you for waiting.
I'll explain the result
of the examination.
Please do.
AIHARA
Enjoy.
It's rare for you
to come here by yourself.
Sometimes...
I feel like drinking by myself.
-There.
-Thank you.
That's good.
Your food and sake are
the best combination.
It's such a nice restaurant.
Thanks.
Hey, Ai-chan.
Ai-chan,
what are you going to do
with this restaurant in the future?
Is your apprentice taking it over?
Or are you going
to have Kotoko marry someone?
Kinnosuke.
You always say you'll marry Kotoko
and take over this restaurant.
Aren't you going
to interrupt them like that?
Eventually, I want Odawara
and Kinnosuke to be independent.
I want them
to have their own restaurants.
For cooks,
it's their dream to have
their own restaurant.
But what's going to happen
to Aihara then?
Even if I want a successor,
Kotoko is a bad cook,
as you know.
This restaurant ends with me.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Even though you've made this
into such a great place?
It's my fate to have a daughter
who's not so smart.
I just have to accept it.
However,
finding a husband for her
can still be an option.
In fact, that Kinnosuke has been
in love with Kotoko
since high school, right?
Just between you and me,
Kinnosuke is talented for sure.
He can become the chef
and successor of this place.
He has the potential.
Then why don't you?
It all depends on how Kotoko feels.
I think you're the same,
but I've been doing whatever
I wanted to do. That's why...
I can't tell my daughter
that in order to keep the restaurant,
she'd have to marry the cook
of my choosing.
Even though my daughter would do that,
if there's someone
who wants to marry her,
it's best to marry the man
who really loves Kotoko.
That's what I think.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Hey, watch out here.
Uh, sorry.
Kinnosuke?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I'll take the trash out.
What's up with you?
It's unlike you, Kinnosuke.
What's up?!
What's this pent-up feeling?
-Chef.
-Yes.
Here they are.
Is it my ego wanting my son
to take over the business?
-About Naoki?
-Yeah.
He's not interested in it.
Well...
even if Naoki doesn't want it,
you still have Yuki.
You have two great sons.
You're a lot different from me,
who only has Kotoko.
Things will work out.
If it's Yuki,
it'll be too late.
What?
Satomi is late.
The class is starting soon.
It's already time.
You're here. Good morning.
Just in time. You're late today.
I worked late last night.
I didn't sleep.
Did you pull an all-nighter?
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
The editorial department gets crazy
before printing.
Everybody is in full swing.
The more they work,
the better the articles get.
Even an amateur like me can't tell.
You know,
magazines are like living creatures.
Just being there makes me excited.
It's a very fulfilling job.
I can relate. It's so exciting.
-I love you, Jinko.
-That's what society is.
Right. I don't get tired
even if I don't sleep.
Not at all. I was fine, too.
-Can you feel my excitement?
-Yes. I'm feeling it.
-I'm tired.
-Me too.
-I'm hungry.
-What do you want to do for lunch?
Shall we go to the cafeteria?
Sorry, I have to work this afternoon,
so I'm leaving.
I'm having lunch with an alum
who works at a music label.
-Sorry.
-Okay.
See you later, then.
-See you tomorrow.
-See you later.
Bye, see you later.
Bye-bye.
Kin-chan.
Could you try this one?
Sure, but what is it?
Soon...
my cuisine might be offered at Aihara.
-So....
-Your cuisine will be served there?
Great.
It's only one dish.
Besides it's served
before the appetizer,
like an hours d'oeuvre.
First, Chef has to taste-test it
and approve it.
For someone like me
to make the full course
will take many years.
But it's great.
I'll take your praise after you try it.
Okay, I'll taste it now.
Let's see.
What?
Was it bad?
Did I fail on flavoring?
It's very delicious.
You've been good at cooking
since high school,
but it's totally different now.
It tastes like a pro.
Really?
But you don't look very happy.
I thought...
everyone was amazing.
I've been wanting to work
at an editorial department
for a women's magazine.
You know,
magazines are like living creatures.
I get excited just being there.
It's a very fulfilling job.
I'm aiming for record labels
and music production companies.
I got interested
in indie music more and more.
The band that'll be known worldwide...
I want a job discovering that band.
You, Jinko and Satomi have found
what you want to do.
You've started chasing your dreams,
but...
I haven't found anything yet.
Everyone has... their own pace.
You can find your own pace.
Hey, how did you feel
when you decided to be a cook?
How did you know that it was
what you wanted to do?
Well...
I wonder what it was like.
No.
It's not something
that you think about.
It's the same as falling in love.
Same as falling in love?
Right.
When you fall in love,
you know it without thinking, right?
"I love this person like that."
It's the same thing.
Without thinking complicating things,
you get excited and feel happy.
You want to be
with that person forever, right?
It's the same as that.
Before I knew it,
I was doing what I wanted to do.
I see.
But...
wanting to do a job
just to be close to your love
and things that you want to do
are different, aren't they?
For example,
if my love is the president
of a company,
I want to be his secretary.
If my love is a pilot,
I want to be...
a flight attendant.
If he's a tennis player,
I'll be his manager
to coordinate his schedule.
If he's a college professor...
Give me a call.
...I'll be his assistant
to aid his research.
Just like that,
I imagine my future jobs
and dream about it
every now and then.
But there's a problem
in this dream.
Depending on my love's job,
the thing that I want to do
changes all the time.
It's different from what
I really want to do, isn't it?
I can't say that this is
my future dream.
Kin-chan?
So, if your love is a chef,
you'll be a hostess
at his restaurant.
Living your life to support
someone's dream is a good thing.
Men think...
they want to make
a woman like that happy.
I'd bet you'd be a great hostess.
Kin-chan, stop joking around.
That was a good one.
May I have this?
I'll try some more.
It's jiggling. Delicious.
JOB SEARCH MATERIALS
Oh, this is it.
Job search materials.
The same as falling in love.
I'll know it naturally, huh?
Even so,
I can't help getting frustrated.
What kind of a book was Irie reading?
To find what I want to do,
I wanted to live on my own.
I stay home forever,
graduate college,
then take over my dad's business.
Is it really okay just like that?
That's just living out the plan
my parents laid out for me.
I feel like...
I was left behind.
Irie.
It's rare to see you studying.
Are you preparing
for the second foreign-language class?
It's a medical book, isn't it?
What's going on?
What changed your mind?
CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR PROMOTION
Naoki and Kotoko,
congratulations on being promoted
to sophomores.
Cheers!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You're throwing
such a wonderful party for us.
Not at all.
Yuki, you're in 5th grade now.
Studying to entering junior high
will become more serious.
Work hard on it!
I'll go to Tonan
just like my brother did.
Of course I'll be in class A,
and I'll become number one
like my brother.
Oh, that's very promising.
Right, Iri-chan?
Let's have dinner.
-Please eat.
-Let's eat.
-Go ahead.
-This is great.
-This is your mom's specialty.
-Temari-sushi.
-Eat up.
These are cut so beautifully.
I'm honored
to get praise from a pro.
Naoki, Yuki, eat a lot.
This, this and this.
Here they are.
-This one is really good.
-Right?
Eat this, too.
This one, too.
I can't eat all of them at once.
It's because
I worry if you're taking
enough vitamins and calcium.
Eat it all up.
Naoki is not a child anymore.
Honey, have some champagne.
Wow, darling, thank you.
-I'll drink tonight.
-Go ahead.
Your mom looks so happy
since you are here.
-I'll take some, too.
-Then I'll serve you.
Yuki, are you eating?
I'm stuffed.
Kotoko, you'll get fat
if you eat that much.
You were eating a lot, too.
I'm okay.
I'm going to grow tall soon.
For you, it's not like you're going
to grow out your boobs.
What?!
You dodged me.
It's nice to have
the whole family together.
There's no place like home.
Thank you for including us,
even though we're not your family.
What are you talking about?
You're the same as family.
She's right.
About Kotoko and Naoki,
I haven't given up yet.
Naoki, are you still going
to keep living by yourself?
You must have had your fill.
Why don't you come home soon?
That's right, bro.
Right? Then Kotoko and Naoki
can get married
and we'll become a real family.
Are you drunk, Mom?
You're drinking too much.
I'm not drunk.
Right, Kotoko?
It's too soon for me to get married.
Why?
When we got married,
I was the same age
as you are now,
I9 years old.
It's not too early.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Thank you for dinner.
I have to get going now.
Why?
He's right.
My presence, for Irie,
is only a nuisance.
Naoki, wait.
I have something
that I want to tell you.
Can you come to the study with me?
Please.
Honey, you too.
I want you to hear it, too.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave for now,
but have some tea
and enjoy each other.
I'll be back. Sorry. I'm coming!
What is it?
Naoki, what are you thinking
about your future?
I want you to tell me
what you really think.
You may have known it already,
but I want you
to be the official successor
of my company.
After you graduate from college,
I want you to join my company.
I agree with him.
You're still a sophomore,
but it's better to learn
about the job now.
So...
like during summer vacation,
during the long break,
I want you to learn
about the jobs at my company.
I want your opinion
on managing the company, too.
They're taking too long.
What are they talking about?
Kotoko,
why don't you take them some tea?
Okay.
What do you think, Naoki?
Whether I take over
your company or not,
it's not something
that I can decide right now.
I need time to think about.
You must've had enough time
to think about.
About your dad's company
and also about Kotoko.
Honey, let's set Kotoko aside for now.
No, this is also an important decision
for his future.
I'm not recommending Kotoko
to you randomly.
If you are taking over
your dad's company,
Kotoko would be the ideal wife for you.
Right, honey?
Certainly...
managing a company
is not that easy.
You definitely need a support system.
So, you want a girl
who cares about you
and supports you.
And, also,
a girl who's loved
by people around her is the best.
Marriage is not just falling in love.
In that sense, Kotoko surely is
the ideal wife, I think.
But the most important thing is...
your feelings.
Let me hear your opinion.
What do you think, Naoki?
Before I tell you what I think,
you both are...
...forcing me to act the way you want.
You're pretending to let me choose,
but in reality,
the way I live has already been decided.
From the very beginning.
That's a dirty trick.
Dirty trick?
Naoki, what are you saying to your dad?
He's thinking about you first.
It's not that he's thinking about me,
he's worried about himself.
How could you...?
You're the same.
Since you like Kotoko,
you're ignoring my feelings.
You're blindly trying to get us marry.
So, I just told you.
I like Kotoko for many reasons.
Besides, you and Kotoko
are meant for each other.
Enough already!
Not only is choosing a job restricted,
but loving someone is as well.
That's why I don't want to be here.
The family that constrains me.
Honey!
Calm down.
Sorry, I...
Irie!
-Kotoko, what's wrong with him?
-What happened?
No, nothing.
Irie's coat.
I'll take it to him.
Irie, Irie, your coat!
Irie, that's not the way
to the station.
I'm taking a walk.
Sorry about that.
We showed you our ugly argument.
I'm sorry that I ended up
eavesdropping on you.
But I think...
Mrs. Irie just lost her temper.
You know, you don't...
usually...
say much, right?
You don't tell people
what you think.
That's why everyone got so frustrated.
They didn't know
what you really think...
and became impatient...
and nervous.
That was how it happened,
but both of your parents are...
definitely...
treating you as their first priority.
There's no doubt about it.
But I understand how you feel.
You only live once.
You want to decide
what to do yourself, don't you?
Right.
I think so.
You've said this before.
College is the place
where you find what you want to do.
Have you found one?
Unfortunately,
I haven't yet.
Not only Kin-chan,
but also Jinko and Satomi are
chasing their dreams, but...
I'm not.
My mind is preoccupied with you.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Kin-chan told me...
if I find what I really want to do,
I'll know it without thinking.
He said it was the same thing
as falling in love.
But...
until you find it,
you feel nothing but anxious.
Right.
So, I think you're brave.
If I was told by my dad
to take his restaurant over like that,
I would probably give in.
But you didn't.
So...
not only your job...
but also your love...
Not only is choosing a job restricted,
but loving someone is as well.
Without being pressured,
you should be able to do what you want.
So, do what's best for you.
Falling in love with someone
is not written in a book.
Even if people tell you that,
it's better to do it this way.
If it's someone you can't love,
then there's nothing
you can do about it.
Irie, you should...
choose someone you really love
and be happy.
I...
want to be a doctor.
I'm planning on taking a test
to transfer to medical school.
I don't know if it's for me...
but I want to study it properly.
Human life is...
dependent upon a momentary decision.
A little thing can lead...
to easily curable from incurable.
I was scared, too.
Until now, I thought that life was...
decided by God...
and humans could do nothing about it.
Being a doctor is...
the job that interests me
for the first time in my life.
Why didn't you say that to your dad?
Until just now...
I still wasn't sure about it.
Just now?
When did you decide it, then?
While I was taking a walk now.
I guess.
But I don't want
to tell my parents just yet.
Why is that?
I want to get ready.
I want to tell them
when I can take action.
So, you too,
don't tell anyone else about it.
Got it.
But...
why did you tell me
such an important thing?
Well...
I don't know why.
Is this the station?
Why, we went a different way.
To get to your destination,
there are different paths you can take.
Even if it looks like a detour,
you may find something important
along the way.
See you later, Kotoko.
Irie.
An important thing like that...
why did he just tell me about it?
You can make things happen.
Developing new medicines or...
becoming a doctor...
and curing diseases like magic.
I'm...
the worst mother in the world!
We're a family.
There are times when we'll fight.
Even so...
Honey.
Honey, I have something important
to tell you.
What?
Actually,
I wanted to tell Naoki, too.
To be honest...
Darling.
Darling?
Darling, are you okay?!
Naoki, Naoki!
Darling, darling, are you okay?
Hang in there.
-Darling.
-Iri-chan.
-What's wrong?
-Dad!
Don't give in.
Darling.
Darling!
-Iri-chan.
-Don't leave us.
Darling.
I'm the deputy president now.
What's going to happen
to Dad's company?
I'll protect Dad's company.
I'd like to discuss the investment
in your company.
We might be merged into them.
We're like newlyweds.
In that kind of situation,
Kotoko and Irie may get close.
Is Matsumoto confessing
her love to Irie?!
-No!
-Have you...
-given up on Kotoko?
-Stop kidding.
Naoki, do you want to have
a marriage meeting?
It's a good deal
for the company, right?
If I take over the company,
everything will be solved.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
Are you giving up
on becoming a doctor?