I'm glad that we can all attend
Tonan University.
Congratulations.
If you go to Tokyo University,
your parents will be proud of you.
You've only brought me troubles.
-Are you okay?
-How about your entrance exam?
I didn't take it.
I'm really sorry.
Because of my daughter,
your precious son had to ruin his future.
Let me be clear. It's not your fault that
I didn't take the entrance exam.
I felt that it would be nice for me
to go to Tonan with others.
You mean you want to go
to the college with me?
That's not what I meant.
After many twists and turns,
Irie has decided to go to Tonan University
with me.
It's March.
It's time to say goodbye to Tonan High
School where we spent three years.
That's right.
Our graduation is getting closer.
8 DAYS TO GRADUATION CEREMONY
You have only eight days
until the graduation ceremony.
Soon you have to say goodbye
to your friends,
with whom you spent three years together.
What's wrong? C'mon. Cheer up.
Hey, what's the matter?
Hello, Class F?
Finally we all know which university
we are attending.
Many in this class do not go to Tonan,
unlike other classes.
I will miss you all.
Many? Tell the truth.
I'm the only one to stay with Tonan.
That's true.
I don't mean to make you feel bad.
Are you really sure about your choice?
If I really want to go to Tokyo
University, I can try again next year.
That's right.
I'm sure that you will be accepted
if you apply.
Watanabe, Waseda is your first choice.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Irie is really staying with Tonan.
I'm shocked.
I've heard that he missed the entrance
exam of Tokyo University on purpose.
Why?
Don't tell me that it's because the girl
in Class F goes to Tonan.
Soon we will be a high school graduate.
Kotoko, you must make special memories
with Irie before the graduation.
Not really. We are going
to the same college anyway.
What's wrong with you?
Our high school life will be over soon.
It's a perfect time to get closer to him.
Irie goes to Tonan,
because she goes there.
Everyone is guessing so.
I can't believe it.
What is he thinking?
You two get together at the graduation.
I'm blushing.
At least you should get a kiss.
That's good.
To commemorate the graduation,
you should have the first kiss.
Stop it. It is not going to happen.
Do you know a legend of this school?
A couple who kisses on the
graduation day stays together forever.
-Really?
-I've heard about that.
But I don't know if Kotoko has a chance.
You may be right.
You may be right. A kiss?
The first
kiss?
It is
a special kiss which you can experience
only once in your life.
I have been longing
for the first kiss for a long time.
But I didn't expect
that it would happen in that way.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
-What do you wear for a graduation party?
-A suit jacket or jeans?
WHO WILL GET THE FIRST KISS!?
Three of you are organizers of this party,
huh?
That's right.
We haven't picked the venue yet.
But we really want you to come.
Of course I will.
All of you studied so hard.
I'm proud of you.
I really congratulate you
on your graduation.
Thanks.
We are so glad that everyone
of Class F was able to graduate.
We will make our party the best.
Right, teacher?
-Yeah!
But a student doesn't
want to attend the graduation ceremony.
What?
Didn't you hear
about Kinnosuke Ikezawa?
Kin-chan?
Now I realize
that he is absent today.
Are you saying that he can't graduate?
It's possible.
He always fails...
Wait. He got enough units to graduate.
He can graduate, but...
Hi, Kin-chan.
Kotoko. How do you find me?
Gintaro and Dozo told me.
Idiots! They shouldn't have told you.
Kin-chan.
Let's attend the graduation ceremony
together.
Both Gintaro and Dozo
are so worried about you.
They told you everything, right?
I got rejected by Tonan University.
But you are not the only one
who was rejected in our class.
Gintaro and Dozo go
to a technical school. Right?
You know what?
I came to Tokyo from Osaka,
hoping to do something big.
Something big? Like what?
I don't know that yet.
But you only live once.
Every man would like to do something big,
to marry a perfect girl,
and to have a perfect family.
To accomplish these,
I convinced myself to go
to the biggest city in Japan.
I came to Tokyo by myself.
But I failed.
How could I compete
with Irie?
Why Irie?
You know why.
I declared defiantly that I loved you
more than anyone.
But now I can't even go to a college.
Irie gave up Tokyo University
to attend Tonan University with you.
Not exactly.
I keep on losing to him.
I'm disappointed by myself.
College education
won't determine your value.
Remember?
I'm sure I told you about this.
My father and Irie's father
are the best friends, right?
Irie's father is
a graduate of Tokyo University.
Yeah, yeah.
He started his own business
and developed it into a big corporation.
On the other hand, my father didn't even
attend a high school.
Right after graduating the middle school,
he became an apprentice to a chef.
You know that, right?
But they like each other so much.
They respect each other's profession.
If they didn't, you guys
wouldn't have a place to live now.
He wouldn't invite you into his house.
I know.
What I'm trying to say is...
you and I are not good at academic stuff,
but we can find something we are good at.
Something I'm good at?
Find something big, something that only
you can accomplish.
Hey.
If I find it and become successful,
will you fall in love with me?
Well, that's another issue.
Well...
As Irie said, nobody knows
what will happen next.
"I don't like her today,
but I may like her tomorrow."
I don't mean that I dislike you.
You are my friend. That's all.
That's fine for now.
I will find something I'm good at
and become the best of it.
Kotoko, wait for me until then.
Will you come
to the graduation ceremony?
Okay.
I will attend it with head held high.
Grades do not determine my value.
I won't lose to Irie, no matter what.
I will be a big shot.
Let's make the graduation ceremony
great together.
-Okay. Let's make great memories.
-Yes.
Miss, what can I get for you?
Well...
Let's see...
Mandhe...ling?
Sure.
It's called Mandheling coffee.
-Kotoko.
-Yes?
What's that?
I will miss you.
I will miss you, too.
I will miss you, but we have to move on.
Hey!
Kin-chan is back.
Bro!
Kin-chan, have you gotten over it?
-"Gotten over it"? What do you mean?
-About college.
Jinko, shut your mouth.
No, no, no.
I've decided to become a man
earlier than you can.
And I will be ready for...
C'mon, Kotoko.
That's my goal.
I got it. Instead of going to a college,
he will get a job.
Kin-chan, you are very positive.
Or I would say "happy-go-lucky."
I'm glad to see you in the graduation
ceremony with us.
Thanks. By the way,
you are the organizers of the party,
right?
That's right. Jinko and I were just
debating which restaurant we should pick.
Our budget is very small,
so we don't have many options.
Butalian? No, this place isn't good.
I will help you organize this party.
I will make it the best. Trust me.
What do you think?
Well...
We can trust your judgment
only about food.
"Only about food"?
What are you trying to say?
Kin-chan, thank you for your help.
Listen up, everyone.
I will make
our last night of high school
the most memorable one.
Just "wash your face" and wait.
I will show you.
If you want to use the old proverb,
it is "wash your neck."
Neck. "Wash your neck."
Just "wash your neck" and wait.
I will show you.
Yeah!
Let's wash our face, too.
Sure. Wash your face, too.
GRADUATION DAY
You look so cute, Kotoko. Smile.
Good.
Give me upturned eyes.
Imagine that the camera is my son.
Stop it.
Go behind the chair.
And do like this.
That's right. That's right.
Ready? Say cheese.
So cute.
You are so cute.
Now sit here and lean to your left.
Just like that.
Are you ready?
You are so cute. I love this shot.
This is the last day
I can see you in the uniform.
C'mon, Dad.
I got enough interior shots.
Now let's go outside.
Good timing.
This is a memorable day.
Let's take a photo of you two.
He wouldn't do that, of course.
You want to take a photo or not?
Kotoko, this must be your lucky day.
Let's go.
I'm coming.
Are you ready?
Get closer.
C'mon, guys.
Closer.
That's it. You look great.
You have bread crumb on your face.
Since this is the last day,
can we walk together?
Anyway...
Time flies. Don't you think?
This is our last day of high school.
In the last three years,
this is the best year for me.
This was the most painful year
in my 18-year life.
They come together again.
Bro, you should do something.
He
gave up Tokyo University,
because of Kotoko.
Kotoko is worth it.
I admit that Irie has a good taste.
Well,
the stronger my rival is,
the more I get motivated.
I have a brilliant plan.
Plan?
After the graduation party,
Kotoko and I will...
What?
We will kiss.
Kiss?
Kiss! Everyone can hear you.
-Sorry.
-Kiss?
Shut up. Shut up.
Let's go.
Guys.
Have you heard a legend of this school?
A legend?
A couple who kisses
on the graduation day
will stay together forever.
-I know. I know.
-That's why you are planning to...
That's right.
Kotoko and I will
vow eternal love.
But how?
-Are you going to force her...
-That's not good.
I wouldn't do that.
I told you.
I have a brilliant plan.
A brilliant plan?
What is it?
Kotoko will be stunned by my love.
Too loud. Everyone can hear you.
-Bro!
-Good morning. Good morning.
Presentation of a diploma.
High school diploma.
Naoki Irie.
This diploma proves that this person
has finished the general education
curriculum at Tonan High School.
Congratulations.
Kotoko Aihara.
Jinko Komori.
Satomi Ishikawa.
Kinnosuke Ikezawa.
Kin-chan!
This is it.
Our high school years are over.
Kotoko!
Kotoko, is that Irie's mother?
Hi, Mrs. Irie.
Thank you for coming today.
Congratulations.
Both my husband and your father
had to leave for their work.
That's good.
My father must have been
very emotional.
I would cry
if I saw him crying.
Of course, he has a right
to be emotional. This is the graduation
day of his only daughter.
I can't help crying, too.
Kotoko, you look like
a real member of Irie family.
Of course.
I have not given up my hope
that you will become my daughter-in-law.
Look.
Wow, this makes the graduation
ceremony more memorable.
You are a cool parent.
A life full of love is so cool.
Look over there.
If you want mine.
It's the second button.
This reminds me of my youth.
But our uniform has only two buttons.
Happy to get someone's button?
It only happens on the graduation day.
I'm jealous. I wish...
Listen, Kotoko.
What are you doing?
You are a new graduate, too.
Take the plunge and tell my son
about your feelings.
That's right. You have permission
from Irie's mother.
You won't get a more powerful
endorsement than this.
Well, yes, but...
Speak of the devil.
Your love interest attracts
a lot of attention.
-Can I have your second button?
-Request denied.
Will you take a picture with me?
Request denied.
Sorry. Excuse us.
Sorry.
I didn't know that he had
such a large number of fans.
Unlike you, they know
that they don't have a chance,
so they have remained
as a secret admirer.
Since this is the last day,
they can't hide their emotion anymore.
This is exactly what I thought.
I believe he likes you, Kotoko.
He is keeping his second button
for you.
I don't think so.
I am his mother.
I know exactly what he has in his mind.
-Kotoko, go.
-What?
This is our last day of high school.
That's right. You should make
a long-lasting memory.
-Go.
Go!
Go.
What if
I can get Irie's second button?
Hi, Irie.
Congratulations on your graduation.
If you don't mind,
can I have your second button?
-Sure.
-What?
Cool!
Does this mean
that I'm
his special girl?
Irie.
The button.
Well...
Well, Irie...
If you don't mind, can I have your--
Request denied.
Sorry, Kotoko. I'm really sorry.
Even after graduating high school,
he still has no interest in girls.
You still have a rocky road ahead of you.
Bro, everyone loves your fried noodle.
It will capture Kotoko's heart for sure.
I know that.
Everyone will come soon.
Oh, no.
Why is there a partition here?
Can I remove it?
We have to share this room
with another group.
They have made reservation first,
so we have to live with it.
This is the graduation season.
In this neighborhood, this is the largest
venue as far as I know.
And we have your fried noodle.
That's right.
Put the fried noodle in the middle.
Put it in the middle.
Here you go.
But your best card is that,
isn't it?
GOODBYE, CLASS F
I know it.
This stage is your secret weapon.
I'm impressed, Gintaro.
That makes it easy.
What are you talking about?
You are too slow.
We are talking about "it."
He and Kotoko will...
The kiss, huh?
Aren't you excited?
Besides, don't say the word.
I'm embarrassed.
-I'm embarrassed.
-You are embarrassed.
In all ages,
the same thing captures girls' heart.
Which is?
A song
Test. Mike test.
I will dedicate a beautiful love song
to Kotoko.
Then it will
melt Kotoko's heart.
Kin-chan.
I'm sorry for having turned down
your love for a long time.
I don't know why,
but I didn't find you attractive.
Instead, I was in love with such a jerk.
I was such an idiot.
Don't cry.
What's going on?
Kin-chan, here we are.
C'mon. You interrupt my fantasy.
Fried noodle looks delicious.
Kin-chan, thank you so much.
Can we eat it now?
Sure. Eat as much as you can.
I did the best.
Thank you.
My favorite fried noodle.
Bon appetite.
Kin-chan's fried noodle is the best.
Is that right?
Hey, Kotoko.
You have green dried seaweed
on your face.
It won't come off.
Irie?
Class F?
Why is Class F here?
Oh, no...
You are the ones who have reserved
the other half?
Move quickly.
GOODBYE, CLASS F
KEEP IN TOUCH
Hi, everyone.
Let's start the graduation party of
Tonan High School Class F.
Look around.
We have plenty of food and drink,
which I prepared.
Have a pleasant chat
while enjoying the food.
Wow, it looks awesome.
So gorgeous.
Look at that. Spectacular.
What kind of cuisine is that?
What kind of cuisine?
I think it's Chinese.
Chinese?
What?
What's going on?
It's amazing.
I like this.
It's catering from Robuchon of Ebisu.
-Robuchon? The famous restaurant?
-Yes.
My father is a good friend of the chef.
Really? Wow.
-Lucky you, Watanabe.
-It's nothing.
What a shame! Class A got everything,
while Class F got nothing.
That's true.
I love this fried noodle.
This sausage is also delicious.
Eat it, everyone.
I will try this one, too.
Right. Let's have fun here.
Let's eat, everyone.
This is awesome.
Hey, listen.
Well...
A star of this graduation party
is not us or the food.
It's our teacher.
Mr. Shibukawa.
Thank you for teaching us
for three long years.
Can you make a speech for us?
We want your speech.
Hello, everyone of Class F.
Congratulations on your graduation.
I know you were discriminated,
just because you were in Class F.
But
you fought back.
I fought with you all for three years.
I'm really proud of what
we've done together.
It has been a privilege
for me to educate a group
of such high-achievers
for three years.
Waseda, Keio, Sophia and others.
Many of you are accepted
to highly competitive universities.
I'm so proud of you guys.
Without your help,
we wouldn't be able to earn
such high grades.
You are flattering me.
I want to make it clear.
Go ahead.
Academic success should not be a sole
goal of young people.
Agree.
You shouldn't be measured only
with grades at school.
Yeah!
If you don't have good grades,
it's no easy to get a college education
as well as to get a job.
I'm so happy that
I don't need to see you
go through such hardships.
Applause.
Hey!
You are smart. So what?
Well.
I wasn't talking about Class F.
I guess you are very sensitive
about grades, huh? I wonder why.
That's why I don't like underachievers.
They tend to have a victim mentality.
-What did you say?
-And to appeal to the violence.
What? I haven't done anything violent yet.
A verbal abuse can be prosecuted.
You know that?
Can you guys compete against us
in anything but the physical strength?
-Kin-chan.
-Bro.
Kin-chan.
Kobayakawa, I am proud of you.
Thank you, sir.
I'm sorry, but all the other rooms
are booked.
I understand, but can you do something?
This is our last night of high school.
We can't have fun in the same room
with such jerks.
But there is nothing I can do.
Kin-chan.
Kotoko, I'm trying to get another room.
-I'm telling you--
-We don't need another room.
-Let's go.
-But Kotoko...
Let's go, Kin-chan.
The teachers just lost their cool, because
they had some alcoholic drink.
Let's have fun together.
You've promised me.
We will find something we are good at.
Anything other than studying.
If you believe in that,
you won't care whatever Class A
says about us.
You are right.
I guess
I lost my cool.
Thank you for making me realize that.
Kotoko.
You have green dried seaweed
on your face again.
Allow me.
Bro...
Naoki Irie.
Well, I have to go back to my friends.
What do you want, Mr. Genius?
Did you come to check
what Kotoko and I were doing?
Are you jealous?
Hey, are you ignoring me? Stop.
While you are enjoying a college life,
I will do something big
and become a big shot.
I've promised Kotoko that I will do that.
That would sound cool
if you were accepted to a college.
Since you were rejected
by all the colleges,
that sounds just sour grapes.
That's not the only thing
I have promised Kotoko.
Tonight I will kiss...
I will kiss Kotoko.
If you want to have a dream,
go to bed.
You will see.
Kotoko is the one who wants
to have a great celebration party.
At the end of high school,
finally she realized
who cared about her most.
You are jealous now? It's too late.
Understand, Mr. Genius?
Attention please!
Hello, Class A.
Hello, Class F.
Let's have fun together.
This is our last night of high school.
Good idea.
Why don't we share dishes
with each other?
Good idea. Let's do that.
Come over here.
Of course, you are excited.
You've got everything you want.
Irie cannot go to Tokyo University,
because of you.
Because you are dumb, you have a right
to drag someone excellent down?
Unbelievable. You are so pathetic.
It's not her fault.
It's not her fault
that I don't go to Tokyo University.
-Irie.
-What?
-You are not a complete jerk, huh?
-It will change my view on you.
Why on earth should I give up going to
Tokyo University, because of this one?
"This one"?
Are you okay, Kotoko?
Hold this for me.
-Are you okay?
-That's right.
A smart guy like Irie
wouldn't be manipulated
by a nobody like her
and wouldn't ruin his life.
Nobody?
That makes sense.
Irie wouldn't fall in love
with such a dumb girl.
I shouldn't have believed the rumor.
"Such a dumb girl"?
Wait a second.
How dare you call me
"this one," "nobody" and "dumb girl."
It's very rude. Don't you think?
It is true
that Irie helped me.
-I may have caused him some troubles.
-Some?
A lot. I mean.
-That's right.
You don't need to say that.
What a cold-blooded guy!
You like the cold-blooded guy, don't you?
Hey, hey. It's getting too hot here.
The bottom line is that
the power of Kotoko's love
started everything.
Irie and Kotoko are
meant to be together forever.
Not a chance.
Then how about the good-luck charm
for the standardized test?
-What are you talking about?
-We can laugh at it now.
Irie fell down the stairs, because
of Kotoko's handmade good-luck charm.
Right. I remember
his walking on crutches.
He missed a train
and had his leads all broken.
Moreover, he couldn't eat lunch.
It caused a lot of troubles.
It's not a good-luck charm,
but a bad-luck charm.
But my point is that
it had the power of her love.
Just the power worked
in a opposite direction.
Wait.
Her house was destroyed
just after she gave Irie her love letter.
Am I right?
Besides, Irie refused to accept it.
No, thank you.
Wow, she is a woman
who causes a storm.
Did you get chocolate
on St. Valentine's day?
Yes, a pathetic one.
She also gave me a strange tool
to massage my head.
Almost comical. You don't have
good taste for a gift, huh?
These failure stories are so entertaining.
Who wants to share your own one?
Oh, no... Kotoko is breaking down.
Kotoko?
This is so fun.
I love to hear failure stories.
Fine. Now it's my turn.
Are you prepared?
What?
Do you think that you have
no failure stories to be exposed?
I've never done anything
embarrassing in my life.
Even a genius has a weak point.
Don't tell me...
What is this?
Don't tell me that this is Irie?
-He is like a girl.
-He wore a female dress.
How did you get hold of it?
Your mother gave me another copy
and I kept it in my wallet.
Because it's a photo of my love
in his childhood.
But even a 100-year romance
can turn sour,
if anyone sees this photo.
Now you know how we feel
when you make fun of us.
Look. Look. Oh no, it fell.
You come with me now.
It's time.
Okay, guys.
Let's do it.
Hey, hey, hey
Both Class F and Class A,
are you having fun?
I, Kin-chan,
will excite you more.
I wrote
this song
to dedicate to a girl whom I love.
Now I share my love with you,
which I have nurtured for three years.
Now I confess.
I love you, Kotoko.
I love you
I love, love, love you
Kotoko, Kotoko, Kotoko.
Tokyo is a lonely city
Really
They don't look at each other
Seriously
But listen, Kotoko
Your smile
-What do you want?
-Thank you for the mess.
I'm not scared of you.
You are the one
who made fun of my feelings for you
and laughed at me with others.
Do you know?
I'm just glad
That I met
You
I
Am just happy
With that
Kotoko!
I had enough.
I won't
love you anymore.
Really?
You will forget about me, huh?
That's right. Now I know who you are.
I will forget about you and find
a handsome boy at college.
Go ahead. Forget about me if you can.
Can you forget about me now?
Kotoko.
Am I not good enough for you?
Kotoko, I'm a man of action.
Kiss?
Is that the first kiss?
Is that the first kiss in my life?
Is that the kiss
I have been dreaming about?
Did I
have a kiss
with Irie?
Who is that beautiful woman?
NEXT EPISODE
Is she your girlfriend?
-Hell no.
-Join the same club as Irie.
Then you can stay with him even though
you two belong to different departments.
Kotoko Aihara!
If you don't take action,
that woman will take Irie.
She is beautiful and has a great body.
You know nothing about him, huh?
Let's go back to a life with you
and me only.
Can't you forget about me?
I don't want to see you hurt.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION