Kotoko, look at that girl.
Who is that beautiful girl?
Obviously she is flirting with Irie.
Kotoko, you are in big trouble.
Kin-chan?
I'm working here during the day
and at your dad's restaurant at night.
I want to protect you from this devil.
Join the same club as Irie.
Then you can stay with him
even though you belong
to different departments.
You live in the same house as him,
but you know nothing about him, huh?
Let's leave this house and go back
to a life with only you and me.
-Dad found a good house.
-Are you leaving our house?
If so, will you miss me?
Finally, I can go back to my old life.
No! I don't want to lose Kotoko!
-Calm down.
-But, honey...
Thank you for saying that,
but we've already made up our minds.
Ai-chan,
we are happy to have you two here.
We really want you to stay with us.
You pay us your living expenses.
You're not a freeloader.
We took advantage of your kindness
and stayed with you too long.
If we move out,
Kotoko will be able to forget about Naoki.
Is that the reason?
I will do something about him.
Mrs. Irie,
this is an issue between the two of them.
You may think that I want any girls
to live with us, but that's not true.
I love Kotoko
because she is so positive...
so resilient...
and so adorable.
Thank you. What a lucky girl Kotoko is.
I'm really sorry.
Brother, did you hear that?
Kotoko is leaving. Yeah!
She has caused us so many problems.
It means that we don't need to be exposed
to "idiot virus" anymore.
I'm so happy! Dumb Kotoko will be gone!
Ta-da! What do you think?
I really wanted a daughter and wanted to
decorate a room like this for a long time.
We've lived with the Irie family
for about a year.
Finally, my dad and I have decided...
to leave them.
Bye-bye.
See you again, Kotoko.
Mr. and Mrs. Irie were so nice to me.
They treated me like a real daughter.
-Honey.
-And...
I have to say goodbye to Irie.
Everything is over.
Kotoko, we are leaving.
This is it.
Come in.
Our new house was just vacated
by the renters and isn't ready for us
to move in yet.
For a while,
this is our temporary residence.
Why don't we stay at the Iries'
until the house is ready?
It's for you.
You need space to get over him.
If we stay with them,
you will be hurt more.
The sooner, the better.
A week or two. That's all.
I don't live with Irie anymore.
My life without Irie starts today.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
You moved out of the Irie family's house?
LOVE ACED
Right now we live in a temporary place
until the new house is ready.
-I thought you would never leave them.
-Me, too.
But her tie to Irie is gone
now that she's left their house.
Jinko, don't say that.
I don't care.
I've given up on Irie.
No way!
You never gave up on him
no matter how bad he treated you.
You always say too much.
I've changed.
I won't chase him anymore.
I'll stay away from his department campus.
What happened to you?
To tell you the truth,
my dad convinced me.
He's right.
I have been watching you two.
Naoki, unfortunately,
will never develop feelings toward you.
You have no chance.
His words made me think it over.
-Kotoko...
-So, I forget about him from now on.
I will enjoy the college life
and find a cool boyfriend.
I'm proud of you.
-What is this?
-Only for Kotoko?
-It's not fair.
-It's a Kin-chan special.
Kotoko became a new person today.
So, today is her new birthday.
My birthday?
Good. Happy birthday to you! Got it?
Thank you, Kin-chan.
Cheer up. I'll help you forget about Irie.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, KOTOKO
I'm home.
Now drop it in the egg.
Then drop it in the bread crumbs.
What's going on? Where is Mom?
She's looking down.
She has no appetite
and doesn't want to do anything.
She's depressed.
So, we should do the housework
for a while.
-Housework.
-I've never seen her so depressed.
Yuki, let's make it.
I'm home.
How was your day?
Today I'm making your favorite, lasagna.
Oh, no, dumb Kotoko is home.
Watch your mouth, Yuki.
How's college life going? Cheers!
Dinner is ready. Have a seat.
Hello. How was your day?
Stop it!
I've promised myself
that I will forget about Irie.
I won't see the Irie family anymore.
Bro, what's wrong with Mom?
Don't tell me
that it's because dumb Kotoko left us.
Yuki, you have your own room now.
Why don't you stay there
instead of hanging around here?
I know,
but I'm used to being in this room.
Now I feel comfortable here.
Good night.
You gave up on Irie, right?
Then why are you still in the Tennis Club?
This is about my pride. I'm ready.
Serve! Go!
Ninety-five.
Ninety-six.
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred.
You did it.
So many dropped out.
But you survived our hard training.
I'm very proud of you!
So, I will give you a prize.
You can finally be on the court today.
No kidding? Really?
Yeah!
Fight. Fight.
We can be on the court? As ball boys?
Who's aiming at me?
You haven't dropped out yet, huh?
I couldn't stand it if I were you.
Only basic training
and being a ball boy every day?
To make matters worse, Irie is not around.
-I'm not doing this to see Irie.
-Really?
Fight! Fight!
Why do I have to be a ball boy?
Hey, move your foot off the ball.
You shouldn't do that if you're--
You're still a ball boy, huh?
-Irie! Why are you here?
-Because I'm a member of the Tennis Club.
But you usually don't come
to the practice.
I come when I feel like it.
Irie, come over here.
Let's practice together.
The serve practice is over.
Next is volley shot and stroke practice.
No, no. I promised myself
that I'd forget about Irie.
Why do you show up in my life?
I'm trying to forget about you.
Irie!
Long time no see.
What brought you here?
Let me guess.
You want to challenge me. Am I right?
If you want.
But I don't want to embarrass you again.
You really want to do this?
It's your choice.
You are so confident, huh?
Why don't you allow me to set the terms?
Fine.
Then we play doubles.
My partner is Yuko Matsumoto.
-Your partner is Kotoko Aihara.
-What? Me?
-You must be kidding.
-Mr. Sudo swallows his pride.
He is desperate to kick Irie's butt, huh?
What's your problem?
Matsumoto is a girl in the freshman class.
Aihara is a girl in the freshman class.
It's very fair.
No way. It's totally unfair.
If someone won doubles with that one,
he could be a world champion.
Irie, you don't need to say that.
But it's true.
You said that you would accept any terms.
Matsumoto and Aihara, get on the court.
I'm sorry, but I won't be easy on you.
Please forgive me.
It's impossible, right?
I know it's impossible.
What is your answer, Irie?
Would you like to default?
Give up without trying?
What kind of man are you?
-Listen. You don't need to hit a ball.
-What?
Are you really doing it?
I have no choice. I can't back out now.
Anyway, you just stand there.
Never stand in my way.
"Never stand in my way"?
I feel that Irie has told me
the same thing repeatedly
since high school.
Serve. Play.
Hit it.
Fifteen-zero.
Game.
It hurts.
I'll never stand in his way.
Is that all you got?
Take this!
It's my ball. Get out of my way.
What?
Game set. Sudo-Matsumoto win.
The score is 6-2.
Good game. That was so close, Irie.
She is a perfect match for you.
Do you want to have a rematch?
Perhaps next week?
-Sure.
-What?
-Are you serious, Irie?
-You don't want to?
I may embarrass you again.
Fine. Rematch at the same time next week.
Understand, Matsumoto and Aihara?
-Yes.
-Yes, sir.
What should I do?
What? Play doubles as Irie's partner?
And you practice with him?
Kotoko, are you sure about that?
You are trying to get over him.
Meet him every day and forget about him?
How could you do that?
That's impossible.
To be honest with you,
I'm not sure if I can handle this.
That's what I thought. It's not easy
to forget about someone who kissed you.
Well, think of it this way.
This could be a great opportunity.
By accomplishing something with you,
Irie may become attracted to you.
No way.
I can't be any help to him in this match.
And I have done a lot of things with him.
He prepared me for exams
when we were in high school.
He even helped me do my summer homework.
-But Irie never became interested in me.
-You're right.
He was always cold-blooded.
He'll never change.
This may be a painful week for you.
Right, Kotoko?
I can't avoid Irie
for the rest of my life.
I will work hard at tennis
and at forgetting about Irie.
You're late.
I'm sorry. My class didn't end on time.
No excuses. Let's practice.
Hold it, Irie.
Aihara has not passed our tryout yet.
So, I can't let her practice on the court.
She is still a ball boy.
We have a match in a week.
I can't break our club rule.
Aihara, what are you doing? Pick up balls!
-Mr. Sudo is unreasonable.
-He won't back down.
He doesn't want to lose to Irie,
no matter what.
I'm sorry, Irie.
Fight! Fight!
Six, seven, eight... and 9.
-What was that?
-Don't close your eyes.
Heads up even while picking up balls.
Keep your eyes open
and follow the ball with your eyes.
And move to where the ball is heading.
Understand?
Understood.
I keep my eyes open
and follow the ball with my eyes.
Keep my eyes open and follow the ball.
That's it!
Yeah!
Good job.
You are dismissed.
Your practice starts now.
What? I can't do that.
As I followed your instructions,
I got hit by balls a lot of times.
You can't practice with the club.
So, we have no choice.
Practice your swing 100 times.
It's started raining.
Starting tomorrow, we'll have
a morning practice, too. Get ready.
It's raining.
Faster.
Bring the shoulder in.
Get back in position quickly.
It's the rainy season, huh?
-It never stops raining.
-Shut up. Just do it.
-Yes, sir.
-Again.
I'm home.
Listen, Kotoko.
I got a fresh rockfish today
and cooked it exactly the way you like.
You want to try it now?
What?
You've gained weight,
so, you should go on a diet.
-Hey.
-The low-fat diet is popular.
-Low-fat diet, huh?
-Hey. Hey.
Kin-chan?
Where is Kotoko today?
-Kin-chan, you don't know, huh?
-Kotoko is in trouble.
What? She is in trouble?
Ta-da. Ta-da.
-Good morning.
-Kin-chan.
I heard.
You have two practices every day
and are exhausted.
In such a situation...
you must eat well.
Otherwise, you can't continue.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
-It's so delicious.
-Is that so?
Hey.
Are you trying so hard at tennis...
because you want to be with Irie?
You can't forget about him, can you?
He told me, "Never stand in my way."
Remember you told me the other day
that it was my new birthday?
To become a new woman...
I must become somebody
who won't bother him.
If I just say, "I will forget about him,"
without any actions...
it sounds hollow.
It means that I may not be able
to get over him yet.
I got it.
Kotoko, you are on the journey
to get over Irie.
It may take time...
but I will support you.
-Kin-chan.
-On the other hand...
I'm not giving up on you.
I'm very tenacious.
Don't be surprised.
-Thank you, Kin-chan.
-You're welcome.
-Eat it.
-Okay.
Let's do it.
Again. Here you go.
Swing with your shoulder. Here you go.
Keep your eyes on the ball.
That's good. Again.
The light's out, huh?
We have no choice.
Let's practice a swing now.
Think of it as a ball and push it.
Good. Remember that.
The shoulder should be higher.
-One.
-Two.
-Come on. Visualize the ball.
-Sorry.
Toss the ball up as high as you can.
Bring the racket back faster.
-Okay.
-Again.
-Run.
-Got it.
-Okay.
-Again.
-I'm ready.
Faster.
-Back in position with side step.
-Yes, sir.
Again.
Back to the position.
Keep your eyes on the ball.
-Faster.
-Trying.
Back in position with side step.
Get back on your feet.
Let's do it again.
Faster.
Excuse me?
Wait.
Excuse me.
-Where is the Department of Literature?
-That way.
-Thank you.
-Mrs. Irie?
Hi, Mrs. Irie.
Hi, Jinko and Satomi. Long time no see.
Why are you hiding your face?
My son will be mad if he finds me here.
That's why I am in disguise.
Actually, you stand out.
And it's easy to tell that it's you.
You behave like Kotoko.
Kotoko?
I haven't seen her for a while.
I miss her so much.
We also thought that Kotoko and Irie
would be a good couple.
-They even kissed once.
-No.
Shut your mouth.
Kiss? You mean...?
Yes. The kiss.
Ki...
Did they kiss?
-Don't you need to see Kotoko?
-She's on the court.
That's okay.
I don't need to see her at the college.
I will bring Kotoko back to my house.
What? Kotoko is trying to get over Irie.
She doesn't need to get over him.
They kissed, right?
No matter how much my son opposes it,
I will bring Kotoko back.
One, two.
-Again.
-Sure.
Bring the shoulder higher.
With count one, toss the ball. One.
You crossed the line. Again.
One, two.
Take aim before hitting the ball. Again.
One, two. Keep your eyes on the ball.
One, two.
I did it! I did it!
I made it for the first time!
I'm sorry.
Even a kid could learn how to serve
within a day.
I guess so.
You have a lot of things to celebrate.
Sometimes I envy you.
-Do it again.
-Sure.
THE DAY OF REMATCH
-See you later.
-Have a great day.
-Wait, Kotoko.
-Yes?
We're moving into the new house today.
Right. I totally forgot about that.
Don't come back to this apartment tonight.
Go to the new house.
Don't worry. I know where it is.
-See you later.
-Have a great day.
I hope she won't forget.
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
-Kin-chan.
-Hi, Kotoko.
-Are you okay?
-Yes. I'm fine.
Kotoko, you've worked so hard.
I'm proud of you.
-You have a rematch this afternoon, right?
-Yes.
I brought some food for good luck.
Pork-cutlet sandwich.
Wow! Pork-cutlet sandwich!
Thank you, Kin-chan.
Enjoying that pork-cutlet sandwich?
You don't look nervous at all.
It's good-luck food.
If that kind of superstition worked,
nobody would lose a match.
Are you aware
how much trouble you cause Irie?
I'm working hard not to be a drag on him.
Your working hard is causing him trouble.
He was embarrassed
by the loss of the last match.
He will be embarrassed again today.
He also had to waste his time
to train you.
I don't understand how you can be okay
with the fact
that you're causing trouble
for someone you love.
-Which?
-Rough.
Smooth. Service!
Listen. Believe in what you've done
for a week.
Keep your eyes open and follow the ball.
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
You are not alone. I'm with you.
So, don't be scared.
Understood.
Sudo-Matsumoto, serving play.
I can't believe
that that novice touched my serve!
But her ball didn't come to our side.
We're winning with a large margin.
It's a matter of my pride.
I don't care about Irie anymore.
-Let's try to humiliate Aihara.
-Sure.
Keep your eyes open and follow the ball.
Move where it is heading.
Wow. I'm not afraid of the ball anymore.
On top of it, both Sudo's shot
and Matsumoto's shot
are much slower than Irie's. That's why...
Take this, Aihara.
-Kotoko!
-Yes, sir.
I see it.
Wow, she returned Mr. Sudo's serve.
No girl in our club could do that
except Matsumoto.
I'm impressed, Aihara.
You did it.
When did I grab a racket
for the first time?
It was when I was born...
Did you twist your ankle?
What a pity.
-Right here?
-It hurts!
It's impossible to continue.
Mr. Sudo, we withdraw from the match.
Wha...? What? Are you sure about that?
Take my racket.
I'm sorry. We lost again. It's my fault.
Actually, I didn't believe we could win.
Lord, will you get mad...
if I'm even more in love with Irie?
Where is your house?
It's strange.
It wasn't that far from the station
when I came to check it out the other day.
I don't think that it's far from here.
You said that before.
That's why I suggested taking a cab.
-It's waste of money.
-Put yourself in my shoes.
Okay.
When I returned Mr. Sudo's serve
in that match...
you called me by my first name.
I don't remember.
That's the first time
you've called me by first name.
As I said, I don't remember.
I was so absorbed in the match.
Look. That's the one.
That's our new house.
This is my house.
-Say hi to your father for me.
-Wait.
I think he's home.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Dad wants to see you.
I'm sure that he wants to thank you.
Fine. Okay. So, let go of my arm.
Sorry.
-Yes?
-Dad?
Is he your grandpa?
I don't know him.
-Who are you?
-That's so rude.
-Who the hell are you?
-I live here.
-This is my house.
-No way. I think this is mine.
-But I came here once.
-Whatever.
This is my house.
I'm confused.
What are you talking about?
-I know you two kissed.
-Kiss?
Go out with my son.
That is your mission.
Are you going to follow Irie's date?
Let's make a pact to help each other.
-So cool.
-He took Kotoko to see this movie?
You are so dirty.
We make a good couple, don't we?
-Maybe.
-It doesn't mean that you dislike me?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
You are hard to deal with,
but I don't dislike you.