Kiss in Tokyo.
It's time for "Kiss in Tokyo" again.
I'm the host Tama.
This show will be on air for four hours
until the morning. Enjoy it.
I went to see a fortuneteller
the other day.
I'm told that I have a good chance
for a new love. Yeah!
But I may lose the opportunity,
because I tend to be too shy.
That's not good.
I need courage to confess my feeling.
But it's easier to say.
Don't you agree?
So tonight I want to hear
your story about love.
Hey, you. It's not time to yawn.
I want to hear funny stories
as well as heartwarming ones.
Don't hesitate. Send me your story.
The Lyra meteor stream
can be seen tonight.
This will be a rare opportunity
to see a meteor stream in Tokyo.
The Lyra?
I hope you know that
your dreams come true
when you wish upon a star.
If you have not confessed your love yet,
why don't you wish upon a star tonight?
It may help you get your love.
I wish Irie to notice my feelings
and to love me back.
HIGH SCHOOL AFFILIATED TO
SENTO UNIVERSITY
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-You are early today.
I have to go. Talk to you later.
Dear Mr. Naoki Irie,
how do you do?
I'm Kotoko Aihara of Class F.
You may not know me.
But I know you well.
While I was walking to this school
with my mother,
I found beautiful cherry blossoms
and other spring flowers.
They seem to me--
I have been in love with you
for two years
since I heard your speech
at the entrance ceremony.
Since I have no chance to be
in the same class with you,
I dare write a letter to tell you
my feeling.
I felt like struck by a shooting star
when I saw you for the first time.
This special feeling
has stayed in my heart.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
I am Kotoko Aihara of Class F.
Well... could you please read this letter?
Irie,
I love you.
No, thank you.
I thought that my first love ended
disastrously at that moment.
I can't believe this.
But I didn't know that
miraculous events
were waiting for us.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
LOVE FOLLOWS A SHOOTING STAR
JR SHIBUYA STATION
HIGH SCHOOL AFFILIATED
TO SENTO UNIVERSITY
Look. It's Aihara of Class F.
I hear that she just confessed her love
to Irie of Class A.
Seriously?
-Kotoko Aihara confessed her love.
-Are you serious?
To Irie?
Aihara of Class F told Irie
of Class A that she loved him.
She should have known
that she had no chance.
Poor girl.
Enough.
Leave me alone.
Kotoko, did you really tell Irie
that you loved him?
Jinko, everyone can hear you.
How do you know that?
Handing a love letter at the gate?
It's so obvious.
Everyone knows it now.
I'm so embarrassed.
Why did you do that at the gate?
It's almost like a publicity stunt.
And why Irie?
I agree. You are reckless.
No doubt that he would reject you.
A miracle may happen.
By some chance, I thought he might
like me.
Come on. You are so naive.
He is the famous Naoki Irie.
As you know, this school groups classes
by test scores.
Irie is the smartest one in Class A,
which is a class of
highest achievers in our school.
He even got the highest scores
in the nation with the last trial exam.
You see, in life, lots of people
know what to do.
But few people actually do
what they know.
Knowing is not enough.
You must take action.
They say that his IQ scores are 200.
He is born to be a genius.
And he is so handsome and his father
is a successful business man.
HEIGHT 178 CENTIMETERS
WEIGHT 60 KILOGRAMS
I hear that he is fluent in English.
He is a great athlete, too.
He is the ultimate super boy.
On the other hand, we are in Class F.
We are the bottom losers of this school.
He lives in a different world.
But I tried hard.
In the last three years,
I have studied hard,
hoping to join Class A with Irie.
What?
Listen, Kotoko.
You know alphabets, right?
Of course, I do.
Then tell me how many letters there are
between A and F.
A, B, C, D, E, F.
That's right. It would be a miracle if you
could jumps up to Class A.
It would be less possible
than winning a lottery.
than snow in the summer.
Less possible than being hit
by a shooting star?
What? What did you say?
Nothing.
Anyway, Irie is in a different league
from you. Understand?
I know that, but at least I wanted to
tell him about my feeling
before both graduate.
You are so naive.
Please accept my gift.
Irie is handsome, but everyone knows
that he is a jerk.
He has no interest in girls.
Innumerable girls
have been rejected by him.
He has had no girlfriends so far.
29,999 GIRLS WERE REJECTED
Look. It's Kotoko Aihara.
She confessed her love to Irie.
Shut up!
You guys are annoying.
So, what happened?
He is a boy and a high school senior.
No interest in girls?
There is something wrong with him.
I agree. I believe that there is someone
more ordinary out there,
who is perfect for you.
Kotoko! Hey, Kotoko!
Hey, Kotoko.
Here he comes.
Is it true that Irie of Class A
rejected you? Is it true?
Kin-chan, you are too close.
I didn't know that you liked such a nerd.
How dare you?
I thought you liked me.
I'm not your girlfriend.
Damn it. I made special Takoyaki
just for you.
I wasted my time.
-Excuse me.
-I want it.
Hurry.
-I love Kin-chan's Takoyaki.
-I will open it.
Here you go.
Wow. Thank you.
So delicious.
Don't forget to sprinkle
green dried seaweed.
-You sprinkle it.
-Yes, sir.
Cooking is the only thing Kin-chan
is good at.
Only? What do you mean?
I love Kotoko more than anyone.
I'm proud of that.
Class A? Whatever.
I'm better than Irie.
Rejecting Kotoko?
I will punish him for it.
This means a war.
He is too arrogant.
Forget it.
You all are right. I was reckless.
He didn't even read my letter.
What a jerk he is!
I...
don't have an eye for boys.
So... I'm okay now.
I will be over him.
Kotoko...
Really? How can you yawn
in this situation?
I was up all night last night
and made sure that there would be
no misspelling in my letter.
I even checked kanji characters
of my name with a dictionary.
AI
HARA
KOTO
KO
Are you kidding?
That's how nervous I was.
I was so nervous that I couldn't eat
breakfast this morning.
So... Kin-chan, thank you.
I could survive this morning
with this meal.
I love your smile.
I could make Takoyaki
as many as you want.
Get over it quickly.
It's really good.
Don't take advantage of this situation.
This is not for you.
Sorry.
Well... that's so cute.
-Let's sprinkle dried bonito shavings.
-Put mayo on it.
MR. NAOKI IRIE
Kotoko!
Sorry. We had to talk to the teacher.
Don't worry. I didn't wait that long.
-Let's go home.
-Okay.
By the way, is your new house completed?
Yes. We are moving in on Sunday.
A new home, huh? Very nice.
I guess so. I need it for a change.
That's right. When you move,
luck may turn in your favor.
-Okay.
-That's right.
I believe it.
"I believe." Right?
Yes, I believe it.
I believe, huh?
I will help you move in.
-Thank you.
-Me, too.
Thank you. I'm getting excited.
Yeah!
-Wow, it's huge.
-Here you go.
I bring some help.
Dad!
You guys must work for Kotoko.
Okay.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Hey, guys.
Thank you for coming.
Father!
I will do anything for Kotoko.
I'm Kinnosuke Ikezawa.
-I'm Gintaro.
-I'm Dozo.
Nobody cares about you guys.
Father, think of me as your real son
and tell me anything to do.
Kin-chan, stop your self-promotion.
Start working.
-Sure.
-We appreciate your help.
Let's do it.
Thank you for coming, everyone.
Kin-chan is the one
who organized this.
He wanted to come to cheer you up.
Is that so?
Be careful with that.
Let's start working.
-Should I take this one?
-Yes, please.
Upstairs.
-Upstairs. Okay.
-Wow, this is heavy.
-Upstairs?
-Upstairs.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
Well, now we have everything
in the house.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
What an impressive house it is, Father!
My late wife, Kotoko
and I went through a lot.
But finally we have
our own brand-new house.
Come on, Dad.
Stop it. Everyone can see you.
He won't let you, Kotoko,
go easily when you get married.
No worries.
I am willing to live with your father
if we get married.
Father, please consider me
as your real son from now on.
Please call me Kin-chan
as a family member.
Thank you, everyone.
Thanks to your help, we could finish
the move-in quickly.
Let's go inside and eat something.
I will serve my best dishes.
That's right. Kotoko's dad is a chef.
I'm looking forward to it.
We can't wait.
Wait a second.
What?
Can't you hear something strange?
-What?
-No, I can't hear anything.
It's your imagination.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What are you talking about?
What? A shooting star?
During the day? No way.
Are you kidding?
SHIGEO AND KOTOKO AIHARA
It got hit by a shooting star?
News 7:00.
Around noon today,
a shooting star, which is believed to be
a part of the Lyra meteor stream,
hit and destroyed a house in Tokyo.
My daughter noticed something first
and then--
This is Mr. Shigeo Aihara,
whose house was destroyed.
Something flashed
and hit the roof of my house
in the brink of an eye.
Then the house trembled and...
And suddenly
collapsed.
First, we saw a hole in the roof
and I didn't think it would be a big deal.
Fortunately,
we all were outside.
My late wife might
have saved our lives. I'm sorry.
I put all the money I had into this house.
So we don't have anywhere to go.
The fallen meteor is a small rock
with 3 centimeters in diameter.
The meteor only triggered the collapse.
The investigators suspect
corner-cutting construction
as a main cause.
Let's move on to the next topic.
NO BUSINESS TODAY
I'm sorry, but we are closed today.
Thank you. We are looking forward
to seeing you again.
Dad, cheer up.
I have worked so hard for that house.
Let's start over.
How could I open my restaurant
right after such a tragedy?
We need to rent an apartment,
but I spent all the saving to build it.
It would be easier to accept
if it was an earthquake or a fire.
Meteor stream? Really?
Even the insurance doesn't cover that.
What rotten luck!
You are wrong.
We got lucky.
Think about it.
If we all had been inside the house,
we would have died.
If you had been injured, you might have
not been able to work as a chef again.
In that case, you would've had no choice
but to close this restaurant permanently.
Am I right?
Look. We escaped without a scratch.
We are lucky.
This is the best luck we've ever had.
Be positive. We are very lucky.
What?
You sound exactly like your mom.
Your mom was happy-go-lucky, too.
Happy-go-lucky?
Are you making fun of me?
How rare would it be
that a house is struck by a shooting star?
Struck by a shooting star?
Why do you say that?
It sounds more romantic
being struck by a shooting star
than being destroyed by meteor.
It makes me feel that it is just
a beginning of something special.
I can't believe it. You have become
more and more like your mom.
Hello, this is Aihara.
Yes.
What?
Wait a second.
Boss,
somebody wants to talk to you.
Okay.
Yes. This is Aihara speaking.
Sorry about today's closure...
Iri-chan?
How are you doing?
You are still alive, huh?
Iri-chan?
Hi, Aihara of Class F.
It is her house that was destroyed.
-Did you see the news?
-Yes, I did.
It was reported by newspaper, too.
Right after she was rejected by Irie.
She has no luck.
It is Kotoko who was struck by the Lyra
meteor stream.
A tragedy after a tragedy.
Something sinister is haunting her.
Kotoko! Kotoko!
Jinko and Satomi.
Everyone is talking about you again today.
I'm so ashamed
that I want to crawl under the rug.
Do you have a place to stay?
Thank you for your concern.
We will stay with my dad's best friend.
Really? You got lucky to find
such a place quickly.
He saw the news and called
my dad's restaurant.
Very generous man. I'm happy for you.
This will be a turning point of your luck.
That's what I thought.
Odds of being struck by a shooting
star are one in hundreds of millions.
I believe that I will have great luck.
Good.
That's Kotoko whom I know.
Is that right?
Donation, please.
What's that?
Even 10 yen is good enough.
Please donate.
How about 5 yen?
Any amount, please.
Donation, please.
We are collecting donation for poor
Kotoko Aihara,
whose house was hit and destroyed
by the Lyra meteor stream yesterday.
Please help your fellow student
who suffers the tragedy.
He is an idiot.
That's Kin-chan. What else can we expect
from him?
-I'm sure you have at least 10 yen.
-Stop it, Kin-chan.
We have the victim here.
She just suffered a tragedy yesterday.
But today she comes to school
with a smile.
Her resilience makes me cry.
Stop it. Kin-chan, you are an idiot.
What's wrong with you?
I'm trying to help you.
I've been humiliated. I don't want
to be in the spotlight anymore.
This makes it worse.
Everyone will make fun of her more.
Get out of my way.
Irie.
Irie, who do you think you are?
Be nice to her.
Kotoko is hurt.
Whose fault is that?
-Blame the Lyra meteor stream.
-That's another issue.
You rejected her in a humiliating way.
Everything started from it.
-That's not a reasonable argument.
-I agree.
Your rejection led her
to another disaster.
A chance of being hit by a telluric planet
is one in ten billions.
A telluric planet?
You mean a shooting star?
Are you blaming me
for such a rare phenomenon?
That's right.
Kin-chan, your argument
is not convincing at all.
I didn't know that I had such a power.
I donate my money.
Are you happy now?
What?
Do not pity me.
I wasted my last two years
by being in love with such a jerk.
I will never want your help.
I will never want your pity.
Really? Are you sure about that?
Of course, I'm sure. You are such a jerk
that you don't even have a friend, do you?
Look. I have a lot of friends to help me
when I am in trouble.
Like Kin-chan, Jinko and Satomi.
Kotoko, you are doing great.
I don't need your help at all.
Understand?
DONATE FOR KOTOKO AIHARA
Here is your 5,000 yen.
We are in Class F, so?
Do not look down on idiots.
You get famous again,
whether you like it or not.
Kotoko, you are the only girl
who would pick a fight with Irie.
Oh no, what have I done?
What should I do?
That's not what I intended to do.
Sorry that you had to leave school early
to help me.
Stop it. I'm happy to help you
in such an emergency.
My teacher knows my situation.
AIHARA
This is Iri-chan's house.
It's a huge house.
You are right.
Iri-chan is a CEO of a big company.
-He is a graduate of Tokyo University.
-A graduate of Tokyo University? Really?
He must be someone.
It's huge. They can have a barbecue party
in the yard.
What?
Iris fomica?
No, it reads Irie.
Irie? I see.
Irie?
Yes. His last name is Irie.
That's why I call him Iri-chan.
Why on earth does he have a name Irie?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Hi, Ai-chan. Welcome.
What took you so long?
Sorry. It took us so long to pick up
our stuff in the rubble.
Really? I am glad to see you.
Hi.
I was so surprised.
I was talking to myself.
Ai-chan!
Iri-chan!
You two are so close, huh?
-I was looking forward to seeing you.
-I'm so happy to see you.
Make yourself at home.
-We really appreciate your kindness.
-Don't mention it.
Mrs. Irie, thank you for having us.
I'm sorry that you had such a disaster.
Stay as long as you want.
I'm his daughter, Kotoko.
Nice to meet you.
You are so cute.
I'm so glad to meet you.
Unfortunately we have only boys.
You have sons?
You will meet them later.
Come in.
Come in. Come in.
Excuse us.
-Use the slippers.
-Thank you.
This is so cute.
Hi, Yuki. Come down.
Introduce yourself. They are
Mr. Aihara and his daughter.
He is your son?
So cute.
-Hello.
-How do you do?
My name is Yuki Irie.
I'm in the third grade.
Very smart boy.
Very nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Yuki.
You two must be tired.
Let's settle down.
Let's move.
I'm coming in.
-Here you go.
-This is delicious.
I'm glad that you like it.
Have more.
Thank you.
Kotoko, you've grown up so much.
Have we met before?
You were still a baby.
I saw you at your dad's restaurant.
-You've come to his restaurant?
-Yes.
Of course. We have been best friends
since the kindergarten in Kyushu.
Both of my parents were working.
So I stayed at his house after school
and had dinner with him.
And I was a poor student at college.
Since Ai-chan was a chef,
he often fed me.
You took care of me.
It was nothing.
You introduced a lot of good customers
to me when I started my business.
It was nothing.
Your friends from Tokyo University
and your clients.
Many of them are still
my regular customers.
I owe you a lot in my business success.
That's not true.
We both got married, had kids
and got busy with our own business.
We became estranged a little.
I was shocked at the news.
It was very unfortunate,
but it made us get closer again.
I'm so happy to see you again. Right?
I'm happy, too.
Kotoko, please make yourself at home
and enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
Kotoko, you will find that this
is a small world.
What?
Speak of the devil.
Here our big boy comes.
Big boy?
-What's wrong with you, Kotoko?
-Kotoko is full of energy.
Hi, I'm the oldest son, Naoki.
Very nice to meet you.
He told me that
you two attend the same high school.
Really? I didn't know that.
It's very nice to meet you.
Hey, Kotoko. Say hi.
What's the matter?
That's because...
I'm so stunned.
Iri-chan and Irie
do not look alike at all.
Don't be silly.
Both of our sons take after their mother.
In that sense, they are very lucky.
Stop it, honey.
Come on, you sit down here.
I'm so glad that you two are not hurt.
We are lucky.
You were at home?
If Kotoko hadn't stopped me,
I would have been inside the house.
Then you would have been killed.
You dodged a bullet, huh?
How big was the meteor?
Like this big. It was pretty small.
-About 3 centimeters?
-Yes.
I must wonder how such a small one
could destroy the house.
I'm glad that you two
have known each other.
Are you two in the same class?
Not in the same class, but we got to know
each other in an unexpected way.
Right, Kotoko?
I guess so.
That's nice. Now you can get to know
each other more.
He is a little strange, isn't he?
Please befriend him.
Brother, I've already done my homework.
Really? Good.
But I have a kanji character
which I don't know how to read.
Instead of asking you,
I may want to ask it to Kotoko.
Good idea.
Can you teach me how to read
a kanji character?
Su...sure.
He is in the third grade.
I'm sure I can read their characters.
What's wrong?
Yuki, I'm impressed.
You are studying such difficult characters
in the third grade.
Which one do you not understand?
This one.
TONIKAKU
(REGARDLESS)
This one, huh?
This one reads "Usagi-ni Tsuno."
It means "a rabbit with horns."
Are you kidding?
This reads "Tonikaku."
Can't you read this? You are
in a high school, aren't you?
Yuki, you are so rude. Apologize.
Regardless, I don't like you.
Yuki!
Hey!
I'm really sorry. He is so rude.
It's true that I couldn't read it.
It's my fault.
Well, he doesn't know many teenage girls.
So he is embarrassed.
Do not take it seriously, Kotoko.
Let's forget it.
-Kotoko, you want to see your room?
-Good idea.
I did my best. Come with me.
Eat it, Ai-chan.
-This is so delicious.
-Is that right?
I'm not joking.
Ta-da! What do you think?
No? You don't like it?
I did too much?
We only have boys, right?
I really wanted a daughter.
I have wanted to decorate a room like
this for a long time.
Such as curtains with frills
and stuffed animals.
I'm so happy.
Since I lost my mom when I was young,
I never had a chance
to have anything girlish.
You know my father, right?
He only buys me simple
and sturdy clothes.
I was so jealous of my friends
who wore a frilly dress.
I feel that my dream finally comes true.
That's why...
My dream was to go shopping,
go to a movie with a daughter
and to exchange each other's clothes.
We are perfect for each other.
Don't you think, Kotoko?
Yes.
This room used to be Yuki's.
What?
He had to move into my room.
Now I feel crammed.
Come on. We were so excited.
Don't be a downer.
Now I get why he was so...
Regardless, I don't like you.
Kotoko, don't worry about it.
Just make yourself at home.
Okay.
Son, please help her organize her stuff.
I must cook dinner now.
Tonight's dinner is sukiyaki.
Kotoko, do you like sukiyaki?
I love it.
I'm so glad to hear that.
See you later.
See you.
Well...
Well,
tell me what to do.
I don't need your help.
That's right.
You don't want to have anything to do
with me.
MR. NAOKI IRIE
I don't care if you live with us or not.
Just don't bother me.
A chance of being hit by a shooting star
is one in ten billions.
What are the odds that
a high school girl must live with a boy
who just rejected her?
Is it a beginning of something special?
Or something else...
Here comes.
We have more.
Thank you.
Mr. Aihara, would you like one?
I love to.
Sorry that we didn't ask you whether
you like bread or rice for breakfast.
Don't worry. This is great.
Are you sure about that?
Eat more.
I feel like we are vacationing abroad.
Like being in Monaco.
Now I realize that
I'm eating breakfast
with the famous Irie.
So clumsy.
Be nice, Yuki.
I'm done.
Is it already time for you to leave?
Kotoko, why don't you go with him?
You two go to the same school.
Sure.
Dad, finish the rest.
Thank you for the meal.
See you later.
Have a great day.
-Listen.
-Yes.
Do not walk next to me.
Why?
I don't want to walk along with a girl
who has bread crumb everywhere.
Stay away at least 2 meters from me.
Follow me today and memorize
the route to the school.
And of course, do not tell anyone
that we live together.
Moreover, do not talk to me at all
at school.
You don't need to humiliate me that much.
I don't want to get involved in such
a ridiculous gossip anymore.
Ridiculous?!
I don't like a stupid girl.
I'm so humiliated.
How could I be in love with such a jerk
for two long years?
I will make him regret what he said,
no matter what.
Even a genius has a soft spot, huh?
NEXT EPISODE
We only have a week until term-end
exams. Help me study.
It's impossible to get an idiot like you
into the top 100.
She has acted strangely since
she moved into a new house.
She is flirting with another man.
As he keeps acting like that,
I'm afraid that he may never learn
something precious.
-Aihara.
-Damn Irie.
I'm afraid that he may change his mind
and go out with Kotoko.
Thank you, Irie.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION