Okay, Aihara. Take this.
-Kotoko!
-Yes.
I can see it.
You did it.
Did you twist your ankle?
-Is it here?
-It hurts!
Dear Lord,
if I say I love Irie even more...
will you be mad at me?
Are we at your house yet?
That's odd.
There it is. That's it. My new house.
Yes?
Who are you? I live here.
-This is my house.
-No kidding.
No matter what you say,
this is my residence.
What's happening?
I'm sorry, Irie.
If I leave you alone with your foot
like that, my mom will get mad at me.
Until you can reach your dad, wait inside.
I wonder where my dad went.
Brother, bad news.
My room is once again...
This girl. It's her fault.
You're home, Naoki and Kotoko.
I thought you were together.
The house that I was moving into
was occupied by somebody else.
I contacted my dad
but couldn't get through.
Your dad is at the real-estate agency now.
What happened?
What I heard was that there was a mistake
in the contract
and the new house was taken by
someone else a day earlier than your dad.
I'm terribly sorry.
The group company seems
to have made another contract earlier.
You're kidding.
Furniture and big items
were supposed to be moved from here
to the new house, right?
That didn't work out either.
He's been calling the mover
and the Realtor since morning
and has been busy all day.
That's why you couldn't get through.
Does that mean that my dad and I
lost our place to live again?
What can I do?
You can just come back to our house.
Mr. Aihara and you can live in our house.
We'll become a family anyway.
Are you still saying such stupid things?
What are you talking about?
You kissed, didn't you?
-I never told her. It wasn't me.
-You're kidding.
It's not true, is it, brother?
I can't believe
that you two never acted like that.
You tricked your parents. You rascals.
How did you find out?
The one who controls information
will control the world.
Yes... yes.
That's right.
That's the deal, then.
Please take good care of it.
I'm so happy that you're back.
-How do you like coming back here?
-You don't understand.
The relationship between Irie and me
is not what you think.
As soon as we find a new house,
we'll move out of here.
I don't know if you can find a new house.
What?
Anyway, I've decided again
to have you marry into our family.
Because Naoki and you have
a good enough relationship to kiss.
That's not true. It was just an accident.
We've never...
held hands.
Not only that...
we've never had a date.
Don't be so weak-spirited.
If you haven't done it...
you can just do it from now.
If you can kiss by accident,
you can go on a date just by some chance.
That's impossible.
Kotoko, go on a date with Naoki.
That's your mission, okay?
Good luck.
I happen to be under orders
to have a first date with Irie.
Of course, if possible...
I want to go on a date with Irie.
But...
he has zero intention of doing it.
What can I do?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
UNEXPECTED FIRST DATE
You're living together again?
For some reason,
Mrs. Irie knew that we kissed.
Did you guys tell her?
Well, that was just an accident.
-Accident?
-Did you say "kiss"?
Kotoko, did you kiss Irie?
Kotoko, weren't you going to give up
on Irie?
Sorry, Kin-chan.
It was too much stress for Kin-chan.
But maybe it's better this way.
Satomi?
Because you're not giving up
on Irie at all.
You already know, don't you?
Even if there's a rival or any obstacles,
your feelings towards Irie won't change.
If that's the case,
Kin-chan should give up on you
and move forward.
But I haven't
gotten Irie's attention either.
Speak of the devil...
Irie, why don't we go to a movie
this Sunday?
I have two tickets.
What? Yuko Matsumoto is also aiming
to have a first date with Irie?
Oh, no. I don't feel like I can win.
-What are you doing, Mr. Sudo?
-Why are you here, Aihara?
You were watching Irie, weren't you?
Are you watching Ms. Matsumoto,
as well?
Maybe Ms. Matsumoto is who you admire.
-Aihara.
-No!
What are you doing in broad daylight?
This is not what you think.
This is... well...
-The rumor I heard was true.
-The rumor?
The rumor that you and Mr. Sudo
have something going on.
Don't make up stories.
Because you told people
that you'd give up on Irie.
That's because of Mr. Sudo, right?
-It's a big rumor in the club.
-What?
-Is that right?
-No, that's not true.
Irie, there's a misunderstanding.
-It's not that.
-It's none of my business.
Oh, Matsumoto.
In answer to your invitation...
I'm free on Sunday,
so, I can go to a movie.
Really? Thank you.
It's your fault.
You put your weight on me all of a sudden.
I forgot that you injured your ankle.
I'm very sorry.
I didn't know that our relationship
was a big piece of gossip
in the Tennis Club.
There's no way that's happening.
It's just Ms. Matsumoto's made-up story.
So that she can give Irie
a good impression of her.
Matsumoto is not the kind of girl
who tells a stupid lie like that.
You really like Matsumoto, don't you?
Aihara, I want to discuss something
with you.
Well, say...
you like Irie and I like Matsumoto.
Matsumoto likes Irie. Isn't that bad?
Nobody can be happy, right?
So, I suggest that we come up
with an agreement
and cooperate with each other.
How about that?
-Cooperate. How?
-For example...
What?
-Really?
-Tail Irie during his date?
What will you do if Kin-chan hears us?
Good. Kin-chan seems to be off today.
What's wrong, Kotoko?
Tissue, tissue. Good.
-Okay. It's done.
-What would you do tailing him?
I don't know, but...
I don't know what to do
if anything happens with those two.
Thinking of that makes me worry so much.
-You're so pitiful.
-I can't help it.
You just got robbed of your first date
by Yuko Matsumoto.
On top of all that,
you're going to tail him?
That's just like Mr. Sudo and you
are going out on a date.
Don't you hear a weird noise?
Jinko, we're talking
about important stuff.
Zip your mouth.
-Do you want this apple tea?
-Orange juice.
Mr. Sudo and Kotoko are going on a date?
What's happening?
Are you sure
that's what you're going to do?
I can't do anything about it.
That's what love is.
Did Kotoko fall for a new guy?
That mustache dude?
-The date is... a movie.
-Ginza.
-Oh, Karasumori?
-Shinbashi.
Ginza, Karasumori.
-I don't care about the place.
The movie date... Roman...
Date, movie.
Ginza, Karasumori.
Shinbashi.
Roman?
"Date, movie, Ginza.
Karasumori, Shinbashi, Roman."
I don't get it at all! I'm going crazy.
-Kinnosuke, what are you doing?
-I'm sorry, bro.
What's that?
-I don't get it.
-Is this some kind of code?
"Date, movie, Ginza, Karasumori.
-Shinbashi, Roman."
-It drives you crazy, doesn't it?
I see.
-Did you figure it out?
-Are you going on a date?
-No.
-That's what I thought.
There's no way you could go out
on such a sexy grown-up date.
What? What? What?
Sexy?
Sorry, Kotoko.
I went to many different Realtors,
but even when I found a good one,
somebody else won the contract by a hair.
-I see.
-I'm so unlucky.
Anyway, we won't be able
to find a new house anytime soon.
So, we'll have to live
with the Irie family for a while.
It's not something
that you have to apologize to me for.
But...
we made a big decision
to move out of the Iries' home.
I'm wondering
if you were having a hard time.
In answer to your invitation,
I'm free on Sunday,
so, I can go to a movie.
Really? Thank you.
-I thought so.
-No, Dad.
Listen.
I still like Irie.
-But Naoki's feelings are...
-That has nothing to do with it.
It might be impossible for Irie
to fall for me, but...
I don't want to give up until the end.
You always tell me that it's not good
to quit in the middle of something.
I realized after I left the Iries' home...
something that I don't want to give up
is this feeling.
So, don't worry about me anymore, Dad.
Even if I get my heart broken,
it's better than doing nothing
and regretting it.
-You're so similar.
-To my mom?
No, to me.
You are definitely my daughter.
SUNDAY
This isn't it.
The flower print isn't it either.
White looks cute, too.
I pick...
this one.
Even if I put makeup on...
the person who's going on a date
with Irie is not me...
but Matsumoto.
I wanted to go on a date with Irie too.
Get dressed up and put makeup on.
We'd watch a movie and go shopping.
Eat dinner at a fancy little restaurant.
All right.
That's her.
-Nice body.
-Mr. Sudo, when did you get here?
-Is Irie a quick worker?
-What?
Well, not so much.
He's rather slow.
That's because of you.
Matsumoto's sexiness will tempt Irie.
Oh, Irie.
Irie.
-Did I make you wait?
-No, I came early.
-You look good in that dress.
-Really?
-I'm glad.
-That guy is being so affected.
-Shall we go?
-Yes.
Sexy... sexy...
Hey, Kinnosuke, this way.
Kotoko!
I'd like to have seats right behind them.
Hurry, hurry.
Ta-da! See? Isn't it perfect?
Movie, Shinbashi, Roman.
A minute's walk from the Karasumori exit.
How about Ginza?
You don't know that?
When they feel naughty after the movie...
they retire to a fancy little hotel
in Ginza.
That mustache guy, what is he thinking?
Showing something like this to Kotoko
and... doing something naughty?
-Hey.
-I'm sorry.
What are you doing? This way.
What's this?
Oh, my. I... dropped a pamphlet.
Grandma, pull yourself together.
You're right. Grandpa.
-Me, too.
-What are you doing?
You got ketchup on your face.
Oh, my back.
Hey, Kinnosuke, let's wait inside.
I gave up on a kiss...
but I'm never going to give up
against other guys!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Sit down. I can't see anything.
-It was a good movie.
-Do you want to have some tea?
Let's!
I've been interested in you
since I was in junior high.
I heard that there was
a prodigy tennis player in Tonan.
On top of that, you're handsome
and have good grades.
Your dad is CEO of a company
and a Tokyo University alumnus, right?
I thought you'd apply for another college.
But when I heard that you were going
to Tonan...
I was happy.
I felt it was destiny.
Is that right?
Tell me, what type of girls do you like?
My type?
Let's see.
Beautiful and... glamorous.
I want a smart girl.
And... being a good cook is a must.
Aihara.
There's something good about you.
It's okay. You don't have to cheer me up.
I see. What do you think?
Don't we make a good couple?
Probably.
We still have time before dinner.
-Will you go shopping with me?
-Sure.
Which one do you like?
This one. You'll wear it well.
Do you think so?
Excuse me, may I try this on?
Yes. Thank you. This way, please.
How come Irie is looking
at women's accessories?
Is he going to give it to Matsumoto?
No way.
I've never gotten anything from him
even though I've been living with him.
Irie, can you zip up the back?
Thank you. How do I look?
Mr. Sudo.
Hold on.
-What is he going to do?
-I'm scared.
No, don't. Don't touch her.
No!
How about this?
Nice, Irie.
You have good taste.
It goes with this dress.
Because the model is good.
I'm happy to hear that
even if it's flattery.
I feel dizzy with that different world.
Don't you think
that they were made for each other?
What are you doing, approving of them?
-I'll hold it.
-Thank you.
Okay, let's go.
I want shoes, too.
-I have a pair that I wanted.
-Watch out.
Are you okay?
-Thank you.
-It's good that you didn't get hurt.
Mr. Sudo, I'm going home now.
-What are you talking about?
-I can't bear to watch them anymore.
We're here to prevent the situation
that's unbearable to watch.
But there's nothing we can do
if they like each other.
It's too miserable.
-I'm sorry, Mr. Sudo. I'm leaving.
-Okay.
Get home safely.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do with this?
-I'll pay for the cleaning.
-That's not enough!
This shirt is expensive. It's 100,000 yen!
100,000 yen?
-What can I do?
-I'll take care of it.
-Here's 1020...
-Hey, lady.
You have a pretty face.
Why don't you come over to my office
and discuss this and that? Let's go.
Please, stop it.
I'm being punished
because I was interrupting someone's date.
-Let's go now.
-1500 yen should be enough.
Why are you here?
Hey, little fella, what did you just say?
The cleaning fee
for the cheap shirt should be covered
by 1500 yen.
Don't be so arrogant.
He's so cool, isn't he?
Excuse me. Mr. Sudo.
You got it now.
You've been tailing us for the whole day.
Show her your strength
and get Matsumoto to fall for you.
-Irie.
-Sorry, I've got to go now.
-Wait!
-That's what I want to say!
Take this!
I'm...
running away with Irie.
It's like a dream.
I wish...
time would stop right now.
We'll be okay now.
Irie, did you notice that...
we were tailing you?
I noticed your crappy tailing
when I got to the meeting place.
Then you knew
that Mr. Sudo liked Matsumoto?
I thought you and Sudo were a couple
until yesterday.
But I knew when you two followed us.
It was so funny to see your reaction.
I'm sorry.
When I heard you were going on a date
with Ms. Matsumoto...
I couldn't contain myself.
But if you like Ms. Matsumoto...
-I got in your way so bad.
-Shall we go somewhere?
Okay.
Then I'll go home.
I'll go!
-Yes, yes, yes. I'm coming.
-Just say it once.
I'm sorry.
Where shall we go?
Then a movie theater.
We've been there, so...
let's go shopping and after that
we'll go to a nice restaurant.
-We'll eat dinner, then...
-In that outfit?
You're right.
You'll be embarrassed with me like this.
Come on.
It's so beautiful. Look, Irie.
Isn't it beautiful?
Irie?
Irie? Where are you?
Irie.
Is he making fun of me again?
We can't go to the restaurant like that.
Here's dinner.
It's delicious.
Anything tastes good when you're hungry.
No tasty French, Italian or Chinese...
could win against this hamburger.
I'd never experienced anything hard
until a while ago.
But since my last year of high school...
after I got a love letter from you...
almost every day has been a series
of hardships and frustrations.
I think you're the trial that I was given.
Trial?
I... got confused by the first trial
that I was given.
I was trying to get away from it.
You're telling me that I'm a pest
or something.
But...
compared to a life without any hardship,
it's more interesting
to face these trials.
Thank you.
If you don't understand, it's okay.
I can understand that.
Don't make a fool of me.
You mean you wanted to get away from me,
but you changed your mind.
Do you want to marry me?
-Is this a proposal?
-Idiot. How can you think that?
I'm saying that...
I don't mind being in the same house
as you.
That means...
you don't...
hate me?
You're hard to deal with,
but I don't hate you.
Now not just your clothes
but your face will be a disaster.
I can't help it.
It was a good one.
Three movies in a row is something else.
Oh, Kinnosuke, are you still here?
Kotoko, where are you?
Kinnosuke?
It's bad.
After an unexpected turn of events,
I won my first date with Irie.
It was completely different
from what I had dreamed of, but...
more than our first kiss...
or the first time he held me...
I felt Irie...
was even closer to me.
No, I'm against that.
Just when Kotoko finally came back,
you're moving out?
Well, boys need that kind of experience.
If Naoki wants to do it...
it may not be a bad idea
for him to live by himself.
Why don't you try it?
Thank you.
Irie is moving out of here
and living by himself?
He just told me
that he didn't mind living with me.
Why?
What does this mean?
I wonder if he doesn't like me.
Since he moved out as
soon as we're back.
I found out. Why don't we go spy
on him where he works?
I'll work here. That way I can be
close to Irie.
-Thank you for waiting.
-Yeah.
Ms. Matsumoto, how do you know
that Irie works here?
-He told me.
-I'll stay with you right here.
The distance between Irie and me
will get farther and farther.
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION