Irie moved out?
Let's go spy on him
at his work.
What?
They live together?
Fainting with this degree
maybe because of her
mental shock.
Naoki comes
to my house.
I know.
They live together, right?
He's tutoring me at my house.
Tutoring?
I moved out to be
all by myself,
but why even bother living
with someone?
Alrighty!
The suspicion of living with
Matsumoto has been cleared,
but Irie still lives by himself.
The days have passed,
and the first winter
after we entered college
was about to begin.
Eating this will make
everyone smile.
Meanwhile...
Mr. Irie and dad's
classmate is
getting remarried in
their hometown in Kyusyu.
Mrs. Irie is also
attending the wedding.
Now they're going on
an overnight trip.
-Okay.
-I'm ready.
We'll be back tomorrow night.
Kotoko, Yuki, take care
of the house until then.
Yes. Mrs. Irie, I made sandwiches
for you.
Thank you, Kotoko.
Kotoko, don't feed anything
weird to Yuki.
I'm becoming a better cook
than I used to be.
Are you sure you're okay
by yourselves?
Shall I bring Naoki back here?
We'll be okay. It's only one night.
Irie must be busy for himself.
But...
You should let your hair down
once in a while.
Then we're counting on you.
Call us if anything happens.
Okay, we're going now.
-See you later.
-Have a nice trip.
Okay, let's go.
All right.
Yuki, what would you like
for dinner tonight?
Anything.
There. I made your favorite...
hamburger.
Hamburgers are hard
to make them into a right shape.
I made them into the size that's
easy to eat.
Please, eat them.
How is it?
I got the recipe from Kin-chan.
I think I did a good job.
It's better than it looks.
I'm glad.
Eat all the vegetables
on the plate.
There are more soup and rice.
Eat a lot, Yuki.
I'm going to eat now.
Actually, this is Japanese style.
have you noticed it?
It's Japanese style.
Kin-chan taught me how.
What's wrong, Yuki?
Yuki?
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
-Does it hurt? What's wrong?
-It hurts.
-It hurts?
-My stomach.
Stomach?
My stomach hurts.
Is that because of my hamburger?
Are you okay, Yuki?
Yuki, are you okay?
Hang in there, Yuki.
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
There.
So that you don't get cold.
CONFESSION ON A SNOWY NIGHT
Sorry.
His temperature is high.
Towel, towel.
Here.
Wait.
I'll cool you down. Hold on.
Here you go.
Next,
I'll call Mrs. Irie.
MRS. IRIE
I have to.
It's connected to
an answering machine.
That's right.
They're at the wedding party
after the reception.
Irie, Irie, Irie.
That's right.
He doesn't have a cell phone.
I don't know his home phone number.
What can I do?
Wait.
Yuki, wait.
Okay, okay.
This is Japanese restaurant,
Aihara.
Kin-chan, how do you cure
food poisoning?
Kotoko? Is this Kotoko?
What's wrong? Food.
Did you get food poisoning?
Not me, Yuki.
Mrs. Irie is on a trip.
Irie
doesn't have a cell phone so
I can't contact him.
Where's Irie's house?
I don't know.
He doesn't tell anybody.
What's wrong?
Bro, It sounds like Irie's brother
got food poisoning.
How do you cure food poisoning?
Give it to me.
Kotoko, what did he eat?
The hamburger that I made.
It may have not been fully cooked.
It wasn't fully cooked?
Calm down, calm down.
You ate that hamburger, too, right?
-Yes, I did.
-She ate it.
But you're okay, right?
Yes. You may be right.
Then the hamburger
is not the cause.
But after Yuki ate hamburger,
-he started having stomachache.
-Food poisoning is not the only one.
Other sickness like appendicitis
can be considered.
Don't make a judgment yourself,
it's better to see a doctor.
-Call an ambulance right now.
-Ambulance, okay.
I'll find Irie and take him there.
Yes. Please do.
Call me once you know the hospital.
Okay, Kotoko?
Thank you, Kin-chan.
-Bro, can I take off now?
-Yeah, don't worry.
-I'll take care of it.
-Thank you so much.
Excuse me, an ambulance, please.
Yes. Naoki Irie.
No, I was wrong.
Kotoko Aihara. Kotoko Aihara. Right.
Yes. Kotoko.
No, Yuki Irie.
Yuki Irie. Yes. Yuki Irie.
Kin-chan, what happened?
Is Kotoko okay?
They're heading to Takao Hospital.
Anyway, don't you know
where Irie is?
I don't think Irie told his new
address to even his parents.
Engineer guys didn't know it either.
I don't think there's anybody else
who knows about it.
What's that?
Doesn't the Student Affairs office
know it?
Student Affairs office isn't open
at this time of the day.
I know. He is tutoring
at Matsumoto's house
who's in Tennis Club.
Matsumoto may know something.
Also he works at a cafe.
Kotoko told us.
-Which cafe is it?
-Well...
Kotoko knows it, right?
Yuki, hang in there.
Hang in there.
Hang in there, Yuki.
No, she's not answering.
Maybe it's hard to get through
at a hospital.
Don't you know where
the cafe is?
I think she said it was in
Daikanyama.
I see. I'll go around cafes.
Can you do it by yourself?
Daikanyama is small enough.
You guys contact Matsumoto.
Roger.
-Careful on your steps.
-Yes. Hurry, hurry.
You go that way. I go this way.
Irie is coming soon.
You'll be okay.
Brother.
You're okay. Don't worry.
I'll take Irie no matter what.
Wait for me, Kotoko.
Excuse me.
Yes.
It's a hair salon Matsuya.
Sorry.
Irie is not here today.
Then do you know Irie's address?
Well...
I don't have it.
Okay...
you don't know it.
Then tell us the cafe's name.
The cafe where Irie works.
Royal Garden Cafe on 2-chome.
The manager might know Irie's
emergency contact number.
Thank you so much.
It's in 2-chome.
-Royal...
-Royal Garden Cafe.
Royal Garden Cafe. Okay.
How is it? Did you find Irie?
He wasn't at Matsumoto's.
She doesn't know
where Irie lives.
The name of the cafe is
Royal Garden Cafe.
She doesn't know
if he is working there tonight.
His shift is random.
I'll go to the cafe for now.
They might know
Irie's contact number.
Got it. Is there anything else
that we can do?
No, that's enough. It was
a big help. Thank you.
Say hi to Kotoko.
Tell Kotoko to hang in there.
Got it.
It's probably Intussusception.
Intuss. what is it?
It's a kind of
intestinal obstruction.
It's not like he's in critical
condition right now,
but if you leave it alone
it can be fatal.
Fatal?
No way.
It's better to operate on him
as soon as possible.
Then please...
operate right now.
Please save Yuki.
May I ask if you're his family?
-No.
-At this hospital,
we need consent
from a family member
to operate on a minor.
Well, but now...
his parents are on vacation.
Can you contact
other family members?
We need a consent form in case
anything happens.
What am I going to do?
Irie.
Brother.
Where is it?
ROYAL GARDEN CAFE
Here it is. Naoki Irie is here.
Naoki Irie.
What are you yelling about?
You come with me.
Your brother is sick.
He's at Takao Hospital with Kotoko.
-Sorry, I got to go.
-Okay.
Sorry. Sorry.
Taxi!
Hi, Takao Hospital, please.
Irie.
Come soon.
Excuse me, where's Yuki Irie?
Irie. Good.
Yuki needs an operation.
He needs a consent from family.
I've signed the consent.
Everything will be okay.
You'll be okay.
Sorry to have you wait.
Am I going to die?
No, you don't. It's an easy
operation. It'll be done soon.
Hang in there.
We're ready now. We'll take him
to the operation room.
OPERATION ROOM
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
Family members can wait here
until the operation is over.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Kotoko must be relieved.
I'm going now.
Chef is not here today
and Mr. Odawara is all by himself.
He must be busy.
Thank you so much.
Please send my best regards
to Mr. Odawara.
Yeah.
I'm relieved
that It didn't get serious.
See you.
Ikezawa.
Thank you.
Aren't you being too selfish?
I don't care if you live
by yourself,
but give your family
your contact number.
What if anything happens to Yuki
because of that?
I, too, left Osaka
to come to Tokyo by myself.
For you wanting to be
by yourself...
must have a good reason.
But if anything happens
because of that,
you and the people around you
will suffer.
It's too late if it happens.
People can't live alone.
Your feelings and
what you think
should be told to the people
around you.
Kotoko, see you later.
Thank you again.
Irie.
Now I remember.
I forgot to call Mrs. Irie.
Oh, no.
I got lots of missed calls.
It's inside the hospital here.
Right.
TAKAO HOSPITAL
I finally got through. Kotoko!
Mrs. Irie, listen.
Yuki had to have
an emergency operation.
-Operation?
-It's a kind of
intestinal obstruction.
He was able to get operated
as soon as he had symptoms
so it won't get serious.
The operation will be over soon.
Irie came here
and he's staying with Yuki.
Anyhow,
we'll be back soon.
Coming back soon?
You're in Kyushu, though.
There's no more airplanes
nor bullet trains today.
Tokyo, please.
Where are you now?
Don't worry about us.
No matter what,
we'll get back to Tokyo
for sure.
Tokyo please.
-Until I come home, take care
-Okay. You, too.
-of Yuki.
-Come home safely.
-Yes.
-Koto--
Hello. Hello...?
Thank you, Kotoko.
I was scared.
Irie, I was scared.
You're okay now.
I was scared, Irie.
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
The operation was successful.
He can move to the general ward
tomorrow.
Family members
should go home tonight.
However...
No one can stay at ICU.
There's no facility for you
to stay overnight.
You can come back
tomorrow morning.
I see.
Thank you so much, doctor.
Anyway, that lady made
a quick decision
to take him to the hospital.
That was great.
It doesn't get serious
when it's found early,
but many people think it's just a
stomachache and have them endure it.
It's a curable disease,
but sometimes it can be fatal.
Especially for young children.
Your brother was lucky.
You should thank that lady.
How was it?
He's okay now.
He can move to the general
ward tomorrow.
I'll stay with Yuki then.
You can't do it.
-But...
-Let's leave it to professionals.
Yuki will be hospitalized
from tomorrow and on.
You should rest for a while.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
TAKAO HOSPITAL
Oh, wow. It's snowing.
It was very cold tonight.
The trains are not running now.
It may be hard to catch a taxi.
What can I do?
You're right. No cars are running.
-Do you want to come to my condo?
-What?
It's about a ten-minute walk
from here.
How about an umbrella?
Umbrella. Umbrella?
Come in.
Excuse me.
Don't look around.
This is the room that Irie lives.
Right now, I'm in Irie's room
all by ourselves.
In this room.
Did Matsumoto come here?
No.
You're the first one.
You must've been cold.
Do you want to take a shower?
You go ahead.
I can go later.
Well, this is your place.
I have to tell Mrs. Irie
that the operation was successful.
I have to tell her that I can't
stay with Yuki tonight
or they'll go
directly to the hospital.
So you go ahead.
He's taking a shower
and the night with just two of us
is about to begin.
There was one time like that
at the Irie residence,
but it's different this time.
Because this room has...
...only one bed.
What am I thinking in this crisis?
I'm done.
Change of clothes.
These are mine, but...
Thank you.
Then...
I'm taking a shower now.
See you.
Irie's shampoo.
The soap that Irie used.
Yes, yes.
The towels are right there.
Yes.
Irie's towel.
Thank you for the shower.
Sure.
I'm going to bed now.
Right. I'll sleep around here.
You use your bed.
-Of course I will.
-What?
Usually you say to a girl
"What are you talking about?
I'll sleep here.
You use my bed."
or something like that.
I'm just kidding.
You can use my bed.
Well, but, that
makes me feel guilty.
You started saying that.
What do you want?
Just go to bed.
Well, but...
Good night.
Yes.
I'm turning the lights off.
Ye-- yes.
Hey.
What?
Can you turn a small light on?
I can't sleep unless it's
completely dark.
But I can't go to the bathroom
like this.
Seriously?
Is this good?
Sorry. Thank you.
Good night, then.
Hey.
What now?
Irie, aren't you cold?
Of course I'm cold.
I'll go on the floor.
This is your place.
It's okay. Just go to bed.
But I feel guilty.
I don't want you to be cold.
Got it.
Wil you be satisfied if I go there?
I'll go on the floor.
It's okay. You'll be quiet
when I do this.
Good night.
What am I hoping for
when Yuki is in
a serious condition?
Of course.
Good night.
But he's in the same bed
with a girl,
but he doesn't do anything.
I wonder if I just don't have
enough appeal
as a woman.
That's right. That makes sense.
Are you disappointed?
Since I don't do anything to you...
you're disappointed, aren't you?
I'm not disappointed.
I...
don't want to do as
the way my mom wants.
If my mom comes to know that
you stayed here tonight,
and if anything happens to us,
then...
I'll play into her hands.
Then, for the rest of my life,
I'll be her puppet.
Kotoko-chan, you stayed at
Naoki's place? Wow!
I kind of understand.
That's why I didn't
tell my family this address.
Is that right?
My mom is like that, right?
If I give her my address,
she'd make a spare key
and come here every day.
She'll cook three meals
and leave them for me.
That'll ruin the whole point
of living by myself.
The point of living by yourself?
I stay home forever,
graduate college,
then take over my dad's business.
I wondered if it would be
really okay being just like that.
That's just living on the rails
that my parents laid.
If it's what I really want to do,
it will be okay, but...
I still don't know yet.
So, to find what I really wanted,
I wanted to live on my own.
I remember.
You were saying that
in Odaiba.
Compared to the life without
any hardship,
it's more fun to face the
challenge. You realized it.
Right.
Then,
the reason you started living by yourself
is not because you wanted
to avoid me.
Why do I have to
go through hard time
just for that?
Living by myself is not that easy.
Up until now at home...
how spoiled I was!
I was forced to realize that.
I see.
But...
because of that,
things like this happened.
I've been
caused troubles by you,
but I was the one
who caused trouble to you today.
That's...
I...
can only do things like that.
Since you're a genius,
you can do anything, but...
I thought about it
at the hospital today.
Human life
is dependent upon a moment's
decision.
The little thing leads
easily curable to incurable.
Just like that,
human life is so fragile.
Even if it's curable,
sometimes it becomes fatal.
Especially for young children.
In this case also, if she would've
waited until morning...
I was scared, too.
Until now,
I thought that life was
decided by God...
and humans could do
nothing about it.
If it's you, you can make
things happen.
Developing new medicines
and becoming a doctor
and cure diseases like magic.
You have
lots of possibilities.
In order to find your possibility,
you started
living by yourself, right?
No matter how many possibilities
I have,
if I don't know what I want to do,
it's meaningless.
It's been easy no matter what I did.
In other words, I was bored.
Once I got to be busy,
the important thing for me
and my interests became visible.
Little by little,
I started to realize
what they are.
You are always
like this when it's time for
something important.
I'll go to Yuki's hospital.
Have some coffee if you like.
P.S. We talked a lot last night,
didn't we?
Thank you.
Kotoko.
We're home now.
Is she asleep?
She must be tired,
so don't wake her up.
Then I'll pack up things
to bring
to the hospital for Yuki.
Honey, honey, come.
Come with me.
What?
Honey, over here.
See? These.
See? Over here too.
It looks like it's just
as they left.
Kotoko is not in her room.
She may have not come back here.
Where's Kotoko then?
But...
she said she was okay
on the phone.
She could have been
at Naoki's house.
-No way.
It's possible.
Since they were in
an extreme condition,
they finally
realized their feelings towards
each other. Wow!
Your brother is doing well.
Is that right?
She came first in the morning
and did this and that.
He seemed to be relieved.
Oh, my.
They got tired.
Let's not wake them up.
Isn't your girlfriend cute?
I was once like her.
Take your time.
Thank you.
GET WELL SOON
Irie.
Yuki is asleep, isn't he?
It feels like it was a dream
that he was suffering last night.
The doctor said that he'd be
able to be discharged soon.
Okay.
Can you come with me?
It feels good.
Hey...
You say
you like me and all that,
but do you know
how I feel?
Your feelings are
that you don't care about me
at all and...
Silly.
You're wrong.
The second time.
Oh, well.
It was a dream.
Oh, sorry. Did I wake you up?
What's wrong, Yuki?
Your face is red.
Do you have fever again?
I'm okay. Don't bother me.
-Sorry.
-Anyway,
that one.
What's this?
My brother brought it
while you're asleep.
Really?
He should have woke me up.
He left soon to go to college.
Okay.
Wow, it's beautiful.
I'll put these in a vase.
It was not a dream, I guess.
Bro.
Here they are.
Look at these flowers.
They're so beautiful.
That's just like Irie.
He has good taste.
It smells good.
Oh, I know.
I bought underwear for you.
Antibacterial and deodorant.
It comes with a label that you can
write your name on.
Do you write your name
on your underwear?
Well, I'm going to the party, too.
-I love Christmas.
-On Christmas Eve
we'll have a party.
I heard that you couldn't go.
You spend Christmas
with your girlfriends, right?
-Boyfriend.
-When did you both...
Kotoko is being left over.
I'm fine if I can't spend time
with Irie.
I heard that there were
thieves around here.
-It's serious!
-You bastard, bastard, bastard!
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION