What is your future plan? We'll be looking
for a job this time next year.
I must get started.
Everyone has a future plan.
But I don't know what I want to do.
I want my son to take over my company.
Is that too much to ask?
If Naoki doesn't want it,
you still have Yuki.
Yuki? It will be too late.
We need to talk.
I want you to take over my company.
Give me a break.
I can't choose my profession?
I can't even choose my girlfriend.
That's why I want to leave this home.
I want freedom.
Mr. Irie!
I want to be a doctor.
That's the first profession...
I got interested in.
Don't tell it to anyone yet.
I wonder why
he confided his secret to me.
I didn't have a chance to tell it
to Naoki, but...
to tell you the truth--
Honey.
Honey, are you okay? Naoki! Naoki!
It is unstable angina.
I informed him of it
after the annual medical exam.
-He didn't tell us anything.
-Really?
I guess he didn't want to upset you
by sharing the news.
How is his condition?
This attack was a light one.
But he may suffer cardiac infarct
if he doesn't rest.
-That serious?
-I don't want it to happen.
Let's see how the medication will affect
his condition.
No more work for him.
-Mrs. Irie, how is he doing?
-My husband
has had a heart issue for a long time.
But he didn't tell me anything.
I guess he pushed himself
too much for us.
I'm sorry to hear that.
He will have absolute rest for a while and
let's see how his condition improves.
So, he is all right as long as he has
absolute rest. Right?
He is all right for now.
I didn't realize that he had been
suffering it.
I'm a bad wife.
It's not your fault.
Irie-chan has a strong sense
of responsibility.
He may have shouldered too much
burden and gotten stressed by that.
At least, it's not life-threatening.
You should feel lucky for that.
But what will happen to his company
if he cannot work?
I will take it over.
But you said that
you didn't want to take it over.
Dad knew his heart condition.
That's why he asked me to take it over.
So, don't worry. I will take care of
his company.
Thank you, son.
I'm the only one who knows
what Irie's real dream is.
Irie wants to become a doctor.
He finally figured out what he wanted to
do in his life.
But does he have to give it up?
No other choice?
MISCHIEVOUS KISS
QUIRK OF FATE
Will Irie take over his dad's company?
Irie applied to take leave of absence from
the university.
Until Mr. Irie gets better,
Naoki will devote his time to the company.
I see. He is having a hard time, huh?
But I'm sure Irie can handle it.
-He is a genius.
-That's right.
And I'm sure that he has been aware of
his dad's expectation
for him to take over the company some
day.
And how is Mr. Irie doing?
Kotoko? Kotoko?
Mr. Irie? He will stay in the hospital
to have absolute rest for a while.
And Naoki will come back home
to live with us.
-I guess Mr. Irie will be relieved.
-I see.
Wait. This might be a good opportunity
for Irie and Kotoko to get closer.
If you are sick or hospitalized,
you tend to let your guard down, so, you
have a higher chance to fall in love.
But Irie is not the one who is in
the hospital. It's his dad.
I know that, but I'm sure Irie
is also uneasy.
If Irie feels helpless,
I will do anything to help him.
-Anything.
-Good, Kotoko.
But I don't mean to do that in order to
attract his attention.
Think about it. His dad is sick
and the company is in trouble.
I'm happy that Irie is coming back to live
with us again.
But I would be happier
if his dad gets better
and Irie comes back to the university...
to study again...
even if we must live apart.
Come on. You can be honest with us.
Kotoko, I admire what you said.
-That's why I like you.
-Kin-chan.
"Admire what you said"?
You just don't want to see Kotoko and Irie
become a couple.
You idiot.
It's not time for such a thing.
Irie Family is in turmoil.
Irie won't show it, but I'm sure
that he is helpless and uneasy.
Kotoko, do anything to help him.
You are right.
Let us know if we can help him
in any way.
Do not hesitate. Just ask us.
Thank you, Kin-chan.
It's time. I have to go.
-See you later.
-See you.
Hey, Kin-chan. What was that?
"What was that"? What do you mean?
Don't tell me that you've given up
on Kotoko.
-You are ready to surrender?
-Idiot.
I won't stoop low.
I want to show humanity
even to my enemy.
If I take advantage of the turmoil
in the Irie Family
and steal Kotoko away from Irie...
I won't be able to live with myself.
It's funny. You sound like Kotoko.
Don't you think?
What you are saying
is the same as what Kotoko said.
Happiness of your love interest is more
important than your own happiness.
Yes. You are like Kotoko.
You and Kotoko could make...
a perfect couple. Too bad.
Too bad.
Just kidding.
-Kotoko loves only Irie.
-What?
That's right.
Enjoy the meal. Tonight we have
simmered taro,
yellowtail teriyaki, miso soup,
beans with sesame paste,
and what else? Boiled tofu.
-Spicy. It's too spicy.
-Too spicy?
That's not possible. Why?
-Wow, it's spicy.
- Brother.
Don't eat it. It's too spicy.
It's spicy... spicy.
Brother, what was that sound?
It's taro.
Simmered taro is usually soft
and wouldn't make such a sound.
It means... it's not cooked enough.
-Brother, spit it out.
-You don't need to eat it.
Yuki, stop complaining and
finish the meal.
Hi, Irie.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Please.
Irie...
will you take over your dad's company?
You told me that you wanted
to be a doctor.
I don't want to run away
from the challenge.
I told you.
I've faced so many challenges one after
another since I met you.
But I didn't expect my father to get sick.
I won't run away from the challenge.
-Irie...
-Once he gets better,
I will go back to the university.
It won't be too late for me
to do what I really want.
It would be nice to experience
the real world now.
I see.
Let me know if there is anything
I can do.
Right. I was making coffee.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kanamori.
I will assist you
while the president is in the hospital.
This is your chair.
Now let me brief you on the documents
you received the other day.
No, thanks. I read all of them last night.
All of them by yourself?
It looks like that this year's profit is
down significantly from last year.
Yes. Please take a look at the inventory
of our company's signature product.
The sales are drastically down.
We've lost our customers to our rivals'
similar products.
The president has been really concerned
about it.
Pandai may end up being taken over by a
bigger company if it doesn't improve.
We need a huge amount of extra cash
to survive right now.
I can't blame his heart for failing.
Good.
Irie is working so hard.
I should follow his lead.
I will work hard on domestic chores.
Yes, I'm ready.
I look like...
a newly-wed wife.
Fight... well...
H comes before G? Or vice versa?
Who cares?
A heart mark. A heart mark.
Love. Love. Heart.
G should come before H.
Welcome home.
You want to take a bath or dinner first?
I'll take that.
Inhale.
Now exhale.
Wait. Irie.
Here is your bag.
Have a great day.
Do your best.
From every product,
we seek cash revenue.
By producing animation, I will get the TV
right and others...
We will expand our unique business
model into the global market.
Too much miso makes the soup salty.
You know that?
You are right. It's too salty.
But taro is cooked perfectly today.
I regret to inform you, but I can't
continue the club activity.
I see.
-Isn't Irie's father doing well?
-That's right.
That's why I don't have time for the club.
I understand.
Irie and you are important members
of our club.
We want you to come back once his
father gets well. The door is always open.
Thank you, Mr. Sudo.
You are not the only one.
We all care about Irie.
Some girls are in love with him.
-Like Ayako Matsumoto.
-Captain.
Sorry I'm late.
-I can't participate in today's practice.
-What?
We don't want freshmen to miss a
practice without advance notice.
That's why I'm here to tell it to you.
I have a date with my boyfriend.
Boyfriend? When did it happen?
Sorry, but I will take Ayako today.
Kotoko, I've heard about Naoki's father.
Tell him that I'm cheering for him.
Goodbye.
I thought she was totally in love
with Irie.
-How could she...?
-New generation.
-She is a new generation, huh?
-What do you mean?
-She is too young for me to understand.
-Really?
Sorry, Kotoko. Can we talk now?
And how is Irie doing?
He is very busy with the company's
business.
He comes home around midnight
every day.
I'm up every night until he comes home.
Is it possible that he will drop out of
the college completely
and take over the company permanently?
Don't go there yet. He is taking time off
from school.
-I'm sure he will come back some day.
-I doubt that.
If he takes over the company, he doesn't
need a college degree.
But...
Once he gets better,
I will go back to the university.
It won't be too late for me
to do what I really want in my life.
It would be nice to experience
the real world now.
Irie wants...
to come back to the university someday.
Even if he wants it,
the reality may not allow it.
That's all I'm saying.
By the way, why don't you relieve him
from your bento box lunch?
His lunch time is hell right now.
How do you know that I'm making
his lunch?
I know everything between you two.
I assume nothing happened
between you two.
That's not...
-That's not...
-Bye.
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
-Mommy.
-I'm so glad
to be at home. Testing, visitors,
et cetera.
Life is busy at the hospital.
Can Mr. Irie see visitors now?
His doctor wants him to have absolute
rest,
but he can't stay away from his business.
But I have good news.
My husband may be able
to come home next month.
-Really?
-I'm glad to hear that.
It depends on the result
of the next complete physical.
But right now his condition is stable
and he can go home temporarily.
I'm sure that our home is a better place
for him to relax than the hospital.
-You are right about that.
-Kotoko, I need
your help a little longer.
Don't worry about that. You should take
care of yourself.
Thank you. I will pick up a change of
clothes and go back to the hospital.
-Yuki, behave yourself. Okay?
-Okay.
I'm so glad. Once Mr. Irie comes home,
Naoki can go back to the university.
He can start studying to become a doctor,
which is his dream.
Thanks to the doctor, he can leave
the hospital next month.
That's great news.
You are lucky to have
such a brilliant son.
He is doing well as an acting president.
I can't believe that he is still
a college student.
I count on you, son.
Naoki?
That's strange.
I thought that we were the only visitors
he had today.
-I see.
-Father.
-You should be resting.
-Chairman Oizumi?
Hi. I happened to be in this area,
so I paid a visit.
Naoki, this is Mr. Oizumi of Hokuei-sha
and his secretary, Mr. Yokoyama.
I should have introduced myself first.
I'm Naoki Irie.
Irie?
Mr. Chairman, this is my son, Naoki.
He is receiving his training
in my company.
-I see. He is a promising young man.
-Mr. Chairman.
This may be a great opportunity to share
the news.
President Irie.
Regarding our investment
in your company.
Stop it, Yokoyama. It shouldn't be
discussed in a hospital room.
I'm sorry.
I thought that his son and Mr. Kanamori
should hear this news, too.
Sure. That would be fine.
-Honey, pass me the documents.
-But...
I'm sorry to ask you, but can we discuss
it some other time?
Naoki, don't be rude
to Chairman Oizumi.
I'm sorry, but Father needs
absolute rest now.
He is not healthy enough to
handle business matters.
Mr. Chairman, in that case,
I recommend you reconsider this
investment.
-Mr. Chairman.
-On behalf of my father,
I will listen to your plan.
That's not appropriate. You are too young.
Currently I'm the acting president.
I will pay you a visit
at your office tomorrow.
I would appreciate your patience.
I want Father to have complete rest.
Naoki, that's not...
Please let me handle the business while
you are in the hospital.
I planned to pay a sympathy visit to you.
That's all I wanted, but I brought you
trouble instead.
I'm going, Mr. Irie.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry for my son's attitude.
Yokoyama.
-Check my schedule tomorrow.
-Yes?
I need to know what time I'm available.
You have free time before having lunch
with the minister.
Between 11 and 12.
Does that work for you?
Thank you for your patience.
I will be there at 11.
Who could make an appointment
with Mr. Oizumi?
-Naoki is a very impressive man.
-I totally agree.
That doesn't happen often.
That's why we believe that you will earn
significant revenue from this deal.
What do you think, Yokoyama?
It was a great presentation
by a student
who learned business
only in the classroom.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I belonged to the Engineering
Department in the university.
I learned business by myself.
I see.
You are supposed to be the president
of Pandai someday, aren't you?
-Why did you major in Engineering?
-I wanted to expose myself
to broader knowledge and views.
I don't believe that someone with a narrow
view can be successful in the real world.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Take care.
Naoki, thank you for coming.
You are busy at work, aren't you?
That's okay. Just tell me what the
important thing you want to discuss is.
I don't want Yuki to hear about it.
Welcome home.
You are late as usual, huh?
I will warm up your dinner quickly.
I don't need it.
Have you already had dinner?
I have no appetite.
Good morning.
-Here is your bento box lunch.
-Thanks.
You look very tired.
Are you okay?
Irie?
I was thinking something.
See you later.
Have a good day.
Is he okay?
-Here you go.
-Wow, my mouth waters.
Your father made it for you.
He knows that you are working so hard
to feed the boys.
Thank you. This cheers me up.
Thank your father directly.
Hey, Kotoko.
You are missing some classes,
aren't you?
Are you happy with that?
It was my decision
to go to the university.
So, I still want to finish my degree.
But right now I want to help
the Irie Family.
Irie Family? No.
You mean Irie. Am I right?
I know you, so I can tell.
Sometimes I wish that
I couldn't read your feelings so well.
Kin-chan...
no matter what happens...
I will be there for you.
Don't take it all on yourself. Let me know
if there is anything I can do.
I can cook. I can answer the roll call
for you in your class.
Thank you.
The only thing I cannot do is
write a class report on your behalf.
If I do that,
you will fail the class.
The dinner is delicious, isn't it?
Your dad made this, didn't he?
I'm so busted.
It's easy to tell that.
This meal is in a different class
from yours.
Don't be mean to me. I'm trying.
Can't you thank me once in a while
at least?
Thanks.
You are always mean to me.
What did you say?
Your cooking is still bad, but at least
getting better.
Thank you for the meal.
He is really late today.
That must be Irie.
No, it's from Mr. Sudo.
-Hello?
-Aihara. We have a problem.
-What's going on?
-I just...
I decided to confess my love to
Matsumoto.
Finally you confessed?
No. I was about to do that.
Not yet?
Then why are you calling me?
That's not the point.
Matsumoto told me
that she loves someone else.
That's not surprising.
She is in love with Irie.
You knew that, didn't you?
That's not the issue here.
I knew that.
Matsumoto is going
to confess her love to Irie.
If she is in love with someone,
naturally she wants to confess--
What?!
Ms. Matsumoto will confess her love
to Irie?
When will she do that?
Tonight.
Tonight?!
I wonder where and when Ms. Matsumoto
will confess her love to Irie.
Don't tell me that it's too late?
No!
I'm sorry
to ambush you like this.
You must have been waiting for me
so long.
You could wait for me at my home if you
have something to say.
It won't work.
I wanted to have a private moment
with you.
I know that it is very selfish
to disturb you while
you are having a rough time.
But...
But what?
I love you.
I said it clearly.
So, I want your clear response.
What do you think about me?
I'm sorry.
You are just a friend...
for me.
I really love you.
I've never had such a feeling.
That's why...
I can't give up on you.
Are you satisfied now?
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to do that with
you.
Why? Am I not good enough?
Then...
whom are you willing to kiss?
I did kiss.
I kissed Kotoko.
I'm humiliated.
My pride is hurt.
I will be praying for a speedy recovery
for your father.
He kissed me,
but it happened more than a year ago.
Why did he bring it up now?
Hey.
Do not eavesdrop on someone's intimate
conversation.
I'm sorry.
You were late, so, I was worried.
Irie?
To tell you the truth,
father is not doing well.
My mother and I...
met his doctor today.
It appears that his condition is stable.
But the test found...
a serious issue in his heart.
He has to have surgery...
as soon as possible.
Is it a difficult surgery?
It's a heart issue.
Even if it is done successfully,
he cannot go back to work for a while.
I see.
I believe that stress caused...
his heart issue.
Because of the recession,
the revenue of his company has gone
down drastically.
That's why...
he wanted me to take over his company
as soon as possible.
I want you
to take over my company.
Pandai may end up
being taken over by a bigger company.
If I take over the company...
everything will be fine.
But you have a dream to be a doctor.
It is not a long-time dream.
I want to become...
a doctor.
I don't know whether I'm good at it
or not.
But I want to try it.
Are you giving up your dream?
Irie?
Being a doctor is...
the first profession
I got interested in.
He looked so sad.
I couldn't...
help but hug him.
But Irie didn't refuse it.
At that moment...
I felt connected emotionally with Irie.
Here is your bento box lunch.
I made the rolled omelet pretty well
today.
I also grilled green onion.
They say that green onion makes you
smarter.
Then why don't you eat it?
Have a good day.
Despite that...
We are very honored to have you
in our office.
-Thank you for coming.
-That's not a big deal.
I happened to be in this area. That's why.
Did you come here by yourself?
I'm here to discuss a personal issue
with you.
With me?
Are you interested in meeting your
prospective marriage partner?
I know it's a bad time since Mr. Irie
is in the hospital.
I have a granddaughter.
She is the same age as you and attends
University of Sacred Heart.
It's one of the most prestigious schools.
What do you think?
Think of it like a blind date.
You are still young.
I know it's not an easy decision.
Please discuss with your parents
and let me know at your earliest
convenience.
Let's discuss about our investment matter
after that.
Sorry to visit you
without advance notice.
No problem, sir.
Naoki,
please consider it very carefully.
Thank you for coming today.
Naoki...
This is a great opportunity
for the company.
Am I right?
We are about to have...
a new development in our fate.
Is it true that you will meet a
marriage partner?
-Yes. I like her.
-Do you remember me?
-I won't forget a beautiful woman.
-I got a good idea.
To ruin his formal meeting? I'm in.
This is different.
This is a matter
between two families.
I will steal Kotoko from you.
Do whatever you want.
Brother, you love Kotoko, don't you?
DISCLAIMER:
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
Everything will be fine.