-Let's go to one more bar.
-I can't.
One more bar.
WINTER, 2007
Thank you.
No.
It was nothing.
FROM: YAMASHITA
WHERE ARE YOU?
REPLY
I'M THINKING OF
CHANGING THE LAST PUNCHLINE
I'LL BE THERE SOON
Ready...
Go!
This is killing me.
NIPPON BROADCASTING RADIO
Why's he so late?
He's the one that wanted to practice
before the show. What's he doing?
What is it?
Smash!
Both colors look good.
-That's cool, too.
-It is.
Okay. That's it.
As for me...
Red looks cool, too.
This one and...
Mr. Kamiya...
It was like he couldn't stop
punishing himself.
Take both of them.
Thank you.
-I'll pay for mine.
-I don't need your money.
Sir, do you need this?
He was like that
ever since he lost Maki.
-The number you're trying to reach--
-What's he doing?!
-Hello.
-Hold it.
I don't think you work here.
Showing me the inside of your coat
won't help.
-Who are you?
-I'm Yamashita.
That's not much help.
Which "Yamashita" are you?
The straight man.
-Once more.
-Here I go.
-You're worse than I thought.
-Ready?
-Come on.
-You're throwing the ball.
-That's not a serve.
-Hit it back.
I can't tell when it'll come.
Once more.
-Hit it back properly.
-Let me serve.
Here I go.
Come on!
You hit the ceiling!
The wounds were deep.
They took a long time to heal.
HIBANA
- Spark -
-Hello.
BABY HOSHIKAWA'S "TALK-IINO"
MON 24:00 - 27:00
Hello!
-Hello.
-Hi!
Hello.
Mr. Hoshikawa, thanks for
having us on Talk-iino.
-Don't let me down.
-Thank you!
Introduce yourself.
-I'm Yamashita from Sparks.
-I'm Sakamoto.
This guy's a real pro.
-He's the guru?
-He is.
-Wow.
-This is your big chance.
It's our big chance?
Where's your partner? Tokunaga.
He's, um...
The nerves have got to his stomach.
He's stuck on the toilet.
Don't you get sick of shadow boxing?
I'll be right back.
Mr. Kamiya...
INSTANT LOANS
How about calling it a night?
You have plans?
Sorry.
You're right.
Let's call it a night.
-Just one more drink?
-It's okay.
Ready...
Ready!
See ya!
Speak up!
Yessir! Sorry!
We'll be on soon!
Could you please standby?
Okay.
"There's a guy at school
who always plays weird tricks on me.
How can I stop it without offending him?
In need of some advice."
So, they're in a bit of trouble.
I guess in situations like these...
Excuse me.
You'll be on soon.
You'll be on soon. It's time to standby!
Sure thing. Thanks.
-Where is your partner?
-My partner... Hm?
It's still warm. He should be close by.
NIPPON BROADCASTING RADIO
-Hey! You're late!
-Sorry.
-You're late!
-I'm hot.
I haven't run for ages.
Who cares?
Hurry up and get changed.
What's with that?
Don't strip it off.
There's a lady behind you.
-I got you one, too.
-I'm not wearing it.
Why put on a silly costume
for a radio show?
You really do have one for me?
I'm not wearing it!
Where were you?
I was thinking of a new punchline.
-But let's keep the original.
-What?
I nearly had a heart attack--
Blow for me.
Blow!
That's inhaling!
You stink of alcohol!
Were you with Mr. Kamiya again?
-I'm sober now.
-You're drunk?
-I sweated it out.
-You're--
Boys.
-Hello.
Can you shorten your two-minute act
to 30 seconds?
-Thirty seconds?
-We're running over time.
-Two minutes...
-Sorry.
-You're telling us now?
-I'm counting on you!
...today's guest were Sparks!
-Thanks, guys.
-Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
-Excuse us.
-Thank you!
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
If the feedback is good,
we'll see you again soon.
-Thank you.
Thank you, Speaks!
SPEAKS, SPHYNX, SPIELBERG, SUPERMANS...
HYUGA AGENCY
-Good morning.
-Good morning, sir!
You got me.
Is that an impersonation?
The Tokuma Pose!
That's cool.
Where should it go, Ms. Erika?
-Hm... A little higher.
-Higher?
-That's too high.
-Sorry.
BUU FUBUUBU
ON AIR TUESDAYS
If you put that there,
Mr. Tokuma won't stand out.
But, boss, it won't fit.
You can't hang it sideways.
How about...? Oh, that won't work either.
-There's no point.
-You're right.
-You're here?
-Good morning.
Mr. Ogata...
Let me apologize about the radio show.
But we had to cut it to 30 seconds,
just before the show.
We'd practiced a two-minute routine.
-They told us at the last moment.
-It was a bit unfair.
What are you babbling about?
You got a gig.
The New Comedy Star Battle.
Give me one.
-For real?
-For real?!
-The New Comedy Star Battle!
-I know.
Is this real?
Everyone in the industry comes.
For better or worse, they'll remember you.
They will...
Buu Fubuubu were in this contest
last year, right?
The moment they won,
they got three weekly shows.
Three weekly shows?
This is insane.
That's if we win.
If you do well,
the New Star Battle is a big chance.
But if you mess up,
the damage is big, too.
Damage?
According to Buu Fubuubu,
it's all about
how much the audience laugh.
It's not like your previous gigs.
Keep the masses in mind.
Why not make your routine simpler?
"It's important that you realize
what people want from you.
Not only when you have sex,
but in every situation."
Wisdom from the god of porn, Taka Kato.
Bye.
Okay!
You got in thanks to the recommendation
from the writer, Isshin Takada.
Do it like you always do.
See?
GO WITH THE FLOW
Go for it.
It's the New Star Battle.
What'll we do?
I'm thinking.
Don't rush me.
You heard Mr. Ogata.
"Keep the masses in mind."
It's all about how much
the audience laugh.
Remember what Mr. Takada wrote?
"Sparks is unique."
That's what he liked.
But he's a pro.
We want everyone to laugh.
We want to be popular with the masses.
You write it.
That won't work.
My role is to keep the same perspective
as the audience.
Have you read the comments online?
"The funny man from Sparks is gloomy."
"He's unrelatable."
I know.
The New Star Battle...
We won it.
What's with all the confidence?
-Tokunaga.
-What?
The New Star Battle...
We won it.
Thanks, everyone.
-It's great.
-I know.
I think it'll work.
Let's run it through.
-Hello, we're Sparks.
-Please enjoy the show.
-Dial it again.
-Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
The number you're trying to reach
belongs to artificial intelligence.
It has formed its own identity.
It is busy planning
the extinction of the human race.
-Sorry, but we cannot connect you.
-Stop it!
That's way too scary!
I don't know, but maybe you could...
Don't you have a joke
that younger audiences will like?
A joke that's more pop.
-We don't need to be pop.
-Do you have one?
How about this?
-Bip, bop, bop. Prrr...
-Call telephone. No reception--
-Hey. Hey!
Come on. Do it properly.
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
Call telephone.
No reception. Or switch off!
Fuck!
Hey, come on.
-Too much?
-What's with all the energy?
But that's probably better. Any others?
Jokes like that. Energetic ones.
How about this?
-Hello, young friends--
-You can be more pumped up.
Hello, young friends!
I'm in the fairy forest,
singing with my bird friends!
Hop on a Pegasus,
and join us across the rainbow bridge!
That's good.
It's easy to understand. It's good.
-Let's do that.
-I don't really like it.
But let's try it.
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
Hello, young friends!
I'm in the fairy forest,
singing with my bird friends!
Hop on a Pegasus, and join us--
-Aren't we sucking up too much?
-This is perfect for the New Star Battle.
It's so cheesy. Do we need it?
If we want to make a living.
Bip, bop, bap, bop...
Something just drove by. What was it?
"Bip, bop, bap, bop."
I wonder...
Was it a police car? An ambulance?
What made that sound?
"Bip, bop, bap, bop."
What drove by? "Bip, bop, bap, bop."
Ah, I know. It was a "bippobapo-bus."
Hello. Sorry for the wait.
-Where shall we go?
-Wherever we can drink.
We've got sushi...
Soba noodles...
Mr. Kamiya.
Why don't we buy something here
and drink in a park somewhere?
This will do?
I really like these little delicatessens.
You like it trashy.
You win. I'll keep you company.
Welcome.
What would you like?
The most expensive is shrimp tempura.
Ten of them?
That much shrimp?
What do you want?
Tokunaga.
Wanna walk to Nikotama?
Mr. Kamiya...
I don't want my bag to
stink of fried chicken.
Can we eat this first?
Nothing whets your appetite more than
the aroma of fried chicken.
If you think it smells bad
when it comes from your bag,
your mind's just playing tricks on you.
It's cool.
Shit's cool!
There were so many things
I wanted to ask Mr. Kamiya.
You should walk more.
Apparently I'm convinced he knows
the answer to everything.
When you walk around, you realize things.
There are so many funny things
just waiting for you to notice them.
Take care, old lady.
-Something happened.
-I wonder what.
It looks okay.
Mr. Kamiya, don't you ever worry
about other people's opinions?
Where's this coming from?
Well, it pisses me off
when people talk bad about me.
But I don't really care.
Even if they badmouth you
on the Internet?
On the Internet, so many people talk
about others like they were trash.
When that hate gets aimed your way,
it hurts.
I'd rather be punched.
It even drives some people to suicide.
I think it's insane.
But...
think about the hater.
If hating is the only thing they can do
to make it through the night alive,
I think it's okay.
I hope they write the most painful thing
about me they can think of.
But I can't ignore them.
If you worry about what people think,
you'll wear yourself out.
In the end, will their words
have any effect on what you create?
It'll make no difference.
We're not that smart.
We do what we want.
If it's funny, we'll make a living.
If it's not, we'll get weeded out.
That's all.
We weren't making a living.
Were we not funny?
Kudos to the food of the masses.
It tastes great even when it's cold.
How rude of you
to complain about its smell.
Damn.
That stinks!
Tokunaga.
Come on in.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Sorry for making you wait.
-Sorry for calling you in.
-Was it hard to find?
-A little.
Wow.
-Cool?
-Yes.
There was an unwritten rule
for young comedians:
Don't mix with the juniors
that your partner is close with.
-Beer, please.
-Beer?
-I'll have an Oolong & Shochu.
-Coming up.
-You're doing well lately.
-Not at all.
We're still as poor as ever.
Have you heard?
About Kamiya.
He's in so much debt,
he's nearly beyond help.
You know. When he's with you,
he tries to act too big.
I know that's part of
what makes him funny, but...
unless something changes,
we won't be able to do manzai anymore.
I'm sorry.
He always pays for me.
-From now on, I'll try to--
-No.
That's not what I mean.
You should stay close with him.
Stay close.
Are you in the next
New Comedy Star Battle?
Yes.
We're in it, too.
Ahondara will be, too?
You didn't know?
Kamiya didn't tell you?
-He did.
-He did?
But he hasn't decided
which act we should do.
The New Star Battle...
You know how duos break up
if they don't do well?
It might be our very last chance.
What do you mean?
Don't get me wrong.
We're not gonna quit.
Don't write us off.
Sorry.
But Kamiya...
When he talks about you,
he always looks so happy.
He really must like you.
Kamiya...
He likes you.
The big time... Wouldn't that be nice?
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
It is with profound regret that I inform
you this number is currently unavailable.
-Please forgive me. Please, pretty please!
-That message is too polite!
"Please, pretty please!"?
And there's no need to bow.
Nobody can see you.
And stop doing that giggle at the end.
I didn't like it the first time.
No more giggling.
And stop poking your chin out
between jokes.
-It's distracting.
-That, too?
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
The number you're trying to reach
belongs to artificial intelligence.
It has formed its own identity--
Hey. Stop it.
Why do that one?
It's, "I'm in the Fairy Forest,
singing with my bird friends!"
I think this one's better.
Are we going through this again?
We already agreed!
Don't you want to win?
You're asking me?!
Nothing works if you're flimsy.
I took your advice on the first act,
but the second should be more like
the real Sparks.
If either of our acts flops,
we're done for.
I think we're funnier than anybody.
But we agreed to go for the masses.
Put your balls on the line.
We've got two days left.
Okay.
You know which one?
Start from where we were.
I'll start.
"Please, pretty please!"?
That message is too polite.
Do it properly.
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
The number you're trying to reach
belongs to artificial intelligence...
Isn't this one better?
Enough already.
"Hello, everybody!" is better.
Once more.
-"Hello, everybody!"
-"Hello, young friends! I'm in the..."
That message is too polite.
"Please, pretty please!"?
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
Hello, young friends!
I'm an artificially intelligent being!
I've got my own identity!
Why don't we...
-I hate artificial intelligence.
-Hear me out.
I've got my own identity!
Why don't we all make
the human race extinct!
"Bip, bop, bap. Prrr..."
"Hello, young friends!
I'm in the fairy forest,
singing with my bird friends!
Hop on a Pegasus,
and join us across the rainbow bridge!"
Mr. Kamiya.
Congratulations on your 30th birthday.
The first time we met,
you were four years younger than me.
The fact you're still four years younger
is quite a shock.
INCOMING TEXT
FROM: SAIZOU KAMIYA
You seem busy lately.
Are you writing my biography?
OF COURSE I AM
Where was he?
MY BIOGRAPHY SOUNDS BORING
He replied straight away.
PLEASE MAKE IT FUNNIER, MR. KAMIYA
KAMIYA'S BIOGRAPHY
VOL. 7
YOU'RE RIGHT
PLEASE DO SOMETHING LEGENDARY
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm in the Parthenon.
Where are you, Mr. Kamiya?
Inside a gooey chocolate fondue pot.
It's so sweet, I'm melty, melty, melting.
-Are you okay?
-Of course I am!
No, you're not.
Are you okay?
Know what?
I was just eavesdropping
on a nearby young couple.
Stop doing strange things
in the middle of the night.
The girl had one of those...
She had a fluffy white thing
around her neck.
She said to the guy:
"Say ten nice things about me."
She really did.
Did he tell her?
Yeah.
He rattled them off like he was chanting.
I bet she asks him all the time.
Sounds scary.
So...
Say ten nice things about me.
Why should I?
Why not? Tell me.
I don't want to.
I'll tell you next time,
if you're wearing
a fluffy white thing around your neck.
I won't wear one of those. Tell me.
For starters...
You can split dick tempura
in two without cringing.
You're really flexible when you do your
"gateway for up-and-coming comedians."
And you can sing Takuro Yoshida's songs
while impersonating Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi.
Who cares?
Let me see.
Mr. Kamiya...
If he can get a laugh...
he's not afraid to say
something violent or lewd.
He'll take any risk.
And...
Mr. Kamiya...
It doesn't matter who is
or isn't watching...
Even if no one in the audience
wants it...
he does what he believes in.
He doesn't suck up to anybody.
He never fails to fight.
You got it.
But...
above all...
the most amazing thing about
Mr. Kamiya is...
he made me his disciple.
What balls!
You had the balls to say that?
Yep.
Tomorrow was the big day.
The New Comedy Star Battle.
THE 3RD ANNUAL
NEW COMEDY STAR BATTLE
-Hello.
Hello.
I came up with something yesterday.
After "the humble Pegasus,"
I'll keep going a bit.
You'll dig further?
-"Please ride the humble Pegasus and--"
-Mr. Osaki!
Good morning, sir.
Hello, Takada. Thanks for coming.
Not at all. It's a great honor
you invited me as a judge.
But it's a shame.
This year's comedians
are all small-fry.
I guess we could decide
nobody deserves to be champion.
Sir, that'd be going a bit far.
-Are you free afterwards?
-Yes.
There's a nice BBQ restaurant nearby.
Coming?
I'd love to.
-You only drink highballs, right?
-That's correct, sir.
You're small-fry.
That's too polite. Way too polite.
What's with the
"Please, pretty please!"?
And there's no need to bow.
Nobody can see you.
-Once more.
-Do it properly.
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
Hello, young friends.
I'm an artificially intelligent...
Wrong one. Sorry.
Hey.
Hello.
Hello!
-Hello.
-Hi.
Are you nervous?
Hello.
Hi.
-Hello.
-Hello!
-You're rehearsing?
-Of course we are.
It won't make any difference.
Not at this stage.
Let us be.
-You wanna be more successful?
-No--
How sly.
And you look pale.
Hello.
There's some space here.
Welcome to the 3rd Annual
New Comedy Star Battle!
The number you're trying to reach,
tee-hee,
is either out of range,
or the power is turned off,
tee-hee-hee-hee!
Stop being so creepy!
Enough with that creepy giggle!
I want a friendly but polite message
on my voicemail.
Oh, I get it. Call me again.
Bip, bop, bap. Prrr...
It is with profound regret that I inform
you this number is currently unavailable.
-Please forgive me. Please, pretty please!
-That message is too polite!
What's with the
"Please, pretty please!"?
And there's no need to bow.
Nobody can see you.
-Can't you make a happier version?
-A happier one? Okay, call me.
Hello, young friends!
I'm in the fairy forest,
singing with my bird friends!
Hop on a Pegasus,
and join us
across the rainbow bridge!
That's too much like a fairy tale!
"Come join us!"?
And your Pegasus was tiny.
I don't want a baby Pegasus.
The baby Pegasus is still there?
Pegasus, how old are you?
-I'm 62 years old.
-Baby Pegasus is a veteran.
He's quite old.
May I ask your name?
-I don't have one yet.
-Sixty-two years without a name?
Baby Pegasus has lived
for 62 years without a name?
-The... sorry... unavailable.
-The voicemail has bad reception, too?
That's the worst reception ever.
Your voicemail is
the worst I've ever heard.
-I think so, too!
-You think so, too?!
-I've had enough.
-Thank you.
-We nailed them.
-Told you.
-I wrote it.
-I told you.
My, oh, my.
Now we know
why you recommended Sparks.
They were a great hit
with the audience.
Their acts are usually rough,
but that was quite refined.
They've been around for seven years.
It's the least you'd expect.
Hello!
Hi, we're Ahondara.
Please enjoy the show.
The show's nearly halfway through.
You must be a little tired.
I'll help you wake up.
-Mind if I use scare tactics?
-You're gonna scare them awake?
Do you have life insurance?
-You're gonna die.
-Your scare tactics are too scary.
-It's okay.
-Why?
-I have no insurance either.
-You don't?!
Why did you ask?
I won't die
even if a truck runs over me.
What are you talking about?
You're too random.
If you need prior notification to keep up,
you should've told me.
I don't need notification.
Like I said, I won't die
even if a truck runs over me.
Trucks kill.
-Have you ever really thought about it?
-Of course not.
There's a huge truck
racing towards you at 100 km/h.
-Would you die?
-Yes!
-Trucks are deadly.
-But I won't die.
-Why not?
-How dumb are you?
A truck's racing towards me...
Bang!
-I died.
-You died?!
You said you wouldn't die.
When you thought about it,
you survived, right?
Let me try once more.
I'll imagine it properly this time.
Let's go step by step.
Here goes.
If a dozen veteran lawyers talk badly
about me as they approach,
-I'll die.
-Why is that lethal?
Are you that unstable?
A football player is running towards me
as he searches for his long-lost sister...
Unfortunately I'm standing on her head.
I'm dead.
What kind of situation is that?
Take your foot off the sister's head.
Time for the truck!
A truck is speeding right at you!
-Bang!
-I died.
-You died?
You're dead?
What's with the pose?
-Damn, I died.
-You're singing?
-I died!
-He's getting into the song.
-He's really into the song.
-Ohbayashi...
-Will you cry at my funeral?
-Don't go all emotional on me!
What's wrong?
You're not gonna die, right?
That's right, I won't die!
Do the truck again!
-A truck speeds towards you.
-I run towards the truck.
-I died.
-You died?!
-Is this for real? It's a totally new act.
-They're the funniest so far.
-I died.
-You died?
-That's the most dead so far.
-The most dead?
-Me, the driver, and everyone else.
-You killed them all?
-Ohbayashi...
-What?
-Will you cry at my funeral?
-Stop going sad like that.
I never had a friend before.
You're my first friend ever.
Who cares?
This isn't the time to confess.
You won't die, right?
That's what you said.
Stop looking so depressed.
What's wrong?
What is it? Kamiya!
Kamiya! Say something!
-I love making jam.
-What a strange new personality.
I've had enough.
Thank you.
Wow.
Usually they only make
other professionals laugh.
-But it worked with the audience today.
-It did.
I always found them
unsuitable for television.
But I think that act will work.
Out of today's offerings,
they didn't seem bad.
My stomach hurts.
That's the end of
the first half of the show.
We will now have
a ten-minute interval.
-What was their name?
-I don't know.
These guys!
-Truck... Bang!
-I died.
Your act went well.
We only just started.
I told you that would work, too.
Kamiya's Biography, Chapter Two.
Hello, we're Ahondara.
The show's nearly halfway through.
You must be a little tired.
I'll help you wake up.
-Mind if I use scare tactics?
-You'll scare them awake?
Do you have life insurance?
You're gonna die.
Your scare tactics are too scary.
It's okay.
I have no insurance either.
You don't?
Why ask?
I won't die
even if a truck runs over me.
What are you talking about?
If you need prior notification to keep up,
you should've told me.
I don't need notification.
Like I said, I won't die
even if a truck runs over me.
You would die.
-Have you ever really thought about it?
-Of course not.
Are they doing the same act?
They must have some plan.
-It's exactly the same.
-I don't get it.
They are ahondara (boofheads).
How dumb are you?
A truck's racing towards me...
Bang!
-I died.
-You died?!
So you would die. Just as you would
if you got hit by a meteor.
I died. This is bad.
But you're the one making this up.
Hang on. Let me focus.
I'll imagine it properly.
Drive at me in the truck
at just the right time.
See?
They started something.
But that won't go down well
with the judges.
They're not getting
that many laughs.
They really are ahondara.
A football player is running towards me
as he searches for his long-lost sister...
Unfortunately I'm standing on her head.
-I'm dead.
-Of course you are.
-Time for the truck!
-A truck is speeding right at you!
-Bang!
-I died.
-You died?
What's with the pose?
You look alive to me.
I'm dying!
Why are you singing?
Ohbayashi...
-Will you cry at my funeral?
-Don't go all emotional on me.
Stop it.
You're not gonna die, right?
-You said you won't die.
-That's right, I won't die!
-Do the truck again!
-Okay!
-A truck speeds towards you!
-I run towards the truck!
-I died.
-You're dead.
So, Ohbayashi...
Will you cry at my funeral?
I told you before.
Don't go all emotional on me!
I never had a friend before.
You're my first friend ever...
-They're laughing!
-What is this act?!
Manzai is too hard to lip-sync!
We're doing an okay job!
Kamiya! Say something!
I love making jam.
What a strange new personality.
I've had enough. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's congratulate our
Gold, Silver and Bronze award winners!
The New Comedy Stars
have been born.
Now we'll receive a comment
from the head judge, Mr. Osaki. Thank you.
I'm the head judge, Osaki.
Everyone put up a great fight today.
Personally, I was reassured
there's still new talent out there.
However, I was disappointed that one duo
chose to use recorded audio in their act.
It wasn't manzai.
Manzai is all about the organic connection
between audience and artist.
The live chemical reaction
is what creates laughter inside us.
In conclusion, I warn the winners
not to become complacent.
I also warn them to never forget
comedy needs an audience...
As far as Mr. Kamiya was concerned,
the audience expected
nothing but manzai,
but he'd created an accident
right before their eyes.
That was his idea of funny.
Congratulations to our winners,
The Curl!
That's who Mr. Kamiya was.
Please look forward to the next
New Star Comedy Battle.
And thank you all for coming!
Thank you!