When people finish their day
and hurry home,
my day starts.
My diner is open from midnight
to seven in the morning.
They call it "Midnight Diner."
PORK MISO SOUP COMBO,
BEER, SAKE, SHOCHU
That's all I have on my menu.
But I'll make whatever customers request,
as long as I have the ingredients for it.
That's my policy.
Do I even have customers?
More than you would expect.
Midnight Diner:
Tokyo Stories
HOT POT FOR ONE
Hot...
Okae,
you like it?
Yes, I love it.
This is too much hassle to
prepare at home.
Besides, I always have a ton of
leftovers afterwards.
Kae was Chu's classmate.
Recently, she's been coming here
after work
and ordering this hot pot for one.
Thank you for the meal.
Well done.
-Would you like a drink?
-Sorry.
I must go back to work.
Now?
Clean rooms at the no-tell motel?
Nobody leaves until the morning.
There are more people checking in
and out than you think at this time.
A young part-timer took a day off
without advance notice.
I have to cover his shift.
Too bad.
Take care of yourself. Okay?
Worry about yourself, Chu.
You drink too much.
Here.
Thank you.
Well...
See you around.
Take care.
Okae was the daughter
of a shoe store owner
that used to be at the corner.
She used to be quite pretty.
Even though she was born
and raised in Shinjuku,
she was like a pure maiden,
carrying a white parasol all the time.
-She spoke like an upper-class lady.
-I don't like her.
She sounds like a pretentious girl.
I knew some girls like that.
They don't know who they really are.
We can't befriend such a girl.
Chu, she was your first love, huh?
Stop it.
You have the wrong idea.
And then...
she was discovered
by a famous movie director,
but her acting career wasn't successful.
Later on,
she married some rich guy.
That's what I heard.
She doesn't look rich, does she?
I bet the story is made up.
That's why I don't like women.
To be honest,
I don't know if it's true or not.
Besides, we hadn't seen each other
for almost four decades.
She seems to make a hard living.
Then you don't really know
anything about her life
from the past four decades?
She came back to this area recently.
At first, I didn't even recognize her.
This is a great croquette.
You should eat it while it's still hot.
Eat it as soon as you get home. Okay?
Or would you like to eat it now?
Yes?
Here you--
Chu?
It is you.
Chu, right?
What?
It's Kae, from the shoe store.
Okae?
Long time, no see.
How have you been?
Had some ups and downs...
but I'm okay, as you can see.
See you soon.
Teppei.
Wait.
I'm what?
Lavishing money on a young lover?
Chu's losing his mind, isn't he?
I hope he's okay.
But he is not completely...
wrong about it.
That young man is the only son
of Kae's brother.
Apparently, she saw him
at her brother's funeral last year
for the first time in more than ten years.
So...
do you have the money
to cover the service?
Of course, not.
No?
The body's been cremated.
That's why I called you, Auntie.
For money? I don't have any either.
Then we'll have to run.
How can you run away?
-What about the ashes?
-I don't care.
Come on. He's your father.
That asshole? He is no one to me.
I was relieved when he disappeared
without a trace. Then he died.
It's not even worth picking up his bones.
Listen here.
No matter how terrible he was,
he's still your father.
Blood is thicker than water.
You can't ignore it.
And you know it.
That's why you called me.
You are hopeless.
I'll ask them to see
if you can pay in installments.
Unfortunately,
Kae's nephew is a bum,
just like his father.
His wife left him.
He has no job, and he's in his 40s.
I'm home.
Teppei,
have you eaten dinner?
What a mess!
Shut up.
You are so sloppy.
Hey, Nguyen, come here.
Get the other side.
Ready?
Grip the ends.
Okay.
Here you go.
You like it? Delicious, isn't it?
I've wanted to feed you
this hot pot for one for a while.
But it's not "hot pot for one"
if the two of us eat it together.
Okae.
-Want some?
-Sorry.
I have to go back to work.
The part-timer quit.
These days, young folks don't know
what hard work means.
Why don't you ask
your nephew to help you?
-You agree?
-Stop your nonsense.
Where are you going?
I finished it, so don't complain.
Can I borrow some money?
Going out for a drink again?
I lent you money the other day.
Fine.
Wait.
You give me no choice.
You don't have a job?
No job and you just get drunk?
Don't you even want to help her?
Hey, cut it out.
Don't worry about me.
What have you done?
He's struggling to figure out
how to go on with his life.
Why can't he have a drink?
Just mind your own business.
Master, check please.
Twelve hundred yen.
Thank you.
Should I have said nothing?
You are her childhood friend.
That wasn't so out of line for you.
First loves...
never work out.
Right?
Wait for me, Teppei. Look.
I circled the good ones.
Look.
Auntie,
do you think that a man who filed
for bankruptcy can find a good job?
There are a lot of jobs
if you keep your expectations realistic.
What he said may be a good idea.
The no-tell motel.
Do you want me to ask
the manager about the job?
Come on.
I'm still young.
Unlike you,
I can't give up on my future yet.
Then... what do you want to do?
I was like you once.
When I was young,
I chased after something fancy.
A luxurious life that everyone would envy.
But...
I found nothing in my hand
when I thought that I finally got it.
I know you have to learn
from your own failures.
Get a drink, okay?
Come home safely.
Teppei?
Wake up.
Regarding the job,
my manager wants to interview--
Hey, Chu.
Did you lose at the horse races again?
No.
Remember Kae's nephew?
He stole her entire fortune,
including credit cards,
her ATM card, cash, and ran away.
Okae shouldn't have spoiled him.
But still...
Good evening.
Welcome.
Give me warm sake and the hot pot.
Kae,
did something good happen?
Look at this.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Teppei sent it to me
as a birthday gift.
It looks great on you.
Doesn't it?
I was right.
Blood is thicker than water.
Did you get your money back?
I don't care about that anymore.
Okae,
you disappoint me.
Why?
You're deceived by such a gift.
I'm sure he bought it with your money.
I'm telling you,
it's not about the money.
What's wrong with you?
Wake up.
When you were young,
you were beautiful and independent.
You were an awesome lady.
Are you saying
that I'm embarrassing now?
Yes, you're embarrassing.
He's the only family you have?
So, what?
You're being irrational.
You have no idea.
Once I started living with Teppei,
I learned it was a joy
to work for someone else
for the first time in my life.
I should be thanking him.
Okae, are you being serious?
I'm serious. Completely serious.
How can you criticize me?
You have no family.
You get drunk by yourself every night.
You're more embarrassing than I am.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
I'm sorry.
I was too harsh.
Have some.
No thanks.
Just eat it.
So, you like it?
Later, I can make rice porridge
with the soup for you.
Good idea!
Hello?
Yes.
I understand.
Teppei was arrested.
Kae's nephew was charged
with several offenses,
including theft,
swindling on small loans,
and more.
He got a prison sentence.
Now Kae visits him in prison often.
That's what I heard.
About six months have passed
since then.
-Good evening.
-Welcome.
Have a seat there.
Master, make him anything he wants.
Kae, who is this?
This is Teppei's son.
His name is Shohei.
I didn't know
that Teppei had such a big boy.
Since his mother got remarried,
he has no place to stay.
So, I took custody of him.
Man,
what a nuisance, huh?
What would you like?
Meat!
-And you, Kae? Hot pot for one?
-Nothing for me.
We ate hot pot at home
last night together.
Wait. Warm sake.
Sure.
Here you go.
A special plate full of meat.
-Let's eat.
-Go ahead.
Hey.
Make sure you chew it well.
-Master, give him some juice.
-Sure.
I never imagined...
I'd have the chance...
to raise a kid at this age.
Okae...
never looked at her feet,
under her nose,
even though she was the daughter
of a shoe store.
I just guess...
that she wanted to see other scenaries.
You're right.
That's what she wanted.
Tonight, she looked even better
than when she was young.
Chu,
this one's on me.
Are you sure?
It's not easy to live one's life,
whether you're alone
or have someone else.
That's good.
In an earthen pot for one,
simmer Chinese cabbage,
pork and enoki mushrooms
in a bonito broth.
That's all there is to it.
Simple is the best.
It looks delicious.
Here you go.
Hold it, Kae.
Don't forget the bushukan.
That's very important.
Bushukan is a citrus fruit from Tosa.
The juice is a perfect match
for my hot pot.
Make sure to eat a lot.
-It's so delicious.
-Isn't it?
THIS STORY IS FICTION