When people finish their day
and hurry home,
my day starts.
My diner is open from midnight
to seven in the morning.
They call it "Midnight Diner."
Do I even have customers?
More than you would expect.
MIDNIGHT DINER:
TOKYO STORIES
TONTEKI
Once it starts to get cold,
Shigemi knits a new sweater every year.
You're so good.
I'm just used to it.
A gift for your boyfriend?
Boyfriend? Kind of.
To tell you the truth,
she knits one
for a different "boyfriend" each time.
Here is your tonteki.
These days it's rare to see
someone knitting in a public place.
You're right about that.
Welcome.
Mr. Ichihara!
Hi, Ms. Suzuki. How are you?
Well. Thank you.
Is he your friend?
This is Mr. Ichihara,
an interior designer.
He recently opened his office
in this area.
Ms. Suzuki recommended this joint to me.
Two pork soup combos, please.
-A smaller size for me.
-Sure thing.
This is Ms. Suzuki, a realtor
who helped me find the office.
Thank you for finding
such a great property.
I was just doing my job.
Why don't we ask her
to find our condo, too?
That's a good idea.
We are planning to live near my office.
Can you find one for us?
Yes, of course.
Why?
Here.
Don't tell me...
this was for that guy.
Obviously, I'm just a realtor
for Mr. Ichihara.
Were you knitting it for a man
who isn't even your boyfriend?
You didn't even know
that he had a girlfriend?
It was very premature.
It's fine. I'm used to it!
Think she'll be okay?
She was so shocked.
Don't worry.
Are you sure?
Shigemi looks fragile,
but she's resilient.
I was right.
About ten days later...
It's open.
Hello!
Here you go.
Thank you.
He'll make you whatever you want,
so ask for anything.
As long as I have the ingredients for it.
Kurihara, Yoshida and Shirano.
They're younger colleagues of mine.
Did you know, Master?
Kurihara is from Yokkaichi,
and tonteki is his favorite food.
I hear that Yokkaichi
is famous for tonteki.
Yes, the meat has several slits,
and the thick sauce is unique.
My sauce is light,
so I don't know if you'll like it or not.
I'd like to try it.
How about you, Yoshida?
Sorry, I don't eat anything after nine,
so I don't gain weight.
I see.
And you, Shirano?
I will have tonteki, too.
-Then three tontekis, please.
-Got it.
Cheers.
Ms. Suzuki, you like to knit?
Ever since I was little.
I like women who can knit.
They look quite feminine.
I'd like to learn it, then.
Ms. Suzuki, can you teach me?
Here you go.
Like it?
I see.
Yokkaichi's tonteki goes well with rice.
Yours is perfect for drinks.
Actually, can I have rice?
Sure.
Rice with this?
You'll gain weight for sure.
I guess Shigemi's current love interest...
is this guy.
I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow.
I'm going home.
-Kurihara.
-Yes?
For you.
Really?
I hope it's your size.
Perfect.
Can I really have it?
I've wanted a sweater like this.
Thank you so much.
And? What was his reaction?
I think he likes it.
But I don't feel
like it makes us any closer.
Did you tell him how you felt
when you gave it to him?
But he accepted the gift.
That means he probably accepted
my feelings, too. Right?
Am I right?
Men wouldn't be excited
about a handmade sweater
from someone
whom they're not interested in.
But he accepted it.
Which means
he accepted her love, right?
Come on.
Knitting a sweater to grab his attention?
You're beating around the bush.
Why don't you just say, "I love you"?
You're not a teen anymore.
Not everyone's mentally tough
like you are, Rumi.
It's like fracturing a bone.
Once it heals, that part gets tougher.
What do you mean?
Welcome.
What does Kurihara think about me?
Can you ask him casually?
You want me to ask?
You're the only one I can rely on.
Sure.
I'll ask him.
I appreciate it.
Excuse me, Ms. Suzuki.
Yes?
Well...
in return for that,
will you teach me how to knit?
What?
I'd like to knit a scarf.
Okay, but...
Is it a gift for someone?
Is it difficult to knit a scarf?
Not at all. Don't worry.
The important thing is your heart.
She will be so happy
if you give it to her.
Here you go.
-Enjoy the meal.
-Yes.
I see. A scarf, huh?
How old is she?
She is about your age.
I'm so clumsy.
I think you're good with your hands.
When I was in elementary school,
I wrote in an essay
that my favorite food is tonteki.
So, a boy I liked started calling me
"Pig Girl who likes tonteki."
I was overweight back then.
I have low self esteem.
Whenever I like someone,
I knit a sweater, or a scarf.
In most cases,
I don't even give it to him.
By the way, did you ask him?
What?
Right.
I think...
Kurihara doesn't like...
the color of the sweater
you gave him.
But...
he wears it at home.
He's a nice guy.
So, he couldn't tell you
that it wasn't his favorite color.
Is that right?
He should have told me that.
I wouldn't be hurt.
What is his favorite color, then?
I see. The issue was the color, huh?
How about this one?
Or...
maybe a brighter color?
Welcome.
This is your first time coming alone.
Right.
Have you finished the scarf?
I lied about that.
What?
I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Shirano. Do you have a moment?
I've been going out with Yoshida.
Oh really?
And...
Ms. Suzuki gave this to me.
Yoshida ripped it
to see how strong it was.
Women are nasty.
So...
Can you throw it away for me?
Really?
Thank you so much.
A handmade sweater carries
so much emotion.
I can't do it myself.
What are you doing?
It's just trash.
I'm disappointed in myself.
Ms. Suzuki confided in me.
I knew I should tell her the truth,
but I couldn't.
She's...
knitting another sweater for Kurihara.
I feel so bad.
Then...
the reason for making a scarf was...
I wanted to repair the sweater myself.
That's why I learned how to knit.
I know she didn't knit it for me, but...
it's made with Ms. Suzuki's love.
What now?
Will you...
stick to the lie?
Welcome.
Ms. Suzuki?
Kurihara.
Why are you here?
Shirano asked me to come here
and talk to him.
He asked me to come, too.
Would you like to sit?
Why are you wearing that?
Kurihara gave it to me.
Kurihara is dating Yoshida.
Why are you...?
Is that so?
Come on, Kurihara.
You should have told me that.
Ms. Suzuki.
What can I say?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Shigemi!
This sweater...
is warm...
and very comfy.
I really like it.
So what?
So...
I don't care about the sweater anymore!
Shigemi or Shirano
didn't come back for a while after that.
Come in. This way.
It's bigger than I expected.
We can have a dining table here.
The TV would be there?
-It's perfect for two of us, but...
-What?
I'm thinking about a kid.
Have you been drinking alone?
I quit knitting.
I realized that...
it's strange to give
a handmade sweater to someone
I'm not even dating.
It was silly of me to get excited.
I'm such an idiot.
I don't know.
The other day...
Shirano...
came here by himself.
He sat there...
and was repairing the sweater.
Right up here...
there was a hole.
He was not good at knitting.
And I felt bad for him.
He said,
"it's made with Ms. Suzuki's love."
He worked so hard to fix it.
That can't be true.
What is this feeling?
What...
is this feeling?
What is this feeling?
Shigemi?
Are you okay?
What the hell is this feeling?
Ms. Suzuki?
Shirano...
I thought...
that I only liked handsome guys.
Well, how do I say it?
What I mean is...
Well... you...
fixed my sweater.
Master told me about it.
So...
I was moved by your affection.
No, that's not right.
-What I'm trying to say is...
-I love you.
I love you,
Ms. Shigemi.
I love you, too.
If you cover pork with flour,
it sucks up the sauce well.
After adding the sauce to the pan,
drop in the grated onion.
It adds great depth
to the light sauce.
Ms. Shigemi.
What are you making?
Underwear.
It looks so warm.
-Good night.
THIS STORY IS FICTION