Wow.
I can't believe
we're already saying goodbye.
It's been great getting to know you,
Pee-wee Herman.
Earth sure is a great planet.
Your art, music, pizza.
You sure took to our customs fast.
Thanks for showing them to me.
I've loved these last two weeks.
-I wish I didn't have to go.
-[Pee-wee sniffles]
Me, too.
Come with me, back to my planet.
Meet my family and friends.
Live with me.
I can't.
I need to stay here
with the people of Earth.
I'm going to miss my new best friend.
I'll never forget you, Pee-wee.
I'll always remember you, too, Yul.
Look.
I made us both friendship bracelets.
[gasps]
Pee-wee, they're beautiful.
Let's put them on.
[sniffles]
I guess this is...
arrivederci then, right?
Right.
Arrivederci, Pee-wee Herman.
Arrivederci, Yul.
-[spaceship whirring]
-[both gasping]
I want to go, but I can't leave home!
I can't leave home!
-I can't leave home! I can't leave home!
-[alarm ringing]
-I can't leave home.
-[ringing continues]
I can't leave home!
[chuckles] Morning!
[yelling]
[laughing]
[chuckles] Ooh!
[hissing]
-[deflating]
-[gasps]
[yelling]
[screaming and laughing]
[laughs]
Ooh!
Apple-y! [chuckles]
-Good morning, Pee-wee!
-Morning, Mr. Murgatroyd!
[chuckles]
-[all] Pee-wee!
-Hi, kids! [grunts]
Ooh! Ooh! [chuckles]
[cat meowing]
[barking]
Hello! [chuckles]
[chuckles]
Breakfast bar!
Scone, French toast, American toast...
[sneezes]
Green grapes, sausages,
bacon, cinnamon toast!
Buh-bye!
[screaming]
Good morning, Pee-wee!
[Pee-wee grunts]
Good morning, Mrs. Rose!
[chuckles] Oh, look at you.
You're cute as a peanut!
-Ow!
-[both laughing]
Have you heard about
those new corduroy pillows?
-Corduroy pillows? No.
-[chuckles]
I'm surprised,
'cause they're making head lines!
[laughs]
Get it? "Head lines!"
Oh! [laughs]
-Hold on. Hey, Ruby!
-Morning, Pee-wee.
-Last stop, Nana's Yarn Barn!
-Oh!
[both exclaim]
[both laughing]
You're the sweetest boy in Fairville,
Pee-wee.
-Me?
-Is there anything sweeter than you?
Uh... a Root Beer Barrel?
-That's right!
-[chuckles]
I know they're in here somewhere.
There it is. [gasps]
No.
What was I looking for?
[gasps] Oh...
[laughs]
Root Beer Barrels are my favorite!
Boop! [chuckles]
Ah! [chuckles]
Well, listen, you seem really busy.
Let me let you let me run.
-Bye, Mrs. Rose!
-Bye-bye, Pee-wee.
[laughing]
[horn honking]
-Pee-wee!
-Yo, Billy!
-Hey, Pee-wee!
-Hey, Ben!
-Morning, Pee-wee!
-Kevin!
-[chuckles]
-Pee-wee!
I'm so glad I bumped into you.
I've got an amazing deal
I want to tell you about.
You're gonna have to tell me later,
Marvin.
I'm on my way to work. [chuckles]
Just a moment of your time.
Come on, Pee-wee.
Tell me, Pee-wee, where do you
picture yourself on vacation?
Mexico?
Or Morocco?
Morocco?
What is this?
A travel agency or a millinery?
Sorry, Marvin, I'm not interested.
[stutters] Come on, Pee-wee.
Don't you ever wonder
-what life is like outside Fairville?
-Nope!
Marvin, you know I don't want
to go anywhere or try anything new.
Bye! [chuckles]
[chuckles]
[chuckles] Phew!
[screams]
Emily, you scared me there for a moment.
I know I have overdue books.
I'm gonna return them soon, I promise.
-I don't care about silly overdue books.
-Oh?
But I do have something special
I wanted to give to you.
[chuckles]
Hmm.
[Pee-wee gasps] The new Scuba Cop?
The Emerald Sharks?
And the sharks are hammerheads?
These are the exact type of sharks
that Scuba Cop hates the most!
I haven't received your RSVP
for the Book Club tomorrow night.
I was thinking that, maybe afterwards,
you and I might--
Whoa, whoa!
Emily, let me stop you right there.
The fact is...
I neglected to RSVP my regrets.
I have rehearsal that night. NA.
-NA?
-Not available.
-Sorry.
-[chuckles]
Well, what time is your rehearsal?
Oh, uh, TBD.
-TBD?
-To be decided.
LATT, Em. IHTBG.
-[chuckles] What?
-LATT, IHTBG.
-IHT--
-"Look at the time."
"I have to be going."
You understand.
[horn honking]
Yay! Work time!
[chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
Two eggs, fried, extra hash browns,
side of sausage. Enjoy!
Looks fantastic as always, Beverly.
[phone ringing]
Dan's Diner.
Dan speaking.
[humming]
[chuckles]
-French toast is up, Bev!
-[bell dings]
Denver omelet.
Easy on the cheese.
Easy on the cheese-y, coming right up-y!
Boop. [chuckles]
Dudley! Sylvester! Clovis!
What are you guys doing here?
Pee-wee, we need to talk to you
about band rehearsal.
Well, it is unusual to be discussing
Renegades business at my workplace,
but, sure, what's up?
My promotion at the grocery store means
I'm gonna be working a lot more hours.
Nights.
Yeah, and my girlfriend's making me take
ballroom dancing with her
four times a week.
Nights.
My office just pressured me into joining
their nighttime bowling league.
Nights.
But the Renegades rehearse at night.
Hello? How's that gonna work
if all you guys are so busy at night?
It's not.
The Renegades are breaking up.
What?
-No!
-Things are changing.
None of us have enough time
to be in a band anymore.
I do!
That's because you're stuck in a rut,
Pee-wee.
We want to move on to other things.
What am I supposed to move on to?
What am I supposed to do
with my flutophone?
Why don't you think about a solo career?
Why don't you?
[Pee-wee] Good luck, you guys.
Good luck with all your stupid, important
reasons for breaking up the Renegades!
[all sighing]
[grunting]
[clattering]
-[door opening]
-[Dan chuckles]
-Nice seeing you, Dan.
-Bye, Dan!
Pee-wee, I gotta say,
your French toast is perfection!
Thanks.
Same with your pancakes, Herman.
They drive me crazy!
Not that long a drive, Ernie, but thanks.
I'm taking this biscuit with me.
I love it.
-Why don't you marry it?
-[all laugh]
Listen, you guys, you seem really busy.
Let me let you let me run, okay?
All right? Buh-bye!
-Thanks for coming.
-Later!
-See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
Hey, sport, can you watch over the diner?
I gotta go meet a couple pals
at the lodge.
Sure, Dan. I'll be right here.
Where else would I go?
Gonna be right here.
Just like always.
Have fun with your pals!
[laughs] Attaboy!
[clattering]
[crying]
[tears sizzling]
Sharks pulling off a jewel heist?
[chuckles]
It could happen,
but not if Scuba Cop happens to be
swimming around! [laughs]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[soul music playing]
Cool.
[rock music playing]
Double cool.
[songs mash up]
Triple cool.
Uh, hi! What can I get you?
-Milkshake, please.
-Flavor?
Let's say chocolate.
Sure. Three, two, one.
-[both] Chocolate.
-[chuckles]
[Pee-wee humming]
Boop! [chuckles]
[humming]
Ooh! [chuckles]
[continues humming]
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
La! [chuckles]
-[mixer whirring]
-[exclaiming]
[mimics retching]
[chuckles]
Boop! Think fast!
Wow!
Thanks, appreciate that.
[grunts]
Mmm.
Mmm!
[exclaiming]
Wow, man!
This milkshake is outrageous.
I really mean it.
Probably... [inhales]
top five, all-time.
[chuckles] Thanks, my specialty.
You know what would go great
with a milkshake of this caliber?
[both] A Root Beer Barrel!
[both] Only the best candy in the world!
[both] It really is!
[both] Distant second?
[both] Charleston Chew. Third?
[both] Tie between two candies.
[both] Rolos and Skittles!
[both] Shut up!
[both] Shut up.
Well, all right,
Mr. Master Milkshake Maker,
what do you say you show me around
this little burg of yours?
Me? A tour of Fairville?
I'd love to!
Oh, I can't.
I gotta watch over the diner.
-I promised Dan and Beverly--
-"Promised Dan and Beverly"?
Will you listen to yourself?
You sound like a little baby.
We'll only be gone ten minutes.
Chillax, man.
Live a little.
What?
[whispers] Live a little.
[chuckles]
[motorcycle engine idling]
I have kind of limited experience
on a motorcycle.
Shh!
-You hear that?
-What?
It's the old highway callin'.
Get on.
[chuckles]
[engine revving]
[Pee-wee laughing]
-Wicked-awesome view, dude!
-[chuckles]
-And it's right in your backyard.
-I'm glad you like it.
It roughly corresponds
to the model scale HO-187.
Wow, this is a whole new world for me.
A miniature world!
[both laughing]
A miniature world.
I mean, look at the detail.
It's breathtaking.
You got a real gift, man.
Thank you.
Hey, how about that tour of Fairville?
Right over there, that's Dan's Diner,
where we met.
And there, Fairville Public Library.
Fairville High.
Tire Repair of Fairville.
Fairville Fire Department.
Barber of Fairville.
And this right here,
this little building is where Fairville's
premier music group, the Renega--
-What's wrong? What's that building?
-Nothing.
It's just some stupid building
where my stupid band used to rehearse
before we broke up!
Let me get that right out of there.
[Pee-wee grunts]
Stupid! Stupid!
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
You okay?
Yeah, sure. I'm fine. [chuckles]
Hey! What's that?
[chuckles] Is that your house?
I didn't notice you had a tree house.
Oh, I don't.
That's the only detail
of this entire model that doesn't exist...
yet.
-[both laugh]
-That's funny.
You know, I always wanted
a tree house, too.
That is funny!
[both laughing]
Say...
What do you say you and me
get a picture of us
at the site of your future tree house?
You ready?
Three, two, one.
-[both] Root Beer Barrels!
-[shutter clicking]
You know, I never caught your name.
Oh, it's Pee-wee. Pee-wee Herman.
And you are?
[laughs] Good one.
Uh... what?
Wait...
you don't know who I am?
How could I?
Why would I?
I'm Joe...
Manganiello.
Well, pleasure to meet you,
Joe Man... [mumbling]
Manganiello.
Sorry, trick ear.
One more time.
Manganiello.
I'm an actor.
I'm told show business
can be very competitive,
so hang on to your dreams
and who knows? [chuckles]
I wish you luck, Joe Man... [mumbling]
-Certainly you've heard of True Blood?
-Uh-uh.
-Magic Mike?
-Hmm, you'd think so, but no.
Man, you're so real.
That's what I like about you, Pee-wee.
You're normal.
-[chuckles]
-[laughs]
[exclaims]
Your miniature world is awesome.
Hey, what's on the other side
of those railroad tracks?
Beyond Fairville?
I don't know, I've never been there.
Never?
May I tell you something
I've never told anyone?
Sure.
What is it?
Once upon a time, I won a contest.
A trip to Salt Lake City, Utah.
-[fanfare]
-[kids exclaiming]
-But I never made it to Salt Lake City.
-[tires squealing]
-Or Utah.
-[car crashing]
-Long story short...
-[faint sirens wailing and gunfire]
I came back with a metal plate in my head.
-[metal clinking]
-[EKG flatlining]
That explains why you don't travel.
[sighs] Hmm...
[stutters] Do you ever get worried
that life's just passing you by?
Ha!
What could possibly be going on out there
that I haven't tried already in Fairville?
-You ever been in a fight?
-No.
-You ever broken a rule?
-No!
You ever had two women fight over you?
Uh...
Have I? No.
Breaking rules and breaking hearts,
that's what life's all about.
I believe in fate.
And I think I know why you and I met.
You're gonna leave Fairville...
and you're gonna take a holiday.
I got your reason right here.
What is it? What?
I want you to be at my birthday party.
New York City! [chuckles]
How would I ever...
[stammering] I couldn't possibly...
This is all happening so fast.
See you in five days, brother.
"Five days"?
"Brother"?
-I've never even been on an airplane.
-No!
The only thing you're gonna
learn about yourself on a plane
is that you like the honey-roasted peanuts
better than the plain-salted.
If you're really hungry,
the open road is a smorgasbord
of life experience.
A few days on the open road
is worth a lifetime in Fairville.
The way I see it, Pee-wee Herman,
you got a choice to make.
Stick around here...
[engine starting]
...or live a little.
[tires squealing]
Stick around here...
or live a little.
What should I do?
I wish I had some kind of sign.
Whoa, that's a big apple.
Big Apple!
That's it! Bingo!
-Can I get anybody more water?
-Where's my order?
Where's the food?
I'm starving!
Bev, my lunch break is practically over!
-Me hungry!
-[thudding]
Shoot! Heck! Darn!
Pee-wee, where have you been?
I'm leaving town.
I won't be at work tomorrow
or the next day or the day after that.
I'm taking a holiday.
[humming]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
Come on, Little Connie.
We're going to New York City!
[horn honking]
[Pee-wee]
♪ One million bottles of pop on the wall ♪
♪ One million bottles of pop ♪
♪ You take one down and pass it around ♪
♪ Nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Nine hundred ninety-nine ♪
♪ Bottles of pop on the wall ♪
♪ Nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Bottles of pop on the wall ♪
Nine hundred ninety-nine ♪
♪ You take one down and pass it around ♪
♪ Nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Nine hundred ninety-eight ♪
♪ Bottles of pop on the wall ♪
♪ Nine hundred fifty-five ♪
♪ You take one down and pass it around ♪
♪ Nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Nine hundred fifty-four ♪
♪ Bottles of pop on the wall ♪
[gasps]
A traffic light!
Just like I've seen in
National Geographic!
[exclaiming]
[shutter clicking]
[laughing]
I hope I'm not tempting fate
by saying this out loud,
but my very first holiday
is off to a perfect start!
-[alarm ringing]
-[women shrieking]
Uh-oh, those nice women are in trouble!
Hitchhikers!
Hop in!
Where you headed?
-Hello--
-Drive, pip-squeak.
Oh, my gosh!
Time is of the essence, Daddy-o.
Put the pedal to the metal!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my--
Ow!
Floor it, worm!
-Hey!
-[tires squealing]
Watch where you're going, maniac!
[siren blaring]
Why are the cops after us?
Are you guys witches?
Never ask a wimp to do a lady's job.
-Ooh!
-Faster, granny!
-[engine revving]
-[screaming]
Please, don't make me
wreck Little Connie!
[all exclaiming]
This is one moving violation
after another!
Ladies, hold on to your switchblades!
[tires squealing]
[all screaming]
[driver] Congrats, twerp.
You're a criminal.
[muffled speech]
We just fed you.
Listen, ladies, it's been real
and it's been fun.
But has it been real fun? Mmm-mmm.
Nope.
Come on, let me go.
I gotta get to New York City,
to my friend's birthday party.
I don't care if your friend
is the Queen of England
and she's throwing her
100th birthday party
in the Statue of Liberty's underpants!
You're not leaving this motel room.
Hey, Pepper.
He seems okay.
Maybe we can trust him.
No way!
He'll go and squeal to the cops.
-But I--
-Pipe down, squirrel!
My name's not Squirrel.
It's Pee-wee.
[both laughing]
What's so funny?
We never introduced ourselves.
I'm Pepper.
Freckles.
My name's Bella. Nickname...
Pee-wee.
Your name's Pee-wee?
Yeah, Pee-wee.
I've never met another one.
Me neither.
Uh... Pee-wee and Pee-wee.
Touching.
Gets me right here.
-[giggling]
-Can someone get me a tissue?
[knocking at door]
Police! We have you surrounded!
Open up!
Oh, thank goodness you're here, officers!
Ladies, you're under arrest.
Mmm-hmm.
For being too hot!
Fooled ya, girls!
I got these hunks out of the yellow pages.
Pillow fight!
[rock music]
[tires squealing in distance]
[Bella] "Pee-wee,
we will always have our name.
This is for you.
-Sincerely, Pee-wee."
-[gasps]
Great, Little Connie's gone.
Perfect!
It's all good.
No worries.
-Same difference!
-Pardon me.
Sir?
Everything okay?
My car's been stolen.
[exhales] That's terrible.
Well...
I'm heading east.
Need a lift?
You are a life-saver!
[both laughing]
I'm no hero.
Just a traveling salesman. [chuckles]
-Hey, don't forget your coffee.
-Mmm-hmm.
I...
I thought you might say that.
-Ah!
-[both laughing]
Magnet!
Good one! You got me!
One of my top sellers.
Oh!
And...
got this bag of groceries.
-[both laughing]
-Come on, let's hit the road.
Right on.
[vocalizing]
There's a bag of groceries on your roof!
[laughing]
[Pee-wee] Gotcha!
[both laughing]
Bingo.
Ew! Snake farm, yuck.
Ugh, I hate snakes.
One of the area's
most popular attractions!
And, it just so happens, our next stop.
I supply their gift shop. [chuckles]
These...
are what I call "the classics."
-The big-sellers.
-[gasps]
You're looking at some of the most
sought-after retail items in the world.
-[chuckles]
-Please do not touch the merchandise,
however tempted you may be.
-I won't, I promise.
-Okay.
-Hey, what's that over there?
-Hmm?
[rustling]
I think that's a...
-tumbleweed.
-Oh!
-Forgot that word.
-[both laughing]
Ooh, pecan logs.
-Mmm!
-[laughing]
Here.
A solar-powered calculator
the size of a business card.
-[gasps]
-Complimentary.
Ooh, thanks.
Want anything else?
I'm feeling generous.
Top Secret Disguise Kit?
Wise choice!
It's yours.
You never know when
you're gonna need one of those.
-[speaking Spanish]
-[laughs]
[speaking Spanish]
Ah, they sell themselves.
Ew! Snake farm.
Yuck. Ugh!
Have I mentioned I hate snakes?
Ah, Pee-wee.
[speaking Spanish]
[laughing]
[muttering in Spanish]
[screaming]
Blech!
Yuck.
Ugh!
-I think I'll just wait out here.
-[laughs]
Come on.
By the time we leave this place,
I bet you'll be a snake lover, Pee-wee.
Bet me!
Come on.
Baby rattlers are the most dangerous,
because their venom is the strongest.
-That's stupid.
-[laughs]
Come on, I can't wait
for you to see this place.
They got a snake in here
as big as that bus.
Clay and Jimmy, behold the Cuatro Fuego.
Light four flames at the same time.
-[exclaiming]
-[laughing]
What do you think, honey?
We'll take four boxes.
-Deal.
[both laughing]
Lame.
Yawn.
Stupid.
It was a pleasure doing
business with you, as always.
How you liking the Snake Farm, Pee-wee?
I thought it would be a little scarier.
You want scary, huh?
If you're really looking to see
something scary...
who's he gotta see, Jimmy?
The Monster.
That is, if you're brave enough.
I think I could handle it.
Well, let's go.
You'll have to sign this release form
before you go in.
We take no responsibility
for any damage that occurs to you,
physically or mentally.
Including death.
Now, initial here.
Here.
And here.
Here and here.
Here.
And here.
Here. Oh, oh, oh...
I forgot this. Here.
And here.
Okay, I'm ready.
-Let's go, let's get this over with.
-Okay, be my guest.
[door creaking]
[gasps]
[sighs]
That's it?
Rip-off.
[hissing]
[high-pitched screaming]
[screaming continues]
[shuddering] Uh-oh.
Getting dark.
[distant wolf howling]
Sure would be nice
to see some sort of sign of civilizat--
[gasps] Jackpot! [chuckles]
Hello, there.
Sorry, I don't mean to trespass.
Trespass? [chuckles]
No such thing in the heartland, stranger.
They call me Farmer Brown.
They call me Pee-wee Herman.
Pleased to meet you.
What brings you to my farm, Pee-wee?
Well--
Say no more.
You've got yourself a place to stay.
Thanks, Mr. Br...
I mean, Farmer Brown. [chuckles]
[Pee-wee humming]
-Hungry, by any chance?
-Ooh, I'm starving.
Pee-wee, meet my daughters.
[chuckles]
Meatloaf?
I'm Linda. Freckled and furious.
-Howdy.
-[Linda giggles]
Ambrosia salad.
Louise. Perky and fun.
Tomato soup.
Donna. Gregarious and wily.
Mmm.
Green bean casserole.
Diane. Petite and polite.
Mmm.
Waxed beans.
Janice. Tall and studious.
The way she said "waxed." [chuckles]
Mashed potatoes.
Betty. Smart and coy.
-That looks delicious.
-[Betty giggles]
Biscuits and gravy.
Pam. Thrifty and thoughtful.
Yum.
Melon balls.
Judy. Tan and demure.
Pigs-in-a-blanket.
Peggy. Athletic and peppy.
[both exclaim]
That's it? Just nine?
[both laughing]
Uh, where should I sit?
[all] By me.
Slow down, girls.
Pee-wee'll sit next to me.
[all groaning] Aw!
Would you like to say a few words,
Pee-wee?
Oh, sure.
Uh...
Encyclopedia...
pimple...
and hairball.
Amen.
[all] Amen.
Mmm.
Dinner sure was delicious, girls.
[all] Thank you, Pee-wee.
[all giggling]
Ladies, it's getting late.
Bedtime.
[all groaning] Aw!
They are my prized jewels, Pee-wee.
You are a lucky man, Farmer Brown.
[yawns]
-I better be hittin' the hay.
-Just one thing, Pee-wee.
[shouting] Stay away
from my daughters tonight!
I will.
I really will.
[knock on door]
[whispering] Milk and cookies?
[whispering] I'm kind of still full
from dinner, but thanks.
[knock on door]
Can I come in?
I have extra blankets.
It's 80 degrees in here.
-Is that a yes?
-No.
But thanks.
[knock on door]
[giggling]
Remember me? Linda? I've got blankets.
[whispers] I'm saving myself for marriage.
Let me in!
-I wanna snuggle!
-I promised your dad, no.
[tapping on window]
-Catch me!
-No.
What are you doing here?
I was here first.
-Hi, Pee-wee.
-[tree branch creaking]
-[both screaming]
-[thud]
Boo!
-[screams]
-[giggling]
-[Pee-wee exclaims]
-[gasps]
-Why, hello.
Fancy meeting you here.
What up?
-[screams]
-[thud]
[snoring]
[speaking Spanish]
[laughing]
[Farmer Brown mimicking rooster]
[mimicking rooster]
Rise and shine.
Well, come on.
I got a surprise.
[all] Good morning, Pee-wee.
[all giggling]
Excuse me, where are we going?
Oh, that's the surprise.
To the wedding chapel where my daughter
is getting married today.
Oh, congratulations.
Who's your lucky new son-in-law?
Well, he's riding in the truck with me.
I don't see him.
It's you.
[both laughing]
-[door rattling]
-[grunting]
All the girls sure like you.
Every one of 'em.
You know, all breakfast,
it was "Pee-wee-this" and "Pee-wee-that."
Which one of 'em
are you thinkin' about marryin'?
What about Pam?
She's great at impressions.
-Gee, I don't--
-Did you know Judy is a flautist?
And don't get Linda started on submarines.
[chuckles]
So, well, who's it gonna be?
Geez Louise.
Louise!
Congratulations, he picked you!
[all exclaiming]
Yahoo! I'm getting married!
Louise!
[door rattling]
[organ music playing]
[minister] We're gathered here today
to honor the deep love
between these two soul mates.
Louise Bobbie J. Brown,
do you take Pee-wee Aloysius Herman
to be your lawful wedded husband?
I do.
[girls giggling]
And Pee-wee Aloysius Herman,
do you take Louise Bobbie James Brown
to be your lawful wedded wife?
I...
[chuckles] I...
Uh... I...
[gun cocking]
What?
Oh, I hear nature calling.
I've gotta use the restroom.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me, won't you? [chuckles]
Drat!
[gasps]
Well, howdy, cowboy.
Howdy, partners.
Excuse the intrusion
to this most joyous occasion.
Hey, Peanut, you think these two kids
are made for each other?
-Nay!
-[girls giggling]
[Pee-wee] All right, then.
Well, then, let's get going.
[kissing]
Come on, girl.
Have a good day, cowboy.
[Pee-wee chuckles]
[Pee-wee laughing]
[chuckling]
[horn honking]
Ooh, ooh! Look at you.
You? You're coming with us.
-This your lucky day.
-[Pee-wee] Ooh!
[all laughing]
Right, and that's how we three met.
Best friends since beauty school.
That's a lot of hairdos ago.
-Okay.
-You tell him.
What about you, Wanda?
How'd you get involved?
I had the bus.
[all laughing]
And look at us all now.
Four friends on our way to represent
Freewheelin' Hair Mobile Salon
-at the National Hair Competition.
-[exclaims]
And if we win, we get to go to
the International Hair Competition.
-What do you mean "if"?
-Well, I mean--
-Wanda, pull over.
-Pulling over.
Demo.
My friends, let's show Pee-wee
what's definitely gonna make us win.
[Pee-wee] Ooh, wow!
Hairy. Whoa! [chuckles]
Big.
Who doesn't like giant hair?
You haven't even heard our theme.
[all] Patriotism.
[gasps]
The United States of America.
Wow!
It's way bigger than I thought.
I'm not gonna make it.
The party's in two days.
Look where I am.
Look where I need to be.
I won't get there in time.
What's wrong, baby?
I might as well give up
and go back to Fairville.
My friend won't even notice
I'm not at his party.
Oh, I bet he will.
I would notice if Brook or Lane or Wanda
didn't show up to my party.
[Brook] Pee-wee,
the hair-spray that holds
Freewheelin' Hair together,
upright and pert,
is our friendship.
We endorse friendship.
[all] To friendship.
Come on.
[all giggling]
Thanks, you guys.
I just know that you're gonna make it
to New York City
in time for your friend's party, Pee-wee.
I can feel it.
[Wanda chuckling]
And you know what, Pee-wee?
You are going to look fabulous.
Ooh... Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Ooh, probably.
Ooh, ooh, I think I probably know, too.
[all] Makeover!
[all laughing]
[Wanda] We're here, girl.
We're actually here.
[both laughing]
[Pee-wee] Here I come!
[all cheering]
[exclaiming]
Helicopter-y.
[all laughing]
Have fun at the party, Pee-wee.
Hey, good luck in the contest.
I really hope you guys win.
-Aw!
-Thank you.
And thanks for the makeover!
[all exclaiming]
[all] Mwuah!
-Bye, Pee-wee.
Good luck.
[woman] How much longer
do I have to wait for my car?
I'm in the prime of my life here.
You!
Why don't you take a picture?
It'll last longer.
[shutter clicking]
Come over here.
Is that helicopter on your head
operational?
[device beeps]
[whirring]
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
Ooh, dog-do.
[both laughing]
You're funny!
Amusing.
Bet you'll get a kick out of this.
Easy there, sport.
There's only four of these babies
in existence.
Here.
Whoo!
-[whirring]
-Whoa!
-What is this thing?
-[engine starts]
It's a flying car, darling.
I'm flying her back to New York City.
That's where I'm going.
I knew you weren't from here.
You stick out.
You've got cosmopolitan
written all over you.
[chuckles]
Unless you object to being in Manhattan
in five hours...
-[gasps]
-...be my co-pilot.
-Get in!
-Yes, ma'am!
Ooh! [laughs]
[Pee-wee exclaiming]
[barking]
Oh, breathtaking view, is it not?
Welcome to the skies.
The name's Penny King.
Pee-wee Herman. [chuckles]
How'd you get your hands on a flying car,
Miss King?
I'm the heiress
to the King Doorbell fortune.
Every time you ring, I hear ka-ching.
[chuckles]
Do you live in Manhattan?
Oh, this will be my first visit.
Fascinating.
Tell me everything.
Well, I'm out on the road.
So I could live a little.
Live a little?
I say live a lot.
Live it up.
People like us crave fun and excitement.
Which do you prefer,
salted or honey roasted?
Oh, I don't know.
I can't decide.
Well, why decide, baby?
Take 'em both.
-Sandwich?
-Oh.
Ooh! [chuckles]
[laughing]
[laughing] Pee-wee!
You're eating the garnish.
I never thought of that.
You're a trendsetter.
[laughing]
[alarm buzzing]
Engine failure.
That can't be good, right?
-Oh, don't sweat it, kid.
-[high-pitched screaming]
Here.
Au revoir, Pee-wee.
[gasps]
C'est la vie! Live it up!
[screaming]
[laughing]
[gasps] It's all good.
It's all good!
It's all good.
It's not all good.
[screaming]
[speaking Spanish]
[laughing]
Welcome back to life.
[grunting]
They call me Grizzly Bear Daniels.
They call me Pee-wee Herman.
[chuckles] Where are we?
The woods.
In the mountains.
I gotta be on my way.
-How do you get out of here?
-You don't!
Not without a seasoned guide.
Someone who knows these woods
like the back of their weathered hand.
Someone who's lived with nature
since they decided to live alone,
off the grid as a hermit,
and leave the dog-eat-dog world
of certified public accounting.
Is it you you're talking about?
[laughing]
[chuckling nervously]
[sighs]
Come on.
Follow me.
I'm your only way out.
Where are we going? It seems
like we're going deeper into the woods.
[laughing]
-[rustling]
-[gasps] What was that?
Bigfoot!
Nah, I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
What do you think,
I'm a crazy man living in the woods?
I don't know.
Are you?
[laughing]
[snorts]
Welcome to my cave.
"Cave"?
Did you say "cave"?
Oh, my. [chuckles nervously]
What a beautiful abode.
Rustic.
Who's your decorator?
Davy Crockett?
Well, listen,
I love what you've done with it.
I simply love it!
[chuckles]
So, I'm gonna let you let me run, okay?
-You just got here.
-[exclaims]
Sit it.
Don't move a muscle.
I'm gonna slip into something
a little more comfortable.
[Grizzly Bear Daniels over PA]
Please welcome Grizzly Bear Daniels!
♪ Dad, Dad
Why didn't you love me? ♪
♪ I said, Dad, Dad
Why don't you hug me? ♪
♪ You told me I don't know how to behave ♪
♪ And then I found myself
Living in a cave ♪
♪ I said, Dad, Dad
Why didn't you love me? ♪
Why don't you hug me? ♪
[high-pitched screaming]
[distant screaming]
[screaming continues]
Where we headed?
Our village is two miles away.
We'll be there in five hours.
What's up with you guys?
Abe, Ezekiel, you time traveling?
No, no.
We are Amish.
-Gesundheit.
-No, Amish.
Gesundheit.
[Ezekiel] No, Amish.
[Pee-wee] Gesundheit!
[Ezekiel] No, no. Amish.
[Pee-wee] Gesundheit.
[Ezekiel] No, no...
[Ezekiel] We Amish people
live a simple life.
[Pee-wee] Gesundheit.
With no reliance on modern technology.
-Wow! You don't even have cars?
-Nope.
-What about lawn mowers?
-No.
Manual only.
-How about hair dryers?
-Nope.
-How do you dry your hair?
-The wind.
-Air.
-Oh.
-How about electric butter churns?
-No.
We churn by hand.
Stop it! Shut up! [chuckles]
Whoa!
Wow!
Cool village.
Amish-y.
So, Abe, Zeke, what do you guys
do for fun around here?
-We work.
-Yeah.
Whoa, slow down.
Hold on there.
What do you like to do for fu-un?
Uh... Oh, check this one out.
[blowing]
[chuckles]
[squeaking]
[all cheering]
[Pee-wee] Yay! Yay! Thank you!
Thank you.
[balloons squeaking]
My goodness,
there's not been this much excitement
since Yoder's horse learned how to count.
You know, being here with all of you,
I feel something.
Peace.
Serenity.
I feel at home here with all you Amishes.
Oh, that's wonderful, Brother Pee-wee.
Now, I'd like to introduce you
to some other guests
-we're having dinner with tonight.
-Oh.
Ruth, Miriam, Orpah,
I would like you to meet Pee-wee Herman.
Wait a minute.
These women are-- Ow!
Out-of-towners.
That's right.
We're out-of-towners.
No, they're-- Ow!
Owl hunters.
It's our hobby.
No, these women are--
[shouting] Fudge!
Fudge makers.
From way back.
They're from an Amish village in...
Oh, where did you say it was?
-Las Vegas.
-[Abe chuckling] Yes.
[Pee-wee] Interesting.
I've never heard of an Amish community
in Las Vegas.
Wow! I love this scrapple!
I'm digging this corn soup! Mmm!
This bologna and chow-chow
is worth the price of admission.
So, Brother Pee-wee,
will you be spending the night here?
Well, I guess I could leave
early in the morning for New York.
We can take you into the city
on horse and buggy tomorrow morning.
If they have a horse and buggy
tomorrow morning.
Time for bed.
But it's 6:00 p.m.
We should've been in bed an hour ago.
[Ezekiel] We need to go to bed, everybody.
[Freckles] Shut up.
[Bella] You shut up.
[Pepper] Both of you, shut up.
[door creaking]
Fancy meeting you here.
I don't know what you got
up your sleeve, kid,
but if I were you, I'd get off that buggy.
No.
You kidnapped me, stole my car,
and left me tied to a chair.
I should be calling the police.
[laughs] Amish don't have police,
or phones.
Pee-wee,
I beg you, please don't blow our cover.
Me, Pepper, and Frecks will drop you
in New York City on our way to Canada.
Why would I go anywhere with you?
You and your friends
are nothing but trouble.
Now you're stealing
their horse and buggy?
What is wrong with you guys?
Don't you care about anything?
You know what?
You're right.
And when you're right, you're right.
[snaps]
"Dear the Amish...
Sorry, we are stealing
your horse and buggy,
but [sighs] we are leaving you
enough dough
to buy a fleet of horses and buggies."
You happy, wimp?
Come on!
What's it gonna be, Herman?
You joining us or not?
Pee-wee.
It's your big holiday.
[softly] Come on.
What are we waiting for?
I was wrong about you, kid.
Freckles, saddle up the hay-burner.
Pee-wee?
-[both] Yeah?
-Herman.
Hop up here in front.
Take the reins.
Giddyup.
[horses neighing]
-Yee-haw! Yee-haw!
-[laughing]
[horns honking]
Ladies, it's been real and it's been fun.
And it's been real fun.
Grab Manhattan by the horns, dude.
[chuckles]
You're badass, Herman.
You got my respect, rebel.
Thanks.
[inhales]
-I--
-Here.
No, keep it.
It's yours.
It's got your name on it.
Pee-wee's your name, too.
It's our name.
Four days ago, you were the guy
who was going to New York.
And look at you now.
Here you are.
You made it, baby.
[chuckles]
Arrivederci, Pee-wee.
[exhales]
-[Freckles gasps]
-[Bella chuckles]
[voice breaking] Can someone
get me a tissue?
-No, I mean it.
-Oh...
-Bye, Pee-wee.
-Bye.
Have fun.
[sirens blaring]
[officer] Step out with your hands up!
[Pepper] Damn it.
[Freckles] You'll never catch me, copper!
[officer] Hey, stay right there.
-Hey, come back here!
-[Bella] No.
I am not going back to the...
[Bella] No.
[Pee-wee] Ow!
[gasps]
Howdy, New York.
♪ New York, New York ♪
[choir singing]
♪ You high and mighty, bright and shiny
Fabulous place ♪
♪ New York ♪
♪ New York, New York ♪
♪ You busy-dizzy, razzle-dazzle
Scandalous place ♪
♪ New York ♪
♪ Hello, New York
New York, New York ♪
-[man] Hey! Watch where you're going!
-[chuckles]
♪ I'll watch where I'm going
In New York ♪
♪ New York, New York ♪
Ooh! [gasps]
♪ The Empire State Building
Wow, it's tall ♪
[choir singing]
♪ The tallest building in the world ♪
♪ The many bridges
They feed the city ♪
[choir singing] ♪ Boats and planes
Tunnels and trains ♪
[alarm beeping]
[gasps]
It's birthday party time!
♪ Madison Square Garden ♪
♪ It isn't square
And it isn't a garden ♪
[choir singing] ♪ Pee-wee, you're right
It's misleading ♪
♪ Grand Central Station
The city's train hub ♪
♪ Choo-choo ♪
Hello.
Hi, how's it goin'?
Where are you off to?
[choir singing]
♪ Choo-choo, Choo-choo ♪
♪ Africa, Antarctica
Asia, Australia ♪
♪ Europe and the Americas ♪
♪ The United Nations
The hope for our future ♪
[choir singing] ♪ World Peace
The choice is ours ♪
♪ Let's make it happen ♪
♪ I'm riding the subway
Beneath the city ♪
It's underground!
Hey, is this going uptown?
[chuckles]
♪ I'm in the shower
Getting clean ♪
Happy birthday, Joe!
[grunting]
♪ I never had pizza ♪
-One slice, please.
-One slice.
Mmm!
♪ Pizza's delicious
I never knew ♪
I feel alive!
[choir] Mmm, pizza!
♪ The Statue of Liberty
Liberty ♪
[choir singing] ♪ The Statue of France
It rhymes with underpants ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
[yelling]
♪ Times Square ♪
♪ Way to go, Pee-wee
You made it, dude ♪
Happy birthday, Joe!
It's Joe's birthday. [screaming]
[choir singing]
♪ Happy birthday, Joe ♪
♪ Armani or Alfani ♪
♪ I'm inside a taxi
I'm on my way ♪
I'm on my way!
[laughs]
♪ Central Park
I'm almost there ♪
I'm almost there.
♪ This is it
I'm finally here ♪
I'm finally here.
[choir singing] ♪ It's party-time
A night you won't forget ♪
[choir] Look out!
[screaming]
[thud]
Oh, my gosh.
I'm gonna miss Joe's party.
Help!
Help! Somebody, help! Help!
Help! Somebody, help!
And now for another
one of Joe's favorites!
[dance music playing]
Have you guys tried this Oreo salad?
I give it a ten.
I love these pickle wheels.
I'm obsessed with this cookie tower.
-Where is the birthday boy?
-Huh.
What could be keeping him
from the party of the century?
Where are you, Pee-wee?
-[knock on door]
-Come in.
Pee-wee's never gonna make it.
It's okay, there's still time.
The party's only been going on
for a couple of hours.
Nah, I know him.
If he was coming, he'd be here already.
[sighs] Why wouldn't he come?
Did I do something wrong, Shelly?
Of course not.
Inviting him to a party cross-country,
I mean, who does that?
I should've known better.
Stupid Joe.
Stupid, stupid Joe.
[softly] I'm gonna let you
have some space.
[door closes]
Pee-wee, where are you?
Well, well, well.
I'm trapped in a well.
Halfway to hell.
I sure hope I don't crack up down here.
Uh-oh! Too late!
[cackling]
Mr. Lincoln, what are you doing here?
I am here to tell you
something very important.
Always eat your vegetables.
I hate vegetables!
Eat those Brussels sprouts!
-[gasps]
-I command you.
I am the President of the United States.
Your Majesty.
Don't you "Your Majesty" me.
Do you happen to know,
has the hamburger train arrived yet?
[sighs] Why don't you look
at the schedule?
-Why don't you?
-[both chuckle]
We suspect that you've stolen
the palace jewels.
Where are they?
Hand them over.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I've never seen those jewels.
Uh-oh.
My last match.
[high-pitched screaming]
Shut up, you little baby!
It doesn't matter
if you make it to the party.
-Joe won't even notice you're not there.
-Yes, he will.
You're a nobody.
From Nowhere-ville.
It's Fairville.
Nobody will notice or care!
Not Joe, not Fairville...
Not nobody.
You'll never get out of here.
[cackling]
Help! Help! Help!
-[in distance] Help!
-Hold on...
-Help!
-Do you hear that?
[cartoon music playing on TV]
I'm here live in Central Park,
where a boy has fallen down a well.
Paramedics have just arrived on the scene.
Due to safety concerns and restrictions,
a rescue team--
Now you're in bed?
It's my party, Shelly.
Your guests are asking where you are.
Some of them have traveled half-way
around the world to be here.
There is only one person that I wanted
to show up to my party and he didn't.
I know that you're upset about Pee-wee,
but why don't you come downstairs,
open some presents?
Venus and Serena are here.
Elton.
No, I'm just gonna stay here.
Okay, I'll tell everyone
that you aren't ready yet.
When he was asked if he needed anything,
the boy requested, quote,
"Root Beer Barrels.
A lot of Root Beer Barrels, please."
-And a search is underway...
-Root Beer Barrels?
...at this very moment,
for those Root Beer Barrels.
Reporting live from Central Park,
I'm Julie Andrews.
Central Park!
-[helicopter whirring]
-[sirens blaring]
Hold on, Pee-wee.
Joe Manganiello to your rescue.
[whirring]
May my hand be steady.
Bull's-eye.
Here I come, Pee-wee!
Captain Jones.
Good evening.
Joe Manganiello?
-What are you--
-The boy trapped down the well.
What's his name?
Well, Mr. Manganiello,
I can't give that information.
Captain... is his name Pee-wee Herman?
Well, yeah.
Yes, it is.
How'd you know?
He's my friend.
-Now, what's the plan on getting him out?
-Well...
And we have just received the name
of the boy who fell down the well,
Pee-wee Herman.
Shut up, everybody!
We know this guy.
Turn up the volume, Tugboat!
Pee-wee?
You know Pee-wee?
Quiet down, everybody!
Pee-wee's in trouble.
Pee-wee!
Joe!
Welcome to New York.
Happy birthday, Joe.
I fell down a well.
Yeah, I heard.
How are things going down there?
Great! Really good.
I'll be right up!
-[chuckles]
-Actually, Pee-wee,
I was just informed that,
for safety reasons...
they won't be able to get you
out of this well for another two days.
Oh...
So, I guess I'll be...
Missing my party, yeah.
[sobbing]
I did everything you said, Joe!
I broke rules, I broke hearts.
I lived a little.
I wanted to find out who I was.
Well, I found out, all right!
I'm a stupid little baby
crying at the bottom of this crappy well!
[sobbing]
Come on, Pee-wee.
You can do it.
They'll get you out, sport.
You probably didn't even notice
I wasn't at your party!
Are you kidding?
Pee-wee, can I tell you something?
Ten minutes ago,
I was bawling my eyes out.
You were? Why?
Because...
I thought you weren't coming to my party.
[sniffles] Really?
Mmm-hmm.
[sobbing]
I'm getting you out of here, Pee-wee.
Just hang on.
I'll be right back.
-Captain...
-Yeah.
I can't wait two days.
I need Pee-wee out of that well now.
No, it's too dangerous.
Gotta make sure the well
doesn't collapse on him.
Collapse on him?
Darn it, Captain, how could
something like this even happen?
Why wasn't there something
covering the well?
You're right, Mr. Manganiello.
That's the problem.
This metal plate should've
been covering the well.
Metal plate?
Wait...
I've got it.
-Heads up, Pee-wee!
-[gasps]
-[metal clinking]
-Ow!
[grunting]
[straining]
[Joe] Hold on, Pee-wee.
My God!
-Come on.
-Just a little further!
-[Pee-wee] My brain!
[groaning]
I gotcha!
[all gasping]
[whispers] Pee-wee!
[straining] Come on!
-Joe!
-Pee-wee!
Happy birthday!
The boy in the well is free!
[all cheering]
What do you say we get to my party?
What party?
[both laughing]
Wait, I thought you lived
in the penthouse.
Oh, I do.
Aren't we going to your party?
Pee-wee, we are the party.
[elevator bell dings]
[gasps] Holy fudge!
-A giant miniature world!
-[Joe] Yep!
A giant miniature world.
I made it all myself.
From my imagination.
[Pee-wee] Dinosaur world!
-Cool volcano!
-[Joe] That lava's cotton candy.
Hey, you and I hit it off
the minute we met, remember?
[chuckles]
You inspired me.
This is Glitter Mountain. Look!
I covered it with pixies.
[train horn tooting]
-[gasps]
-Oh, hey, looky here.
Wow! You even have Fairville!
Dan's Diner.
The town square.
[gasps] My house!
[gasps] Look, a miniature of my miniature!
I knew you'd notice that. [chuckles]
And... the best part.
[gasps]
My tree house!
Look, Joe.
I made this present for you.
Happy birthday.
A friendship bracelet.
Right.
And look.
[chuckles] It's just like mine!
-Yeah!
-[both laughing]
-You know what would make this perfect?
-Yep.
Boop!
-[both] To friendship.
-[clinks]
[both] Ah!
[both laughing]
Here you go, fellas.
-Thanks, Bev. Yum!
-Thanks, Bev.
What's this stuff on my plate?
Look, it's on my plate, too.
Let's ask the chef.
Hey, Pee-wee!
Yes, Beverly?
What is this on these gentlemen's plates?
-Fish sticks.
-No, there.
-Oh. You mean the garnish.
-Garnish?
Yes, garnish.
A decoration or embellishment
of a prepared food-plate or drink
to augment the visual impact on the plate.
Can you eat it?
My garnish tastes like an orange.
It is an orange.
[Beverly] Yes, your meal
will come with garnish.
Welcome back, Pee-wee!
I can't put my finger on it, but there's
something different about you.
[Emily] He's worldly now.
Right, Pee-wee?
[Renegades] Pee-wee!
Pee-wee, why don't you stop by
and jam with us tonight?
Why don't you?
-This adding machine... hmm?
-Dan, check this out.
Solar-powered calculator.
Solar?
Yep, from the Latin, solaris,
meaning, "Derives its power
from the sun or sol."
Hmm?
[chuckles] It works!
And this thing is just the size
of a business card!
Ain't that a miracle?
[chuckles]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[Pee-wee exclaims]
[Pee-wee laughs]
[Pee-wee chuckles]