-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Well, let's see.
Last week, we saw the end
to Makoto and Minori's relationship.
But the next time we decide to hang out...
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
...it's not intended to mean
I'm responding to your feelings toward me.
Minori clearly told him
she wasn't interested.
-She was very clear.
-As to why?
Minori and Tatsuya's relationship
is making steady progress.
And they made plans to see each other
at their favorite places.
-That's right, and we'll get to see that.
-We will.
At Girls Award.
And the memorable scene
when Tatsuya gave Minori a head massage.
The head massage is like
foreplay in India.
Powerful words.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
-It was a sexy scene.
-It made for a good picture.
-That was really nice.
-And she made pasta to thank him.
-The two of them are set already.
-They sure are.
Yuriko said she can't forget her ex.
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
TADAMICHI KAWANO, 25 YEARS OLD
Before exams, we always tried
to focus on our own studies.
At least while we were together.
I know you're looking for an answer,
but I'd rather you concentrate
on your studies as a med student now.
After I get through exams...
will I be able to get an answer?
I think I'd like to
give you an answer then.
I understand.
What an amazing guy.
Just like these gentlemen.
-Oh, guys who wear sweaters like this?
-A very serious sweater.
Yamasato and I were inspired by the ex.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We wanted to at least give
the impression of a good guy.
-It's nice.
-But your mouth...
Yes, a little too spicy perhaps.
Thought I'd add some sweetness.
-It's very sweet.
-Thank you.
-And...
-What?
-Makoto...
-Makoto will be leaving.
Yes, so he said
at the end of last episode.
The league matches end on October 18th.
I told you before, right?
And when it's over...
-I'm thinking of moving out.
-For real?
Well, maybe now...
What was that?
Is the sweater restraining you?
This sweater keeps my mouth shut.
Hi, I'm looking forward to
working with you.
Come this way please.
-Watch your step.
-This way.
MS. SEINA SHIMABUKURO
-Good morning.
Hello. I'm ready.
SEINA SHIMABUKURO,
28 YEARS OLD, MODEL
Oh, are you the one from Terrace House?
I'm Uchihara.
It's nice to meet you.
Is it all right to ask
how things are going?
It's fine.
I made my feelings clear to her.
-Really?
-I'm waiting for her response.
-Oh, you're already at that point.
-Yes, at that point.
-Waiting for her answer.
-I see.
-I am going to take her to dinner.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Seina Shimabukuro.
-I'm Minori Takada.
I watch Terrace House.
-Sit here, Minori.
-Over here?
Is it fun at Terrace House?
It... is.
Are you in love?
Maybe I am?
-He confessed his feelings to you, right?
-I think so.
-He kind of told me.
-"Kind of"?
-It wasn't a complete confession.
-Not completely?
-He said it was.
-What?
He's right there,
so this is a little embarrassing.
-It wasn't totally clear at all.
-Are you serious?
I don't think you guys
are quite on the same page.
-Yeah, maybe not.
-But you're living together, so...
maybe you need to discuss it.
But we're planning to go
for dinner after all this.
So we'll probably talk about it then.
-You're not turning him down, right?
-No.
Yay!
Tatsuya's going to be so happy.
-I'm so embarrassed.
-I see.
I'm going to spray your hair.
Hey.
So I heard from Minori.
What is it?
Are you about to drop a bomb?
No, no, Minori was saying
she wasn't sure about your feelings.
-Really?
-Yeah.
For real?
You asked her right?
I told her she didn't have to
give me an answer at that moment.
Oh, so not at that moment.
I told her she didn't need
to answer right then.
I'll tell her more clearly next time.
-Yeah.
-I didn't try hard enough.
Yeah, you need to push harder.
You need to be confident.
-Thanks for the advice.
-Oh, of course.
I'll be clearer next time.
Yeah, but when I asked
if she'd turn you down, she said no.
-Great!
-Good luck.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Looks good.
Beautiful.
-Thank you.
-Good luck.
I'm exhausted.
-Good work today.
-Thank you.
-It was good.
-Too stiff?
You were, but it was good.
You were cute.
Thank you.
-The smile at the end...
-What?
Your smile at the end was beautiful.
-Was it on?
-Yes.
-But you seem exhausted now.
-I am.
You can relax when you get home.
You can eat, right?
I want tasty food.
Let's go eat soon.
-Yes, please.
-Dinner?
Dinner.
I'm glad, though.
You might get more jobs after this.
I really hope so.
My other job is about to end.
-Let's do our best.
-I will.
"Thank You Everyone" PARTY
Everyone sitting?
-Good work!
-Cheers!
The best part was
when Minori smiled at the end.
-Yeah, it was cute.
-Yeah.
-It was super cute.
-Thank you.
-Did you see, Uchi?
-Yeah, from the back.
So things have settled down for everyone
except for Yuriko?
When do exams start?
-Day after tomorrow.
-Wow, that's soon.
What kind of test is it?
If I pass, I get to move on.
If I fail, I have to repeat the year.
-Are you ready?
-I think so.
Did I tell everyone
that baseball ended yesterday?
-Yesterday?
-Yesterday.
-Way to go.
-The end of college baseball for me.
-Good work.
-So you're retired.
So I'm leaving Terrace House tomorrow.
-What?
I'm leaving.
He told us this already.
-Tomorrow morning.
-Tomorrow morning?
He wanted to time it
with the end of the baseball season.
That's why you said
we should all have dinner together today!
That's right.
You could have told us sooner.
It's so sudden!
-I'm leaving.
-For real?
Why'd you whisper that?
-What?
-It's so sad!
I know it's hard to digest,
but it's something Makoto decided.
Right.
Don't get all sad.
Let's keep this fun.
-Let's make it fun!
-Shall we drink?
-To Makocchan's new start.
-Yeah.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you!
Good luck, Makocchan.
I don't know how to send him off.
-Hey, guys.
-Good morning.
-Wow, a lot of stuff.
-Yeah, it's crazy.
Were you able to sleep?
Yeah.
-Thanks for everything.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
I'll miss you guys.
We'll miss you, too.
I've got...
We don't need anything.
-For real?
-What is it?
I wrote each of you a letter.
For Yuriko.
Thank you!
-For Minori and Mizuki.
-Thank you.
-For Yuki Adachi.
-It's so formal of you.
Read it after I leave.
-Thank you.
I think I'll go.
-Get going.
-Okay, let's go.
-To the door?
-Yes, and say goodbye.
-See you later!
-Later!
-Thanks, Makocchan!
-Wait, wait.
-What?
This is a surprise!
For real? From Hawaii?
They've got a wide audition range.
-For real?
-Wow!
Oh, because it's Netflix!
-They service the entire world.
-That's right.
It is a foreign company, after all.
We're country bumpkins in comparison.
Oh, wow, my heart's starting to pound!
Wait a second!
We're so quick to forget
the person who left.
The impact was so huge.
All our attention was pulled that way.
-We should just thank Makoto.
-Thank you.
Well, a lot happened, but he got through.
He was honest and good toward the end.
Well, not quite an honest person.
Oh, his sweater must be on the thin side.
It's actually really uncomfortable.
Can I take it off?
Well, let's hope
he learned something from this.
-He experienced love as well.
-Yes.
But wasn't it a little much,
all those tattoos on his arm?
-I can't wait to see his face!
-Yes, I can't wait.
What'll we do if his face is like Tyson's?
If it's all tattooed up here, too.
How scary would that be?
What does he do?
He's aspiring to be a firefighter.
-So he's a student still?
-Maybe.
He's gonna show up.
We're still in the first half of the show.
I wanna see!
How long are you gonna do that?
This? Until I'm done.
-When will you finish?
-I don't know.
-I have another exam in a month.
-For real?
The doorbell?
Ow!
Wow, that was explosive.
-You're not coming?
-That's fine. You can go.
Let's go.
Yes?
I'm Arman, the new roommate.
-What?
-A new...
Come in.
Here he comes!
-I'm nervous.
-Yeah, me too!
Evening.
-Good evening.
-It's nice to meet you.
Come in, come in.
Can I come in?
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Arman, the new roommate.
Arman, I'm Uchihara.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Minori.
I'm Yuriko.
It's nice to meet you.
-Oh, shoes.
-Oh, yeah!
I'm sorry.
I'm from America.
Oh, I see.
What do you do, Arman?
Me? I work part-time
at a sunglass shop in Hawaii and--
-What kind of shop?
-A sunglass shop.
A sunglass shop?
-What? You're from Hawaii?
-Yes, Hawaii.
-Oh, you're so lucky!
-I came yesterday.
-What?
-Yesterday?
Yes, Hawaii.
I was originally born in Japan.
Wait, you're not half?
You're from--
-I'm half.
-Half Japanese and...
Japanese and Iranian.
-How old are you?
-I'm 24.
You don't look it! 24?
Arman?
It's Arman Bitaraf.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
Most people just pronounce it Aman,
since it's easier.
Aman.
-Is it okay if we say "Aman"?
-Yes, that's fine.
Are you going to stay in Japan?
-That's my plan, to stay as long as I can.
-Oh, I see.
What are you going to do in Japan?
I hope to teach English
while I'm in Japan.
-I'd like to learn English.
-Sure, of course.
-Let's do lessons here.
-Oh, yay!
We can't speak English at all.
I can teach you.
Your Japanese is so good.
Have you lived in Japan before?
I lived here until I was ten,
and then I lived in Hawaii for 15 years,
and then I came back yesterday.
So you can speak three languages?
Japanese--
-I can only speak a little Farsi.
-Oh, it's Farsi.
-So Farsi is spoken in Iran?
-Yes.
Why did you want to come to Terrace House?
-No reason really...
-Nothing specific?
I just wanted to live in Japan.
-You've come to an amazing place.
-Yes, I know.
-There's a pool!
-Really?
You can't go in, though.
It's too cold.
What are your interests?
Interests?
-What are yours?
-My interests?
Surfing, boogie-boarding.
I also kickbox.
-You seem strong.
-Yes, you seem strong.
Can I ask?
-Sure.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-No, I don't.
-That was quick!
How long have you been single?
-For about six months.
-Six months?
-What's your type?
-Well, cute...
and someone who's kind to everyone.
And someone who enjoys
outdoor activities and sports.
For example,
I like hiking really tough trails.
-That's Mizuki!
-I totally thought that!
That's perfect.
The other girl, she's rather active.
And the other guy, if he drinks,
he'll talk passionately about his dreams.
Really? Every time?
-Every time.
-That could be a little tiring.
A little.
He already knows.
It's not what I thought.
This'll be your bed.
Sorry, the room's messy.
This is the bed.
Feel free.
It's nice.
-You have a lot of luggage.
-Yeah.
-And it's messy.
-It totally is!
-I'm too lazy to unpack right now.
-You can do it later.
Hey.
-Welcome back. Our new member.
-New member?
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you. I'm Arman.
Arman? I'm Yuki.
-Nice to meet you.
-He arrived yesterday from Hawaii.
Wow. Your Japanese is so good.
I'm Japanese. Well, half.
I didn't expect someone with tattoos.
Yeah, it's intense. It's cool.
-Yeah, it goes pretty deep.
-Does it?
He can speak English,
so he's planning on teaching here.
-Part-time maybe.
-And he's super athletic.
Kickboxing, surfing, boogie-boarding.
-Totally athletic.
-Yeah, totally.
-Any aspirations for the future?
-The future?
-A firefighter.
-Oh, a firefighter?
-In Hawaii.
-A firefighter in Hawaii?
Yeah, up until I came here,
I was studying to be a firefighter.
He's single.
-Are you both single?
-We're single.
-I'm looking.
-He's looking.
Right now...
I'm pursuing.
-One of the members?
-Yeah.
-Which one?
-The one sitting by me, the model.
I'm in pursuit.
Well, you're free to as well.
-Do your best.
-I will.
Yeah, that would be fine with me.
I think I'll wait for the other girl.
Yeah, I'm sure you want to meet everyone.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
Did you meet him?
He's here?
-He's here.
-I haven't met him!
-What's he like?
-What do you think?
You're smiling.
What kind of guy do you think he is?
I have no idea.
-What's he like?
-He's from Hawaii.
What?
He's half-Iranian and half-Japanese.
-Can he speak Japanese?
-He can.
-Wow.
-Right?
Is he cute?
He's very manly.
-He's got a nice body.
-Yeah, a good body.
Nice! That's nice.
-Dark eyes, tall nose.
-Yeah, tall nose.
-What's with the happy face?
-I like people with tall noses.
That's true.
Strong features.
-Good morning.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm Arman.
-Arman?
I arrived yesterday.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Mizuki.
Good morning.
-Your T-shirt is cute.
-It's from my friend's store.
-I see.
-That's a cute turtleneck.
This? Thank you.
Are you a model?
I work at an office.
-You seem the most like a model.
-Really?
Really? Wow.
So, you're from Hawaii?
That's so nice.
-Do you surf?
-I do.
Nice.
It's so cold.
It is, and I actually don't have
winter clothes.
-I have to go buy some.
-Oh, you have to buy some.
Where will you go?
I'm not sure.
Well, I only know of Uniqlo.
-I'm going to go look.
-Like the Gap?
-Oh, is there a Gap?
-There is.
-What are you going to do today?
-Go on an adventure.
-I still haven't--
-Adventure?
-I'm going to look for a part-time job.
-An exploration?
Do the roommates have parties here?
Yeah, let's have one tonight.
A welcome party.
Oh, a welcome party?
That'll be nice.
I made some rice for breakfast,
but I don't have time to eat,
-so please have some.
-I can have it?
-There's natto. Can you eat natto?
-For real?
-I can have it?
-Yes, the top shelf on the right is mine.
There's some marinated fish as well.
-Got it. I'll have some. Thanks.
-Please do.
-Okay, I'm off.
-Have fun.
-Later.
-See you later.
What a surprise. Arman.
Seems nice.
-You're a big fan already, right, Tri?
-Yes.
-You like him?
He was hitting it off with Mizuki.
He made a good impression
on everyone so far.
Mizuki hasn't had
a chance at love recently.
-They make such a good match.
-They do.
They both acted like they were interested.
It feels like they're each other's types.
And western guys are so good
at giving compliments.
He told her he would've guessed
she was the model.
Or maybe the mistake was on purpose.
He doesn't seem like that kind of person.
It's not a strategy?
I think that walking in with the shoes
and saying he's from America
was totally on purpose.
-It was a nice morning.
-It really was a nice morning!
She complimented him on his shirt,
so he complimented her turtleneck.
If she left, she completely miscalculated
how long it takes to cook rice.
Leave it alone!
-She just meant for anyone to have it.
-That's right.
What's Adachi going to do?
He's all alone.
There are no potential girlfriends
for him.
We don't know what'll happen with Yuriko.
There's no way!
She's already intending
to get back together with her ex.
Well, we don't know that for sure.
They will for sure!
You don't know that for sure.
I think it'll depend on the ex.
He just said he couldn't be back with her
before the exams.
He told her he'd go out with her
after the exams.
That ex may already be going out
with the hospital president's daughter.
-That's right.
-There it is, the drama.
It's possible he's already engaged.
I think we talked about this before.
-That's the drama we want.
-That's right.
10TH WEEK UNAIRED SCENE
So, Yuriko studies hard
to get back with her ex.
But then she spots him
with another woman on the street.
And that woman turns out to be
the daughter of the president
of the hospital where he works.
Oh, no!
He really wants to get back with Yuriko,
but his boss is pressuring him
into marrying his daughter.
"You're not going to make
the wrong choice, are you?"
That's what the boss would say.
Oh, no, what should we do?
Those people don't exist!
He might not be into
getting back together with her.
The ex, that is.
You're saying that if he really liked her,
he should've said he'd be happy
to get together right then.
But he said maybe.
So you feel the presence
of the boss's daughter.
When you put it that way, I can't deny it.
Outside of Yuriko's school,
a red sports car will be parked.
And when Yuriko comes out,
the window will come down,
and she'll say, "Are you Yuriko?"
-The boss's daughter?
-That's right.
Like a young Yuki Amami.
People will suspect there's a script
if that ever happened.
Welcome Arman!
-Should we start?
-Yeah, let's start.
Welcome, Arman.
Cheers!
-It tastes a little off.
-It's a little warm.
Let's drink today.
Thanks, everyone.
-Have you met everyone now?
-I met everyone. This morning.
Mizuki? What did you think?
Mature and cute.
Kind of elegant.
Yeah, she's elegant.
And she likes sports,
so I think we'll get along.
You think your interests match?
I think so.
Oh, she's back.
-Sorry I'm late. I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Wow, pizza.
-How was your quiz?
-I'm done with my quiz.
-You passed?
-I don't know yet.
-How do you feel about it?
-I think I did all right.
-Sorry I'm late! I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-I'm late.
-We should've waited.
Wow, it's like a party.
I brought cookies, so please have some.
-Oh, I love those!
-Thank you.
-Are they that famous?
-I don't know them.
-What did you do today, Arman?
-I went on a little adventure today.
-I walked around.
-That's an adventure?
I walked around Shibuya.
-What about tomorrow?
-I'm going to look for a gym.
-For kickboxing?
-For kickboxing, too.
I heard there were
some good ones in Japan.
I finished exams today.
So I feel like it's a good time
to tell you all...
My ex, his name is Tadamichi,
I met with him and told him
how I felt about him.
-I see.
-What's wrong?
Well, I hadn't heard
what had been happening.
-You guys can figure that out later.
-She said she could tell me anything.
-I'll be quiet now.
-Please let her talk for now.
-Should I be quiet now, Uchi?
-It'd be better if you were.
I hadn't told Yuki this yet,
but I haven't been able
to forget Tadamichi,
and wanted to get back together with him.
But I thought
that staying in Terrace House...
is selfish of me.
So I'm going to tell Tadamichi
how I feel about him again,
and after I tell everyone how it goes...
I'm thinking of leaving.