-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Previously,
-Minori and Tatsuya's relationship...
-That's right!
-...is in an awkward state.
-Awkward.
The show was extended, right?
We hadn't really discussed our plans.
Well, when we talk about it...
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
...it gets really heavy.
It becomes really negative.
It's a difference in thought...
I think.
An issue of mismatched personalities?
Or did something happen
in that Japanese-style room?
Bedroom issues.
Bedroom issues?
You don't know
who to go to for bedroom issues.
Qracian can't help with this.
-They can only help with plumbing issues.
-That's right.
-Bed-cian.
-Bed-cian?
Bed-cian? That's like...
Bedroom problems?
That's like a call girl service.
Come this way, Ayumu.
I apologize for that one.
-And, Arman--
-Arman won his match!
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
We have a unanimous decision.
Hooray!
They made plans to go to Yomiuriland
on a date.
The reason for their date,
"If you win, I'll take you anywhere."
There's probably going to be a kiss
at Yomiuriland.
Wow!
Yomiuriland will be all lit up!
That's right!
-It's that time of year!
-It's really pretty.
-Definitely a kiss, then.
-Yeah, for sure.
I hope she realizes it's just LED.
And Mizuki and Tap left.
-Yes, they left.
-Thank you, guys.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD
And so...
-Oh, yes!
-That's right!
-New members.
-Are coming today?
Are you telling us
if they're coming today?
I can't say yet.
No? That means they're coming.
Yeah, that's definitely yes.
TENGENJI GARDEN CAFE
TENGENJI GARDEN
HIROO, TOKYO
Hey.
KURUMI NAKADA, 23 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, MINORI'S OLDER SISTER
Sorry I'm late.
It's fine.
I thought Uchi would be here.
-I was looking forward to it.
-Why?
"Hi, I'm Minori's boyfriend, Uchihara."
You wanted him to say that?
It would've been funny.
Nothing's changed.
Nothing?
Since you got together?
Nothing's happened?
Like going out?
He doesn't have too much time off.
Any new couples?
-Oh, Mizuki left.
-What?
Mizuki and Yuki left.
Really?
Arisa came, right?
And Arman...
Arisa snatched him?
-So, Mizuki left?
-Yeah.
-Professor Tap, too?
That's tough on Professor Tap.
Nothing happened for him.
Do you decorate in Kagoshima, too?
-What?
-In Kagoshima.
We've never had such a big tree at home.
I'm all tangled.
Did you decorate in Hawaii?
Everyone does,
but I've never done it.
Christmas this year is a little different.
Yeah, it's different.
What did you do last Christmas?
-I had dinner with friends.
-Dinner with friends?
And you?
Right before Christmas,
I broke up with my ex.
That's the worst Christmas.
Yeah.
What are you doing for Christmas
this year?
This year?
I only have plans for the 25th.
Oh, so you're free?
-The 24th.
-You're free on the 24th?
Leave it open, then.
-The 24th?
-Yeah.
Let's go somewhere.
-The amusement park?
-No.
That's Sunday.
-This week?
-This Sunday.
-The 20th?
-Yeah.
I was wondering when we'd go.
Done!
Finished!
-Looks good.
-Yeah.
What a glamorous tree.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
Oh, it's on.
-It's so pretty.
-It's pretty.
It's really pretty.
Congrats!
So, basically,
it's two couples living together.
I don't know what's actually going on
with Arman and Arisa, though.
You mean everyone's just saying that?
That's good, though.
You should just change rooms.
Did you know
there's a Japanese-style room?
-Toward the back?
-Yeah.
They said it can be our room.
What?
-So, we've been sleeping there.
-The two of you?
Does it feel
like you're in a relationship?
-No.
-No? Why?
You're sleeping together.
We live together,
so I know he's coming back.
So, I don't really worry about
what time he's coming home.
Is it just because we live there?
-If we left...
-Most likely.
So, Uchi might ask you to leave with him.
We haven't really discussed that.
-You should talk about it.
-Yeah.
I know, but we kind of argued about it.
-You fought? You fought about it?
-We didn't fight, per se.
"Living here, it's fun,
but we should be doing
something more meaningful."
-That's what he told me.
-Is this an after school activity?
What should be a simple talk turns heavy.
Wonder why?
He's the one who said, "It's soba"
while eating soba.
-It was so simple.
-Yeah.
We'd say, "Cow!" when we saw a cow.
No make-up kisses?
-No.
-No make-up sex?
It's not like that.
Wait, it hasn't happened?
Since going out?
-We have.
-You have? Good.
-I was worried Uchi was still a virgin.
-That was your worry?
Well, you know, sometimes
your fights don't really matter after sex.
Your voice is too loud.
Stop, this is embarrassing!
No?
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
I wanna see Star Wars.
Let's go see it.
Yeah, let's go.
The 22nd?
The 22nd.
I'm off Tuesday.
You can't?
I can.
I'm free the whole day.
No plans.
Even though it's your birthday?
Well, now that Miss Minori has invited me
to Star Wars...
-What are you doing?
-Yo!
Don't "yo" me.
I had lunch with my sister today.
What did she say?
She asked if we're leaving together.
I don't know.
Well...
To be honest, right now,
I do think that this house,
this environment,
makes things convenient for us
to a certain degree.
-I think--
-What do you mean?
How well our relationship is going.
Do you ever think about that?
-You mean if it wasn't like this?
-Yeah.
If we can't see each other so easily.
-We'll eventually leave.
-Yeah, but...
I feel like we'll suddenly be too distant
from each other if we left now.
Maybe it's selfish of me,
but this place works for us.
I understand.
But if you say you want to leave,
I'll go, too.
If you're not here, there's no point.
But if we leave together,
it's like I came to just find a boyfriend.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I don't really want to be seen that way.
I totally came to find a girlfriend.
-That's right!
-I announced that already.
That's right.
We haven't talked like this in a while.
-We don't usually talk so much.
-Yeah, we don't.
We don't talk often.
Usually.
-We both don't talk.
-That's not totally true.
There's no conversation.
All our talks get too serious.
Just look at our past conversations.
I don't find that fun.
I think that's why I tend to clam up.
Well, I think disagreements are important,
but I do want things to stay enjoyable.
You're right, though.
I've been too serious lately.
I'm sorry--
If we can discuss things like this,
I'll be happy.
We'll talk things through
and enjoy our relationship.
If you can understand that,
then I'm happy, and it'll be okay.
-Okay?
-Well, I meant it would make me happy.
-I look forward to the relationship.
-Thank you.
While Arman and Arisa were decorating,
it got a little risqué. From behind...
with the tree.
You mean like this?
Pulling the tree along, too?
He's using his martial arts all wrong.
They're like Minori and Uchi
before they started going out.
If one person admits anything,
it won't stop.
It already seems like it's happening.
Yeah, like when he asked her out
for Christmas.
Like, it was natural.
If you ask someone out for Christmas,
that's saying you like them, right?
I mean, it's a special day.
Asking someone to keep that day open
is like asking for a relationship.
I wouldn't say a relationship,
but that you want to spend time with them.
So, if you're okay with that,
then you're okay
with a relationship, right?
-Well, maybe in this case.
-Yeah.
-And Kurumi's great, isn't she?
-She is.
She's great. So blunt.
Well, it looks like...
they were able to talk.
Was that progress?
It's getting better little by little.
So, if this talk was better than usual,
how boring is their usual, then?
They did say
that normally they don't talk.
Yeah, why would he say that?
Tatsuya just wanted to say
that he didn't want to leave
because he wouldn't be able to see
Minori as often.
-But--
-The way he said it.
Yeah, it's the way he said it.
-He's terrible at it.
-Terrible.
He made it seem like
their relationship was so weak
that it would fall apart
if they left the house.
Like they're only going out
because they're in the same house.
He should've just said he wants to stay
since it's where he can see her the most.
So, he's just a bad communicator.
-He's not the smoothest guy.
-Not at all.
A man can't help it sometimes.
Old man.
Need a soda, old man?
I can't speak of other people.
That's so true.
You're like that, too.
Really? You seem so suave.
Not at all.
I don't talk at all.
Should I take this off?
He really doesn't.
I was yelled at for not talking at all
at a sushi restaurant on Christmas.
I heard about that incident.
It was something.
She said, "Poor me."
-I remember you mentioned this.
-That was my Christmas.
"Even the chef is trying
to liven up. Poor me."
What a line.
The "poor me" fiasco.
Makes my heart ache.
-I wonder how she's doing.
-I wonder.
I passed her on the street once.
Anyways...
let's watch!
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
It's good to see you again.
You haven't been here lately.
-I heard you won.
-I did.
Thank you, thank you.
-Was he strong?
-He was.
DAIKI MIYAGI, 25 YEARS OLD,
ACTOR, TARGET SHIBUYA OWNER
IPPEI SHIMA, 31 YEARS OLD,
COMEDIAN, PART-TIMER
Did everyone come watch
from Terrace House?
Uchi had work and couldn't make it.
I only met up with Arisa.
Everyone else came, though.
That's like you, Daiki.
-What?
-It's your pattern.
-What do you mean?
-You know, at the end--
-The ringside kiss?
-Yeah.
I'm not that cool.
-What happened?
-Something happened?
She asked me out on a date.
There's another match in February.
I'll think about it.
-He's good with the win for now.
-He got the date.
-You've got the date.
-Isn't that all you care about?
More importantly, I have to find a job.
Wanna work as a trainer?
That sounds fun.
I can introduce you, as well.
I can introduce you, too.
-Same place as usual?
-Yeah.
-The Loco Mart in Kamakura.
-The Loco Mart?
-You know it?
-Yes, I saw it.
Oh, yeah.
It's tradition from Tetsu's year.
It's been handed down.
-Gardening, right?
-Yeah, I think it's a good fit for you.
If you want, I'll talk to them.
-Why don't you give that a try first.
-Yeah, I'll give it some thought.
KAMAKURA, KANAGAWA
ONARI STREET
-Hello.
Ippei told me I should come in.
HISATO KOJIMA
OWNER
I heard you're looking for part-time work?
Yes, I'm looking for work.
Well, I told Ippei
I'm okay if he's vouching for you.
Thank you.
Location won't be an issue?
I can, but it does take me an hour
to get here.
What time would I start?
Well, we usually start at 8:00 a.m.
And if the location is Tokyo or Yokohama,
you can meet up with us.
I'm confident in my endurance.
You surf?
I did a little surfing in Hawaii.
-Not in Japan.
-No, not in Japan yet.
I would like to.
-It'd be close here in Kamakura.
-That's true.
And you can start any day?
Yes, I can.
The sooner the better, actually.
It's almost Christmas.
I wanted to make some money for a gift.
-There's a girl I like.
-Is there?
That's nice.
-It's inevitable.
-I suppose so.
At Target's Christmas party.
Will be home late. -Arman & Arisa
Arman?
Are you okay?
I'll leave some water.
He's dead.
-Good morning, Arman.
-Good morning.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-What happened to your eye?
-I don't know. I don't remember.
-I don't think you got in a fight.
-I didn't, right?
Maybe I ran into a door.
I'm sorry if I did anything yesterday.
I don't remember.
Nothing happened.
But you fell asleep in the taxi.
I fell asleep?
-I totally don't remember towards the end.
-Really?
You drank a good amount, too.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Going somewhere?
-I thought we were going to the park.
-Oh, yeah.
What do you mean, "Where am I going?"
-You're early.
-What?
Didn't we say we'd go in the morning?
-Did we?
-We did!
Will we make it?
We will.
It doesn't have to be there.
I'm okay if we go some other day.
No, I'll be fine.
Will you be able to do the rides?
I don't know.
YOMIURILAND
INAGI, TOKYO
-What shall we ride?
-What should we?
-The go-carts--
-I want some ice cream.
You said ice cream earlier, too.
I feel so sick.
I don't think I can ride on anything.
Want to go have ice cream then?
-You want to ride the go-carts?
-I want to.
This is fun! Stop!
-This feels good.
-It does.
Scary?
This is scary!
Wait!
I'm scared!
I said stop!
SKY CYCLE
Is it good?
It's good.
WANDIT
Oh, no.
It's gonna fall.
I'm scared!
I feel nauseated.
I feel like vomiting.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Do you want to use the bathroom?
I think I do.
Sorry about today.
That's okay.
I don't feel well.
I'll never drink again.
-Never? That's impossible.
-Never.
I feel sick.
Should we head back early today?
-Or...
-No.
Let's ride the Ferris wheel
before going home.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
Let's ride it, then.
-Since we're here.
-Yeah.
Excuse me.
-Bathroom?
-Yeah, I'll be a sec.
Sorry for the wait.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Are you sure?
It's so pretty.
It's amazing toward the back.
The greens.
Arisa.
It might be a little crushed, but...
Merry Christmas.
-It's a little early.
-A present?
For me?
-I didn't get you anything.
-Don't worry about it.
Thank you.
-A scarf!
-Yeah. It'll get colder.
-It's warm.
-It looks good.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's warm.
Thank you, Arman.
I'll use it.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-It looks warm.
-It's super warm.
I wasn't expecting a gift at all.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
-It looks good on you.
-Does it?
Arman...
why are you up there?
Yesterday, I came home trashed.
-I threw up on my bed.
-Gross.
-Wasn't it a special day today?
-Yeah, it was.
-So, even though it was special...
-Before Christmas.
We got there,
and I threw up an hour later.
Disgusting.
I threw up a total of five times.
-That's horrible.
-It was.
That's the worst.
Normally, there's a popular image...
of the Ferris wheel kiss when you go,
but I didn't feel romantic at all.
I couldn't say anything romantic.
-The kiss?
-Of course not.
-The worst date ever.
-It really was.
The worst one in my life.
-What are you gonna do? Try again?
-Yeah.
I'm thinking dinner,
then maybe taking her to the Tokyo Tower.
Does that mean you're asking her
to be your girlfriend?
Since you're going for it?
I'll go for something, for sure.
Just the kiss.
What? You're gonna kiss her
before telling her how you feel?
Isn't that normal?
It's totally different from how I think.
Next time.
Today was a total fail.
Don't drink the night before.
-I won't drink anymore.
-Yeah, you shouldn't.
Is Arman okay?
Arman?
Arman looked totally sick.
Well, he was trying really hard.
The roller coaster?
He couldn't do the adult ride.
So, we went on the kid's ride,
but even that was a bad idea.
Arman felt that sick?
That's terrible.
He gave me a Christmas gift.
-What is it? Acne?
-This.
It's from my favorite brand.
-I don't know how he knew.
-Which brand?
-Acne.
-Really? From Acne?
-Wow.
-Right? I didn't have anything for him.
I wasn't thinking of a Christmas gift.
-I see.
-Should I get him something?
-You should.
-I should, right?
I'm glad I got to see him
not trying to impress me.
He was saying he wanted to do it over.
But maybe because I got to see
that side of him,
I feel closer to him.
Really?
I thought you'd be unhappy
since he was hungover...
and you couldn't have fun.
Not at all.
I didn't mind at all.
Because, you know...
If you go out, you'll see their faults.
So having seen it,
I feel like I know him better.
What the heck?
This is stupid.
What do you mean "stupid"?
She feels closer because he threw up?
That's just perverse!
Unexpected events can bring you closer.
She's excited by a guy who threw up!
That's totally perverse!
That's not it!
She's just a pervert from Kagoshima.
He totally changed after the crepe scene.
Oh, the crepe.
It was an indirect kiss.
It was a shock.
He said it was the end.
It never started.
Not every occurrence brings them closer.
-It could distance them.
-Yes.
He went to the park hungover.
Even though it was hard for him, he went.
His behavior was probably good.
Because he was trying hard?
She did feel as if he was usually trying
to act a little cool.
So, on the 24th?
That's right.
You said it'll happen.
Yeah, it'll happen.
It'll happen.
He was saying
he's going to kiss her first.
What a dog.
Too risqué.
He's going to be kissing her all the time
once they get together.
He's the kind of guy
who'd do it all the time.
Definitely.
I don't care anymore.
Don't care.
-Everyone.
-Yes?
I have some sad news.
This will be Ayumu's last appearance.
-He's leaving us?
-He's leaving.
-He's studying for exams.
-Oh, of course!
Oh, it's exam season.
-What grade are you in?
-Ninth grade.
Wow, so you are entering exam season?
It's no time to be watching
some strange foreigner throwing up.
That's so true.
You must learn about
more important historical events.
Were you able to learn
anything about relationships?
Well, what was it... Locomoco?
The name of the shopping mall?
-Oh, Costco?
-Yes!
It sounds like food.
That?
-Costco?
-That's so cute!
I was waiting for one of our great lines,
but Costco?
It left an impression.
You learned
there was a store called Costco.
-So cute!
-Cute!
Were our words so meaningless?
You'll focus on your studies for now,
but there may come a time
when you'll experience love.
When you need advice,
come to this guy.
Ayumu has the right to choose.
I'll be happy to give you advice.
You're the expert now?
So can I ask you for advice, too?
Tell me, why did you decide
to move in to Terrace House?
Mainly, because I thought it'd be fun.
Simple as that.
Would you be taking turns
with others to take a bath?
But if I am first,
since I am so filthy,
no one wants to after that.
You must use it in the end.
I will when I come home
from the construction site.
Let's all go visit him.
At Terrace House?
Hello?
Can I talk to you right now?
Is dad with you?
I see. Remember I went for an audition
for Terrace House?
I passed.
I have been without a boyfriend
for about a year.
So maybe...
Would that be too good to be true?
No guy left to be a good match for me?
I am not prepared for this yet...