-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Previously, love ended for two people.
It was hell, wasn't it?
-Let's use it sometime.
-The car?
Everyone said they wanted to go to Costco.
I'll think of where we can go
for a day trip.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
-A day trip?
-Yeah, with the car.
-Let's drive somewhere.
-Not Costco?
"If it's to Costco..."
"If it's to Costco with everyone."
That was terrible, wasn't it?
She's obviously not interested in him,
but he's a little oblivious.
I didn't get to properly
ask you out earlier.
With just the two of us.
Instead of going with just the two of us,
like a day trip.
I'd rather go somewhere with everyone.
That second attempt was hell.
It really was hellish.
-And Mizuki had dinner with Arman.
-It was so sad!
To be honest, since Arisa came...
I've been attracted to her.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
I'll be rooting for you.
-And Yu's famous words here.
-That's right.
"Mizuki cut her hair because feelings
linger in the ends of your hair."
-Such beautiful words.
-They were.
-I had goosebumps.
-Me too.
They could've just closed
the show with that.
Like, "Oh, of course!"
-And Tap and Mizuki considered leaving.
-Tori-chan.
You can't call him Tap.
It sounds a lot more mean coming from you.
We have one more month.
-And I wanted to stay until the end.
-Yeah.
I am considering leaving.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
I might leave now.
Really?
Maybe Seina is going to come back.
SEINA SHIMABUKURO, 28 YEARS OLD
Saying, "What's going on, guys?"
"What's going on?"
Let's just answer, "Nothing,"
and turn her away.
Where's the traditional Japanese room?
It smells good.
-I've never been here.
-Me neither.
-It's the first for me, too.
-This is nice.
-I didn't know we had this.
-Yeah.
Wow, what's this?
It opens.
Oh, I've never opened that before.
Wow, luxurious feather comforters.
Smells new.
There's a lot.
-Want to lay it out?
-This one?
There are two sets, so two sets?
Maybe just one set.
-I guess two.
-I'll lay out both for now.
Isn't this a great room?
It is.
It should be used.
-Hey.
What's up?
What?
Mizuki called us here.
To go upstairs.
The two of you always sleep here.
-Yeah.
-And look really cold.
You guys always look cold sleeping here.
So we...
Well...
-Don't make it so serious.
-What?
You're scaring them.
-What's going on?
You're trying to be considerate of us.
We're not.
-There's another room.
-Another room?
There's a Japanese-style room upstairs.
I see. A traditional Japanese room?
-So, you know, you can use it.
-If we want, you mean?
We set it up just in case.
Set it up?
Like at a traditional Japanese inn.
That's why you called us?
Thanks, guys.
You're welcome.
-Well, then...
-Take a look.
Oh, yeah. Wanna see it?
-Yeah, sure.
-It's really nice.
Since you went through the trouble.
Wow.
This...
-Isn't it a bit much?
-Definitely.
I can't believe they did this.
You look unhappy about it.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
-Good morning.
Leftovers from yesterday?
-Want some?
-I do.
Working today?
-Right now...
-Yeah?
...I'm making samples for an exhibition.
There's a shop that carries the materials.
But because there's so many,
I could look at them all day.
You mean, like, fabrics?
Yeah, it's the size of a stadium.
I can spend the entire day there.
You're going to finish your samples?
I'll finish them by the end of the year,
and then I'll rework them
and get them ready for the exhibition.
How many are you making?
There are eight base models,
but there's color variations,
so a total of, maybe, 25.
-I see.
-Yeah.
Do you have work today?
School. School then work.
Do you have plans for Christmas?
The 24th.
He asked me to keep it open.
-So, you haven't made plans yet?
-No.
So, Uchi's planning for you.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
-What are your plans for Christmas?
-Me?
I don't have any right now.
ASAKUSA, TOKYO
DAINI TOSHO CENTER
BUILDING TWO
OFFICE ELEGANCE ONE
Hello.
Yes, the hats...
How much are the Panamas?
-The Panamas, including tax?
-Yes.
The whites are 4,200 yen.
-The black Panamas?
-Those are 3,400 yen.
-The blacks are 3,400 yen?
-3,400 yen.
And the balibuntal?
Balibuntal in natural?
If you have natural, white and black,
that's great.
Hey.
-You awake?
-Yeah.
Where's Uchi?
Your hair's crazy.
It's okay, right?
What's up?
I'm thinking of leaving.
-That's sudden.
-Why?
I've always wanted to go to Africa,
the birthplace of tap and rhythm.
What're you gonna do, Uchi?
Me? My plans?
I'm going to discuss it with Minori.
I'll talk to her.
-Wow.
-Is that almost done?
This is just the material.
It's cute! Really cute.
I like it as is.
-As is?
-Try it on.
-Wow!
-But as is?
That one is raffia.
And this one's a Panama from Ecuador.
-Ecuador?
-Yes, from Ecuador.
I'm gonna work on these, then go to sleep.
-Work?
-I'm going to work, then sleep.
Then before you do that,
I have to tell you guys something.
I'm going to leave.
-Is it decided?
-Yeah.
When?
Why?
Because I don't want you to go!
-It's because the show is extended, right?
-Yeah.
I've come to a decision.
I figured it was time.
There's nothing more
you wanted to do here?
No, not really.
Well, except maybe spend Christmas here.
-I'm sad.
-Me too.
Wait, what was that prank about?
The traditional Japanese room prank.
And they never touched
on what happened after.
That's right.
It just cut to the chige breakfast.
-Chige and natto.
-Yeah.
Well, chige and natto, both are soybeans,
so I'm sure it went together.
-I wasn't talking about the food.
-No?
No, I wasn't.
Well, the fact she was able to eat
chige, natto and rice in the morning,
means that she was hungry.
That means...
It means...
I totally thought Arisa would be the type
to blush and leave the room.
No one would do that.
Not with a lame joke like that.
I see. But it was still a shock.
And what's even more of a shock,
towards the end, there was a moment
where I felt
maybe she wasn't a good person.
When?
Well, when she asked Mizuki
whether there was anything more
she wanted to do there.
I just felt like
she should be the last person to ask that.
After all, she is the reason
that things didn't happen for Mizuki.
-But maybe she's just the oblivious type.
-Which is it?
Which is it?
Are you talking to yourself?
-Or are you asking us?
-What are you asking us?
I'm talking to myself. I'm sorry.
Your idea of Arisa
is falling apart, right?
And you can't accept it, right?
The two Arisas are battling in my mind.
It's already broken.
But, anyway, as Tap was asking,
what are they going to do?
-That's true.
-They're a couple now,
is there any point in staying?
Just like how Tap asked Uchi.
Maybe they're all going to leave?
-That's a possibility.
-That's true.
Did something happen?
That was sudden.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
You guys look relaxed.
We're just chillin'.
Something happened, right?
-You okay?
-No, I'm not okay.
I knew something must have happened.
Something happened?
I was out with Uchi.
We went to eat sushi.
We biked there.
-Today?
-Today.
It's been a while since we really talked.
Our schedules haven't lined up.
Towards the end, things got awkward,
and we came home in silence.
You talked about your future plans?
We didn't say too much about it.
But since the show was extended,
we hadn't discussed what would happen.
Uchi's plans and mine...
are different.
I didn't want it to turn into an issue,
so I didn't press it.
You tried to avoid talking--
Not that I don't want to discuss it,
but I do tend to clam up
about issues I want to avoid.
I know it's bad.
The discussion didn't really go anywhere.
He can't talk about things lightly.
When he start talking it gets really...
-Heavy?
-Yes, heavy.
The talk becomes serious.
He has that tendency.
That's not good either.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-Oh, sorry I left the dishes.
-Don't worry about it.
-Thanks.
-Yeah, just leave it there.
-Nice work.
-Yeah, nice work.
It's been a little awkward lately.
-With Uchi?
-Yeah.
-How come?
-Well...
the show was extended, right?
We hadn't really discussed our plans.
It's kind of difficult.
Can't you guys talk like you always do?
Well, when we talk about it...
it gets really heavy.
It becomes really negative.
Uchi has that tendency.
He tells me to speak my mind, so I do,
but then he interrupts with objections.
Even though he told me to say what I feel.
It's a difference in thought...
I think.
What time are you going tomorrow?
I'll leave around 8:00 a.m. tomorrow.
To weigh in.
-Oh, you have to weigh in?
-Yeah.
The match starts around 3:30 p.m.
-Finally.
I can finally drink.
That's not the right attitude!
Not that! It's what's before that!
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Looking forward to it.
-What did you eat today?
-Today?
Pizza and--
-Pizza?
-I'm jealous.
Pizza and a burger.
Arisa made it for me.
Pizza.
Your weight doesn't matter?
My weight's fine.
I checked this morning and it was 64.2kg.
It has to be under 65kg.
It should be the same in the morning.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
I've got an early morning,
I'm going to sleep.
-Me too.
-Good night.
-Good luck tomorrow, Arman.
-Thanks.
-Good night.
Good night.
It's tomorrow.
-Tomorrow.
-Yeah, it's tomorrow.
-It was a long road.
-Yeah.
You don't seem like you get nervous.
Before, about a week before a fight,
I got really nervous.
But this time, not at all.
-When was before?
-High school.
When I was in high school.
-But high school was a while ago.
-Yeah.
It's been four or five years
since my last match.
Is it time to sleep?
Should we go to sleep?
Do you have to leave earlier?
I'll leave around 8:00 a.m.
-I have to be there by 9:00 a.m.
-Oh, by 9:00 a.m.?
-Let's sleep.
-Yeah.
Thanks.
-Wish me luck.
-Good luck.
-Good morning.
You're up early.
Sleep well?
-No. I'm still sleepy.
-Really?
Do you have time to eat breakfast?
-Breakfast.
-Breakfast?
It's probably better not to eat
before the weigh-in.
-Oh, that's right.
-I'll eat after the match.
-You will?
-Yeah.
I'm starting to get nervous now.
It's not good.
If you win, let's go anywhere
you want to go.
Sounds good.
You're gonna take me?
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
I'll take you wherever you want.
Okay. I'll think of where to go, then.
I'm going to win.
-I'd better go.
-I'll see you later.
Thank you.
GOLD'S GYM SOUTH TOKYO ANNEX
OMORI, TOKYO
RISE AMATEUR TOURNAMENT
KAMINARIMON
Please confirm your class and line up
by the scale.
Body weight is okay.
DAIKI MIYAGI, 25 YEARS OLD,
ACTOR, TARGET SHIBUYA OWNER
Oh, man...
For our 70th second-class match,
two rounds of two minutes.
In the red corner, we have Tony.
Blue corner, from Target Shibuya,
Arman Bitaraf.
Go, Arman, go!
Round one!
ITO TAKASHI
CEO OF TARGET
He's got it. Go, Arman!
Do your best, Arman!
Second round.
Round two, final round!
We have a unanimous decision.
Three to zero!
A certificate.
Can I see?
CERTIFICATE OF HONOR
ARMAN BITARAF
"Arman Bitaraf, for your win,
we present you with this certificate
in honor of your victory."
-Congratulations!
-Thanks.
-What a relief.
-Yeah.
Finally.
You even refrained from drinking.
This morning,
you said you'd take me somewhere.
I did.
I want to go to Yomiuriland.
-The amusement park?
-Yeah.
You want to go to an amusement park?
-No roller coasters, though.
-You don't like roller coasters?
-You do?
-I do.
-Let's do it.
We haven't taken a day trip
since Mt. Takao.
Congratulations!
Wow.
-It was three to zero.
-Amazing.
He's strong.
But he lost...
What?
It's very sad.
His opponent lost.
How can you root for a stranger?
Arisa has completely...
-fallen for him, right?
-Yeah.
She told him she'd take him anywhere.
Twice. "Anywhere you want."
She said it twice.
That means she wants to go
somewhere more adult.
She's giving the signal.
-She's including it.
-Yeah.
Mt. Takao, the amusement park,
and that kind of place. "Anywhere."
-Right?
-That's what she implied by that.
And if Arman had said something
that alluded to that,
she would've said, "You idiot."
"Idiot" meaning "yes."
-She didn't say no.
-No. "Idiot" means "yes."
Oh, watch out!
Oh, man,
so they're gonna get together, then.
You haven't given up yet?
Don't worry.
I've started to hate her.
Don't worry?
Yeah, I made sure of it.
I think I can move on now.
Did something happen?
I experienced passionate love.
You should cut your hair immediately.
So many feelings linger here!
Cut it immediately.
Yes, I'll get rid of these feelings.
-What about Minori and Tatsuya?
-That's right.
Surprising.
She said things were really awkward.
Tatsuya is much too serious.
The issue isn't whether they're going
to continue with Terrace House, right?
It's whether they get along as a couple.
When the topic turns serious,
they immediately disagree.
And the way Tatsuya communicates...
-Annoys her?
-...probably stresses her out.
You're told to say what's on your mind,
but when you do,
you're met with objections.
That's extremely annoying.
She does seem to be under a lot of stress.
It can't be controlled.
She's starting to get annoyed with him.
This is starting to get interesting.
That's terrible.
Enjoying other people's problems.
Feeding your hunger.
I've been pretty hungry lately.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back!
Nice work!
This is fancy.
-Congratulations!
-Thanks.
-Wow!
-Nice work, nice work.
Cheers!
-Congratulations!
-Thank you!
Congratulations.
It tastes amazing.
-The long awaited...
-I've been waiting.
It's a victory dinner.
Let's get rowdy.
And a goodbye for you.
Me? Oh, yeah.
It's my last night.
We need to toast that, too.
Thanks for everything, Yuki.
You're stuttering!
That made me sad!
-Isn't the timing wrong?
-What?
I'm leaving, too.
When?
It could be at the same time.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I'm going to drink until morning,
then go.
I don't have plans tomorrow,
so I'll join you.
Great.
Mizuki, good morning.
I have to leave early for work.
Thanks, Uchi.
Come by for a haircut.
See you later.
-Thank you. I'll see you.
-Thank you.
See you later.
Yuki.
Your face is a mess.
-I'm heading out for work.
-Okay.
-See you around.
-See you.
I don't know when I'll see you again.
Thanks for these past four months.
I had fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you to you.
-Shall we?
Jinx!
-Okay, let's go. See ya.
-Let's go!
Thanks, Minori!
Thank you!
-See you.
-See ya!
Thank you, bye!
-Bon voyage.
-Thanks, I'm off!
See you later!
Thank you for everything.