-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Yes.
Well, everyone,
we have a new member in the studio today.
That's right.
-The actor Kentaro.
-Nice to meet you.
-Kentaro!
KENTARO, ACTOR
-Welcome.
-Thanks for having me.
-Your skin is so smooth!
-Yeah!
-You're 18 years old, right?
-Yes, 18.
It's like bring it on 4K!
He's made for 4K.
-Have you seen all the episodes?
-From the beginning.
From when Yu was in the car.
I guess he watched that.
Do you have a favorite girl
in the group by any chance?
Right now, Arisa.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
-Oh, her.
-It's that one, is it?
What does that mean?
Well, you know,
it's a predictable choice.
It's not like you're wrong.
It was just, "Oh, Kentaro likes her, too."
That's our opinion anyway.
You too, right, Yamachan?
I did, but I've already moved on.
You have? You've moved on?
She's just different
from the Arisa I imagined.
So, I'm sorry, but I had to move on.
Kentaro, you haven't developed
a discerning eye for women yet.
-I'll teach you today.
-Thank you.
Today?
So, previously...
Arman and Arisa are already set, right?
That's right.
He was throwing up, and she likes him?
She must be crazy.
Is it good?
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
-It looks warm.
-It's super warm.
I wasn't expecting a gift at all.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
So, he's going to ask her, right?
-On Christmas.
-So, maybe we'll get to see that today.
There's gonna be a kiss.
-Probably.
-Yeah.
I think it's a bad idea
if they become an item at this point.
I don't think they'll last long.
That's what you're hoping for.
Will Minori and Tatsuya be leaving?
-Things were awkward, but they made up.
-They talked.
All our talks get too serious.
I think that's why I tend to clam up.
Well, I think disagreements are important,
but I do want things to stay enjoyable.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
In the Japanese-style room, they spent
the night and worked things out.
-Yes, the Bedroom Solution.
-Bedroom Solution?
-Oh, and new members!
-That's right.
Why did you decide
to move in to Terrace House?
Mainly because I thought it'd be fun.
Simple as that.
I have been without a boyfriend
for about a year.
So maybe...
Would that be too good to be true?
A manly blue-collar-type guy.
Scary.
And someone from the Kansai region.
-A beautiful profile.
-Yes.
-Beautiful straight teeth.
-She did have nice straight teeth!
Oh, I love straight teeth.
Oh, so now we've got someone
that fits your criteria.
Also, Terrace House
has been extended for 18 weeks.
For a total of 36 weeks.
-There will be more to come.
-Wonderful!
Another 18 weeks?
A lot can happen.
SHINBASHI, TOKYO
-Well... cheers!
-Cheers!
-Merry Christmas.
Delicious.
-The amusement park was fun.
-It was.
I'm sorry about what happened though.
It'll be in my memories forever.
Really.
-In a good way?
-Yeah, in a good way.
There's some place I want to take you.
It's within walking distance.
Let's go after.
-Near here?
-Yeah, it's walkable.
-Do you have time?
-Totally.
-Merry Christmas.
From me to you.
A Christmas gift to show my appreciation.
You're like Santa!
Nothing extravagant, but...
Thank you.
-Can I open it?
-Please do.
It's a scarf.
-I wasn't sure about black...
-Yay!
Sorry if you already have one.
I don't have a black one.
Not in this style, either.
-I'm glad.
-Thank you.
Yay!
I hope you like it.
Thank you. I'm so happy!
Ta-da!
-Wow.
-Amazing, right?
CARETTA SHIODOME
It's so pretty.
Wow.
So pretty.
-Reminds me of the amusement park.
-Yeah.
I'm actually alive this time.
Do you want me to take it?
Let's take one together.
Wow, it's really pretty.
How'd it turn out?
Wow.
Oh, they take a picture for you.
-Wow, it's nice.
-It's beautiful.
-Amazing.
-Right?
You can see all of Tokyo!
Wanna sit?
Oh, there's a place to sit?
You remember at Yomiuriland last time?
There was something I wanted to say then,
but I was sick and all.
You were.
So, I couldn't say it then.
I really like you right now.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I know it's sudden.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
We've been spending
a lot of time together lately
and going to lots of places.
Living together,
I've given it some thought,
but...
I'm comfortable with you,
and I have fun, but...
I don't want to change
the relationship we have now.
That's how I feel.
I'm...
sorry.
It's like...
Family? Brother? Like friends...
The more we hung out,
the more my feelings tilted that way,
I guess.
I understand.
Thanks.
-I'm sorry.
-No, I'm glad I know how you feel.
-Shall we go?
-Yeah.
-Wow.
-The unexpected.
-What's going on? This is fun.
-Here it is.
This is it.
Mr. Yamasato? What's going on?
She's a cunning and wily girl.
That was close. She almost had me.
What do you mean? She totally had you!
Man, that was a close one!
What do you mean close? She had you!
You fell for her already.
She played him.
I think this one shocked all of us.
Are you surprised, Kentaro?
-They went hiking together, right?
-Yes.
They held hands like this.
-The normal clasp.
-And now it was intertwined.
-You've got a good eye.
-Good job, Kentaro. Good eye.
That was... a bit of a surprise.
I mean, Arman was planning on kissing her.
She walked away at the sound of the bell.
Things were going well until then.
So Arman, rather naturally, holds her hand
and puts his arms around her.
It seemed like Arisa was thinking,
"Oh, is that a Hawaiian thing?
Girls in Japan might read more into it."
It seemed like Arman
was the stronger force.
But she was deftly letting his actions go.
That's right.
Not just that, but going above and beyond.
-Amazing. It's aikido.
-It is aikido.
It is aikido!
Kickboxing versus aikido.
Aikido wins.
She just blocked all the punches.
Arman thought he was in, but he wasn't.
What is she trying to do? This girl...
What's she trying to do?
It's so absurd!
There are girls like this from Kagoshima?
There are different types of people.
She's probably being nice.
Maybe she's just too accepting?
Holding hands and all that.
-No, no, no...
-There are girls like that.
No, no.
It's fine to accept it.
But to lead someone on,
that's the crime.
If she means she wants to see
how things go
and to take things slower,
that's understandable.
-Exactly.
-That's right.
But she wants things to stay the same?
-She said like friends or family.
-She said family, like siblings.
So, she's saying she doesn't want
to be anything more than friends.
It was like the Costco incident.
Like the way she rejected Tap.
"Let's go to Costco with everyone."
"With everyone, everyone."
If she was going to reject him,
she should've just used Costco again.
-So true.
-Yeah.
Costco was there for the taking.
Yeah, she might as well have said,
"Forget that, let's go to Costco."
And bam!
Then she still would've been horrible,
but funny at least.
Yeah, then I'd even forget my anger.
Uchi.
You awake?
Can you hang with me, like, five minutes?
Sorry.
Just for one drink?
What's up?
Just five minutes?
First off, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
We had dinner.
And went to see the illumination.
-With Arisa?
-Yeah.
We were holding hands like usual.
-Holding hands?
-Yeah.
And then she said she could only see me
as a friend or brother.
Then why is she holding hands?
That's what I don't get.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
Arisa's at fault then, I think.
Why would you hold hands
if you're not interested?
So, she's not saying that she's not ready,
but that she doesn't see you
that way at all?
Yeah.
That's crazy,
who holds hands with family?
Right?
You wouldn't hold hands with a brother.
She said she doesn't want
to ruin our relationship.
What?
That's a little...
That's bad on Arisa's part.
-She's just leading you on, then.
-A little.
So he asked, and you rejected him?
Is that right?
I said I wanted things to stay
as they were.
As friends.
That's what I told him.
I don't know how Arman feels.
Come in.
Can I come in?
I wanted to talk to you.
Did you hear what happened?
Yeah, I heard.
Did you hear from Arman?
Yeah, and I was wondering how you felt?
It's true that I felt something
more than friendship for him,
but to have a relationship with him?
-Is something else?
-That's something else.
That's how I feel.
If that's the case,
why did you hold hands with him?
It's not as though I didn't like...
holding hands with Arman today.
And I did think...
that he might ask me today.
Maybe it's easier to hold hands
since I don't have those feelings for him.
Yeah, I don't get that.
There's no need to say that.
-Yeah, but...
-You know...
It's Christmas.
You're surrounded by beautiful lights.
You're holding hands.
And then be told you're like a brother?
Wouldn't that make you say, "What?"
Wouldn't it? I don't know.
It would.
Yeah, but there's nothing to be done now.
That's what happened,
and she can't lie to herself
and go out with him.
Then I wish you hadn't held his hand.
It's misleading.
Maybe that's just you trying to be nice,
but it seems like you were leading him on.
You're right.
I enjoyed hanging out with Arman.
I had fun.
And I wanted to get to know him.
But...
I shouldn't have held hands
with him today.
Though it's not like I didn't want to.
I mean, I do like him.
But...
But I should have said no.
I do think that I hurt him.
Arman?
What?
I didn't explain myself yesterday.
-Not now.
-What?
Not now, please.
Cleaning Duties
Women: Dining, 2nd Floor Girls' room
Men: Living room, Guys room, Game room
Uchi & Minori: Japanese-style room
Have you talked to Arisa?
No, not yet.
She came to see me this morning.
Like, in my room.
She came to your room?
She said something, but I was sleeping.
And I didn't feel like talking.
It was just too much of a hassle.
Have your feelings for her cooled?
Is it too soon?
Just depends on how you look at it.
Things are a little awkward then?
-A little.
So, he's hurt.
And won't talk to you?
What was the reason you rejected him?
I didn't want to say
I still had feelings for him.
I figured that would just lead him on.
So, I could only say I was not into
being his girlfriend.
I think it's okay to tell him...
that you had feelings for him.
If you think that'll hurt him or whatever,
then he'll never know
what you were thinking.
I think it'd be better if you said,
"This is how I felt,
and that's why I held your hand."
I think it'll help Arman accept things.
That's true.
I'm sure he'll listen to you.
But, he hasn't so far.
If you try again and he doesn't listen,
then I think
that's pretty immature of him.
What should I do if he doesn't?
-Good work, guys.
-Good work.
Uchi, let's go clean
the Japanese-style room.
Okay.
Let's do.
Where's my phone?
-Can I help, too?
-Sure, thanks.
-Japanese-style room?
-Yeah.
I wanted to talk to you.
You came to my room, right?
And I was sleeping.
I was pretending to sleep
because I didn't feel like talking.
I'm okay now, though.
I was a little down.
Not because I was rejected...
but because you said we're like siblings.
Maybe you were just trying not to hurt me,
but that's the worst thing
you can say to a guy.
So, I was a little upset about that.
There are lots of things
I didn't get to say. Um...
Do you want to sit and talk?
Yeah, let's sit.
We can do this later.
I...
I'm not ready for a relationship now,
but it's not that I don't like...
So, you don't think of me as a sibling?
Well, I have lots of
different feelings about you.
But, since I don't want a relationship,
I didn't want to give an ambiguous answer.
I thought that would be wrong.
I'd rather you give it to me straight,
my feelings aside.
Just say what you're really thinking.
What you're saying right now
doesn't make any sense to me.
Are you saying it's too fast for you?
That you want to date and then see?
Or are you not interested in me?
Which is it?
I don't want to waste your time either.
And I don't want to waste my time.
So...
I like you.
That's why I wanted to go places with you.
I do want to get to know you...
better.
I understand.
I'm sorry I didn't communicate it well.
-Shall we continue cleaning?
-Let's clean.
It's late already.
-We're not going to finish.
-I want ramen.
I'm hungry.
Where's Uchi?
-Uchi left already.
-Oh, I see.
He probably didn't sleep.
-Yesterday?
-Yesterday.
-Morning.
-Sleepy?
-I'm going.
-You're leaving?
You're not leaving yet?
Day after tomorrow.
-Day after tomorrow?
-Oh, I see.
What does it say for you?
My cousin's house.
Oh, Uchi is going home on the 31st.
-Have a good New Year's.
-See you next year.
-Have fun with just the boys.
-Just the boys.
-Bye.
-Bye!
I don't get it!
I don't know now.
Which is it?
I don't know. That time...
she just didn't say it right.
So, she didn't reject him?
She just didn't explain herself.
She just didn't feel ready
for a relationship.
Perhaps.
I don't know, but Arisa
was sort of told that by everyone.
-So, maybe she's just confused.
-In a panic?
You really think so?
I agree with you.
She's not that type.
She gets what's going on.
That's right. She knows the deal,
but since people are on to her,
she is making things vague.
"I do like him, but..."
"It's not like I rejected him, but..."
"So, let's leave it like this for now."
"I don't really understand either."
"So, for now..."
Is what she means right?
-Exactly.
-That is possible.
I was annoyed when she said,
"Have a good New Year's."
My New Year's day is ruined thanks to you.
HATSUMODE
Hey.
-Welcome home.
-I'm back.
-Alone?
-Alone.
-Long time no see.
-Happy New Year.
That's a lot of luggage.
-It's Uchi's.
-Oh, I see.
Where's Uchi?
-At work.
-Oh, at work.
Where's Arisa?
-I think she's at work.
-Really?
How was your vacation?
My vacation? I went home...
and just chilled.
-Nice.
-I did nothing.
Did you see Arisa?
I haven't.
I haven't talked to her at all.
-I haven't kept in touch.
-You haven't?
I was initiating everything before,
so I thought I'd give her some space.
-Why? You've talked it out, right?
-I suppose.
Did you meet with Uchi?
He stayed with me
since he doesn't have a place.
That's why I have his luggage.
That's nice. So lovey-dovey.
Oh, stop.
I'm jealous.
Who is it?
-They're here.
It's them for sure.
There's only two of us here.
-Come in.
From today onwards, I'll be staying.
What?
-Come in.
-Yes.
-A guy.
-Yeah.
-Definitely not 20.
-Wasn't his voice really low?
It's nerve-racking.
It's more nerve-racking waiting.
Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
I'm Hikaru Ota.
It's nice to meet you.
I was so nervous.
It's just the two of us here.
Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Please sit.
Excuse me.
What was your name again?
Hikaru Ota. Call me Hikaru.
How old are you?
-I'm 18.
-For real?
-A student?
I'm not a student.
I model and act.
And I do construction on the side.
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
I also do construction.
-Are you half-Japanese?
-I am.
Me too.
-From where?
-Iranian and Japanese.
You?
-Italian and Japanese.
-I see.
-But I grew up in Brazil.
-Brazil? Why?
Well, my mother and father
met at a university in Brazil.
They married and had me there.
But my ethnicity is Italian and Japanese.
How long did you live in Brazil?
Until two years old.
So, I grew up mainly here.
Do you do any sports?
I kickbox for fun.
-I box.
-Seriously?
Boxing and I've played soccer
for a long time.
I played with a team called Santos
in Brazil, studying abroad.
But I'm down to just boxing now.
They have gloves here.
-Gloves?
-Downstairs.
-What?
-Yeah, Minori does it sometimes, too.
-Yeah, he teaches me.
-You do it here? Really?
-I'd love to join you for practice.
-Sure.
-Looking forward to it.
-Lucky you.
Sounds like you'll get along.
-Girlfriend?
-No girlfriend.
What's your type?
Mature.
Well, I've only dated older women.
So, someone mature.
And I like to stay active,
so someone outdoorsy.
I like having fun,
so someone who'll let me do anything.
Someone understanding.
Seriously?
Another member.
Is that what it means?
-That bell means a new member?
-A new member.
-That was quick.
-Really?
-It hasn't settled in yet.
-The other two are gonna be so surprised.
Hi.
Hi, I'm supposed to start living here.
For real? The same timing?
-Please come in!
-Come in.
Think she's the sexy type
or the cute type?
Wasn't her voice cute?
-Hello.
-I can't see her face.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
-Wow.
-What's your name?
-I'm Natsumi Saito.
-Ms. Natsumi.
-How old are you?
-I'm 26 years old.
-He just arrived too.
-I just got here.
Really?
-Are you from the Kansai region?
-From Osaka.
I see.
-How old are you?
-I'm 18.
So young! No way.
What do you do for work?
My job?
I'm a model.
I'm studying to be an actress.
It's what I hope to be.
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
This is sudden,
but do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
It's been about a year.
What type of guy do you like?
Someone manly, I think.
Do people have real relationships here?
-Yeah.
-Watching it on TV...
I was wondering
if you really fall for each other.
That's a question for her.
You've got someone too, Arman.
She likes you back?
That's what I thought anyway.
-I see.
-That's where it's at.
Do you want to find love here?
I'm not in a rush.
I think love should come naturally.
But I would like to.
Of course.
-I hope so, too.
-Yes.
But I'm the youngest.
18, huh...
I usually drink by myself.
-Do you like to drink?
-Yes, do you?
-I love it.
-Let's drink together, then.
So, there's two more?
So, now there's six of us?
Yes, we're six now.