We offer our deepest condolence
to Yosuke Imai in remembrance of his life,
who loved and was loved by many.
-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Let's see, last time, Makoto left
and a new member, Arman, arrived.
Arman!
Your Japanese is so good.
Have you lived in Japan before?
I lived here until I was ten,
and then I lived in Hawaii for 15 years.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
Wait, you're not half?
You're from--
-I'm half.
-Half Japanese and...
Japanese and Iranian.
Surfing, boogie-boarding.
I also kickbox.
You seem strong.
I hope to teach English
while I'm in Japan.
-He's so cool.
-He's from Hawaii.
Netflix is really international.
You plug Netflix
at least once per episode.
-I'm just expressing my feelings.
-That's a little unfair.
I'm just explaining
how Netflix offers shows globally.
Also, it gives you perfect recommendations
depending on what you watch.
So sneaky.
You're in on it with Netflix, aren't you?
I went to the marketing meeting
for two days.
He's attractive.
You're into him, right, Tri?
He is attractive,
and he seems nice.
It might finally be
the start of something for Mizuki.
-I'm glad.
-That morning scene was great.
-That's a cute turtleneck.
-This? Thank you.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
Are you a model?
I work at an office.
-You seem the most like a model.
-Really? Wow.
I feel like if you give either a push,
they'll get together.
-They just need a trigger.
-I just get that feeling.
And during Arman's welcome party,
well, I don't know if that was
the right time for the announcement.
Ms. Hayata, was it?
So cold to her suddenly.
A wonderful announcement
while stepping all over Adachi's heart.
I believe she smiled the entire time.
So I'm going to tell Tadamichi
how I feel about him again...
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
...and after I tell everyone
how it goes...
I'm thinking of leaving.
And thanks to Ms. Seina,
-Tatsuya and Minori...
-Oh, that's right.
Yes, Seina, who tends to be blunt,
ends up helping them get together.
-I didn't try hard enough.
-Yeah, you need to push harder.
You need to be confident.
-Thanks for the advice.
-Oh, of course.
-I'll be clearer next time.
-Yes.
Maybe today they'll make things clear
and start their relationship.
-Yeah.
-What if they both say they want to leave?
It could happen, right,
with how quickly things are progressing?
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
SINGLE FOR 6 MONTHS
ODAIBA, TOKYO
Good work.
It's cold.
Is your cold better?
No. It just won't get better.
I go to work and come back late.
The whole country is going to send
their sympathies.
-You work, too.
-It's ending tomorrow, though.
-It's good, you got work.
-But it's still not consistent.
-Bon appétit.
-Looks delicious.
-No, I'll do it!
-I'll do it!
-Rock, paper, scissors?
-Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Here you go then. Man...
-It's your risotto donburi.
-It brings back memories.
-That was the day summer vacation started.
-Oh, when we went out?
That was fun.
It brings back memories.
Minori, you're...
-I'm hard to read?
-Yeah.
I can't tell what you're thinking now.
That looks fun.
It looks like it feels good.
Wanna walk?
Wanna go for a walk?
-Oh, a sand beach.
-It's not a sandbox.
-Not sandbox, sand beach!
-Oh, the beach.
Sandbox? How silly.
It's cold.
We left things unsettled.
-So I thought I'd make my feelings clear.
-Make them clear?
I really like you, Minori.
So, if you feel the same...
I want you by my side.
I knew how you felt
after we went to Chichibu,
and I've thought about it a lot.
I really like you, too.
I want to be true to my feelings.
But...
I'm still not sure.
It's moving a little fast for me.
I want to be surer of my feelings,
so I feel like I can't give you
an answer until then.
I'll figure it out soon.
One thing that's been bothering me...
You went out with all three of us.
So it feels like I was
the best choice of the three for you.
So I've wondered about that.
That's not exactly how it is.
Even if I try to say it with words,
you'll probably still...
If we continue to live together
and get to know each other better,
if you get to know me better...
-I'm sorry it's taking me so long.
-It's all right.
Should we head home?
Let's go home.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
So, we went to dinner yesterday.
How did it go?
You don't know about this, right, Arman?
In the beginning of September--
-Oh, I heard from Uchi.
-Oh, you did?
That's all I heard, though.
We went on a date.
And Minori enjoyed it.
And they went out a few more times after.
And yesterday they had dinner.
Oh, so that's what happened yesterday.
He asked me to be his girlfriend.
But I told him I wanted to take more time
and get to know him.
I wonder if he just chose me
out of the three he dated.
-Oh, so that's what you're afraid of.
-Yeah.
It's been bothering me, so I asked him,
and he said it'd be better if he showed me
through his actions rather than told me.
That's what he said, anyway.
-But it's still going well?
-Yeah, it's going well.
And you got to communicate your doubts.
-Isn't that right?
-Yes.
But I didn't get to hear
his thoughts on that.
Well, he's planning on showing you.
I know Uchi's trying really hard
to go through the proper steps,
but it's hard to feel...
the passion, I guess.
That part's not coming through, I guess.
He's probably the type of guy
who wants the right setting.
Maybe he doesn't want to say those things
unless the setting is right.
He wants to be prepared.
You're at a tough point right now,
but it'll be more fun once you're sure.
-Were you able to find a job?
-I haven't heard back yet.
-You're looking?
-Yeah.
-Did you go all over Japan?
-I did.
-"All over Japan."
-You know, kind of approximate, right?
Is there anywhere besides Tokyo
you'd like to see?
Kamakura.
-Or Chiba.
-Both are nice.
Kamakura has a beach, right?
Shonan beach?
-Surfing?
-Can you surf?
-No, I've never done it.
-Do you surf?
-I didn't bring my board.
-You can surf, right, Mizuki?
-Let's rent boards.
-Yeah.
-Let's do it.
-Let's go to Shonan.
Shonan? Or either one?
-Let's plan the day then.
-Are you usually free on Sundays?
-Yes.
-Then let's go Sunday.
Okay.
Minori told me that she felt like
I might have only chosen her
because there were three of them.
So she feels like she's one out of three.
And I couldn't really say then,
"No, you're the only one in the world."
It felt cheap to say it like that.
But she did say things are going well.
Show her how you feel every day.
-You're sure you like her, right?
-Yes, I like her.
She has to feel that from you every day,
and not just on your dates.
-Otherwise she might feel uncertain.
-That makes sense.
One more push.
Thanks, Arman.
-I bet Arman would just go for it.
-I'm sure.
Yeah, I would be direct
and express how I feel on dates.
-You're that type.
-Yeah.
I used to express by action,
but then I'd wait for the right moment,
and sometimes it'd be too late,
and I'd miss it.
So now I'll say what I feel in the moment.
Even if the setting isn't romantic,
I'll just say it.
I'm glad there's a new point of view.
You have what I'm missing, Arman.
It's great.
-It's what Japanese guys aren't good at.
-Yeah.
We're no longer in the Edo period.
We haven't freed
our national isolation of love.
The national isolation of love.
I wish the Perry of love would come.
But the Perry of love is here!
From Hawaii.
Arman is Perry.
It seems like things are moving smoothly
now that Arman is here.
-Yeah.
-Arman seems passionate.
-I totally thought they'd kiss at least.
-I thought so, too.
But I guess not yet.
I guess Minori isn't the type
to just jump into a relationship.
But I think that was a legitimate place
to ask her out.
-Completely.
-Right?
The official place of love, Tokyo.
-I didn't realize that existed.
-Of course.
Yeah, it's on the map.
Did Governor Masuzoe really approve that?
YOICHI MASUZOE
GOVERNOR OF TOKYO
"Actually, that's where I asked
Satsuki out."
SATSUKI KATAYAMA
You don't get to call her "Satsuki."
My first date
with my ex-girlfriend was there.
Seriously?
-While working here?
-Well, two and a half years ago.
How'd you end up there?
Well, after work, I was driving
and asked her where she wanted to go,
and we ended up there.
It's like we were sucked in.
I guess that's the power of Tokyo's
official place of love.
But, like Arman was saying,
if Uchi doesn't convey his passion soon,
-Minori might just say, "Forget it."
-He might miss the opportunity.
-Right?
-Yeah, it'd be unfortunate.
She said "passion," so she does like him.
She just needs to be reassured.
That's probably all she wants.
That's true.
Like, "I'm in love with you!"
kind of thing.
-Totally?
-Totally.
Totally!
-Isn't that a little cheesy?
-It's passion.
She's looking for cheesy.
-Really?
-She wants to feel it.
It seemed like he took
Arman's advice to heart,
so he'll probably go for it
and show his passion for her.
He's a serious guy.
And Mizuki and Arman...
-will be going to Kamakura.
-They've got a date next Sunday.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
-Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
I'd like to try out your gym.
-Do you have reservations?
-Yes, I should.
-Your name please?
-Arman Bitaraf.
DAIKI MIYAGI, 25 YEARS OLD,
ACTOR, TARGET SHIBUYA OWNER
There you go again.
Oh, hi, perfect.
-Hi, I'm Miyagi.
-I'm Arman.
-Arman?
-Yes, it's nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm Ippei Shima.
-Have you done this before?
-Yes, a little.
Those are totally kickboxing shorts.
-I did it for about five years in Hawaii.
-Oh, I see.
Can you stretch a little on your own?
-You kickboxed?
-Um, Muay Thai and a little boxing.
Boxing?
So you were pretty serious then.
It's been two years, though,
so I'm a little rusty.
-Was it a hobby?
-Yes.
Well, I did compete a little...
-Amateur?
-Yes.
-How did you do?
-I was five and one.
That's great!
-You're half?
-Yes.
-Japanese and?
-Iranian.
Iranian? Oh!
You're all over the place.
You're doing Muay Thai,
but you're Iranian...
I'm all confused now.
-I bow to your comedic senses.
-Thanks.
I'm working part-time here,
but I'm also a comedian.
-I lived at Terrace House before.
-Oh, really?
What? You didn't know?
-Do you know about me, though?
-I do.
What? You know him and not me?
I heard you were a champion before.
Let's start.
Let's start light.
Straight hook.
-Okay!
-Thank you.
It would be interesting if you competed.
There's an opening for a match
on December 13th.
-The 13th?
-Yes.
A match in one month might be tough.
Well, if you're serious...
If you can move this much
after a two year gap...
-Okay, I'll try.
-You'll try?
-Let's work at it.
-Thank you.
-Let's work together.
-Pleasure to work with you.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-No one else is home?
-No.
-You just finished work?
-Yeah, I was at the office and stuff.
You're washing dishes?
Whose is that?
-I don't know.
-Oh, there's a lot. I'm sorry. Thanks.
-No worries, it was no problem.
-Were you home today?
No, I went to train
for the first time today.
It was fun.
-It was fun?
-It was.
-Done!
-Thanks.
How are things with Uchi?
-With Uchi?
-Did anything change?
Well, it's barely been two days.
It hasn't been very long.
-Has he said anything?
-No, not really.
-No?
-Well, it seemed like he got it.
-You're going out with Mizuki, right?
-Yeah, tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
-Tomorrow.
-Where are you going?
-To Shonan.
-To surf?
-If there are waves.
-Oh, you will.
-Yeah, if not, maybe just shop around.
Sounds fun.
-I want to go in the ocean.
-Yeah, me too.
But there won't be any waves today.
-Let's go to Chiba next time.
-Yeah!
Sounds fun.
It's been about a week
since you've arrived.
Yeah.
-Have you gotten used to it?
-Yeah.
You blended in pretty quickly.
ZENIARAI BENZAITEN UGAFUKU SHRINE
KAMAKURA, KANAGAWA
Wow.
It's like old Japan.
This is Japanese style.
What's that?
If you put your head to the smoke,
-it'll make you smarter.
-Really? I'm gonna do it later.
It's for good fortune.
-Like this?
-Yes.
You wash it to purify it.
Hello.
What do you want?
Can I have a Ramune, please?
-Two, please.
-Two.
-You don't have to do that!
-It's no problem.
Thank you.
Cheers!
-It's so good!
-It brings back memories.
The marble's in there.
When I was little,
I'd break the bottle to get it.
-I'm kinda hungry.
-Let's go eat then.
-Bon appétit!
How should I eat this?
-It's big.
-Yeah, it's huge.
-It's good.
-It's good?
Want to try some?
Are you sure?
-Good, right?
-Mmm-hmm. Want some of mine?
Yeah, it's good.
Is it hot?
-Oh, it's good.
-What do you want to do after we shop?
If we're in Kamakura,
we have to see the ocean.
Let's go.
Do you think we can catch the sunset?
KAMAKURA
It's so cute!
These look warm.
Which ones do you like?
-Maybe this?
-A knit...
This is good.
-What do you think?
-Gray.
Gray?
Ready?
-What do you think?
-It looks good!
It fits you perfectly.
Will you try this one, too?
-That's cute. Maybe too cute.
-It is.
And this one too.
-What do you think?
-It looks good!
-It's warm.
-Is it?
-And?
-That one looks good, too.
Which do you like better?
I might like the gray better.
YUIGAHAMA BEACH, KAMAKURA
The ocean!
-It's so pretty!
-This beach is nice.
But there are no waves at all!
-Should we stick our feet in?
-Should we?
We should.
It looks cold!
The sand is cold.
It feels better than I expected.
It's freezing!
It feels good!
It's so clear.
It's clearer than I expected.
This is nice.
Ready?
-How is it?
-It looks good.
It's so beautiful.
-I had fun today.
-Me too. Thank you for bringing me.
Do you have plans on December 13th?
No.
At the gym I went to yesterday...
I want to compete once in Japan
as an amateur.
-You're going to compete?
-I'm thinking about it.
I was practicing with Miyagi,
and he said I should enter a match.
-On the 13th?
-The 13th.
-I'll leave it open.
-Come see my match.
I'm looking forward to it.
Once training and work starts,
I'll be busy.
You'll be productive.
They're perfect for each other!
It's perfect!
So perfect.
Why isn't Glasses over there applauding?
She was acting so cutesy!
She actually had her hands here
while she said, "That looks good, too!"
What's wrong with that?
Everyone does that. Everyone!
-Everyone?
-Everyone.
-That's a good change.
-That's right.
-Really?
-Yes.
-It becomes that apparent?
-Yeah.
Wow. Well, it was interesting.
It kinda made me laugh.
Which part?
She was shouting at the ocean,
"The ocean!"
They had a good vibe at the shop.
It was definitely not the sort of vibe
just friends would have.
It only happens
when there's mutual interest.
That initial lovey-doveyness,
I want that for the rest of my life.
I completely understand.
It's one of the best moments
in a relationship.
-You want just the fatty part of the tuna.
-That's right!
You want to catch the tuna,
take the fatty part,
and move on to the next tuna.
-What do you think, Ayumu?
-It makes me nervous.
If she sees him at his match,
she's caught.
-Daiki and...
-Yes, Hana Imai.
It'll be a reenactment
of that scene with them.
Man, guys from Hawaii move quick.
What? Nothing's happened yet.
He just said
he was going to compete for fun.
Arman's got that kinda cool,
kinda shy thing going for him.
Yeah, it's not too much.
That "this is fun" kind of thing.
It's just the right balance.
It's so good.
That was a good date!
I wanna see that again!
You know, you can replay in Netflix.
Oh, man, you're still going on about that?
Because you said you wanted
to see it again.
So I'm just letting you know,
with Netflix,
you can replay it whenever you want.
I think I need to check
if we're getting paid the same amount.
It seems he's bought a house recently.
Oh, stop.
The new season of Terrace House
should be at your place.
That's right!
-My parents live there, too.
-That's fine.
The food scenes will have
lots of stewed vegetables.
-That's delicious.
-Sure, if the studio wants to do it.
-Are you nervous?
-I am.
I wonder how it'll turn out.
I was just thinking about
what I should say.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
I'm sure he's thinking about it, too.
-Well, I just have to hear what he says.
-That's right.
-Add the barrette, and it's done!
-Thank you!
Okay.
NAKAMEGURO, TOKYO
It's wet.
-Long time no see.
-It's good to see you again.
TADAMICHI KAWANO, M.D.
YURIKO'S EX-BOYFRIEND
Did you get a tan?
A little.
-A little.
-You got pretty dark.
-From Hawaii?
-Yeah.
How were exams?
-I think they went well.
-That's great!
Wow, so you were able to study?
-Yeah, I studied pretty hard.
-I see.
If your exams went well,
then you get to relax.
It's summer vacation.
I still have the CBTs,
so I still have to study.
Well, you still have a month...
So, I have something to tell you.
Tomorrow...
I'll be leaving Terrace House.
Is it because of me?
Since my internship will be starting
in December,
I felt like, as a medical student,
it wouldn't really be appropriate for me
to treat patients in hospital
while living in Terrace House.
That's the reason I'll be leaving.
Last time we went out,
I told you how I felt.
I told you then
that I couldn't forget you.
So it's not your fault.
It's something I decided for myself,
so you don't have to worry about it.
I'd just like to know
your honest feelings.