-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Not at all.
Last week, Rikopin and Hayato went
to Tsukiji on a date.
-Yes, they did.
-They had seafood bowls.
And that night,
Hayato went to the girls' room
-and asked Rikopin out on another date.
-Yes, that's right.
I came to ask Riko out again.
-What?
-Hmm?
Remember when we first talked
about Yokohama?
What about Yokohama?
What's in Yokohama anyway?
The Cupnoodles Museum.
That sounds like fun.
Things seem to be going well.
-It does.
-Yes.
-And Momochan invited Arman to the beach.
-Like, "I wanna go."
When is she gonna come to her senses?
Let's go to the beach sometime.
-Okay.
-Will you take me?
Sure.
-Okay, please take me.
-It's a deal.
-We talked about it before.
-Yeah, that's right.
She might only be asking him out
'cause she's excited and a bit confused.
-About Arman?
-Yeah.
Why would you fall for Arman otherwise?
-And Handa left...
-Yes. Is everyone doing okay?
Also, do you remember what happened?
You cried the most when Handa left.
The big incident.
That was shocking.
-That's right. You were bawling.
-She was.
I don't think I've ever...
-I've never seen you cry.
-...really cried on camera.
It's the first time I've seen you cry.
I vowed not to cry on TV,
but I was crying before I even realized.
-Hansan's really amazing.
-Yeah, the tears just kept coming.
He's amazing.
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD
Don't make me cry, guys.
I have to leave now!
Sorry.
See you around, Hansan.
Okay, see you around!
That was so anti-climactic.
I refuse to accept it.
-You don't believe he's gone?
-Right.
You think he's gonna come back?
-Because I love him!
-Torichan!
That's a serious confession.
You haven't been yourself
since Hansan appeared.
The new person
just looked like Hansan to me.
Oh yes, the new member.
It's the usual pattern.
We only saw his bottom half.
He looked like him.
It's not Hansan.
-We don't know that yet!
-We do.
If it is, our staff members are idiots!
I can't see behind me.
-Nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm Yuuki Byrnes.
You're from the variety show
Tensai TV kun.
-Yes, that's right.
-Really?
I used to watch it!
Crazy!
You've grown up.
Wait, you know him?
Yeah, he's from Tensai TV kun!
I used to watch it all the time!
-You were really young then.
-Yes, I was.
I was on it from the fifth grade
up until the ninth grade.
-How old are you now?
-I turned 23.
Same as me!
-Please sit.
-Thank you.
A good-looking guy.
-You're half-Japanese?
-Yes.
-What's the other half?
-I'm also half-American.
I work at a burger shop in Nakameguro.
So you work part-time at a burger shop,
but also work in the industry?
-Yes, as a dancer.
-A dancer?
-Yes, a dancer.
What kind?
-The style is called krumping.
-Krump?
-Oh, like the band Exile?
-Yes.
I also model once in a while,
when I feel like it.
When you say dancer,
do you mean backup dancing for pop stars?
Yes. The year before last,
I toured as a backup dancer
with Jin Akanishi.
Wow, you must be really good.
I was thinking of starting dance lessons.
-You mean your own?
-Yes, to teach lessons.
Can you speak English?
I can, but I've forgotten a lot of it.
What do you speak with your family?
I speak English with my dad.
-Japanese with your mom?
-Yes.
So you can speak English then.
But my parents live in Virginia now,
so I don't really speak to them too often.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-I don't.
What type of girl do you like?
I tend to joke around a lot...
so someone who likes to laugh.
Someone cheerful?
-What about looks?
-Looks...
I prefer... taller girls.
How tall are you?
-I'm 5'11".
-You're tall.
Any preference in age?
Probably someone my age or older.
Not younger?
I've never dated anyone
younger than me before.
Maybe that's why.
-Should we take him up?
-Oh, yeah.
-I'll take your bags.
-Are you sure? Thanks.
This house is so huge.
That was a surprise.
And...
-he's the same age as you.
-Yeah, he is.
He has a pretty face.
-His vibe is very different from Hansan's.
-Right?
-Do you have work today?
-Yeah, at the burger place.
Until when?
Probably around 10:30 p.m.
Krumping... Like Chris Brown?
My dream is to be
a backup dancer for Chris Brown.
Even if it's just once.
-That's cool.
-Yeah.
What did you think of the girls?
I think Misaki...
is really pretty.
-Physically speaking, she's your type?
-Yeah, totally.
Well, I mean...
-She is energetic.
-Yeah, energetic.
I like that she initiates conversation.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 21 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
I'm sorry. I've already started drinking.
-I'm already having one too.
-Are you?
-You've worked hard.
-Thank you.
Cheers.
Oh right, they haven't met.
I just moved in earlier today.
I'm Yuuki Byrnes.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Momoka Mitsunaga.
He came after you left.
The doorbell rang right after Hansan left.
-A few minutes after.
-Really?
-You're the ballerina, right?
-Yes, that's right.
-He's a dancer.
-Wait, what?
-I dance as well.
-Really? What kind?
I do hip-hop.
What style of hip-hop?
Krumping.
-You know it?
-It's my favorite.
I love watching it.
-It's very dynamic.
-Yeah, I know what you mean.
Come to my lessons.
-I do want to try it.
-Do you want to pas de deux?
-Pas de deux krumping?
-Is that like this?
Yeah! You know it.
We had a class in high school.
-Ballet?
-Yeah.
You seem suited to pas de deux.
Yeah, the white tights
would look good on you.
I don't know if that's a compliment.
I just meant you're handsome.
Like a prince on a white horse.
-Bon appétit.
Would you be able to come
to a dance showcase?
-I wanna go!
-We'd love to go.
-Showcase? What's that?
-Basically a show.
-Oh, a show. I want to go.
-Me too.
Please come.
-Seconds please!
-Okay.
That was quick.
The portion was too small for Misaki.
Who wants more?
I'll have some.
When do you come back, Misaki?
-The eighth...
-When are you leaving, tomorrow?
-In the morning.
-That's why your bag is out there.
-You're gonna start cooking now?
-Yeah.
Then maybe I'll go shower and change
in the meantime.
Sure.
Looks like it's ready.
-It smells so good.
-Bon appétit.
So good.
-It's so good!
-Delicious.
Riko and I made it together.
Riko oiled the pan.
She oiled the pan?
It's okay. It's edible.
-Thanks, Hayato.
-Thank you.
There are a lot of dishes to wash.
I'll do it tomorrow.
I'll do the dishes.
I'll do it since I ate a lot.
-How do you guys usually do it?
-There's a dishwasher.
-I think it's in use right now.
-I think it's done.
-Let's go hang out, Riko.
-I don't want to.
-You don't want to?
-Oh, it's done. So...
Never mind, it wasn't done.
This is definitely still running.
This is totally still running.
It's giving off too much steam.
Maybe the steam is good for your skin.
-There's a good amount of dishes to do.
-I know it's still running but...
You put the dishes in here.
You add the detergent here.
You sprinkle it here.
Do you have to do this
at the burger place?
-No, we hand-wash dishes there.
-Hand-wash?
Sounds like a lot of work.
-I'm used to it.
-Here you go.
Be careful.
-We're the same age, right?
-Yeah.
It's been a while
since I've talked to someone my own age.
-No way. Because they've all been older?
-Yeah.
-No one?
-Wait a second.
-Why'd you put this here?
-Does it not go there?
No, it goes down here.
-Here.
-It might take me awhile.
Glasses go here.
-The dishes go down here.
-Down here?
Got it.
-See that?
-Byrnes.
It's not Hansan.
-Torichan.
-Triendl.
-Yeah, it's not.
-No, it's not.
The moment Byrnes came out,
she looked down like this.
She refused to look at the screen.
I still can't accept it.
He seems lovely though.
A pretty boy.
-Mr. Handsome.
-Right? Very pretty and a dancer.
-He seems to be getting along with Misaki.
-Right?
But Rikopin...
Yeah, I was excited
by her first expression.
I want her to be interested in him,
but then she and Hayato acted all chummy.
So boring.
Weren't you excited
Riko might be attracted to the new guy?
I would like to see all three girls
interested in one person at least once.
Right?
Am I the only one
who felt she had that kind of expression?
-No, she did seem--
-She did, right?
-She did stare at him, but...
-Maybe not necessarily interested?
Momochan and Arman seem to be doing well.
What about the dance connection
between Momoka and the new guy?
They even brought up the pas de deux!
But we don't really know
what he's like yet.
-Yeah, we don't know his personality.
-That's true.
-We're only at the beginning.
-I'm sure he's a nice guy.
You seem to have had
a good impression of Byrnes.
It's not that I particularly like Byrnes.
I just like anyone
who can potentially create conflict.
-Oh, that's how it is.
-Yes.
I'll be on tour for three days in Sapporo!
-Misaki
-Good morning.
-Thanks for washing the dishes.
-No problem.
-Do you have work today?
-Yeah, at the burger shop.
Yesterday...
You know how you and Misaki
were doing dishes?
-Yeah.
-What were you guys talking about?
About a bunch of things.
Is she easy to talk to?
It helps that we're the same age.
Yeah, she is easy to talk to.
But I was thinking...
I didn't get to hear
what kind of guy she likes.
What's the guy she fell for before like?
-Was there someone?
-There was.
There was? What was he like?
He was 19...
and a little intense...
-Intense?
-The way he spoke was strong.
-Not quite a thug, but...
-Not a thug, but kind of like that.
I see.
And she confessed...
-her feelings to him.
-She did?
So that didn't work out?
But she did say
that she's liked different types of guys.
-I see.
-I don't think she has a specific type.
I think there is a part of me...
that is attracted to her.
Have you asked her out to dinner?
-I haven't yet.
-Maybe a date or something.
I'll ask her when she gets back.
It might be better
not to go Yokohama with Misaki.
Why is that?
That's where she was rejected before.
I'm so glad you told me that!
Thank you.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
Do you want to see
a picture of the 29-year-old?
Yeah!
Guess which one he is.
HASUMI FUTABA - AYAKA NISHIDA
-Wait, there's a macho guy!
-You like that?
I love that!
This guy on the very right.
He's on TV now, right?
-He is.
-Right? I think he's so hot!
-He's your type?
-Yeah.
But the guy you're talking about...
is in the middle.
-I think it's the guy on the left.
-No way!
-The one on the left?
-Yeah, with the towel.
-He looks young!
-I think he looks good.
Yeah, he looks good.
-Does he look 29?
-He looks young.
But can you see yourself
in a relationship with him?
-You know what I mean?
-Because he's 11 years older?
But I feel like we're always hanging out.
-Naturally you mean?
-Yeah.
And we got a new member yesterday.
-He's a 23-year-old guy.
-Nice.
-That's better.
-Yeah.
He's tall and half-Japanese.
-And I like tall, half-Japanese guys.
-So he's perfect then!
-Yeah.
-Oh, but there's the 29-year-old.
But he...
seems to be into one of the other girls.
Really?
And his type is
the complete opposite of me.
-He likes tall...
-Like, the slender types?
Girls the same age as him or older,
so he doesn't go for younger girls.
So someone tall
who isn't younger than him.
-That's totally not me.
-So he likes the womanly types?
I don't know about womanly, but...
So the girl he's interested in
is the same age as him,
and she's taller than I am.
-So she fits his criteria better.
-Yeah.
I can't help but think
there's no hope there.
So you're interested,
but you can't get close?
-Like, you can't come on too strong?
-No, I can't.
-What about the 29-year-old?
-I'll see how it goes.
The 29-year-old is interested?
He does ask me out on dates.
He's asked me out three times now,
but I don't know what he's thinking.
He hasn't talked about that kind of stuff?
No.
I wonder what he's thinking.
-Studying?
-Yeah.
-That's a lot of work.
-Yeah, I have to write a report.
I can't graduate if I don't do this.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What is all this? Social studies?
-World history.
-Oh, world history.
-Do you know anything about it?
-Not at all.
-What about English?
-I'm not taking English.
-You're not?
-No.
-Aw, I could've helped you with English.
-Yeah.
I took something else.
It's so hot.
-It is, isn't it?
-Totally hot.
-Right? I'm glad I wasn't the only one.
-Should I turn on the AC?
Where's the switch to turn it on?
-I don't know. I've never used it.
-Then let's open the window.
Thank you.
It might help a little.
-Oh, it feels cooler!
-No, really?
-I feel the breeze.
-Oh, yeah.
-It feels nice.
-Yeah.
-Now you can study better.
-Thanks.
Right.
-You're gonna study some more, right?
-Yeah.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
-I'm gonna...
-You're gonna go drink?
I'm gonna go have a drink.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
-Studying?
-Yeah.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
It's pretty cold today.
-It's hot!
-It was cold.
-I was hot, so Yuuki opened the window.
-You're all made up today.
-Looks cute. What's the occasion?
-What?
-You look cute.
-How can you say stuff like that?
What? You look pretty.
-Stop.
-Why do you have makeup on today?
I went out with my friends.
Did you guys have fun talking about me?
Did we?
Did they say anything about my age?
They asked to see your picture.
They said you don't look your age.
You mean I look young?
Did you show them a good picture?
Did you?
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Welcome back.
-You studying?
-I am...
and not getting very far.
Of course you can't study here.
Arman, my friend thinks you're hot.
Have we met before?
-Oh, I mean...
-What? You should know.
I showed them a picture
and one of them said you're hot.
Seriously? Thanks.
Why don't you introduce us?
She's cute, fashionable,
super trendy and super tanned.
Apparently she's rooting for me.
When are you guys going out?
-This week.
-Oh, this week?
Where?
-Yokohama.
-Oh, Yokohama?
This time, Riko's really excited about it.
Right?
I am. I'm excited...
about the Cupnoodles Museum.
Look, Riko.
Hey, I thought
it was supposed to be sunny on Sunday!
-Oh, it might rain.
-I hope it'll be sunny in Yokohama
since we'll be there.
How about you make
a teru teru bozu good luck charm?
Why are you telling me what to do?
-I'm sure it'll help.
-Yeah.
It's a little scary looking.
-Make it cute.
-It looks demonic!
-It's scary!
That is a little scary.
-But what should we do if it isn't sunny?
-I'll laugh if this doesn't work.
Let's hope it'll be sunny.
If this doesn't work,
I don't know what will.
Yeah.
-How is it?
-It's freezing!
-Feels good though.
-Yeah.
Have you gotten used to living here?
Yeah, pretty used to it now.
When are you going on your date?
Me? Next Sunday.
-Next Sunday?
-Yeah.
You should go when Misaki gets back.
Yeah, I'm thinking of just grabbing
some food and drinks close by.
-Sounds good.
-Yeah.
SHINJUKU, TOKYO
-Cheers!
TSUKASA AOI
EBISU MUSCATS
-Sapporo was fun, wasn't it?
-Yeah, it was.
How are...
Are you having fun?
I worry about you.
-You do?
-Yeah.
You're like a mom sometimes, Tsukasa.
Do you like anyone right now?
-No one right now.
-No?
-You know how I was rejected before?
-Yeah.
But...
a new member did come in.
You like him?
-He's also half-Japanese.
-Again?
You really like them.
-Younger?
-No, the same age.
-It's been awhile.
-You need to stop with the younger guys.
-Just stop.
-The younger guys?
But there's another girl I live with,
her name's Riko,
and he's exactly her type.
He's pretty funny, he's nice
and he's tall, 5'11".
-You're gonna fight over him?
-Even so, I'm still interested in him.
You mean
you can put a stop to your feelings?
-You don't want to like the same guy?
-No, I'm not going to stop.
So you do like him.
I meant I'm not the type
to stop liking someone
just because a friend likes him too.
I mean, that's up to the guy.
So you'd fight over him.
I'd tell my friend, of course,
that I'm also interested in the guy.
-Of course I'd tell my friend.
-Wow.
But there's also a chef named Hayato...
who's been hanging out with Riko a lot.
They seem to be into each other.
So it'd work out if they got together.
-At least from your perspective.
-I guess.
-I don't want to have to ask him out.
-Why should you have to?
-I'm sure he's used to asking girls out.
-What?
He seems like
he's used to asking girls out, right?
-Probably.
-So you don't have to initiate.
The two of them and Byrnes...
Nice!
Usually it's the buns
that do the sandwiching.
Instead Byrnes's being sandwiched.
Unexpectedly! That's so true.
Things are flipped inside out.
This is the ideal situation.
That scene when she's studying?
You can tell she likes him.
Riko is still young,
so she's easy to read.
Like the way she stared at him
in the kitchen.
-This time she had stars in her eyes.
-Yes.
And then came Terashima.
Terashima...
He was pretty sure of himself.
Did you see how he demanded
she make the teru teru bozu doll?
Was he serious?
"Did you guys have fun talking about me?"
When he said,
"Riko is totally excited about the date."
She could agree, but Byrnes is behind her,
so she doesn't really want to.
-She kind of lets the comment pass.
-Yeah, she does.
Instead, she says she's looking forward to
going to the Cupnoodles Museum.
She rewords it to emphasize
she's looking forward to the museum.
I'm getting chills.
She was clearly conscious of Byrnes.
Yes, very aware.
Between Byrnes, Arman and Terashima,
you can see the difference
in the level of sensitivity.
One asks if she's going to study more
and leaves to give her space.
The two others keep asking
what her friends said about them.
It was really sad to watch.
I mean, as a mature adult.
-Terashima wasn't very smooth there.
-Yeah, not so much.
I guess it happens to the best of them.
Terashima's such a character.
What if the Cupnoodles Museum date
turns into a double date?
That's rough.
I want that to happen!
"Why don't the four of us go?
It'll be fun.
Right, Riko? Right?"
That'd be a stupid move.
-Are you guys off today?
-Yeah.
-You have work?
-I've got work.
-Tomorrow too.
-Hmm?
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-Did you have fun in Hokkaido?
-I did.
It was super fun.
I brought back souvenirs.
What's with the teru teru bozu?
That was because
on the day of Riko and Hayato's date,
it's supposed to rain.
So you guys decided on a day?
It's not for sure, but this coming Sunday.
But it's the rainy season, so...
-That's so cute!
-Yeah, that's why...
-That's why you made it?
-Yeah.
You cut off a good amount of hair.
Not really. Just the sides.
-It wasn't that much.
-Sorry.
Why? Does it look funny?
Not at all. It looks refreshing.
-I hope it'll be sunny.
-Yeah.
-Where are you going?
-Yokohama.
Where I was rejected.
So Yokohama's taboo?
Not at all.
It just so happened.
Are you busy next week?
Next week, I'll probably be in Yokohama.
-For a live show.
-Oh, your tour.
But other than that,
I'm free between shows.
Let's go grab food when you're free.
Just the two of us?
Or with everyone?
It could be either.
Yeah, let's go.
What's with this vibe?
-What's going on?
-It's gone silent.
Did I say something weird?
Think about where you want to go.
Thanks.
Good.