-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
First, Natsumi...
or Princess Natsumi, is back from China.
She's scared of her
after that last episode.
It's okay.
-Arman and Natsumi head to Enoshima.
-That's right.
-They went.
-Yes, they went.
You sound like you're reporting
the royal family news.
"Princess Natsumi has visited Enoshima."
About Arisa...
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD
Do you really like her?
Yeah, I do.
I want to be in love, too.
That could've been her making an appeal.
But later on...
-I went to Shonan.
-By yourself?
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD
Of course not!
With Arman.
Why?
-What do you mean?
-For fun?
It's just sudden.
-What? Sudden?
-What?
It just sounds like you're mad at me.
They're both at fault.
It's an accumulation.
If they got mad over one thing,
then they could reason it out
how it happened and solve it.
-But they're all intertwined.
-And from there...
-The house meeting.
-That house meeting was scary.
I didn't really like
the way Minori was talking to me.
Her tone...
Minori denied it,
saying that was not how she meant it.
So that was me just honestly asking.
But you kept taking it as criticism.
You've just misunderstood each other.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
So let's not let this happen again.
Cheers!
If you brush it off like that,
the friendship
will always remain superficial.
This honest exchange of feelings,
you clearly see
this is how people build relationships.
The current mood at Terrace House
is horrible.
-Horrible.
-The worst!
And the worst part was,
in the middle of the talk,
when it was nonchalantly mentioned
that Arman still likes Arisa.
So he told you why, right?
That he likes Arisa,
and as a roommate, you'd help.
You had that conversation, right?
Wow, I wonder
where we're gonna start this episode?
It'll be scary
if it's from the middle of the meeting.
It's easy to say, "Okay, we're done."
To figure out what went wrong or to say
who was at fault is the easy way out.
If there's something you don't like,
no one will know if you don't speak up.
But, like Minori, there are people
who just aren't that type.
Which makes it difficult.
But if something bothers you,
I think it's better to say it
in any way you can.
If we're going to live together,
it's better to voice it.
Otherwise, what happened yesterday
will happen again.
I think it's important to figure it out,
but it's a matter of personality.
You're the type
who wants to get to the bottom of things.
No, we're not just talking friendship.
That's fine
if you're just hanging out for the day.
But living together...
Why don't you hear her out first,
and then respond.
The same goes for you.
You're interrupting me.
Not everyone is like you.
-I understand that.
-You do, right?
-So Minori has her own personality.
-I know that, too.
So I'm just asking you to hear her out.
Minori wants it
to be phrased better, right?
-But...
-Nacchan's words sound harsh to you.
I don't mind that.
And I'm not asking her to change.
But the way you say things
can be controlled in that moment, right?
As far as my personality goes,
I don't think
the change is something to be forced.
I just think, "Oh, well."
There's no need to change yourself
for someone else.
I think so, too.
-Not yourself, just how you word things.
-How you say it.
If we don't compromise a little,
there are some areas that won't work out.
If we don't try to understand each other,
this will happen again.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
MISHUKU, TOKYO
SHABU SHABU ONYASAI
You made that "don" thing, right?
The poke don?
How did Arisa like it?
She said it was good.
I wish it hadn't been
under those circumstances.
That's true.
-You told her your feelings though, right?
-I did.
Why don't you tell her again?
I do want to ask her.
The next time I ask her out for dinner,
I'll ask how she really feels about me.
-The feelings are there, I think.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, for real.
Why don't you go on a date with someone?
Either way, there has to be
more conversation.
But I guess going out to eat would work.
A date is
a way to get to know them, right?
That's true.
What about the fireman thing?
Or work, I mean...
I don't have anything
from the place in Kamakura right now.
Wanna come work at my place?
The construction company.
I can work with you?
-Yeah.
-Seriously?
-Yeah, together.
-Like Tom Sawyer?
Yeah.
-Sounds good.
-Yeah. It'll be fun.
It'll start either this week or next week.
-The project in Nakano.
-For real? Then...
-You'll do it?
-Will you ask for me?
-You'll come?
-Yeah.
I'll lend you the outfit then.
It'll be fun working with you.
This is the first time the three of us
are having breakfast together.
We're never home.
We all have different schedules.
-You're both off today?
-Yes.
No, I've got to go to Aoyama for 4:00 p.m.
Oh, your audition.
Thanks for the food, Minori.
Thank you.
Of course.
-Thanks for the food.
-Sure.
It was delicious.
What's this?
This here, what is it?
Oh, it's meat.
-Meat?
-Uchi got it as a gift.
-Wow.
-Huge steaks.
It's in a wooden box.
Oh, wow! Look at this!
Amazing, right?
-Wow!
-Oh, it's Hidagyu.
I don't know how to cook it.
Just salt and pepper would be
probably enough for this.
-That's true.
-Wow.
-Maybe cooked medium...
-Yeah.
-Or even rare.
-That's true.
-Wow.
-Wow, Uchi.
-I'm going now.
-Bye.
Thanks for the food.
I just heard today that Minori's leaving.
At the end of February.
-What? When did she say that?
-I just heard today.
She's going to leave
when she graduates university.
Are they related somehow?
Not really.
-It's good timing?
-Yeah.
What'll you do when Minori leaves?
I'd probably leave then, too.
If you do, would you get an apartment
and live together?
I don't know yet.
I might live on my own.
When you have different priorities...
-You have different priorities?
-Yeah.
Well, our views towards work
are different.
I want to work hard right now.
She's fine with minimal finances
as long as she can have a normal life.
Kind of like that.
It would've been great
if we were just friends.
But if we're going to be
in a relationship...
then I think...
we should have similar goals.
Yeah, you could motivate each other.
At first, she quit her other job
and said she'd focus on her modelling.
But lately she's either just at home
or going out.
I've been...
a little concerned about that lately.
We've talked about it before,
but she just says
she knows what she's doing.
She's just living off modeling, right?
-Yeah.
-Or is she?
She said she can get by.
-So then she's here when she's off.
-I can't get by with just modeling.
On her computer or watching TV...
And she says she's...
perfectly happy doing that.
That's fine if that's the case.
Oh, it's Nacchan.
-Who'd you think it was?
-You couldn't tell?
-You have bad vision?
-No, it's 20/20.
20/20 and you couldn't tell?
-20/20 is pretty good.
-It's perfect.
Oh, yeah.
-Long time no see.
The three of us had breakfast
for the first time this morning.
-Well, more like lunch...
-Which three?
Minori and Asari, not Asari...
Asari? That's bad.
I meant Arisa.
What do you girls talk about?
It's light stuff.
-We avoid mentioning the other day.
-I see.
-Minori's home, right?
-Yeah.
Do the two of you talk?
Not really.
You don't get along?
-We're not close.
-Well, you're probably just different.
Do you know about Minori?
-That she's leaving?
-Yeah.
So, before then...
I'd like for our relationship to change.
You scared me.
-Going to sleep?
-No.
-I wanted to talk.
-About?
You said you're leaving, right?
-So I am going to leave, too...
-Together?
Yeah, at the same time.
-End of February, is it?
-Yeah.
End of February.
Does it need to be timed with your school?
There's a month left.
If there's no merit being here...
I thought maybe I could only enjoy this
while I was still a student.
That's...
-Not right?
-Yeah, maybe not.
What's not right about it?
I thought maybe...
it'd be good to have
some kind of goal here...
so that it would benefit you.
But to just rely on this environment
or to just live easy feels wrong.
What do you want me to do?
-You want me to just leave?
-I'm not sure.
But I don't want you
to just pass time here.
I'm not here just because it's fun,
and I'm not just lying around.
How are things with Nacchan?
-It's awkward.
-Right?
You're used to withdrawing
and just giving up.
You tend to avoid
things that take effort.
Maybe that's something you can work on.
If there's an opportunity for growth,
maybe that's a good thing.
You quit your job
so that you could focus on modeling.
But I feel like you were more focused
when you were working.
I think right before the Girls Award show
was when you were working the hardest.
Why did you want to be with me?
You're easy to be with.
But I'm not the type to motivate.
No, you're not.
Is being with me
different than you imagined?
No, it's not that.
So this next month, maybe
you can think about what you can do
to try and show some growth.
I think about that, too. About growth...
I think it's your attitude.
Why don't you listen to me?
That's what I think.
I understand.
I'll think over what you said.
Is it too much to deal with?
-What?
-Is it too much to deal with?
Are you just saying that to end this talk?
-I did think that.
-I figured.
That's the part, I think, is bad.
I got upset because I tried to talk,
and you didn't listen to me.
That's what I mean.
It's that.
Just shut up and watch.
Okay.
I'll shut up and watch.
-This is messed up.
-This is a little...
When they were having breakfast,
Natsumi made...
some effort and tried to be friendly.
She did.
She found the meat and said,
"What's this?"
-I felt her effort.
-We all did.
But after such a big argument,
the power of meat is amazing.
-The power of Hidagyu.
There was an English label.
-The labels were fancy!
-Yeah, they were.
Things between Minori and Tatsuya
are a mess.
He clearly said they didn't match.
It was good before, but now its...
different.
Well, for Minori herself and her life,
maybe a little change on her part...
is necessary.
She must be pretty lazy
when the cameras aren't on.
She's at home all the time.
When something she doesn't like happens,
she shuts down.
She has that kind of attitude.
I think Uchi has noticed that about her
over the last little while.
I wonder who Hikaru will ask out?
-Arisa.
-Arisa, of course.
"You should,"
is what Aman meant?
While eating Shabu-Shabu meat,
he said, "You should ask her out."
He did say that.
Arman is worse than Pepper.
Need me to tear?
Oh, you did it.
-I did.
-I'm back.
Welcome home.
Oh, meat.
-You cooked the meat?
-Do you want some?
-Did you eat already?
-Just a bit.
Do you want some good meat?
I'll pass
even though I wanna eat.
-But will he be upset if we use it all?
-I'm sure it's fine.
-Is it just the two of you?
-Yeah.
-Nacchan, when's your next day off?
-My day off?
Near the end of January.
Do you want to go have dinner?
Dinner?
Sure, let's go.
Are you sure? If you're busy--
No, I'm free in the evenings.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
What? Where were you?
-I was at the gym.
-I see.
Are you making dinner?
I thought I'd cook Uchi's meat.
-It looks delicious.
-It's a luxury.
You should leave two pieces at least.
Small ones.
-Leave some?
-But it'll go bad if he doesn't eat it.
Maybe we should eat it.
What's your plan tomorrow, Hikaru?
I have construction work.
Oh, starting next week,
I'll be joining Hikaru.
Oh, yeah, Arman's coming.
-Really?
-I called my boss today.
You're going to wear them, too?
The parachute pants?
-Parachute pants?
-Is that what you call them?
-I don't know. They're like parachutes.
-Super long.
I saw Hikaru in them once.
It's really embarrassing
to wear them on the train.
Why? They're cool.
You look good in them.
Really?
It's huge.
It smells really good.
-It smells good.
-Yeah.
-I think that's good.
-Is it?
Watch out.
Looks amazing.
-Where are you going?
-I was gonna watch a movie.
-Got it.
-You're not eating?
It's okay.
-Bon appétit.
-Thanks, Uchi.
-Thank you.
-Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
-Is it good?
-It's delicious.
Wow, is this for real?
That's all you want?
-For real?
-I'm eating most of it, is that okay?
Can I eat it?
It's not my favorite.
-This?
-Yeah, it's a little fatty.
Yeah, it's got a lot of fat.
SAMEZU, TOKYO
PEARY GATES SHOOT
-How long have you lived there?
-It's been...
only a month still.
Is there anyone you're attracted to?
There's a guy from Hawaii.
His name is Arman.
We get along, but he's always home.
I wish...
I wish he'd work more.
He doesn't work?
Off and on.
Really?
Great personality though.
I wouldn't recommend a guy like him.
It should be someone who works.
And the new guy who arrived
at the same time as me...
his personality is totally my type.
Manly, but a little boyish,
straightforward...
but he's 18.
So young!
Eighteen, huh?
If he was 27 or something,
I would've totally fell for him.
Ready.
Cute.
Nice.
-I'm back.
-Welcome home.
-You're alone?
-Yeah.
-Hi.
-Welcome back. I mean, I'm back.
Welcome home.
Oh, there's Chamisul here.
Chamisul?
It's a Korean sake.
You finished the meat.
Finally.
What's wrong?
-Is everything okay?
-What?
I don't know.
I don't know, but he was quiet.
-Hi.
-Welcome back.
The meat is all gone.
About that...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, about that...
I wanna say something...
Oh, about that?
I'm kind of bothered by that.
You're mad?
Yeah, I'm pretty upset.
Where did the meat go?
I had some of the meat.
We had it for dinner last night.
Why?
I didn't have any.
There wasn't anything else
to make dinner with.
Isn't that a little strange?
I'm sorry.
That meat was from a client who came
all the way from Nagoya to visit Blast.
They run a Yakiniku Restaurant.
They liked their haircuts and our service,
and they went back to Nagoya happy.
And they sent the meat from Nagoya.
They even wrote a letter
saying how to eat it.
Explaining exactly how we should cook it.
They specifically wrote a letter about
how to eat it.
I told you that this was from a client.
And that it was from Nagoya.
I have a relationship with my clients.
There's value in the gift.
I'm sorry we ate it without permission.
Of course I'd be upset.
It's hard to draw the line
for things in the fridge.
That's not what I'm talking about.
It was obviously different.
The line doesn't matter here.
I'm very sorry.
Whatever.
He's mad we ate it yesterday?
I hadn't told him about it.
I get where he's coming from.
I get it, but...
-We shouldn't have.
-He should've just told us before.
But we should've asked him first, too.
Maybe we were wrong.
-We were definitely wrong.
-Usually, you would...
leave a note, "Don't touch."
No, we were wrong.
It's not enough to apologize.
That's all we can do.
That's all I can do.
I'll apologize.
But he's so mad.
This is so entertaining.
I didn't know these things happened.
You've got to be kidding.
-In the year 2016.
-You've got to be kidding.
This is new for Terrace House.
This incident has been recorded.
The meat crime topped everything.
The meat crime?
People really get angry at meat crimes.
I thought, "No way."
When Uchi seemed unhappy,
and the camera cut to the empty meat box,
I thought, "No, that can't be it."
-I think we all felt that.
-We all thought, "No way."
"That can't be it."
I mean, no one would write a script as,
-"The Meat Crime."
-No way.
-It's so insignificant.
-It would've been vetoed.
Yeah, like who cares.
The meat crime would never happen.
I wonder what he'll think
after he watches this episode?
"Minori said she didn't like it."
-She said it was fatty.
-That's right.
Oh, no. And the client might see it.
And the line from the 18-year-old.
"If you don't want us to eat it,
you should leave a note."
Hikaru is right, though.
He's right.
There was a scene like this
in Under One Roof.
The brother got mad
about his pudding being eaten,
saying, "You guys ate it
without telling me."
There was a scene like that.
-He should've approached it that way.
-That's right.
There was no need for such a serious tone.
I understand Uchi values his client
and their thoughtfulness,
but everyone else didn't know that.
The way he approached it was too dark.
-Way too dark.
-Yeah, dark.
He's not saying anything wrong, but...
But this...
This...
What should I do?
I'm going to crack up during the scene
when Minori apologizes.
"I'm sorry, but I ate the meat."
So, right now, I hope
she goes to the Japanese-style room,
and I hope they start talking
about meat again.
Like, "So, how'd you cook it?"
-Wouldn't that be hilarious?
-Yeah.
"That's not
how you're supposed to cook it."
"But it was so fatty..."
-"Did you add oil?"
-"I did."
"It's a teflon pan, so you didn't need to.
It's quality meat; it has fat already."
"I'm so sorry."
"That's not enough."
That's totally what he might say.
"Your apology won't bring back the meat."
She should just go buy some meat.
I really hope we end with that scene.
It's been so serious lately.
A light-hearted crime...
If the meat crime is his plan to distract
Natsumi and Minori from their fight,
and if it's a part of Uchi's master plan,
I'd be really impressed.
That's true!
Ah, a common enemy to allowing bonding.
How cool is Uchi!
That definitely did not happen!
They might break up over this.
Her boyfriend got mad
because she ate his meat.
You'd be okay with this?
If it were me getting lectured
about meat in front of everyone...
-Well, he's upset on behalf of his client.
-That's right.
But if you're asked why you broke up...
-Break up caused by meat.
"Yeah, I ate his meat."
And if he's asked why they broke up,
he'd say that she ate my meat...
Tori-chan's cracking up.
-You shouldn't laugh.
-It's gonna come back to you.
Tori-chan can't stop.
That was a treat.
Seriously, it's my first time
witnessing a break up caused by meat.
Uchi.
Sorry about before.
It's a mess in here.
I totally thought
it was for everyone to share.
No, it wasn't.
But...
was it something to get so mad about?
You were pretty upset.
I know it's just meat to you guys.
But it was something
that meant a lot to me.
So for you guys, just to go and eat it
like it was nothing
made me really upset.
Like if you got something
from someone special,
and if it was treated carelessly...
-Yeah.
-It's the same feeling.
I worked really hard.
And it was my client's recognition
and appreciation of my hard work.
So, for me, it meant a lot.
I understand that you didn't know.
So maybe it couldn't be helped.
But I had told Minori
and she still ate it.
I'm really starting to get angry at her.
She didn't tell me
after you guys ate it...
or even before.
And I came home
and found the meat was gone.
Isn't there something wrong there?
Yeah.
I was mad that it was all gone
when I got home.
Either way, I'm sorry.
I need to zone out for a bit.
I don't want to think about anything.
I'll get too upset.
I'm going to the store.
You want anything?
-I'm okay for now.
-A bento or anything?
-You haven't eaten, right?
-I'm okay.
Goodnight then.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I know it's all I can say, but I'm sorry.
I can't calm down right now,
no matter what you say.
Goodnight.