-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Ayumu is absent again today
for reasons related to him being young.
That's right.
-Now, so far...
-Yes.
First of all,
-Tatsuya is now on summer break.
-Yes.
He has asked all
three girls out on dates.
-It's Uchi Week.
-Uchi Week.
It's ridiculous.
-Something I can enjoy.
-What?
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22
Isn't it usually the other way around?
Then I'll make plans.
-Really?
-What?
I'll go out with Minori, too.
How about you, Minori?
-I...
-We'll discuss.
So each of the three has their own way.
He's approaching each girl differently.
-In front of everyone.
-Yes, he was.
I hope it will be disastrous.
Is it possible to screw them all up?
-What he thinks of you.
-You asked that?
MINORI NAKADA, 21
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21
-In a different way.
-Very straightforward.
-What do you think of me?
-Seriously?
-I think highly of her.
-Highly?
Why doesn't anybody think of me as a girl?
-I do.
-No, you don't.
I do too.
-She doesn't feel it.
-I don't.
So what's with that?
Why is Makoto ambiguous like that?
Does he like her or...
-He likes her.
-Oh.
And Minori is ready
to return the feeling, too.
-Yes, she is.
-And the tap dancer,
-Mr. Adachi.
-That's right.
-A problem about the aquarium.
-Yes, they made similar plans.
-Which aquarium?
-The one in Sky Tree.
I'm taking her to Enoshima.
Different aquariums.
What kind of duel will this be?
YUKI ADACHI, 28, TAP DANCER
Right.
So, Yuriko is showing interest
in the tap dancer,
but what if Uchi, kinda,
comes in high-handedly on to Yuriko,
who is innocently watching the fish,
and kisses her?
What?
And because of the kiss,
her feelings are forcibly shaken up.
-What?
-I want something like that to happen.
No, I totally don't want that.
Yeah, I want to see that.
I want a walrus to make outrageous
sounds when the vibe gets good.
-A walrus?
-Walruses make crazy sounds.
-I know.
-Right?
Yeah, walruses are scary.
That's not what I wanted to talk about.
I can't really distinguish
between a seal, a walrus and a fur seal.
Is the gentlest one a seal?
-Isn't it the fur seal?
-The fur seal.
Fur seal, seal, then walrus.
-Isn't it enough already?
-Therefore,
who's the fur seal, who's the walrus,
and who's the seal?
I get it.
I thought they were all walruses.
None of them are decent.
You got wrapped up with the walrus talk.
Shoot! I was trying to pull things back.
DAIBA, TOKYO
-This is amazing.
-Wow.
Excuse me.
It's so beautiful here.
It's so nice.
-Is this the first part of the date plan?
-The first part..
Thank you.
-I've decided.
-Are you ready to order?
How about you?
Hmm? Me? Ahi poke.
Me? Ahi poke.
Why?
It's the same.
-Shall we?
-Let's eat.
This is great.
Yuriko told me something.
It seems like we're being compared
or something.
Yes, like it's a taste test.
No, not like that.
Well, Makocchan said that it was weird
for you to date all three of us girls.
Really?
-Why?
-Maybe he's jealous.
Well, it's not like Minori
and Makocchan are together.
-If I--
-No, not yet at all.
No matter how much
Minori and I hang out together,
-it's none of his business.
-For sure.
TOKYO LEISURE LAND
It's nice here.
-It's nice.
-This is great.
Just great.
I did it!
Did you see that?
-I'll hit the seven.
-Seven.
-That was good.
-All right.
What? You go like this?
Wait.
Okay, okay.
Watch out.
It fell down.
This is so difficult.
Exercise is nice.
-Yeah.
-The exercise...
I want to exercise.
Girls I can exercise with are...
I'll do it, but I suck.
I like girls that have the attitude
to just do it regardless.
It was a good date.
-It was a good date.
-Good date.
Next will be my turn.
-Okay.
-I'll think of something.
I look forward to it.
I wonder what you like.
Think about it. Think about it.
-You throwing it out?
-Here.
Thanks. You're so kind.
-You want to go?
-Okay.
We'll miss dinner if we don't.
IKEBUKURO, TOKYO
MO-MO-PARADISE
How was Leisure Land?
I think things opened up today.
I see.
-Don't you think so?
-Hmm?
-I had fun.
-You had fun.
-A lot.
You had a day off, Mizuki?
I took a day off.
-She took time off.
-For Uchi.
And tomorrow?
Tomorrow is a date with Yuriko.
-This is totally a different subject.
-You're changing it?
-Yeah.
Yuki is amazing at tap dancing.
-I researched today.
-You researched.
-Did you research?
-Three-time champion?
National champion three years in a row.
-Really?
-What's with that?
-Remarkable in the tap dance world.
-He's grinning.
You've never said a word about that.
-Humble.
It's amazing.
Isn't three times in a row just amazing?
We're going to see you dance
this week, right?
The day after tomorrow.
That's right.
I'm just so-so.
I found a yuzu.
When are you gonna leave?
You have something after this?
-I have a rehearsal.
-Oh, yeah?
All of a sudden.
-Makoto, here, for now.
-Oh, cash.
You're going?
I'll zip out and zip back.
-Do your best.
-I'll do my best.
See you.
When are you going out tomorrow?
In the morning?
-Around 5:00 p.m.
-After school?
-Is it okay?
-Sure.
Where are we going?
-It's a secret.
-It's a secret?
I gave a lot of thought
about how I could entertain you.
Thank you.
What's going on with you two?
-You're all flirty.
-It happens.
-Yuriko.
-Tatsuya.
There you go!
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Phew.
-Rather...
-It's really low.
It's really low.
-I can't see what it looks like.
-You can't see.
All right.
-Are you working tonight?
-I'm working tonight.
At the cafe.
-Right, at the cafe tonight.
-Yup.
-I'll go there sometime.
-Please.
Barista.
All done.
But you can't see the back.
You're all ready.
What are you wearing?
It's Yuriko's style.
Is it Yuriko's style?
-Did you do it?
-I got it done.
-It's nice. A hair clip?
-So?
-Did Mizuki do it for you?
-Yes.
Yes, Mizuki did it for me.
-Want to go?
-Let's go.
Thank you, Mizuki.
Have fun.
I've been nervous all day.
-I couldn't focus on my studies.
-That's good, good.
It's good to be nervous.
-Actually, I...
-Yes?
What, are you making
some kind of shocking statement?
I like aquariums.
What? What's that?
I heard we're going to an aquarium.
-Was that leaked somehow?
-A little.
Moreover...
Enoshima?
You know!
-I wonder who gave it away?
-Who could it be?
It's pretty backed up.
We might make it just in time.
-It closes at 8:00 p.m.
-Oh, really?
ENOSHIMA
NEW ENOSHIMA AQUARIUM
-It's already closed.
-It's closed.
CLOSED FOR TODAY
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU AGAIN
I'm so sorry about that.
Oh, I'm so sorry, too.
-This isn't good.
-It's not good.
I want to bow down on my knees.
I must make up for this.
-Yeah?
-Next time.
-Let's do this again.
-All right.
NEW ENOSHIMA AQUARIUM
I'm shocked.
Oh, come on. Cheer up.
Cheers.
-It's good.
-Delicious.
Can I try?
Ginger and pineapple, right?
It's delicious.
-It's not for me.
-Really?
It doesn't taste good.
I want to go to Enoshima Aquarium.
Man, you're really dwelling on it.
I am truly sorry.
-Let's go.
-Next time.
-Oh, it's really coming down.
-Yeah.
This feels really new to me.
New?
I've never been out for dinner
with someone dressed so beautifully.
-Do I look that beautiful?
-Yeah.
Looks appealing.
-To the general public.
-Not that much.
Objectively speaking.
Objectively, huh?
What? What do you mean?
What do you mean?
Well, you yourself
look widely appealing.
No, not me.
-I'm pretty horrible on the inside.
-Really?
But actually,
you seem to be the most conscientious.
Or is that a mask?
-I'm back.
-You're back.
Hey.
-Uchi, how was your second date?
-How was it?
Being alone together was different.
-Really?
-With Yuriko.
-Totally different?
-But in a good way?
-Well...
-What?
I don't think in a good way.
-Not in a good way.
-Really?
What do you mean?
It took a lot of effort.
-You did?
-I did.
-Why?
-It's not like it was Yuriko's fault.
I think it was the way I approached her.
Among other things.
I was really tense.
Well, when I went for drinks with Yuriko,
she said you made her nervous,
or something like that.
I wasn't really able
to keep a conversation going with her...
-well.
-You?
-Something about Yuriko--
-It seems you have regrets.
I'm reflecting on it.
Like, my--
You don't need to feel so down.
-I think he is.
-Yeah, really. I'm feeling down.
Wow. The stress is awful.
Just amazing.
Hey, you're really feeling it.
Such amazing stress.
Only words of disdain come to my mouth.
He's a new type.
It's amazing.
But with Mizuki he seemed all right.
Yes, they seemed to be having fun.
And he said right in front of her,
"I've thought about our date tomorrow,
so please look forward to it."
But in the end,
because it didn't go well,
he got nervous, and in a bad way,
that the date didn't go the way he wanted.
But that thing about Uchi getting nervous,
perhaps...
-Yes.
-From his perspective,
"What's up with her?"
Like, "Why am I, of all people,
being so awkward?"
Like, "What is this?"
So, I think that has a chance of
evolving to romantic feelings.
Is it like,
"Why am I struggling with this?"
That's right.
But then again, Uchi...
despite that does things
-like grab her drink.
-Yeah.
Yuriko is quite something, too.
She doesn't seem in any way
affected by any of that.
Huh!
It's not working,
so Tatsuya is like, "What?"
-Something like that.
-I think so.
Usually, there would be
some kind of hesitation, but there wasn't.
So, "My moves aren't working."
Man, it's like Goku and Vegeta.
Amazing.
That's right. Like, pow, pow!
Then, pow, pow!
-What?
-Like, pow, pow, pow!
Amazing!
I wonder what Yuriko thinks about it.
-I wonder.
-Right.
Oh, like, "She's this type."
Like when Yuriko said,
"I wanted to go to the aquarium."
Like that.
That's a leading punch, you could say.
-I see.
-Right.
Yuriko told him
that she wanted to go...
but not necessarily with him.
And she's putting him on the line for it.
Right, so, her punch landed.
-It landed heavily.
-Heavily.
-So Tatsuya was caught off guard.
-That's right.
-Yuriko is the better player.
-Yeah.
-Amazing.
-She's an unexpected monster.
Maybe Yuriko was the walrus.
-What?
-She's a beast.
Amazing.
NAKAMEGURO, TOKYO
-Where?
Minori, can you put this in?
Sorry.
Hold this.
-Hmm?
-Never mind.
-Here?
-It's here.
-Here it is.
-Here.
It's under Yuki Adachi.
Someone else is coming later.
That will be 3,000 yen.
-Three thousand yen.
-Okay.
Hey.
Sorry for making you wait.
-You look kinda cool.
-Kind of? Thanks.
-Phew.
-The career woman vibe.
Like a career woman?
-Can I eat it?
-Sure, eat it.
Oh, it's starting.
-Adachi.
-That startled me!
Really?
-Amazing.
Thank you very much.
-I'm knocked out.
-That was really cool.
That was beyond expectation.
It was cool.
Outrageous.
That was badass.
I was surprised.
Were you impressed?
-That guy is cool.
-It was cool.
-Yes?
-It's Yuriko.
-Come in.
-Is Uchi here?
He's here.
Uchi, Yuriko's here.
-Can I come in?
-Yes.
-Hey, what's up?
-Thanks for letting me in.
I was thinking about
what we'd do tomorrow.
Right, tomorrow.
What'll we do?
We can't go to the aquarium, right?
Do you want to go to the aquarium?
-It doesn't have to be.
-It doesn't?
Well, you'll be going to
the aquarium with Yuki.
Yes, that's true.
If you just want to
do something with Uchi,
-then something else is...
-It doesn't have to be the aquarium.
So, do you want to just hang out with me
instead of having a do-over?
What? What's with that response?
It doesn't have to be the aquarium.
Let's just go out tomorrow.
Whatever the case,
do you want to go out tomorrow?
I'll think of something.
-I feel bad to make you plan again.
-No, no. It was me who...
Because of the time,
we weren't able to make it.
Okay.
-So, be ready for tomorrow?
-Yes.
Tomorrow...
Yes.
Are you okay to hang out with me tomorrow?
-There's some pretense there.
-Yeah, some pretense.
Yeah, you did that with some pretense.
That's right.
It doesn't have to be with me?
-I don't know.
-Right.
I don't know what's going on
with your mind, so...
I guess you don't know.
So we'll go?
-Okay.
-Sorry about this.
I'll think about it tomorrow.
-I suddenly showed up here.
-Oh, no, no.
-Good night.
Good night.
I'll think about it.
I wonder what was on her mind.
Indeed.
That's what I was thinking of asking.
-Right.
-Just now.
She made a suggestion first.
What's the matter, Yuri?
What is it?
What happened?
Tissue, tissue.
I'm so confused and...
not sure at all.
After seeing Yuki's dance,
I came home, and Makocchan
was in the living room.
He said that Uchi told him...
that his date with you
was carefree and fun.
But it seemed he was
quite tense on our date.
Uchi told him something like that.
So, I heard that from Makocchan.
And then I really didn't know
what was going on anymore.
And then I just went to the guy's room
just to ask what we were going to do.
But then...
Makocchan kind of implied that
I didn't seem eager to go
to the aquarium.
He asked if I wanted to go.
I don't know what made him say that.
So, like, I heard it from Makocchan--
-Like, it means he knows, too.
-Yes, that's right.
So they both asked me what I wanted.
After that, Makocchan texted me,
like, "Are you all right?
Let me know if there's something
you find hard to discuss with Uchi.
I'm in my room, so you can call me
over anytime."
And then something like,
"I don't want to see you sad."
I kinda forgot.
I'm really confused.
Like, why did he text me that?
You know, these past two or three days,
I had a moment when I thought that
Makocchan liked you.
-But...
-Is that...
But, I don't know.
Maybe I'm thinking too much.
But isn't Makocchan like that
with everyone?
Recently, I've been a little unsure
of Makocchan.
I'm really not sure about him.
-Whoa!
-What, what?
-Amazing!
-We're confused too!
Let's all cry together.
I can't get my mind in order.
So, to get to Yuriko, Makoto...
did this little thing...
-No.
-Is he that type of guy?
Maybe he doesn't know that
he shouldn't tell.
-He doesn't know.
-He doesn't.
Wait.
A normal adult
wouldn't tell someone that
their date was tense with them.
You don't ever do that.
He's a lot like Seina.
Really?
SEINA SHIMABUKURO, 28
He's Seina as a pitcher.
Everyone sees Makoto as
trying his hardest at baseball.
-He's tanned.
-Yes, he's serious.
Remember he quit for two years
to just lounge around.
-That's right.
-However,
it's like we've been fooled to think
he doesn't have experience with girls.
-It is weird.
-He's a real monster.
This person is not a decent human either.
-Mr. Yamasato?
-Yeah?
-They're not listening to you at all.
-What?
-Oh, sorry.
-No way!
They're totally not listening.
If this was a crime drama,
I would be off the cliff.
-By yourself.
-By myself.
-No one there.
-Sorry.
No, really.
If he was evil, what would you do?
-That would be a shock.
-If he was a mastermind.
Even the barista said that.
"I think he's been strange lately."
-She doesn't know.
-Right.
It's like they suddenly noticed something.
Yes, come to think of it,
he's been asleep the whole time.
-But why did Makocchan say that?
-Yeah.
I don't think he's just dumb.
It's astonishing...
Really?
Is he just a child?
But that text,
"I don't want to see you sad."
-For a child, that seems like...
-Oh, that's right.
how an adult would approach someone.
Maybe it's a line he's seen before.
Maybe he borrowed the whole line.
"I don't want to see you sad."
-"I think I read that in a book before".
-That's right.
Oh, Guri and Gura's Adventures.
What an idiot!
"When Gura was sad,
this is what Guri said."
It's weird that a 21-year-old is
referring to Guri and Gura.
What an idiot!
The best case scenario is that
he's an idiot.
If he isn't, then it's quite unusual.
-Right.
-All of it.
If this was all calculated behavior,
it would be...
-That's frightening.
-A real horror.
That would be frightening.
You got a minute?
What's up?
You startled me.
You said to Yuriko...
that Uchi expressed...
how he was tense with her.
What did you intend by that?
To Yuriko?
If it was something that was
just between you guys
that you secretly told Yuriko,
then, of course, that would be uncool.
Or, if you like her or whatever
and was concerned about her--
-Me?
-Yes. Just, if so.
And you told her because of that,
well, it was still a wrong thing to do.
If that was something positive, it's fine.
But if it's something negative for Yuriko,
it could mess her up.
I wonder if you thought of
how it could affect her
and how it would negatively affect Uchi.
Like, they're going to be unsure
of each other now.
Yuriko is so concerned about it,
she can't think of the date.
Don't you feel bad that she's concerned
about how he thinks of her?
I mean, I feel sorry for Uchi, too.
I'm sure he told you
because he trusts you.
Well, I just said
whatever I heard yesterday.
It just came out.
You have to make things vague.
Well, she can still ask about it
if I make things vague.
I feel bad for what I started.
Whatever the case,
I figured something wasn't right.
Just be careful with what you say.
Good night.
What a bummer.