-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
KENTARO FUJIMURA NOT PRESENT
DUE TO A FILM SHOOT.
Things are happening at Terrace House.
-Last week...
-Yes, they seem to be.
-We had our fifth couple form on the show.
-That's right.
I like you.
I want you to go out with me.
I like you, too.
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD
-Do you really like me?
-I really like you.
There's no stopping their feelings.
-Yeah, it was so great.
-In Yokohama...
There's some anxiety.
They go camping.
-Yes, it turns into a harsh trip.
-That's right.
Lots of things happened at camp.
-Can so much happen in one night?
-It could.
Misaki cries, frustrated at herself
for being jealous of an ex.
That's right.
It was an old picture on the camera.
Does she like him too much?
I realized...
how much I really like you.
Me, too.
-I realized how much I like you.
-I really thought that.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-I just have to believe you.
-After she said, "I'm sorry."
-Right?
Like, "I love you."
Anything that happens to them turns
into something positive at this point.
-They're in a cool spot.
-That's right.
A festival or to see fireworks.
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD
You sure you're okay it's with me?
I want to go with you.
Let's go then.
-They're going to wear yukatas.
-That's right.
He asks if it's okay that it's with him...
But, "Let's go!"
He says let's go.
Like, is it okay to attack, too?
Poor Martha.
-Yeah...
-Yes, poor girl.
-Arman's engine was roaring.
-That's right.
Even though he's got no tires.
Of all the girls I met here,
not many would say what's on their mind.
-You mean my personality?
-Yeah. And you're cute, too.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD
Out of all the girls that have been here,
I think you're the cutest.
I'm serious. Why are you laughing?
He might still be able to convince her.
I don't know. She looked sad.
The guy she likes
is out there with another girl.
And while she's thinking about that,
this guy's coming on to her.
Even though there are fireworks,
nothing is fun at that point.
-I suppose.
-Yeah, for Martha...
But Martha is headstrong,
so I'm sure it won't end there.
What move will Terashima make?
And Arman...
Arman... even at skateboarding,
Byrnes was doing well, but he...
Arman was terrible!
He was quietly falling
in the background.
The kind of fall
that has no entertainment value.
That's Seina.
-This person?
-Yeah.
They started going out at Terrace House.
These two...
-Oh, you mentioned Daiki before.
-Yeah.
Martha...
Why are you hanging out?
-We were...
-It's unusual.
-You were watching Terrace House?
-Yeah.
-The movie version.
-Which one is it?
The movie version?
What's wrong? You seem down.
Yeah, during the campfire, too.
There was something wrong.
-She asked if I was okay...
-There was something wrong.
Misaki asked if I was okay.
-I can stop it, it's okay.
-Oh, no. Okay.
-Take it slow.
-I'm sorry about yesterday.
No worries.
There's been a lot on my mind.
I've been bothered.
Since the barbecue,
I found myself being careful
about my behavior.
Sort of being reserved.
And at the campfire, Arman invited me
and it was the two of us.
And the other two are somehow
in perfect position in front of us.
So I don't know.
We'd talk, right?
But my focus keeps going over there.
None of what Arman was saying
was registering, right?
It did! It did, but...
But still, it's like,
why is this happening?
I couldn't help but think that.
But that bothered feeling
is probably there
because I'm aware of my uncertainty.
I don't know.
And then afterward, we all gathered
and went to get fireworks.
But after that...
Riko asked Hayato out on a date.
Oh, really?
Riko was talking really happily.
That expression really affected me.
-You must really like him.
-No, but...
Maybe.
If it's making you cry this much.
It's what you want to do about it.
I really don't know.
-Yeah.
-I thought that you...
I thought you'd be the type
to ask him out more casually.
-But you're pretty...
-I was going to try that.
I thought about asking casually.
I think that's fine.
Just ask him.
Because you never know.
It might not work out either.
But you're thinking about Riko.
So is that why you can't?
If I just casually ask him out to lunch,
I think it'd be okay.
I don't think there's any reason
you have to withdraw.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
-Welcome back.
-You look sleepy.
-Why do you have your hat on?
I went straight to work.
Oh, that's right.
To work, that is.
-I'm exhausted.
-You must be super sleepy.
And you drove.
You're in pajamas.
-What?
-You're in pajamas.
Yep, I'm in pajamas!
Oops, I kicked my leg.
-The pajama-look is great, isn't it?
-No way.
-It's looks cute.
-That makes me happy.
How'd it go?
What? With Misaki?
An easy make-up?
-Yeah.
-It wasn't awkward?
That's good.
Hayato, for lunch...
What do you do during work?
Just eat at work?
-Food from work?
-No.
I eat out. Whatever I feel like.
No way.
Let's go grab quick lunch.
A quick lunch.
-Sure. Lunch?
-It could be tea.
Sure.
Okay.
-It'll be late though, most likely.
-What?
How about tea?
-No, I...
-Why did you stutter on "tea"?
-Tea?
-No, I...
What happened?
After lunch time,
so it'll be around 2:00 or 3:00 p.m.
-That's fine.
-You'll get hungry.
-Most people would be.
-I can wait.
-You want to?
-A quick lunch.
Should we go, then?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Any day.
-Any day that works for you.
-This week works.
Any day that works for you.
Okay.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Hello.
-Is here okay?
-Yeah.
-Break time?
-Yeah, break time.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Not at all.
-Did you wait long?
-I'm hungry.
-You're hungry? Should we order?
-What were you doing?
-Nothing.
I haven't been doing anything.
Just a quick lunch?
We haven't really talked.
-What?
-I've been meaning to ask.
You invited me to lunch, right?
-What are your motivations...
-My feelings, you mean?
I'm sure it's just casual, but...
I asked because I wanted to get to know
you better.
Of course.
Why? Why?
For me, because I know how Arman feels.
Not that he's fallen for you yet.
He said something?
-Well, he's asked you out on dates, right?
-Yeah.
-So it's tough to go out with you.
-I see.
-So I wanted to make that clear.
-It's the same for me.
-Because of Riko?
But...
But I... Oh, thank you.
-Bon appétit.
Did you hear that Riko asked me out?
To the festival? You heard?
For Riko, I think it took a lot of effort.
How did it make you feel?
Is it okay to ask? You don't have
to say if you don't want to.
It made me happy.
-Yeah, it was the first time, right?
-Yeah.
But I'm not sure if it's okay.
What makes you think that way?
-She's working hard right now.
-What do you mean?
-With work. She's just starting.
-Yeah.
My presence might have
a negative impact, I think.
But that's not for you to decide, is it?
-It's not, but it concerns me.
-Well, yeah.
If Riko asks, would you be able
to tell her about this?
-I could.
-You could?
-You mean this lunch, right?
-Yeah. You can totally tell her?
I don't mind telling
Arman about this, too.
Of course we can tell them about this.
I could, but...
But what?
Maybe we shouldn't go out
alone together anymore.
Us, you mean? Sure.
That's totally fine.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
He knows what's right, it seems.
It's Arman's fault?
-He turned her down.
-He turned her down, but he's Terashima.
People don't usually say
this stuff at this point.
-Yeah.
-I mean, it was just lunch.
-It'd be embarrassing if you're wrong.
-It's hard to bring up.
-It is.
-What if you're wrong?
-That's right.
But Terashima can be like that.
But at this point,
the two of them are meeting.
I think so too, Torichan.
We're the same.
-You. Hey, you...
-The same?
-What?
-You...
You've never experienced this.
What?
Two girls tell you they like you.
And then you have to do
right for both of them.
You're not picturing it!
You're not able to picture it at all!
Your canvas is blank.
So Terashima is going with Riko?
-The love triangle is over?
-Yeah.
-It's ended.
So Arman can get in when she's vulnerable.
I don't know about that.
There's a slim chance
that a miracle may happen.
Yeah, there is that slim chance.
But I'm not sure that Arman
will take that chance.
He probably won't see the slim opening.
Yes?
Why are you knocking?
In case you were doing something.
-Hey.
Sorry to come in suddenly.
-Not at all.
-I don't mean to be all formal.
But there's something I have to tell you.
Something I should have said earlier.
Oh.
-Oh?
-Oh.
You know how we went camping?
And it naturally split off into
me and Arman, Riko and Hayato,
and Misaki and Yuuki.
It really bothered me at the time.
So yesterday, I asked Hayato,
even if it's between shifts,
if he'd want to get lunch with me.
I invited him out.
So we went out to lunch today.
But he said he felt guilty.
He clearly said he felt guilty.
And that he couldn't go out
with just me anymore.
So...
So, I know it's kind of late,
but I felt that maybe
I should have told you earlier.
I'm really sorry I'm telling you now.
No...
I totally didn't notice.
-Really?
-I've never asked anyone out before.
So my mind was occupied with that.
I couldn't think of anything else.
So I don't think just the two of us
will be going out anymore.
Are you okay with that?
It's not that I've stopped
being interested in him.
That's the truth.
I don't want you
to have to lie to yourself.
And I don't want you
to agonize over it.
When I move on, I'm sure I'll be able
to tell you more honestly next time.
I'm glad to hear that.
With this as an opportunity.
I'm still not sure about Hayato.
I'm not really sure how I feel.
But he understood that it took effort
for you to ask him out.
I see.
He noticed the effort it took?
MISHUKU, TOKYO
We did go to lunch, since he agreed to go.
We went yesterday.
Wow, real-time.
MAMI NAKAMURA
HAIR AND MAKE-UP
-It's super real-time.
-So we went.
He told me the two of us
can't go out alone anymore.
I was rejected before
I could ask him out on a date.
That's what happened.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Now I...
I want to support Riko.
-I see.
-Yeah.
When you have
someone you're interested in,
can you really hold back your feelings?
I'm running from my feelings.
It makes me run away, I think.
Maybe it's pride.
-You can't be honest?
-No.
I get how you feel.
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILD CARE WORKER
From Hakata, Fukuoka
'10 Begins work in entertainment industry
'11 Graduates from Daiichi
Pharmaceutical University High School
'13 Moves to Tokyo
Last Relationship: One year ago
Hey.
Welcome back.
What's wrong, Yuuki?
What?
Arman and I were going to the market.
And...
we were on skateboards.
I suddenly heard a big sound.
And when I looked up,
a car was stopped in the intersection
and Arman was on the ground.
We called the ambulance
and he went to the hospital.
When did that happen?
-Just a while ago.
-Just a while ago?
How is he?
-His head was bleeding.
-Seriously?
Yeah.
Was he conscious?
-He was.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
What should we do? Just wait?
Hey.
-How are you?
-You surprised me.
-We were so worried.
-I'm alive.
I'm so relieved.
Your shirt's ripped.
-I'm so relieved.
-Sorry to worry you.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
No bones are broken.
-Scary.
-I just need to take meds.
I got four stitches.
I'm so relieved, though.
I'm sorry, Yuuki.
-I'm glad.
-I'm really relieved.
I'm seriously sorry.
-Sorry.
-You might have been dead.
-My tooth chipped a little.
-Do you want some water?
Thanks.
-Your tooth chipped?
-Yeah, it did.
It's fine that you're always...
so care free to do what you like.
-That's something good about you, but...
-Let me just switch seats.
But...
But I want you to realize
when things are dangerous.
You're right.
I won't do anything stupid anymore.
Seriously.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Everyone.
-Remember that there are people who worry.
-Yeah.
No, I've never done Gravia.
Shonen Sunday Shoot!
-So it's your first Gravia?
-Yes, my first time.
Well, since it's your first time...
-Yes.
-There's probably a lot to consider.
Like how to pose.
-Ready to begin.
-Ready.
WEEKLY SHONEN SUNDAY
COVER GRAVIA SHOOT
-Very cute.
-Cute.
Bring your hood up higher.
-She's the cutest girl in Japan.
-In all of Japan?
Looks cute.
Without the hood...
-Can you do it without the hood?
-Yes.
-You're okay?
-Let's take off the jacket.
Show us your waistline.
-Amazing.
-Stop.
-Please stop.
-You don't like that right?
-Yeah, I really don't.
-You don't?
-It's embarrassing.
-Please stop that.
Okay. Nice.
The innocent look is nice.
Can you lean forward a little?
-Forward?
-The light...
Okay. Good.
Okay, it looks good.
Good work.
Then let's wet her hair.
We'll do a shot
like you came out from the pool.
Are you okay?
Okay.
Good, good.
Nice, nice.
Okay, we're done.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
I was remembering things.
-It made me emotional.
-You were remembering?
Right now, I'm sure there will be times
YUJI MATSUO
MANAGER
when you're not sure
about what you're doing.
But in the end, I'm sure
it'll become something you're happy with.
Yes.
Thank you.
-I hope you work hard.
-Yes.
Did you see the drawings I did?
-You've only done two, though.
-I haven't finished.
-Hayato looks like him, though.
-Right?
-Riko too, actually.
-It looks like Riko, right?
-What are you doing about meals?
-I eat whatever.
-No way.
-Seriously.
-Tell me when you're off.
-Okay.
-Tomorrow.
-I don't know about tomorrow.
If I have time,
I'll totally make something.
I'll be living like this
for the next three days at least.
I think it'll be more than three days.
-You're taking time off work, too?
-I am.
There's so many areas to put this on.
Looks painful.
Looks really painful.
Can I just ask you to do my face?
Just here.
-Why, can't you do that yourself?
-I can't see.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Here.
It looks super painful.
You sure it's okay?
-Just kidding. It's not bad.
-But it looks seriously painful.
It looks so painful.
-I can put some here?
-Yeah.
Looks painful.
Yeah, just there.
-Looks so painful. Okay.
-Okay, thanks.
What about your ears?
-The ear looks painful.
-The ears are fine. It's dry.
-I put some on yesterday.
-It's dry here, too.
I just wanted you to put it on.
Who? By who?
Oh, it's Yuuki Byrnes.
You came back together?
-Yeah, we came back together.
-Welcome back.
-I saw him at the station.
-Oops, I said I'm back.
-Welcome home.
I saw a bunch of books. Are you studying?
-Yeah, a little.
-I see.
-To be a child care worker?
-Yeah.
Did you go?
With Hayato?
Didn't you say you were going
to lunch with him?
-Yeah, I did.
-You said you were going to...
-I told Misaki, but I haven't told you.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, I did.
-How was it?
I forgot about it already.
-It's fine.
-You forgot?
-What about with Arman?
-What?
Well, Arman's in this state, right?
So what about your plans?
-Won't be until later?
-Yeah.
After I get better.
So you guys just had lunch?
-Yeah, we just had lunch.
-I see.
You didn't talk?
We did talk.
But I've forgotten the details already.
When did you go? Recently?
Last week? For now...
the two of us can't go out alone.
Why?
There's a reason for it.
Having heard the reason...
well...
I felt he had a point.
-So I understood.
-Well, we'll see how things go anyway.
-Yeah, we'll see how it goes.
-I see.
I didn't realize.
You asked if she went out
with Hayato, right?
Arman didn't know about it.
You know how Martha feels
and you know how Arman feels.
-I do.
-Knowing that,
it's something you shouldn't have asked.
That's what I thought.
If Arman wasn't there...
then you could've asked how it went.
I'm sorry about that.
I wasn't thinking at all.
We all live together,
so it's something you should think about.
Yeah. I'll be careful from now on.
-Good morning.
-You're up?
-I'm up.
What are you making?
-Green curry and...
-Seriously?
And Tom Yum Gai soup.
-Oh, nice.
-Do you like it?
-I love it.
-Seriously?
-You said you liked Thai food.
-I love it.
-It's my first time.
-What?
-What is?
Being run over by a car
and then having someone cook for me.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
Did you talk to Yuuki?
Yeah. We did.
When we were all together,
you said you had lunch with Hayato.
-Yeah.
-So, about that.
You were concerned about it?
He apologized for saying it
without considering it.
I'm fine, though. I don't mind.
You seem like you'd be fine.
How was it, though?
Was lunch with Hayato fun?
It was fun. It was fun, but...
Yeah.
Like I said yesterday,
it's not like anything's going to happen.
-Bon appétit.
-We can finally eat.
-Looks great.
-How is it?
-It's good.
-It's edible?
-It's great.
-You have to go to the hospital tomorrow?
-Yeah.
Get better quick so we could go somewhere.
Yeah.
If I get cleared,
let's go somewhere this weekend.
-This weekend?
-Yeah.
It was really good. Thank you.
-No problem.
-Kapunka.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for the meal.
-I'm going to go get ready.
I'm going to go get ready.
Leave it. I'll wash up later.
-Will you really?
-I will. I'll be home all day.
So you are going to be home.
I'm full.
I'm so full. See you later, Arman.
Yeah, good luck.
-That was surprising.
-I was so surprised.
So they went to the market on a skateboard
and Arman was run over by a car?
When he looked, Arman was on the floor.
-I mean, he was so terrible at it.
-Yeah.
It was too much.
Also, according to the law,
"For streets with heavy traffic,
the use of roller skates, and other
similar activities, are prohibited."
Arman was reprimanded by the officer
in charge of the case.
-So Arman was at fault.
-Totally.
-Things are going well with Martha.
-She just put medicine on him.
-She also cooked for him.
-That's true.
"Ointment-play" is a thing.
Really? It is nice to have ointment
rubbed on you.
The mucous membrane, right?
I've heard of that before.
So when I hear he's got a fever,
-I really want to put in the enema.
-I don't understand.
"Let me put it in!"
-You've totally lost us.
-Really?
I was right with you
but then you took off!
So I'm happy when they're vulnerable.
I have heard you should
attack when they're vulnerable.
-Well, attack, yes...
-It's like threading a needle.
It's the smallest path. It's there, but...
It's like what we were saying
about a slim chance.
So it's flipped around.
-It was a miracle.
-Yes, thanks to the accident,
they ate together,
and though Martha wasn't love-struck,
she was comfortable.
She realizes it's easy to be with him.
She doesn't have to try so hard.
If she feels that way, then maybe...
Well, even as we say this,
after the accident,
he may have thought
he could get closer to Martha,
but then Yuuki Byrnes comes along
and reveals Martha likes Terashima.
Oh, his expression...
When Arman was run over,
Byrnes was the one
who apologized the most.
-Even though he cried the most.
-He cried the most.
But he dumped salt on his wounds.
Here, take that!
-Of course, Misaki was upset.
-Yes.
Riko's tears over her Gravia shoot.
According to Triendl,
your first shoot was like that.
-Tends to make you feel that way.
-I see.
You didn't like to do bathing suit shots?
I never did a bathing suit shoot.
-You haven't?
-I haven't, but...
But you felt that way at shoots
where you had to show more skin?
-That's never happened to me before.
-Oh, you haven't.
Father, please!
She was acting like she understood.
Well, she's the only here who would.
What about you?
I have, but just sumo wrestling
in a bathing suit.
-Ah, that kind.
-It might've been a little different.
-You didn't cry?
-No, I didn't.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
It's raining. And its my second time
going to 109 with you.
-There's so many.
-There's a lot.
Where should we start?
Did Hayato say what kind he likes?
Hayato...
said something pastel colored.
-Pastel?
-That's what I wanted anyway.
Pastel?
Maybe a white base? That's cute.
-Is this more mature?
-Yeah, it's cute.
This one, then?
Is this one really okay?
Does it match my face?
Yeah, it's good.
The belt will change it's look.
Then I'll go with this one.
Okay, it's decided.
I'm surprised you decided to go.
Because you invited him,
have your feelings changed?
If I'm restricted by my own rules...
-Like Arman said?
-Yeah, I can't be happy.
So if I feel like I want to go,
then I should go.
That's true.
Hayato understands, right?
Because you told him
you didn't want a yukata date at first.
But now that you've asked him...
Even though you haven't said so in words,
he must know how you feel.
I don't know how Hayato feels,
but what are you going to do
if he says something?
-If he says he likes me?
-Yeah.
I'd be happy, but...
-You'd think about it.
-Yeah.
And I'd still feel like, "Really?"
I'd have doubts.
I'd want to be sure.
Yeah.
But that means you're already...
-I must have feelings for him.
-Yeah.
It's gradual.
-You're getting closer to liking him?
-Yeah.
-I know I'm slow, but...