-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
A lot happened last week.
No one saw it coming.
It was shocking.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
Will you be my girlfriend?
Family? Brother? Like friends...
The more we hung out,
the more my feelings tilted that way,
I guess.
Earlier, both Tokui and I said
some things about Arisa...
But neither of us can really say anything
about anyone else.
Why not? You guys are right.
She led him on.
Holding his hand and everything.
It's not right.
I'd hold hands.
-I wouldn't be able to help it.
-That's right.
-That's not true, right, Triendl?
-I wouldn't hold hands!
Right? It's Christmas.
No. It's Christmas.
I wouldn't hold his hand!
What about you, Kentaro?
-I wouldn't hold hands.
-See?
-That's right.
-That's how it should be.
And even if I did...
Let's say I did.
Afterwards, when everyone was telling me
how my actions were misleading,
I wouldn't cry.
No way.
I definitely wouldn't cry.
She's the guardian of tears.
I...
I'm not ready for a relationship now,
but it's not that I don't like...
So, you don't think of me as a sibling?
I do want to get to know you...
better.
I understand.
And we have new members.
Beautiful ones, at that.
I model and act.
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD
And I do construction on the side.
What's your type?
Mature.
Well, I've only dated older women.
He's half-Italian.
Of course he's popular with the ladies.
-Italy, right?
-Yes, Italy.
-The country of love.
-Yes.
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD
Do people have real relationships here?
-Yeah.
-Watching it on TV...
I was wondering if you really
fall for each other.
-Cute.
-She's cute.
Natsumi seems like
a daytime soap opera character.
She does.
Like a heroine from
the inspirational drama.
-She does.
-That sense of purity.
If you line their pictures up,
it's like the start of a new drama.
Opposing Poles.
In another country?
Perhaps we need another meeting
to come up with a better title.
How about, Opposite Poles?
Do you usually cook at home?
Yes, I like to cook.
You don't eat out very often?
-I'll go if I'm invited...
-Want to help?
-The cucumbers?
-But I really enjoy cooking.
-I can do that.
-That's good.
-Let's cook together.
-Yeah...
-while having a drink.
-Great idea!
I want a drink now.
It's ready.
Looks delicious.
Welcome to Terrace House.
-Cheers!
-Bon appétit.
-Welcome back.
What?
Nice to meet you.
-I'm Uchihara.
-I'm Natsumi.
-Nice to meet you.
-I was so surprised.
I thought I possibly came
to the wrong house.
That's so nice.
Like you're in a relationship.
-What is? Now?
-Your back and forth.
Oh, you know already.
You watched the show?
I saw a little bit on TV.
Did they already ask you
why you came here?
I just thought it seemed like fun.
That's good enough.
Fun is reason enough.
-There's no one to be irritated.
-There was someone who used to get upset.
-What do you mean? A member?
-Yeah, one of the members would say
"Why are you alive
if you don't have a purpose?"
I might have seen that part.
He was strict
when it came to pursuing dreams.
Do you two have dreams for the future?
Well, you know how I model and act?
I want to make it to the top.
Especially with my acting.
I want to be an actress.
-Oh, I see.
-I want to act.
What about languages?
How many languages can you speak?
A little bit of Italian.
I'm fluent in Portuguese.
I can understand English.
So if Arman spoke in English,
I can answer in Japanese.
You seem like the shy type.
Not at all.
It's nice to hear her talk
and to hear the Kansai accent.
Arisa has an accent, too.
-Accents are hot.
-Yeah.
We should have this conversation
with just the guys.
-You can do that later.
-We will.
Accents are nice, though.
When they say "Can you help me?"
with the accent...
-It sounds so good.
-Yeah, I wanna be told "Why not?"
Stop.
Now it's hard for me to talk.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-He doesn't.
I don't.
-You must be popular with the girls.
-Not at all.
You seem like you'd be popular
with 40-somethings who'd say you're cute!
-Oh, yeah!
-Well, I've only dated older women.
-What's the oldest you've dated?
-Thirty-six.
And how old were you then?
It was a year ago, so I was 17.
But what's your type?
Did you ask already?
-Yeah.
-What was it?
Someone manly.
-These two guys are manly.
-Yeah.
What do you mean, "Yeah"?
I don't want to be told that most.
-You're kind of girlie.
-I see.
-This is a little awkward.
-It is.
-She's tough on me.
-That's probably best.
-We're both tough on each other.
-I'm super sweet.
On the flip side,
as weird as that sounds,
what do you like about him?
She won't be able to answer that.
I'm still thinking about it.
Thinking about it?
That must be a shock to you.
-There are lots of things.
-Don't say.
But don't ask me here.
I'll tell you later.
Is your week packed with work?
January is pretty busy for me.
I have to leave for China
the day after tomorrow.
-China?
-What? China?
Yeah.
-What for? Work?
-Yeah, for work.
-For a week?
-Four days.
I see.
-So you're here, then you're gone.
-Yeah.
That's true.
-I used it.
-You did already?
-Okay.
-Yay!
Oh, you're done?
Then it's just you.
So we're done.
-So we're done.
-We're done.
Wait, why?
When the poorest becomes the wealthiest,
The game is over. God's promotion.
-What's that?
-I see.
Oh, Arisa's back.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Wow. Two?
-It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Natsumi Saito.
-I'm Arisa Ohata.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Oh, he stood up.
-I'm Hikaru Ota.
-Sorry?
Hikaru Ota?
I'm Arisa Ohata.
-Nice to meet you.
Now that we're all here...
To our meeting.
Cheers!
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
You two are a couple, right?
Are you guys?
-No.
-No, we're not.
-Not a couple.
-No, not a couple.
But sort of?
Well, we went on a few dates.
She's a hat designer.
-Hats?
-Yes.
So you could make a hat for me?
-A hat?
-If you ask, she will.
-For real?
-Yes.
-You're starting your own brand, right?
-Starting?
Yes, I'm planning
an exhibition for February.
Wow.
-It's coming up.
-Yeah.
Is everyone tired of cards?
Should we watch something downstairs?
-In the game room?
-Yeah.
What's the game room?
Oh, you haven't seen it yet?
-You haven't seen it?
-Why don't you show her?
-You should take her.
-Okay.
Let's take these.
-What's the game room?
-So...
The game room?
You'll see.
What do you think?
-You'll see.
-I'll know when I see it?
It's... interesting.
Isn't it?
He's good-looking, isn't he?
-Definitely.
-Yeah.
He has the quality of a model.
You should ask her about her type.
-What's your type?
-Someone who can survive on an island.
On an island?
-Not you?
-No, that's totally me.
He's in construction.
He can build you a house.
By that, do you mean the wild?
Someone who could start anew,
even if he lost everything.
This is the game room.
There are games and Netflix.
-So this is where you watch the show.
-Yeah, we watch it together.
Is it different than how you imagined?
Everyone is...
more reserved than I imagined.
It'll get better once things settle.
I think we're all nervous
because you're new.
That's why we're like that.
I'm sure it'll be fun.
We can drink together.
That's true.
We do seem to have that in common.
Yeah.
Have you gone out anywhere recently?
To Kamakura.
-Do you like the ocean?
-I love the ocean.
Me, too.
Do you know Japanese beaches well?
Not at all.
Then let's explore Japanese beaches.
That'll be nice.
Let's take the car out.
-Whenever you have time.
-Sure, I'm usually free.
What's the oldest you're willing to date?
Forty-five.
You're into the cute type?
More the cool type.
-The cool beauty? That's Arisa.
-Yeah.
-Definitely not.
-She does give a mature impression.
-Yes.
-Really?
-Well, the first impression anyway.
-First impression?
-Yeah.
And Natsumi?
I noticed she's pretty forward.
I thought so, too.
You too, right?
When Arman said he would take her
to the game room.
She said, "Let's take these,"
and grabbed Arman's whiskey.
She did grab his whiskey.
So, I guess, based on first impression,
Arman is her type.
You look like you want to say something.
I haven't said anything.
I was just thinking, "Ah, I see."
-How are things with Arman?
-With Arman?
After cleaning up together, we made up.
Since then, we only exchanged
Happy New Year greetings.
-By text?
-Yeah.
The mood was so languid in Terrace House.
Because of Natsumi's tone.
Like the way she says,
"Really?"
Or, "What's a game room?"
That languid tone permeated.
Natsumi is in control.
It's a little scary, isn't it,
and how perfectly she carries herself?
She'll definitely be able to capture
a guy's heart.
-Oh, definitely.
-Definitely.
-She's unexpectedly forward.
-Yes, it was surprising.
Arman is apparently desirable.
-No, that's not it.
-No, no...
-What? What?
-See, that's not it.
-She's not making a move on Arman.
-She was!
For Natsumi,
she was just asking,
"Where's the game room?"
"Let's take these."
And she took the drinks...
That was really just a light jab.
-Actually, not even a jab.
-No way!
When she said she didn't know
beaches in Japan well either,
I thought it would end there.
But she said,
"Let's explore them together."
If it were me, I'd think she liked me.
No, no. And the way she said it,
"Let's discover them together then."
We're going to get this every week now.
Are you going to do Natsumi's line
in that tone every time?
-I want to recreate that tone.
-He wants to do it.
-I see.
-So the way she asks
won't make people feel bad.
And in fact, they could get to know
each other and make friends in this way.
From Natsumi's point of view,
that's all it is.
You're right. I see.
But now that there's someone
from Kansai in Terrace House,
we'll get to hear, "Why not?"
"I love you."
-Oh, you mean we'll get to hear...
-"Forgive me."
"I can't stand it any longer."
We may get to hear those lines
in Kansai dialect.
What situations are you imagining?
The Japanese-style room, of course.
She'll like someone so much and say,
"I can't stand it any longer."
-We might get to hear it.
-You're right.
"I've overcooked the sprouts!"
-We might get to hear that.
-We just might.
She might say it,
but the staff might edit that one out.
And Hikaru is sort of...
-He seems into Arisa.
-It seems like he'll make a move on her.
This month, I'll be a shut-in.
Or what's the word?
You're stuck inside?
I have so much work.
It's crazy.
But isn't it better to stay busy?
-Yeah, it's fun.
-Right?
You have unnecessary thoughts
when you have too much free time.
I love having free time.
I can live forever doing nothing.
Having time off as a student
and having time off while working
are pretty different, aren't they?
Age definitely makes a difference.
Every year, I realize
how long I've been in Tokyo,
and I panic.
Makes me think, "What am I doing?"
Oh, so, what do you like about him?
-Oh, we're continuing that?
-I just remembered.
-Uchi?
-Yeah.
She wouldn't clearly say.
They kept putting each other down.
I've never seen a couple like that.
He's your boyfriend,
but I felt some distance between you.
They're different from a normal couple,
but I just figured
that's just Minori and Uchi.
Is it different when you two are alone?
-It's the same.
-Really?
For example, I'm really obvious.
I'm always touching my boyfriends.
-Really?
-Yeah.
To an outside observer,
we'd look like a lovey-dovey couple.
It's easy to imagine
a couple like that kissing.
But couples
that are always making fun of each other,
I don't really understand.
It's harder to imagine them kissing.
-Do you have to be able to imagine it?
-No, but...
They just don't give
that impression in public, I think.
-That's...
-You laugh, but it's true!
You guys are probably
just complete opposites.
Total opposites.
-I'm so tired today.
-It's tough to get used to.
It's hard.
Feel like you'll fit in?
No one seems like a bad person.
If you were to pick now,
which girl would be your type?
-By their face? Their looks?
-By looks.
By looks?
I think Arisa is cute.
-I see. Arisa.
-If we're going by looks, she's my type.
We'll see what happens.
What did you guys talk about
in the game room?
We both like the ocean,
so... she suggested we go to the beach.
She asked?
That's exactly what happened with Arisa!
I can't believe it.
-She works fast.
-So you're going to the beach?
I guess so.
What happens to you?
I lose my words with people I like.
-You make them like you?
-How do you mean?
-I wish I could make them like me.
-You seem like you do it unconsciously.
Me?
Do I?
Is there someone
you'd like to be with right now?
No.
But...
there is someone I have fun with.
Well, it could only be one person.
Yeah, I have fun with him.
-Do you think you'll fall for him?
-Hmm?
Do you think you'll fall for him?
Wow!
So many questions!
I'm going to be living here.
Of course I'd want to know!
What about you?
I felt like everyone was reserved.
-Today was more energetic than usual.
-No way!
I was more energetic than usual.
It was fun today.
I'm glad you're here.
You bring fun energy.
Wow. You set up the room?
It's cold.
-You want to sleep here?
-You don't want to sleep downstairs?
I wasn't sure since there's a new guy.
-Did you girls talk?
-Yeah, we talked.
-She's scary.
-Scary? How come?
She immediately asked.
-About what?
-How things are with us.
You know how she asked
what I liked about you earlier?
She asked me again.
She said all we did was
to make fun of each other.
She said it's weird.
She asked about when we're alone,
and I told her we're the same.
Then she asked if we're okay.
We're okay.
She made it sound like
there was something wrong with us.
That seems rude.
She wouldn't let it go.
I was a little ticked.
-There might be a conflict.
-She totally says what's on her mind.
Yeah, she seems like she does.
Like she can't accept people
that are different from her.
-I got a little of that from her.
-Then she's like me.
-Will you be okay?
-I don't know.
Will you be able to get along?
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
FROM OSAKA
'08 OSAKA SANGYO UNIVERSITY HIGH SCHOOL
'08-'12 RYUKOKU UNIVERSITY, LITERATURE
'12 BEGAN MODELING IN TOKYO
'12 CHOSEN AS IMAGE GIRL FOR SANAI
LAST RELATIONSHIP: ONE YEAR AGO
I'm off to China for a photo shoot!
-Natsumi
NOJIMA CONSTRUCTION, INC.
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
FROM SAO PAULO, BRAZIL
MOVED TO NODA, CHIBA AT 2 YEARS OLD
'15 GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL
BEGAN MODELING AND WORKING CONSTRUCTION
LAST RELATIONSHIP: ONE YEAR AGO
KAMAKURA, KANAGAWA
-Hello.
HISATO KOJIMA, OWNER
Good morning. I'm Arman Bitaraf
I'll be starting with you today.
We're building the yard today.
We just laid out the stones.
We also finished the deck and pagoda.
And we're working on the fence.
Inside there will be a garden.
I'm thinking of having you help
fill the garden with dirt.
Hey, it's sort of sinking here.
So let's fill it with more dirt.
Let's take a break.
None of the members
who worked at Loco Mart
got a girl on the show.
-Total failure.
-Really?
-Was it the Kagoshima girl?
-Yes.
Apparently, she's really cute.
-Everyone's cute, though.
-That's true.
I guess we should all watch the show.
-I'll bring her to Kanagawa for a date.
-Nice.
I'd better dress up for that.
I guess things like that happen...
-between girls from Kansai and Kanto...
-Oh, yeah.
As a person from Kansai, if I may say,
she wasn't judging her or anything.
-Yeah, it was just normal communication.
-Really?
Yeah. She was just being friendly.
Sort of teasing her, saying,
"Are you really okay?
You guys are so weird,
always making fun of each other."
And then Minori's supposed to respond,
"Of course it's fine."
It was supposed to be a fun exchange.
Did you see Minori's expression?
I wouldn't want anyone to say that
about my relationship either.
I suppose.
The Kansai audience watching this
are all saying,
"But that's just making conversation!"
-For sure.
-Right?
-Girls would say, "It's just girl talk!"
-Definitely.
It's so tough.
-It's because they just met.
-Yeah.
It was a bad idea to try and be
so personal when they had just met.
It kind of had an edge, didn't it?
-That's how it's interpreted.
-I guess so.
-It's Scissorhands.
-That's true.
She's trying to give them a hug,
but she's got blades.
-It's bittersweet.
-It is.
-It's the Scissorhands of Naniwa.
-The Scissorhands of Naniwa?
-Natsumi Saito.
-It should be her nickname.
Like, "Hi, I'm Johnny Depp"?
Wrong sex.
So actually, everyone at Terrace House
up till now has been fairly quiet.
They've never really had a talker before.
It's the first time.
A beautiful Kansai girl.
She could make things complicated.
She may be your typical Osaka personality.
It's actually Seiji, the comedian,
in disguise.
SEIJI CHIHARA
If that's the case, it'll be complicated.
Crass?
-Complicated.
It definitely turned Minori off.
And after this encounter,
Natsumi left for China for work.
Hopefully, there won't be
some strange meetings.
Yeah, a trial in absentia.
The trial in absentia from hell.
"Those Kansai people..."
"Oh, look, the takoyaki came back."
Oh, they could make jokes!
"The wheels on your luggage,
are they actually takoyaki?"
It would be refreshing
if they could say that.
We're worried because they can't.
You Kansai people can do that.
No one's home?
Didn't Nacchan say she's going to China?
Yeah, she left.
-She left today?
-Yeah, this morning.
-What time?
-I don't know. Pretty early.
-Before I left?
-Way before.
I didn't notice.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Was she at work?
-I guess she was at work.
-Yeah.
-You're not joining us?
-What?
-Later.
Okay.
She seems tired.
-We should talk more though.
-Yeah.
Are you drinking?
-No.
-Yes.
-You're drinking?
-Yeah.
-You are?
-Do you want a drink?
-No, not today.
-Work?
-There's that,
but I also wanted to make udon for dinner.
-Right now?
-I haven't eaten yet.
And Minori said she hasn't eaten either.
Did you know Minori caught a cold?
Yeah, she looked like she was dying.
Does it look bad?
Her fever's gone down,
but she said her stomach hurts.
Her stomach?
Is she okay?
I think it's
because she hasn't eaten any carbs.
-She went to the hospital?
-Yesterday.
How are things?
We didn't talk over the break.
-Recently?
-Do you have your hands full with work?
Since the new year began,
all I've done is work.
I don't think I'll have time off.
You work every day? No breaks?
Vendors are off, so I could rest, but...
You don't have set breaks?
Like on weekends?
I could if I wanted to.
But I have way too much to do.
I have things I need to finish this week.
Do you guys want some udon?
I don't.
You must be hungry.
-Is there enough?
-I have three packs.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I'll have some.
-Okay.
-She is cute.
-She is.
I wonder if she heard.
She's cute, but she seems busy.
If you're still interested in her
after a week,
don't worry about me.
Just go for it.
For Arisa?
It doesn't have to be now.
But something might still happen
between you two, right?
-Yeah, it seems so.
-Then you should keep approaching.
If we get to know each other...
and if I end up liking her,
I'm usually not bothered by other guys.
I usually think about myself first.
That's for the best.
I'll make my move then.