-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show
about six strangers, men and women
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared
is a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Let's see, a lot happened
in the last episode.
First, even though Tatsuya
spoke with Makoto,
Makoto just sulked and wouldn't reconcile.
I'll get angry next time. Really.
I may kick your butt.
Mizuki told me to apologize to you two.
Yeah, I want an apology from you.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
Earlier, we all talked about
how we should share our thoughts,
about who likes or dislikes whom,
about which girl we're into or not into.
But if it's just going to leak out,
I'm not going to share my thoughts.
If you don't want to share,
you don't need to.
I won't share anything then.
-Anyone would respond that way.
-Anyone would.
If he says it like that,
that's the reaction you'd get.
Tatsuya and Minori
went to Izu Oshima on a date.
It was a nice date.
Cows.
-Cows!
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
Yuki and Yuriko went
to the aquarium for their date.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
I want to go to Blue Note.
What? Blue Note?
Let's go.
You mean it?
"I want to go to Blue Note."
Yuriko only sees Tap as Mr. Ticket.
Sometimes it's Mr. Tap,
and sometimes it's Mr. Ticket.
And Yuriko visited Mizuki at the café.
-And surprisingly...
-Surprisingly...
She revealed that Makoto
was still her top choice.
-He's still...
-I know you don't dislike him.
He's still at the top.
-The top?
-The top.
And at the very end, Makoto...
-Yes, he did it.
-What was that anyway?
The mysterious playroom incident.
There was the Uchi Week, right?
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
He announced that he was gonna have a date
with each of you.
I felt that it was wrong.
I saw her making lunch for the date.
That kind of thing
made me lose interest in her.
That was so lame.
He's just bad-mouthing people.
And when someone doesn't side with him,
he gets all sad about it.
That's it! Makoto has a bad habit
of talking bad about others.
-Exactly.
-Shall we watch?
-Shall we?
What's going to happen today?
I think Makoto's gonna keep rolling.
It's crazy how his stock's crashing.
You know, yesterday?
It's about Makocchan.
Something bad about Makocchan?
Yeah, something bad.
You know how I...
initially said I liked Makocchan?
We went running together,
and went to eat Yakiniku together.
And it felt like
there was something there, but...
He told everyone how he's gonna be serious
about baseball, right?
And so I thought,
"Wow, he works really hard."
And I thought that was great.
But he started staying up late again.
And he snacks all the time.
That's right, he does.
And he blabbed to you,
and Uchi and Mizuki
got mad at him about it.
And it kind of made me think,
"Even though I liked him..."
Really?
And later,
after Uchi and I went to Izu Oshima,
he sent me a message like before.
And he told me about
what you and him had talked about,
about how he liked me at first.
But after seeing me go
to Izu Oshima with Uchi,
he no longer felt the same way.
He supposedly had said
something like that to you.
But that wasn't really true.
Or so he told me.
So he's basically saying that he told me
he no longer has feelings for you,
but that he regrets saying that?
Yeah. And so he said we should
hang out together sometime.
That's what he said in his message.
I don't get what he really wants.
I mean, what he wants with me.
How do you feel about it?
If he asks me out on a date,
then I'll try going.
And then I want to think about it.
I see.
But if he doesn't ask,
then it makes me wonder
what he really wants.
I hate when things are this ambiguous.
It doesn't make him look good.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
DAIKAN-YAMA, TOKYO
How are things going over there?
Lots of issues.
Issues? Again?
MAMIKO YOKOYAMA, HAIR STYLIST
Arguments and guy problems.
Guy problems?
MIKI TAKEUCHI, DIRECTOR OF THE SALON
You mean, because you like a guy?
No, not like that.
No, it's not like that.
I...
Well, I went on a date
with this girl named Yuriko.
MEGURI KOJIMA, HAIR STYLIST
And to be honest,
I felt like I had to cater to her,
and felt a little tired afterwards.
And Makocchan told her
that when he saw her...
Makocchan. That little...
And so, Makocchan's still
kind of keeping his distance.
He's saying, no, he's got his own stance.
So he's not willing to compromise?
I don't think it's possible.
Impossible?
I think we're probably both very stubborn.
-So neither of you is willing to bend?
-No.
You can't reach a kind of understanding?
Well, I can't understand
his actions at all.
Well, yeah. That's true.
I can't either.
I don't understand.
When the girls were first talking
about which guy they were into,
your name didn't come up, Uchihara?
Yeah, we saw that.
Well, I've narrowed it down
to one person out of the three.
-You did?
-Yes.
Is that something we'll have to confirm
by watching the show?
Yes, if you don't mind watching the show.
Really?
-Wait, wait a second.
-This is getting crazy.
Mr. Yamasato, will you explain
what just happened?
Yes, please.
Let's start with Minori and Yuriko.
Minori gets a message from Makoto.
In the message, he said he told Yuriko
his feelings for Minori had diminished,
but in fact, that's not really true.
And Minori is like, "What does this mean?"
And she tells Yuriko about it.
-This is bad.
It's really disgusting, actually.
So the fact is that he told Yuriko
he didn't have feelings for Minori,
and then tells everything to Minori.
That's just it.
-It's very strange.
-It is strange.
-Yeah, it's unnecessary.
-Yes, totally unnecessary thing to say.
It doesn't feel good to hear.
Amazing!
He really doesn't get how people feel.
He doesn't.
Tatsuya is looking more and more decent.
More manly, even.
Extremely decent.
Especially when you see it like this,
where our own relationships
aren't publicized.
Maybe we're all like that.
You're right,
maybe we're doing bad things too.
It seemed like
he wanted all the women to think,
"He's only thinking of me."
Yeah, when talking to Yuriko,
he made it seem like
he was only thinking of her.
And to Minori, even if she hears about it,
he still wants her to think he's into her.
That's really manipulative, isn't it?
-Yes, it is.
-Right?
He's not awkwardly trying with the girls,
that's not... quite... right... is it?
He didn't say that, he didn't say that.
He didn't say anything like that.
A stubborn one.
Stubborn has nothing to do with it.
It was in the background
while all the drama was going on,
but Uchi did tell his coworker
he's narrowed it down to one girl.
-Who is it?
-I wonder who it could be.
Maybe it's Yuriko.
Then all the guys like Yuriko.
You're right.
I'm telling you, she's an absolute vixen.
Toward men.
Why is she a vixen?
-She's not a vixen.
-Everyone finds her attractive.
She wants to look good
in front of everyone!
She's not!
We've established she only sees
Mr. Ticket as Mr. Ticket.
So the guys
just misunderstand her actions.
That's right.
But since he says he's narrowed it down
to one at that moment,
it must mean we should be able to find out
who she is soon.
-I wanna know!
Shall we continue?
NAKAMEGURO, TOKYO
TORIGOYA MAIN SHOP
TORIGOYA
HAKATA MOTSU NABE
Hey, hey, hey. He's here.
Hey, hey, hey.
I went toward the Higashiyama line
by mistake.
-That way?
-Yeah, that way.
I barely made it.
-Welcome.
-Thanks.
Can you drink?
Let's go for it today.
All right!
Cheers!
There were a bunch of messages on Twitter.
"There are people
who can never get results,
no matter how hard they work.
To put people like that down,
the two of you are total jerks.
It was really painful."
Those were the comment.
For real?
That's a one-sided view.
Uchi's got a strong heart.
I like to think
that I'm mentally pretty strong too.
I've been bashed on too many times before.
Before? You mean, like, at work?
Your first year as a stylist,
you're seriously treated like dirt.
It was ramen every day.
-Really.
-For real?
Yeah, I really had no money.
The salary was terrible.
Like 100,000 yen.
Uchi, you sleep all over
the place, don't you?
Last time, you were sleeping by the pool.
I think no one should sleep
in the living room.
Why not?
No one can use the living room
if someone's sleeping in there.
The living room should be a public space.
-I suppose.
-Yeah.
Has Makocchan made a move?
Move?
So...
since I went on a date with Uchi,
we haven't really talked.
So no, not really.
So, Mizuki and I talked at the café.
-It's okay, right?
-Yeah, but...
Well, if things have changed.
It's a while ago now, but in the beginning
we all liked Makocchan.
And a lot has happened,
but Makocchan was...
Well, maybe it wasn't
to the level of "like" yet,
but he was on my mind.
But I thought that maybe he likes Minori.
So I was talking about that
with Mizuki at the café.
But I think my feelings have changed.
Lately, everyone's been up
pretty late, right?
Sometimes I wonder if it's okay for him.
Yeah, he's got early morning practice...
Which he goes to, right?
Yeah, he said he's gonna be serious
about baseball...
-He came to tell us that.
-Yeah, he came to tell us.
After that, for about three days,
he went to sleep early.
So I thought
he was being good about it, but...
When I get up to go to school,
I've seen Makocchan sleeping...
more often than not.
I've told him
that I want to go watch him play.
But when I told him
that maybe I could bring everyone,
he said he was taken off the bench,
so he has to practice.
He says he eats mostly protein,
but lately I've seen him eating snacks.
-And he's been drinking.
-He has been.
It can't help but make me think,
"Maybe he's not who I thought he was."
How's baseball going?
Baseball...
Actually, the league games
have already started.
I'm trying...
But I get elbow pain.
So with that...
I guess, your lifestyle at home...
The smoking and drinking.
The late-night snacking,
it's a little discomforting to be honest.
You said you were going to work hard,
a month ago or whatever,
that you were aiming
to be a starting pitcher.
I can't help but feel...
that your actions don't match your words.
Well, I do go to practice.
But, yeah...
It's okay if you don't make it.
If there was evidence of your effort,
I'd think that's great.
So no matter how things would go for you,
we'd say, "Well, Makoto worked hard."
Or that's what we want to be able to say.
Yeah...
So there's another month and a half?
About a month.
I hope you work hard.
Yeah.
If you're gonna do it, do it.
If not, then don't.
You should just make it clear.
If you're just wavering,
the month is just gonna go by.
I should be doing more.
I do think about it.
I think that just thinking about it
is too late at this point.
You just gotta do it.
That's what I think.
TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
ITABASHI, TOKYO
Looks tasty.
-Ruriko, where did you get up to for CV--
-QV?
RINKO UEDA, 4TH YEAR MED STUDENT
RURIKO FUJIKURA, 4TH YEAR MED STUDENT
I'm kind of disorganized about it.
I'd do some of it, and then get stuck
on the last part, so I'd stop.
I'd do some and stop again.
I totally understand.
I only did as much as I could explain.
Really?
When do you study, Yuriko?
Can you study at home?
Not too much, I think.
So it is hard to study there.
I try to hang out with the other members
when I have time.
That's true.
What about the guys?
You mean, who I like?
The one I like the most right now,
is the sporty guy called Makocchan.
-The baseball guy.
-The pitcher!
He's the pitcher.
But I've never gone on a date with him.
But you want to?
It's actually really
questionable right now.
Borderline?
I think he's into Minori.
-Is that the feeling you get?
-Totally.
I see.
The tap dancer guy too,
he's asked me out a bunch of times.
He's easy to talk to.
-He's good?
-He's...
This is fun.
I'm not sure.
I do want to go out with him again.
You don't want to make a move?
I've never asked anyone out before--
Right, you've said that.
Maybe it's a good opportunity.
What should I do?
Okay, I'll try asking.
-You're gonna ask?
-I'm gonna ask.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
-Want to know what I got today?
-What's that?
A roll cake. Want some?
I'll have some.
Welcome back, Yuki.
-Thanks.
-What's that?
Do you want some roll cake?
Yes, thank you.
-Ouch.
-Sorry, sorry.
The kid is awake.
Welcome back!
Thanks, I'm back.
Quiet entrance.
-Don't wake the kid.
-Yes, don't.
-Okay.
-Our kid is sleeping.
Wow.
-What were you guys up to?
-Nothing.
-What should be...
-The topic of discussion?
Today? Well, let's see...
I did want to talk about
what we talked about yesterday.
But someone seems to be knocked out
on the living room couch.
About not sleeping on the couch.
I agree with that too.
It's become hard to have
an "on" and "off" in this house.
I see.
Our kid's asleep.
Should I wake her?
Should we settle
the living room issue today?
-Should we settle it today?
-Should we?
Hey, kid.
-I'll wake her.
-Nice!
You startled me.
-It's too cute.
-If you try to wake her like that...
Kid, go sleep upstairs.
What? What?
-Hey, kid, we've got a serious problem.
-Welcome back.
What is it?
-We're talking about the living room--
-I want some!
-Oh, sure.
-Here, you can eat first.
You can eat first, but we do have
a living room situation right now.
What? What?
We should all sleep in our beds.
The living room is the living room,
and over there is where we eat.
If we could do that, then I...
Let's stop sleeping in the living room.
Okay...
Hey, you, don't try going back to sleep.
No, I was gonna go upstairs.
-Bad girl.
-Go to sleep.
Good night!
She's definitely going to come back down.
You should keep watch for tonight.
-Good morning.
I'm sorry, those were my dishes.
-It's fine.
-I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
-Were you able to sleep?
-What?
-I was.
-I'll wash.
-What?
-These. I used them yesterday.
-No worries.
But...
I was worried you couldn't sleep.
Was it hard?
-It wasn't hard.
-You're okay?
-Sorry.
-It's fine. It's totally fine.
-I did kind of think it bothered you.
-No way.
You were really spread open out there,
so I just wondered if it was okay for you.
Was it painful to see?
If you can sleep in your bed,
there's nothing better.
-Are you okay? Anything else?
-Nothing at all.
Nothing else at all.
What about you?
Just girl problems?
Not even that?
No girl problems.
Today, well...
I'm just...
Just tired from stuff.
-What?
-Tired from stuff.
Tired from stuff?
Man, the guys hung out.
Uchi's pretty outspoken.
-And his arguments are totally sound.
-Completely.
Making starting pitcher with just
another month left seems impossible.
He was told he should practice,
but he says, "Well, I've got elbow pain."
At that moment,
I knew that this guy's no good.
Every athlete has
some injury all the time--
Everyone's in pain.
You rest if you can't move,
pain is just a norm.
Tap should have gotten angrier there--
Yeah, I thought he would have said more.
Yeah, instead of the living room issue,
he should've put greater focus
to the guys' issues.
As the oldest, he should've taken the lead
-and said, "Hey, let's talk this through."
-That's right.
Maybe it has to do with the tweets.
-Because he was bashed.
-He can't say things too strongly now.
-He got scared.
-That's weak! Weak!
To back down
just for that level of Twitter bashing...
Coming from someone who's involved
in some top-class
celebrity Twitter battles,
that's a little--
If he's in shock
because of those little sparks,
it would be instant death for me.
In shock because of those little embers?
That's weak!
In that sense, Mishin here,
he knows all that.
But he's still like,
"I've taken bashings before,
so I'll be fine."
Well, people who've really worked hard
aren't really affected by
attacks like that on social media.
That's true,
they know they've put in the work.
They have confidence. It doesn't matter
what some losers say on social media.
What we can talk about is
how he's gained some points.
It's annoying!
But he's really the one reasonable person.
-Yes.
-That's true.
So now it's about
who he's going to choose--
One vote for Yuriko!
-Damn! Why did I...
-Oh, Yuriko...
I'm so annoyed.
I wanted to bad-mouth him.
I've already declared
how much I hated him on YouTube.
Did you dye your hair, Mizuki?
I did! On my own.
-On your own?
-Color Butter?
-Yeah, Color Butter.
-Really?
-It's cute.
-Really? Uchi is busy, so.
-You're gonna have Uchi color it?
-Yeah. So until then,
I'll dye it.
Yes?
-Hey!
-Welcome back.
Did you just get home?
-Yeah, just now.
-Welcome home.
-Come in, come in.
-Join the girl circle.
-I kind of want to talk to Minori.
-Sure, go ahead.
-Should we leave then?
-No, no.
-We'll go downstairs.
-Should I come?
-I'm gonna borrow her for a minute.
-Of course. See you later.
-What's going on? What's happening?
-I wonder what it is.
-I wonder...
-Is something there, you think?
-I think so.
-Right? I thought so too.
-Is this what the chairs are for?
-It's the first time I've sat in these.
Kind of awesome.
-So, what?
-What?
I was thinking...
that...
I want to ask you out.
-A date?
-A date.
Part two?
I want to talk to you again.
Okay.
-Is it okay?
-It's okay.
-Okay? That was easy.
-Is that bad?
No, it's good. Well, you know...
I'm kind of nervous.
-What is this?
-Yeah, you're acting different than usual.
I'm nervous.
That's so weird.
Say something.
-It's uncomfortable!
-Is it?
Yes.
We'll go somewhere in Chichibu.
-Chichibu? And?
-Chichibu.
Details to follow.
-To follow?
-To follow.
-To look forward to?
-To look forward to.
Okay.
I'm glad.
Why? Did you think I'd say no?
-No, I didn't.
-You didn't.
-I didn't think you'd say no, but...
-That's confident.
But this is the most nervous
I've felt since I've been here.
-I'm gonna go tell the girls.
-Okay.