-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
So last week,
the meat incident continued.
That's right.
Another crisis on top of everything.
Tatsuya's breakdown.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
Why are you crying?
Everything I've held back until now
broke loose.
From this shared living situation.
A lot has happened
and all he's held back finally exploded.
-An accumulation.
-Yes, that's right.
Who knew the meat crime
would come this far.
-That's right.
-That's true.
-But they seemed to have made up.
-Yes.
Problem solved.
And Arman...
Seems to have started working.
-And he went to Arisa...
-That's right.
But if you feel something for me at all,
you could spare even ten minutes a day
to talk to me.
That's what I think.
So I wanted to ask one last time
how you feel about me.
I don't have time to think about
anything else right now.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
I'm sorry.
Arisa, when she first rejected him,
told him that she wasn't ready yet
but wanted to get to know him more.
She left him with false hope.
And Arman, holding on to that hope,
foolishly believed her.
Arisa made that happen.
She's at fault.
She tried to let him down nicely.
-The way she rejected him.
-Is that really niceness though?
-No, I don't think it's nice at all.
-Yes, that's exactly right!
In my opinion, anyway.
-She completely betrayed me.
-You?
Yes.
We were on the same wavelength.
You've never been on the same wavelength.
Will you stop saying "creepy"
under your breath?
You think you're better than me,
don't you?
Well... shall we continue?
-Can I just say one more thing?
-What?
Thanks to everyone,
I've been commissioned
to do a commercial for Netflix.
And there's even
a kissing scene with an actress.
-We just filmed it.
-What?
You kissed?
-We kissed.
-What?
I play the role of her boyfriend
and she's completely into me.
-Well, it's her job.
-You mean within her role.
I know it's terrible,
but because of some bad takes
of the kiss scene,
I delayed production by three hours.
What?
How many bad takes were there?
I'm supposed to lay there
and then react nonchalantly to the kiss.
But I'd get so nervous,
and I'd be like...
Do you think
the actress was upset with me?
Upset? No.
Maybe grossed out.
I understand being nervous about the job.
But you just do it.
You just do as you're told.
I can't emotionally detach myself
from a kiss yet.
I'm sure the actress would prefer it...
-if you could detach yourself.
-Otherwise, it's gross.
Your mom isn't here today.
PUKUICHI
TORITSU DAIGAKU, TOKYO
-Hi.
-Hi!
-Were you able to find it easily?
-Yeah. It was close to the station.
You've got full-on makeup today.
I had work today.
-Are you hungry?
-I am.
The food here is super delicious.
-This is your friend's place?
-Yeah, it's my friend's place.
When I told everyone
you invited me out to dinner,
Uchi was like, "Seriously?"
He said you hardly invited anyone.
Did it make you wonder why?
No, not really.
I was just thinking about
how I could get to know you.
And that's when you invited me.
So it honestly made me happy.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Honestly.
After the meat incident,
did anything change between you and Uchi?
I think that it did.
We both talk to each other more now.
-I think we changed in a good way.
-I see.
-I'm happy for you.
-Yeah. Me too.
-I'm glad we ate the meat.
-That's so true.
It ended well?
I don't know if Uchi feels the same,
but...
It's delicious.
Isn't it?
It's so good.
Totally off topic, but...
did you come to Terrace House
thinking you'd find love?
-Not at all.
-I see.
I totally didn't think
it was a possibility.
I want to find love,
but at Terrace House...
I don't know if I can.
I'm like you.
But you were saying yesterday...
about how Hikaru's great,
but his age...
-That, I don't get.
-Why?
I've never dated or fallen in love
with someone younger.
I want to be the pampered one.
And I feel like
I can't have that with someone younger.
But that just depends on the guy's...
ability.
I'm really glad that we went out today.
-Here.
-I'm glad.
It is really nice
you have someone you love to give it to.
I'm pretty envious.
-He said he wants one from the store.
-Seriously?
-He said he wants Godiva chocolates.
-That's terrible!
-Is it good? Hot?
-It's hot.
It's hot! Hot! Hot!
It's good, but it's hot.
Look at that!
-It's cute!
-It's super cute!
-Happy Valentine's Day!
-Happy Valentine's!
Wow, they're all wrapped.
-Ta-da!
-Did you buy them?
No! We made them together.
Woo!
-Yay!
-Wow.
-Yay, thanks!
-For Arman!
Wow! It's got my name on it.
-Are they all different?
-For Hikaru!
-Thanks.
-Happy Valentine's.
It says, "For you."
-This one's also for you.
-Yeah!
Take a look at this!
Don't you guys want to see?
-Hey, guys!
-You should see!
-Aren't you guys interested?
-It says "Hikaru" here.
They're ignoring us.
-Hey, mine's smaller.
-Hey, over here!
-I knew you'd notice.
-Look here.
Is this, like, the leftover?
It's good.
-Yeah, it's a cookie.
-Yay!
-It's good.
-Thanks.
I'm sure Arisa has stuff for you, too.
Oh, Arisa...
-Is she coming back?
-Yeah.
She said she would be home late.
I have an announcement.
What?
The morning of the 18th...
-we'll be leaving.
-What?
Why so sudden?
You have to tell us earlier.
-That's why we're telling you early.
-There's still four days.
We were gonna say it yesterday,
but decided to wait for Arisa.
-What? This is so sad.
-Hikaru's about to cry.
I'm not, but...
I'm not. I'm not crying.
So, the snowboarding trip
will be our goodbye trip.
I'm glad we're going snowboarding.
-Yeah, let's go have fun.
-You don't even know how to snowboard.
-I can't, but...
-Let's go have fun.
Everyone has scheduled to go snowboarding
except Natsumi.
KAWABA SKI RESORT
TONE COUNTY, GUNMA
-Arman, you're going to wear sunglasses?
-Shouldn't I?
-Wow.
-It feels great!
I hope I don't fall.
-Look out.
-Nice.
It's so beautiful.
-First snow of the season?
-First snow for the mountain.
How do I stop?
Then you lean forward, like this.
You're leaning too much, Arisa!
Little by little.
AZABU-JUBAN, TOKYO
-Welcome back, guys.
-Hey!
Looks amazing!
How was it? Fun?
-It was fun!
-We're all in pain.
-It was great weather today.
-It was.
It was warm.
All of us getting together...
Yeah, not since the incident.
-Incident? It was a house meeting.
-Oh, yeah.
What was the most memorable moment
for the two of you?
-Of course, the "coward" incident.
-"Coward!"
Oh, it's not the meat?
No.
Though that was memorable, too.
For me, it was the meat incident.
-Really?
-Maybe because it was recent.
I was more surprised by the meat incident.
Wish I'd seen it.
-It was your fault.
-Yeah!
Why is it my fault?
I wasn't too involved though.
-You did eat it.
-You did eat some.
That couldn't be helped
because I was hungry.
You owe me ramen, Hikaru.
-What's with your expression?
-I'm suddenly feeling sad.
It is sad, for real.
I mean, you guys met here.
-That's true.
-Right?
Yeah, we were strangers before this.
It's amazing.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 22 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
I'm hungry.
-You haven't eaten?
-I have.
I had a cheese katsu bento.
Ramen! Ramen!
Let's really go.
Sure, I'll take you to a great place.
-Let's go.
-Take us.
My head's starting to spin.
Wow,
from just four percent alcohol content?
Ew, he's grossing me out.
You always say stuff like that.
It hurts, you know.
She does, right?
Like, "I don't like you!"
It always gets to me.
-But you really like her.
-Breaks your heart?
I like you very much.
-More, more.
-Look into her eyes.
I love you.
Man, that was bad.
-You've never said that to me.
-I've told you I love you.
Why are you making a face like a catfish?
A catfish?
He calls me Ms. Catfish.
-Like a catfish?
-Ms. Catfish!
He totally calls me Ms. Catfish.
But you do kinda look like a catfish.
Like a catfish...
You do have a catfish face.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Oh, Arisa.
Uchi's wasted.
His face is all red.
What about ramen?
-His face is hot.
-It's the last night.
-Let's get ramen, Uchi.
-Yeah.
-Let's go then.
-Yeah, let's go.
-We're off.
-Have fun.
-Bye.
-See ya.
I can't drive.
-Hikaru can.
-I'm not gonna drive.
That's the closest
I've ever seen you guys.
You and Uchi.
Very lovey-dovey.
We're not a weird couple?
You're not a weird couple.
-I was pretty hurt by that.
-No way.
Yeah, you were upset.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Since going out for okonomiyaki together,
since I invited you out,
things have changed between us.
I wish I had more time...
with you.
It's a little late now, but...
Why don't you stay another week?
Don't cry.
I guess this is goodbye.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
It was a fun six months.
Six months.
We had our arguments...
but it was fun.
Looking back, it was fun.
Shall we?
See you around, Hikaru.
Bye.
See you, Arman.
Good luck.
I'll see you.
Thank you, Minori.
Bye.
-See ya!
-See ya.
-Bye!
Thank you.
Thanks, Uchi and Minori.
-Good luck!
-Bye!
NISHI-AZABU, TOKYO
So...
I'm going to move into Terrace House.
What?
-Really?
-Yeah, really.
-Yeah.
-When?
-Tomorrow.
-What! Tomorrow?
Are you serious?
I want to experience co-op living.
Seriously?
And it'd be nice to meet someone.
-It's good, right?
-Yeah, I'm envious.
What about your part-time job?
I'll continue working.
-You will?
-Yeah.
I'll continue my other jobs, too.
Only my living situation will change.
So that's okay.
I'm so excited.
It's an unknown world.
The cafe in Asakusa you were working on...
-did you finish that?
-Yeah, I'm done with that.
So when you have to work,
you're gonna work here?
Yeah, I'll work from here.
-You're gonna use it as your studio?
-Yeah.
We've had drinks together often,
but that's it for now.
I'll be moving to Terrace House.
What made you decide?
I'm graduating...
I figured it'd be a good change of pace.
But the people who are looking for working
in the entertainment industry
and the people who aren't
have completely different reasons
for joining Terrace House.
What are you looking to gain specifically?
I don't know what I'll gain.
I don't know what life there will be like.
But there are more possibilities there
than if I stay here.
You're going to accept
both pros and cons?
Yeah, it wasn't a decision
based on logical reasoning.
It's more like an adventure.
It was nice at the end
for Minori and Natsumi...
They became close.
It's been a while since we got to see
a harmonious Terrace House.
Now that they've overcome this together,
they may be really close for life.
-Maybe.
-It's possible.
It reminds me of an old soap opera
with Akina Nakamori and Narumi Yasuda.
-I've seen that.
-Just the Way We Are!
Yeah, it's like the two of them.
Natsumi is Akina Nakamori.
That's right.
The song was, Just by You Being Here.
-By Kome Kome Club.
-Was it?
I bought the CD for my girlfriend then.
-Oh, I see.
-It brings back memories.
Saying, "It's just for you?"
I've become so tainted.
-They're coming.
-The new members.
-The girl seems pretty.
-Totally beautiful!
-This area of the pretty one...
-Yes, the face structure.
Is the guy in architecture school?
Seemed like a group of creative types.
-Maybe graphic--
-Didn't he mention graduating?
-He seems put together.
-Yeah.
I wonder.
It doesn't seem like he'd get along
with Arman and Hikaru.
I wonder.
-Really, now.
-That's true.
-Just curry is fine, right?
-Yeah.
-There's only four of us.
-That's true.
-Can I switch this?
-Yeah, thanks.
Thank you.
"If you use it,
you should wash it right away."
That's my motto.
I see.
-Is it ready?
-Doesn't chicken take a while to cook?
But we're gonna add water.
Oh, sorry.
I'm so hungry.
Could it be...
It's happening now?
Hello.
Hi, I'm moving in today.
Please come in.
-It is a girl.
-I guess a girl is coming first.
What?
Isn't it weird
that we're going to greet her here?
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Misaki Tamori.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
-I'm sorry to greet you here.
-It's okay.
-We were cooking...
-What were you making?
Curry.
Let's eat together.
Thank you very much.
Of course.
-Should I sit down?
-Please sit.
-I'm sorry. What is your name again?
-I'm Misaki Tamori.
-Misaki?
-Misaki.
My friends call me Tamochan or Tamosan.
Tamosan?
-How old are you?
-I'm 23.
What do you do?
I'm trying to break into the entertainment
industry, while working part-time jobs.
-A model?
-No.
-More like variety shows.
-Oh, talent shows.
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
-Where are you from?
-From Hokkaido.
-Do you have a boyfriend?
-I don't.
-How long since your last one?
-About a year.
Oh, we're the same.
It's like a dream.
I've always watched the show,
so it's strange to actually be here.
How long have you lived here?
A little over a month.
-Did you have any trouble sleeping?
-Not at all.
-You too?
-Yeah.
Do you tend to worry about little things?
-Not at all.
-Then you won't have trouble sleeping.
Not at all, huh?
Not at all?
Do you like to clean?
-Oh, no!
-You like to keep clean?
Oh, no, something is bound to happen!
You don't keep tidy?
I'm not going to hold back. Is that okay?
But I might say something back.
-This is gonna be good.
-Yeah.
Like, "What's wrong with that?"
-Okay.
-Something that's the norm for me
might not be for someone who likes
to be clean.
For example, after you eat,
do you leave it behind?
-I do.
-That's the norm?
-It's not, but...
-You might eat it later.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. I get it.
-No, I meant trash.
-Yes, I leave it.
-Do you throw it out right away?
-No, later.
Let's do it right away.
Oh, no! But I thought
maybe being here will make me better.
Oh, then please do.
-But I still might say something.
-Okay.
So, have you asked?
-What's your type? What kind of guy?
-Oh, my type?
Someone who's considerate
of those around them.
And looks?
For looks, I'm not consistent.
I've dated guys
with both soft and welldefined features.
I don't have a specific type.
I think it's ready.
I wonder if we have enough roux?
Oh, we haven't added it yet.
Will you drink today?
I will.
Should we buy some?
-I can go.
-The convenience store?
-Do they sell curry there?
-Roux? They do.
-They do?
-I need to go anyway, so I'll go too.
-Would you mind?
-We'll buy some.
Please.
Thank you.
Everyone seems nice.
-I'm glad.
-They are.
-Probably.
-Probably?
I shouldn't talk about other people.
I wasn't sure if I could be friends.
-Why?
-I thought we might clash.
I wonder.
-You never know.
-I guess we'll have to see.
That's scary.
What do you think of her?
Might not be my type.
-For real?
-Yeah.
But I'm sure it'll be fun.
I seriously think...
she's super cute.
-Super cute?
-Yeah?
Your type?
-She's pretty high energy.
-Yeah.
I love that.
Nice.
But at least, in the worst case scenario,
I want someone with a nice rack.
Of which, there isn't, but...
-I like her.
-Her personality?
Her personality and face, too.
It's nice that everyone eats together.
Cheers!
-Glad to have you here.
-Thanks for having me.
-I'm home.
-You surprised me.
-Welcome back.
-Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
I moved in today.
I'm Misaki Tamori.
I'm Arisa.
Welcome back.
-Did you cut your hair?
-I did.
How does she know?
-Do you want some curry?
-I will.
She's apparently the type
who speaks her mind.
You are?
Yeah, it was a surprise.
Minori would get quiet
when Nacchan was around.
But you just laugh and give it right back.
I'm impressed.
It's good.
So this must be better for you, Nacchan.
-From your point of view.
-Really?
-Arisa, you've really brightened up.
-Work is going well?
-Yeah.
-Same old?
-Is there anything we can do to help?
-Did you tan?
I didn't.
-It's hard to tan now.
-Um...
-Paint?
-It'd be nice if you could paint.
At the place?
Paint what? Boxes?
-Bricks and stuff.
-Bricks?
Are you doing something?
I'm putting on an exhibit in March.
-For hats?
-Yes.
That's nice.
Next week?
Yes, we're starting next week.
-Let's go to help with the painting.
-Of course.
-Can I use the Terrace House car?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
I can drive.
-You can drive?
-Yeah.
-Hikaru's driven us before.
A speed demon.
-I don't drive like that. Cut it out.
-That'd be scary.
-I drive safely.
-You seem like you're a bad driver.
-What?
-Bad?
You're 18, right?
I'm probably the best driver in the group.
Well...
-Have you been in the car with Arman?
-I have.
-I'm good.
-He is good at it.
I don't know
what your definition of "good" is.
It's normal.
Whatever.
I'm never driving you.
Don't pout.
When it piles up...
just drain it.
Wasn't Hikaru totally pissed?
What? About the driving?
-I think he was mad.
-He was.
-Was it scary?
-Yeah.
-I can't tell if he's serious or not.
-Yeah, it's hard to tell.
It always seems like he's joking.
-I did get a little scared.
-Yeah.
Yeah, he was mad.
I wonder.
-Tamosan...
-Tamosan.
She reminds me of Asami Mizukawa.
She is very frank
like an actress, Asami.
ASAMI MIZUKAWA
It's good.
You like her right, Kentaro?
Yes.
-What?
-Yes, she's interesting.
Go Kentaro, go!
That lady there is dangerous.
Don't listen to her.
She really didn't need to say
that he seemed like a bad driver.
-Yeah, that wasn't good.
-Oh, it's bad.
-I thought maybe Hikaru would like that.
-Yeah.
Like it would fire him up.
Yes, yes...
Listen, listen...
Not just you, Triendl,
but to all the female viewers.
Yes.
Men, of course, enjoy being teased...
but not about their driving!
You get it, right, Kentaro?
-You're 18.
-I totally understand.
I see.
Driving is an essential part
of being a man.
It's special.
So, if you're told you're bad at it,
it's very demeaning.
He was pretty pissed.
He was like, "What?"
And to be told that
in front of everyone...
They just met.
-Yeah, so driving...
-So, it's bad.
Better to leave it alone.
Especially coming from a girl
he's interested in.
-It's shocking.
-Yeah, there's definitely that.
Yeah, it was bad timing.
That expression...
From a female point of view,
does that turn you off?
-Is this worth apologizing about?
-No.
That might hurt his pride more.
To say, "I'm sorry I said
you looked like you'd be a bad driver."
"It's fine."
-Crying?
-Yes, crying.
"No one's ever said that
about my driving."
-We've got the new guy coming.
-Yes, we do.
Dreams for the future?
We haven't asked that yet.
-An amusement park.
-She said that earlier.
-Arisa didn't hear.
-An amusement park?
-To build one?
-Yes.
-Wow, like a Disneyland?
Then, I'll build you a hat store, too.
What? For me?
Inside the park?
-An amusement park of everyone's dreams.
-That's right!
-I see.
-I'll build one for you.
For her?
Plans for tomorrow?
-Off?
-Off.
Off tomorrow?
What about you, Arisa?
I have work,
but I'll be home early Sunday.
What about you, Nacchan?
-I'm off tomorrow.
-No way!
Really.
-Did you show her room?
-Not yet.
Why don't you show her?
No way!
Seriously?
-At this time?
-Arman, let's go see the guy.
Really?
Yes?
I'm moving in today.
-Come in.
-Okay.
I'm really nervous for some reason.
Maybe because it's so sudden.
-Wow.
-What do you mean, "wow"?
-Nice to meet you.