-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week, Natsumi and Hikaru
left Terrace House and...
HIKARU OTA, 19 YEARS OLD
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD
Oh, on my way home from work
the other day...
I was driving in my neighborhood
and I saw Nacchan!
I was like, "Whoa!"
It turns out she lives really close to me.
Wow, scary.
No, it's not scary.
This isn't some horror story.
Since we do this, it's really strange
when we see them in real life.
It really is.
Yeah, I was on a variety show
with Tetsuya Sugaya.
-Together?
-Yes.
-How were you together?
-You must be kidding.
We were Team Chiba.
Team Chiba?
It was me, Tetsu and Hideki Takahashi.
-What a line up.
-That's a big name!
So with Tetsu... it went down so badly.
I couldn't talk.
-Still?
-He doesn't understand personal space.
We're in each other's faces,
and it made the audience uncomfortable.
Every time he made a bad comment,
I would rag on him.
That's terrible!
And Hideki Takahashi would say, "Stop it."
He was scolding you.
He was like, "Stop it,"
with his deep voice.
-He's a very gentle person.
-Yes.
-Wow.
-Sorry, we've gone off-topic.
-Sorry to interrupt. Please continue.
-We're sorry.
-And we have new members.
-We do.
A wonderful person.
-Yes, a ballerina. Momochan.
-Momochan.
I'm a ballerina.
-This?
-Yes, that.
I'm trying to make it my profession.
I'm currently
at a professional training facility,
and practicing in order to move up.
I went to an all-girls high school.
-Oh, I see.
-So I'm not sure how to act around men.
-She's like a princess.
-Yes, so pure and innocent.
Yes, pure.
Like all she's ever known is ballet.
-She works part-time at a chocolate shop.
-So cute!
All she's ever done with a man is
dance pas de deux.
-So cute.
-Pas de deux.
And along with this wonderful girl,
we have...
-Don't say it like that.
-Was that bad?
The potential player is here.
Are there any couples here?
-No, no one.
-No one.
So cupid's arrow might be pointing
in specific directions already?
-What, now? You think?
-Don't you think?
What do you think, Momochan?
-You move quick.
-You're so quick.
-Did I jump the gun?
-He seems like a player.
He's definitely a player.
Tamosan seems a little cautious of him.
-He seems like an aggressive type.
-I wonder if he's gonna come on strong.
-We don't know yet.
-That's true.
And Arman likes the new girl once again.
-Arman likes the feminine type.
-Yes, that's true.
-What did you think of Momochan, Arman?
-Yeah.
I think she's cute.
-She's in your strike zone?
-We've never had an athlete before.
-That's true.
-So good first impression.
I want Rikochan
to have more of a fun experience!
-Seriously.
-Yeah, nothing's been fun for her.
She's only been a mediator.
-Yeah.
-Poor girl.
-This makes it feel official.
-Yeah, doesn't it?
It makes me nervous.
Cute handwriting.
Hayato.
Okay.
-I'm going to get ready upstairs.
-Okay.
See you later.
-Are you off tomorrow?
-I am.
-What are your plans?
-I'll do whatever comes up.
Do you want to go somewhere?
Go somewhere? Sure.
There must be a lot of places
you still haven't seen in Tokyo.
Yeah, I think so.
Where do you want to go?
Hmm, where do I want to go?
Any place you recommend.
-It can be anywhere?
-Yeah, anywhere.
-Then I'll think about it.
-Okay.
-Tomorrow then.
-Tomorrow.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Okay.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
STAR DANCERS BALLET COMPANY
Let's begin.
Okay, one more!
All right, next group.
Music please.
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 20 YEARS OLD
FROM CHIBA CITY
BEGAN BALLET AT 5
2011 BEGAN KYOTO BALLET ACADEMY
2013 STUDIED IN PARIS
2014 GRADUATED KYOTO BALLET ACADEMY
2016 CERTIFIED AS AN INSTRUCTOR
JOINED THE STAR DANCERS BALLET JR. COMPANY
Very nice.
-We're back.
-Welcome home.
-I'm back.
-You scared me.
He's making something.
-You came home together?
-We bumped into each other at the station.
Oh, wow.
-Are you hungry?
-I am.
-I made hayashi rice.
-Thank you.
It looks delicious!
I haven't had hayashi rice in a while.
Really?
I didn't know we had placemats.
This is the first time I'm eating in here.
-Oh, yeah.
-What? You've never eaten in here?
There wasn't anybody here who could cook.
-We'll have a hamburger cooking class.
-Please.
Apparently there's a trick
to cooking them.
Even the color is different.
-Bon appétit.
-Please, enjoy.
It's hot.
-Tasty.
-Is it?
So good!
-It's so good.
-It is.
-Thank you.
I'm glad.
Especially since I didn't say
I'd be cooking,
I was afraid you'd have eaten already.
-We would've eaten this even if we had.
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
-It's delicious.
It's restaurant quality.
-Our date is tomorrow.
-Oh, right.
-Nice.
-Or tour of Tokyo anyway.
We're going to the meat festival.
-The meat festival--
-Lucky!
Around noon?
Make sure you're hungry.
-The meat festival sounds nice.
-I'm home.
Welcome back.
-I'm so tired.
-Welcome home.
-Have you eaten?
-Not yet. I'm hungry.
How much can you eat?
I'll bring you some.
-A little bit.
-Just a little?
Did you make a lot?
Don't worry, it'll keep.
You can eat it tomorrow, too.
-Did you eat?
-Yeah, it was delicious.
It was really good.
-Have you ever had a guy cook for you?
-A guy?
-Like this?
-No, never!
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Oh, wow! It's like a restaurant.
-He made the roux from scratch.
-What? Wow.
It's delicious.
I need to learn from him.
They're gonna go eat meat.
-Really?
-Yeah, at the meat festival.
Oh, the one on Omotesando?
-Gaienmae.
-Oh, Gaienmae.
The meat festival sounds fun.
I'm gonna google it.
Some famous yakiniku BBQ restaurants
from Tokyo will be there.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Amazing.
-How great is that?
Amazing.
Do you have any performances coming up?
-I do.
-When?
There are two in June and two in July.
So quite often then?
Where?
-In Kyoto and Tokyo.
-Oh, Kyoto...
Near the Tokyo Tower.
-I want to go.
-Yeah.
Really? I'm going to have to practice.
-Good morning.
-I'm going to have some salad.
-I ate already. Good morning.
-I'm going to have some of your salad.
-Sure.
-Good morning.
Thanks for waiting.
You're wearing torn jeans, too.
-We're the torn twins.
-Oh, we're twins today.
-Ready to go?
-Yes.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's gonna be packed.
Seems like it's really crowded already.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Shall we go then?
-Let's go.
-Did you have breakfast?
-No, not yet.
-What? You must be starving.
-I'm hungry.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 20 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
-It's hot today.
-Yeah.
-And you're hungry?
-And I'm hungry.
-I wonder if we need to wait in lines.
-Probably.
TOKYO MEAT FESTIVAL 2016
-I've already done the research.
-Impressive.
Let's eat meat.
It's not as bad as I thought,
but I guess there'll be lines
at the popular places.
Yeah, there are lines.
-Let's go get gyutan.
-Sounds good.
Welcome!
-Two gyutans please.
-Two orders!
-Here you go.
-Thank you very much!
-Bon appétit.
-Which should I eat first?
-The gyutan, of course.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-How is it?
-So good!
-It's delicious.
-It's so good!
-Doesn't it make you want rice?
-Yeah.
-Aren't you hot?
-This is fun.
-Is it?
-I just happened to be off today.
-Thanks for bringing me!
I start working again tomorrow.
You won't be off for a while?
I have Sunday off, then it's all work.
I have to have some fun while I can.
-How are your nerves doing?
-I'm not nervous anymore.
-You're not?
-I'm not. Are you?
I'm fine.
You're all made-up today.
I thought I'd go for a mature look.
-You look mature.
-That's what I was going for.
-You're 11 years younger than me.
-Eleven.
I'm turning 19 this year,
and you're turning 30.
-How do you feel about that?
-How do I feel?
When I was your age,
30 was way too old.
-Yeah, it seems very mature.
-Yeah.
You're an adult, but you look...
-You look young.
-I do look younger.
I must seem like a kid to you.
A kid? Well, not quite a kid.
You seem mature and calm.
You don't go for older guys?
You said you usually like guys your age.
I can't see myself dating anyone younger.
Only older?
-Did you have fun?
-It was fun.
Was it really?
It was fun.
-Welcome back.
-I'm home.
I'm home.
-She went to eat meat.
-Oh, I want to hear about it.
How was it?
I didn't feel like
there was an age gap at all.
What will you do if he asks you out again?
Will you go?
-I'd go.
-You would?
Just the two of you?
It didn't feel awkward
for the two of us to be alone.
I see. That's the best.
You could see him as a potential boyfriend
the more you know him.
It's a possibility, right?
-Yeah, but it's a little scary.
-Scary?
To fall for someone 11 years older
would be a little scary.
-Because they're experienced?
-It's scary.
I've only ever dated guys my own age.
I like experiencing things together.
Like going somewhere
for the first time together.
So you want to experience
your firsts together.
Yeah, I think so.
Like places you've both never been?
-I'm sure that won't be the case with him.
-You never know.
I've never been on a date
at the aquarium or the zoo.
-I'm sure he has.
-I haven't either.
That's so cute.
But going together for the first time
is a different experience
from going with someone
who's already been.
They can show you what's fun.
That's not what I want.
You want to experience it together?
That's probably
why I've avoided dating older guys.
For example, going to Disneyland
after he'd gone with an ex.
I'd hate that.
-You don't think so?
-There was a time when I did.
But it's a little tough.
Yeah, I know.
-So cute.
-The meat festival.
What a great event to go to on a nice day.
When I was 18, I was dating a 38-year-old.
-Here she comes out of left field.
-From left field?
So experiencing firsts together
was impossible.
So I did have a similar experience.
Like, "Let's go here
because it's really beautiful.
Oh, another place he's been already!"
So there was a little bit of that feeling.
A little jealousy then?
That too, but there was the desire
to experience together
a place he hadn't seen yet.
I haven't thought about it for ten years
until now.
But I totally remember now.
Tamosan's condescending tone
towards Terashima is coming out.
-It's interesting.
-"Did you really have fun?"
She's like the older sister
trying to make sure Riko's okay.
So she's just worried.
"If he asks you out again, would you go?"
It's like she's saying
she should re-think things.
He must really be unappealing in her eyes.
But if things continue this way,
Rikochan may fall for him.
Do you think so?
It'd be nice to see her get
a little more emotional.
She did get emotional when Tamosan said,
"An older guy can show you what's fun."
She said, "That's not what I want!"
-She did say that.
-She shot that down!
-That's true.
-She was emotional in that moment.
It's like it came from
another scene or something.
"It's not that!"
So things are getting
a little more emotional.
I think it's good.
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD
FROM NAGOYA
2009 GRADUATED AICHI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MOVED TO TOKYO
2015 GOT COOKING LICENSE
2016 BEGAN WORK AT TRATTORIA BUCA JUNTA
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
-Getting along with everyone?
-Yeah, I'm having fun.
Nice.
I went on a date yesterday.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
JUNTA ISHIKAWA
OWNER AND CHEF
-That was quick.
-It is, isn't it?
We went to the meat festival.
Nice! You've never had
that kind of opportunity before, right?
I'm not close with anyone younger than me.
I see.
-So it's refreshing for you.
-That's what's fun about it.
I cooked dinner for them.
-Already?
-Yeah.
You move so fast.
Everyone comes home at different times.
-What'd you make?
-Something easy to heat up. Hayashi rice.
Nice.
To cook something for others
which you usually make for yourself
can be stressful.
-It is a little nerve-wracking.
-You can't slack off.
It's good to have a change in environment
and to enjoy life.
Yes, I'm having fun.
I'm sure there's something to gain there.
OMOTESANDO, TOKYO
Once again, welcome to Terrace House.
-So, cheers!
-Cheers!
Cheers.
-Thank you for doing this.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Momoka, it's almost your birthday, right?
-You're turning 21?
-Yes.
We'll have to celebrate.
-Wow!
-It looks so tasty.
Momochan hasn't gone out with anyone yet.
-That's true.
-No, I haven't!
-You were busy this week.
-Yes, I was running around all week.
I really want to go to a comedy show.
-I want to go.
-Really?
-Sounds fun. Let's go sometime.
-Yeah, let's go.
I know a comedian.
-Really?
-Yeah. Wanna go?
-I do, I want to go.
-Yeah, let's go.
-Which comedian?
-He works at the gym.
-His name is Ippei.
-Ippei?
The guy from the comedy duo Earth?
-I know him.
-He was on this show.
-On Terrace House?
-Yeah.
His comedy is always
about the American model Caiya.
-Caiya? Who's that?
-Caiya.
-Oh, an impersonation of her?
-I like it.
It's entertaining.
So, Hayato...
you were an actor at one point?
I was, or I was trying to be.
Can I ask why you quit?
I had already decided
when I came to Tokyo
that I'd quit if I hadn't made it
by the time I turned 30.
How old were you when you came to Tokyo?
I was 21.
That transition...
Yeah, it's difficult.
It's frustrating.
If it's so frustrating,
why wouldn't you keep trying?
I get the feeling
that a part of you still wants to.
Well, I've already made the decision.
Me too.
I'll probably retire from ballet
after turning 30.
Most likely.
The time to quit will come someday.
Listening to you
made me think about my own timing.
So you quit because you gave up?
Yeah.
If it were me...
that would really be...
frustrating for me, I think.
Yeah, well, sure.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Oh, man.
I don't know. It really...
took determination.
It really takes courage...
when you experience
your first big failure.
Things had gone pretty well up until then,
but I accepted my defeat.
Of course it's frustrating.
I don't think you have to give up.
I've already decided.
I think it's good to know when to give up.
-Letting go is important too.
-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to be a downer.
Thank you for telling us.
I truly believe it takes courage
to say what you really think.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
I've always liked Shibuya 109.
I come to SBY often.
I was in customer service for three years
in my hometown.
-I hope to put that experience to use.
-Right.
YASUHA ITO
MANAGER
If you were hired,
what would your availability be like?
I'd like to work
at least two to three days a week.
Is there something in particular
you think you can do
if you worked here?
Something I can do?
Like, something you're especially good at?
What I'm good at?
What I'm good at...
I'm hoping to figure out what I'm good at.
Thank you.
I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-Are you alone, Riko?
Yeah.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Thanks.
-How was your day?
-I had an interview for a part-time job.
-That's right! At SBY?
-Yeah.
-Did you get it?
-I don't know yet.
Oh, I see.
-If you get it, I'll come visit.
-Yeah.
I might not get it though.
It'll be fine.
She asked me what I'm good at...
and I couldn't think of anything.
I don't think I know myself that well.
It's difficult to know your strengths.
I don't think I know my strengths either.
It made me realize
that I should really think about it.
Otherwise, I won't know.
I hope you'll be able to find it here
at Terrace House.
Yeah.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Welcome back.
-You're home.
-Welcome back.
You guys were talking so quietly.
It was a serious conversation.
-How was your day, Misaki?
-I had a meeting today.
-I'm exhausted.
-You seem tired.
It's so difficult to sell yourself.
-We were just talking about that.
-Oh, really?
-No way.
-How'd you know?
-I didn't. I didn't hear.
-How scary.
-I felt that way after my meeting today.
-Really?
What did you say today?
I said I didn't know my strengths
and I'd like to figure out what they are.
-It's very positive.
-Yeah.
I think it's good.
-Hold on. We need the lights.
-Oh, it's warm today!
Wow!
It's so pretty.
-Wow!
-It's definitely cold.
-It's warm.
-No way.
Yeah, it's nice.
It was cold yesterday.
-We can totally get in.
-Seriously?
-You're going in?
-Totally.
It was cold yesterday.
-Do you have swim trunks?
-I do.
I'm gonna go buy some.
You could go naked in the morning.
Maybe not a good idea.
Misaki is gonna hate me more.
Don't worry.
-Has anyone swum here before?
-Arman was the first.
The first?
It looked like it felt nice.
No way!
Thank you! I'm so surprised.
Thank you!
-Can I?
-Of course, go ahead.
Whoops!
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you. Thank you.
-I'm so happy.
-Twenty-one years old.
I'm super happy.
-Shall we eat over there?
-Yeah.
-It's not over yet.
-Don't turn around.
From Handa...
a gift!
-Really? Thank you!
-Happy birthday.
-Let's keep it going.
-Yeah.
Bring it on.
-Keep it coming.
-Wait, wait.
-We all have gifts.
-What? Really?
This is from me.
-Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
Thank you so much.
-There's more coming.
-Wait a sec.
-This one's from me.
-Thank you!
Wow, I'm so happy.
-Happy birthday, Momochan.
-Thank you!
What am I gonna do with all this?
-Happy birthday.
-It's big.
Thank you.
What should I do?
-Why don't you open them in order?
-Right, in order.
-It's so cute!
-Isn't it?
I hope it looks good on me.
-It's so cute.
-I totally thought it's you.
-Is Arman's next?
-Arman's is next.
-What's this?
-What's that?
A planetarium.
Oh, I see.
-What was that?
-The receipt.
-Wow!
-Oh!
-Oh, you can use it in the tub.
-I'm glad I spotted it.
Wow!
-Yeah, you can use it in the bath.
-The bath is spacious. It'd be perfect.
-You can use that in the bath?
-Yeah.
You're always tired after your lessons.
Are you on the top bunk?
-I'm on top.
-Oh, that's perfect then.
-Nice.
-Thank you.
Should we all go in the pool?
You just want to go in.
-You're welcome to.
-No one else is going to?
-We'll watch you.
-I'm gonna go in then.
-Go ahead.
-It's hot.
It's been so happy in the house this week,
with the party and all.
The weather's nice,
and they had the birthday party...
-It's so warm.
-It's so peaceful.
So peaceful.
-They had the welcome dinner.
-Yes, the welcome dinner.
They said they'd go see the comedy show.
-I'm sure we'll be seeing Earth.
-Oh, yes, Earth.
I wonder if they're still doing
Maki Ohguro's impersonation.
I wonder.
They were talking about that,
but then you look over at Hayato--
Yeah, Hayato...
-Tamosan was really pushing him.
-She really was.
-It's like Fuyumi took over.
-Yeah.
Did Nacchan leave Fuyumi behind?
-That'd be too evil.
-Yeah.
The next day he mentioned
how he didn't want to be hated anymore.
He's already picked up
that she doesn't like him.
But seeing him cry
made me like him a little.
-Oh, good.
-I don't mean like in that way.
-Torichan...
-He was so honest.
-You got a glimpse of that part of him.
-And he never wavered.
He clearly said
he made his decision to quit.
-It was very cool of him.
-That's true.
Especially since he seemed
so superficial at first.
Yes.
And Arman gave a planetarium as a gift.
The planetarium...
it's really just a toy that you might get
in high school or something.
But he says it's so she can relax
in the tub when she comes home tired.
-That reasoning might move Momoka.
-I see.
-That's true.
-It's not bad.
"Arman, can you see stars like this
from where you live in Hawaii?"
"Yeah, you can."
"We can pas de deux
under the stars in Hawaii."
-All together.
-Yeah, all together.
-Ready? Three, two, one.
-I'm scared!
Nice.
-It was cold yesterday.
-It's not too bad now.
No way.
It's cold!
-You're getting out?
-I'm done.
That was quick.
-Summer's here.
-Yeah.
I've been here six months,
and this is my first time in.
I'm awake now.
I'm going in.
-Good night.
Hey there.
-Can I come sit next to you?
-Sure.
It's cold.
-It's so nice.
-Yeah.
-I do want to go in.
-You should. Maybe during the day.
Yeah, maybe if it's during the day.
You mentioned
you wanted to see a comedy show.
Ippei said there's something next Sunday.
-Really?
-Yeah, so if you're free...
-The 22nd?
-Yeah, the 22nd.
-I'm free.
-You are? Let's go.
I'm looking forward to it.
-I'll find out what time it starts.
-Okay.
I love comedy.
We're not going to the beach?
-We'll do the beach next time.
-Next time? Okay.