-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Previously, two new members moved in.
-Hikaru and Natsumi.
-That's right.
I think Arisa is cute.
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD
I'm usually not bothered by other guys.
Don't worry about me.
Just go for it.
I'll make my move then.
He's got the passionate Italian blood.
He clearly tells Arman his intentions.
"Oh, really, that's good."
"Oh, really, that's fine with me.
I think that's fine."
Only the bottom half
of Arman's face moves.
The top half reveals no expression.
Maybe he's had a lot of Botox done.
-Do you like the ocean?
-I love the ocean.
Me, too.
Then let's explore Japanese beaches.
Sure, I'm usually free.
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
The spirited and aggressive Osaka accent
of the Kansai dialect.
-Yes.
-Natsumi.
That led to the development
of the Kansai Dilemma.
The Kansai Dilemma?
The first Kansai Dilemma in Terrace House.
Minori experienced Kansai firsthand.
But couples
that are always making fun of each other,
I don't really understand.
It's harder to imagine them kissing.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
-Do you have to be able to imagine it?
-No, but...
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
You guys are probably
just complete opposites.
Total opposites.
She wouldn't let it go.
I was a little ticked.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD
-She's scary.
-Scary?
-She clearly said she's scared.
-She did.
-She doesn't have bad intentions.
-Her intentions are good.
It was just Kansai style teasing.
Arisa is a little busy right now.
-Her exhibition is coming up.
-That's right.
There's potential for new relationships.
-And between Minori and Natsumi...
-That's right.
how will the Kansai Dilemma
be resolved?
If it gets resolved.
And the way Arisa rejected Arman.
Let's have everyone remember
how terrible she was.
She's busy with her work now,
and things have been left at that.
But let's all keep questioning
whether her actions were human.
His dark side is in control now.
I can't see anything else.
Yes, you are wearing a necklace after all.
Bad boys wear necklaces, right?
Arisa seems busy.
Have you talked?
Not recently.
I want to, but I don't want to bother her.
She does seem really busy.
It's not a great time to ask for a date.
Why don't you do something for her?
Yeah, I've told her to let me know
if there's anything I can help with.
Why don't you cook for her?
She did say it'd be nice to have
dinner ready when she gets home.
That's true.
-I can't imagine him cooking.
-I can make poke.
-What?
-Poke.
-Poke?
-What's poke?
-It's a Hawaiian dish.
You cut albacore into cubes,
you dice them,
and mix it with sesame oil and soy sauce.
Sounds good.
Like a maguro-don.
-Yes, a poke-don.
-Sounds tasty.
It sounds cute, poke-don.
Maybe I'll surprise her.
-I'm sure she'll be happy.
-Yeah.
And I'm free tomorrow,
so I'll make it then.
-You're free tomorrow?
-Yeah.
When do you work?
-Nacchan said the same thing.
-What?
"Aren't you worried that you don't work?"
She said the same thing to Minori. Right?
Oh, she said it to Minori, too?
She's back.
Welcome back.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-Back from China?
-I'm back from China.
-Welcome back.
-Thanks.
-It's been a while.
-It has!
I'm so tired!
Wow, you get to travel out of the country.
Did you say you're going to Okinawa, too?
Yeah, the day after tomorrow.
-The day after tomorrow?
-Oh, maybe the day after that.
-For how long?
-Three days, two nights.
You're never here.
-Never.
-You're so busy.
Yeah, really busy.
But you're off tomorrow?
-I'm off tomorrow.
-That's good.
I'm going to get some water.
It's so dirty.
Did no one clean?
Hey, guys.
It's a little messy in there, no?
-Is it?
-The kitchen's pretty bad.
We haven't cleaned.
Looks like udon.
-Udon?
-Did we eat udon?
Yeah, what Arisa made.
-We'll do it.
-We did eat it.
We'll do it.
Let's put in some effort.
Are you guys not bothered?
Yeah, we all tend to not be bothered.
-Yeah, whoever notices usually does it.
-We're all pretty laid back.
Let's just get the dishes done now.
-So impressive.
-Come on.
Doesn't it only take
one person to wash dishes?
-No, two.
-That's terrible!
You're terrible.
-I was kidding. Of course I'll help.
-Let's go.
Very commendable.
How unusual!
It's dirty!
See?
It is dirty.
Hikaru seems messy, too.
-Hikaru keeps using new cups.
-He does.
I only used one of those cups.
-That's a lie.
-It's true.
-It's for sure a lie.
-It's the truth.
I don't really know what you do yet.
And vice versa.
About each other's jobs.
Like how things are going.
You want to focus on just modeling?
Right now? Yeah.
Was I wrong?
-Was I wrong?
-No, that's what I want.
-And in the future?
-The future?
I want to live and work on a ranch.
Oh, so you want to do that
while modeling?
Yes, that's right.
That's what I want right now.
Why did you join Terrace House?
-Because it sounded fun.
-Oh.
And what's the reason you're still here?
My reason?
For me, January just happens to be busy.
If I was home all the time,
I'd think about why I'm here now.
In my case anyway.
You're saying that's me now?
Well... yeah.
Or, if I was in that situation.
I don't think there's anything wrong
with having free time,
or being home because of it.
Do you think about leaving?
-I do.
-No way.
I'm leaving in February.
-What?
-That's my plan. The end of February.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What about your boyfriend?
He knows.
But I don't know what Uchi will be doing.
I'm sure you wouldn't like it if he stays.
-What?
-Your boyfriend.
I think it's up to Uchi to decide
when he wants to leave.
You're not a normal couple.
You're a curious couple.
Our situation is different,
but we're no different than anyone else.
I see.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
Good morning.
-It's cold, isn't it?
-It's super cold.
-What are you doing today?
-Today?
Nothing really.
-I'm staying in.
-You are?
-But isn't the weather amazing today?
-Yeah.
I wonder if it's cold.
It looks cold.
Then let's go eat something delicious.
I haven't had Japanese food in a while.
-Sure.
-Something Japanese.
-Let's go.
-Let's go near the ocean.
-Near the ocean, and...
-Near the ocean?
-Maybe to Enoshima?
-Enoshima?
-In that direction.
-Okay.
-It's warm today.
-Yeah, it's great.
-It's great when men can drive well.
-Right?
It's amazing to be able to drive and talk.
Right?
Hey, so when you're free,
let's go to different places.
Sounds good.
You're going to be my guide?
-Sure.
-Okay, thanks.
ENOSHIMA, KANAGAWA
ENOSHIMA KOYA
Our Two Specialty Dons
Makanai-Don and Horohoro-Don
-It's pretty here.
-Yeah, it is.
It's great around sunset.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's the makanai-don, no wasabi.
-Wow!
-Excuse me.
Looks amazing.
-Bon appétit.
-Delicious.
-It's delicious.
It's been a week, but you've only been
at Terrace House for two days.
-Yeah.
-Three days I mean.
How is it?
Of the girls, Arisa is easiest to talk to.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But out of everyone,
you're the easiest to talk to.
Seriously? I'm glad.
What about Minori?
Minori?
I guess it's just her personality.
Anything I say...
I think she takes offense to it.
-She's sensitive?
-Yeah.
She'll say, "What's wrong with that?"
I don't mean to hurt her.
But anyways...
I thought she might not like me.
-Everyone's pretty peaceful.
-Really?
We don't argue.
Most of the members
don't really talk, though.
That's true.
Maybe that's why.
Since I came, I've thought about
how everyone's so nice.
No one ever complains.
I wonder how they really feel.
It's nice we get along, and it's peaceful,
but that's all.
There's a wall.
You develop real friendships
after arguing, or more talks.
So I think it's good.
You bring a new vibe to the house.
-So...
-Yeah?
An honest question.
-Totally honest.
-What is it?
About Arisa...
Do you really like her?
Yeah, I do.
Really?
She works until midnight every day.
I don't want to bother her
by asking her on a date.
-So it's not like things are awkward.
-Awkward?
No, not anymore.
Do you like her a lot?
Or is it just interest right now?
-I like her.
-That much?
Yeah, kind of a lot.
I see.
What percentage?
Well, I just like her.
I don't know what percentage.
So you really like her.
I see.
I want to be in love, too.
-You do?
-I do!
I don't necessarily want to be
in a relationship.
Just in love.
Sounds good.
Will you pull it for me?
Hold on. Let me go first.
-It's cold.
-No way!
-It's true. Yeah.
-The sand?
Oh, how embarrassing!
Isn't that hard to put on
while laying down?
Wait, will you pull?
I can only do one thing.
I can either hold or pull.
Nice!
Thank you.
I like those socks.
Those are cute socks.
It's so cold!
-It's super cold.
-It's cold!
-Totally.
It's so pretty, though. Look.
Yeah, it's clear.
Nice.
Nice. I'm good at selfies.
-That was fun.
-Yeah.
Sparks are flying
between Minori and Natsumi.
At any moment, Minori could be like,
"What's your problem?"
There was that kind of tension.
-It's gone beyond the Kansai idea, though.
-That's true.
That wasn't quite
the general Kansai teasing.
No, the issue goes beyond that.
"If I was at home with nothing to do,
I might question myself..."
"You're talking about me?"
"Yeah."
Unbelievable!
-That's hard to say.
-Unbelievable!
If she was going to say it...
She said it herself;
she happens to be busy now.
But next month,
she'll have free time too.
So she should have prefaced it with,
"I'll be in the same situation."
-Yes.
-If she was going to say that to Minori.
-Is that an attack on her?
-I wonder.
I wondered if she just didn't notice
how Minori was taking it.
But she knew.
So that means...
maybe Natsumi's also annoyed
by Minori's reactions.
Like, "Why are you all worked up?"
It's a different crassness than Seina's.
-It's different.
-Yeah.
SEINA SHIMABUKURO
Seina's crassness was just stupidity
with no bad intentions.
Like a rampaging dog.
A rampaging dog knocking things over.
But this is a rampaging human.
Yeah, a person.
-A rampaging human.
-A rampaging human?
Maybe she's just
a little immature and spirited.
Yeah, she probably doesn't have
bad intentions.
There's that, too,
but also,
Arman apparently still likes Arisa.
That's true.
And the way Natsumi was questioning Arman.
"Do you like her?"
And he says, "Yeah."
And then, "How much?"
She really questions him.
And she says she wants to be in love, too.
She did invite him out.
How do you think Natsumi feels
about Arman?
Like, she's just playing with a big dog.
-She's a bit of a tomboy.
-I sense a bit of Heidi in her.
You mean the type
that innocently leads men on.
So she's a Heidi.
-Yeah, of Naniwa.
-Heidi of Naniwa.
I'm sorry.
I hadn't made that connection.
How is it, chef?
-It's delicious.
-Is it?
-It's good.
-Right?
It's good.
Hi.
We're making Hawaiian food.
Poke-don?
-Poke-don?
-Yeah, Poke-don.
Ahi poke.
There might not be enough for everyone.
It's supposed to be for Arisa.
-You already had curry, right?
-We did.
You can try some of the ahi poke.
Okay.
-What?
-Nothing.
-It was nothing.
Hey, Arman, let's go chat.
What?
-Let's chat.
-What?
What's going on?
-What is it?
-I don't know.
How scary!
What'd you do today?
I went to Shonan.
By yourself?
Of course not!
With Arman.
Why?
-What do you mean?
-For fun?
-Are you mad?
-What? Why?
What? What's going on?
It's just sudden.
I wondered if you made plans long before.
-What? Sudden?
-What?
What did you do in Shonan?
So many questions.
What?
Did you wonder where we went?
I didn't know you guys went out.
Did everyone share that stuff before?
Everyone usually knew...
I think we usually knew.
-We only decided this morning.
-What?
We only just decided this morning,
so there wasn't time to say anything.
-Are you listening?
-Yeah.
If you need me to report anything,
just let me know.
I've never needed that.
It just sounds like you're mad at me.
Like, "How could you just go?"
Like, "Why wouldn't you tell anyone?"
And here we are just cooking
and trying to have dinner,
and you guys come in and call him out.
Why can't they just talk here?
-I'm sorry?
-What?
-I'm sorry.
-No, that's not it.
It's nothing to apologize for.
-What was going on there?
-You mean being in the kitchen together?
If it's what we talked about yesterday,
I though poke-don was something
you would make for Arisa.
I just figured she could help
if I'm making poke,
and we'd make it together.
You didn't tell her
you were making it for Arisa?
Like, the idea why you're making it?
Well, no.
If you don't tell her,
it's like there's something going on.
Instead of,
"Hey, I made this with Nacchan,"
she'll be happier
if it's completely from you.
She said she'd help,
and we're roommates.
She didn't do anything wrong.
I don't mean she did.
I don't think it's anything
to have a serious talk over.
Sorry for the wait.
-It's done already?
-Not yet.
-The poke, I mean.
-Oh, the poke.
-The color changed.
-Yeah.
It looks a little grotesque.
-Bon appétit.
-Sorry it's gotten complicated.
-What?
-It's gotten complicated.
-It's okay.
I said I was going to make it
for Arisa yesterday.
So he asked why we're making it together,
and he said that she'd probably be happier
if I made it myself.
And that might be true,
but you offered to help.
From now on...
when I go somewhere with you,
-I'll tell Arisa.
-Sure.
But what's the point of telling
Uchi and Minori?
It doesn't concern them.
I don't know why they're so worried.
It was delicious.
I'm really sorry it's gotten complicated.
It's not your fault.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-Did you have dinner already?
-I did.
-I thought maybe you hadn't.
-Really?
Can you still eat?
I'm sorry. I ate some bread while working.
There's some Hawaiian poke...
that I made.
You made it?
I'm sorry. I'll have some then.
Just a little.
-I'm so happy.
-Want something to drink?
-Yeah, some water.
-Water?
-Here.
-Thanks.
-It's very thoughtful of you.
-It's nothing.
You seem so busy.
I've never had this before.
-How is it?
-It's delicious.
-Is it?
-Yeah.
Nacchan helped, too.
How're things going?
I'm busy with work.
If there's anything I can do,
just let me know.
-Like physical labor.
-Physical labor?
-Physical labor...
-None?
I'll let you know.
I asked why they went out today.
Then she asked if I was mad.
Yesterday we were talking about work, too.
I wonder why she's combative towards me.
Can't you tell her?
Even if I do, I feel like
she's not trying to understand.
It's like, "Why are you like that?
Why are you like that, Minori?"
And just now,
she said something like,
"If you say it like that,
it doesn't make me feel good."
I don't know if I can live with her.
It's hard.
Should I talk to her?
To Nacchan?
-That was quite a scene.
-Lots of sparks flying.
-Surprising.
-There were a lot of "what"s.
-What?
-What? What?
Here it is.
The stress is here.
This is what they mean when they say,
they just don't mesh.
They just don't mesh.
I'm sure it was annoying for her
to see her unhappy expression
and yet not clearly saying anything.
It's really easy to see
how conflicts occur.
It's like these earphones.
You put them in your bag,
and they get tangled.
Yes.
I feel like I just saw
how they get tangled.
I see.
I don't really think either are at fault.
It's just a difference in personality.
But when Natsumi helped Arman,
Uchi said, "That's not good."
Why are you nit-picking her actions?
You're a man.
There's no need for that.
-It's so nit-picky!
-He pulled him aside and everything.
I'd understand if it was a girl.
I'd get it if it was
Minori's or Arisa's friend.
But he's a man!
He shouldn't get involved.
He'd listened to Minori's complaints.
Maybe he just felt like he needed to help.
He probably has to hear it all the time.
I bet the Japanese-style room is hell
just until he sleeps.
After getting home from work.
Yes, having to listen to
"This is what she said today,
and she made this kind of face,"
and on and on...
It's bad luck that they happen to be
at Terrace House at the same time.
It's bad timing.
Maybe we'll get to see
how to resolve issues like these.
If it can be resolved.
Let's have a house meeting today.
So what happened was,
when the two of us were cooking,
Uchi suddenly pulled Arman away.
Out of the room.
And Minori sat here.
I didn't really like
the way Minori was talking to me.
Her tone...
Minori denied it,
saying that was not how she meant it.
-That's when things got a little...
-I see.
There was a little argument.
But we didn't want things to be awkward.
That's how this started.
But what Uchi did in that moment
wasn't very good.
Why?
First of all, I didn't know
he was making it for Arisa.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
-So Arman was making it for Arisa?
Either way,
you could've just said it here.
I was thinking of you at that point.
In case you didn't know Arman liked Arisa.
-I didn't want you to feel--
-But that's just an assumption.
-Assumption?
-Your own assumption.
You assumed
that I have feelings for Arman.
-That's why you did what you did.
-That's right.
-I assumed--
-But if that's not true--
And what if it was true?
If you make assumptions,
then while we were just cooking together
as normal roommates, I--
Let's say my assumptions are right--
You don't know that.
You have no right.
So it was just a matter of Arman
not explaining well enough.
So it's Arman's fault?
Not his fault, but yesterday...
So it was all just a misunderstanding.
Yeah, I get both sides.
So he told you why, right?
That he likes Arisa,
and as a roommate, you'd help.
You had that conversation, right?
What do you mean?
No, we didn't.
-I didn't tell her the meal was for Arisa.
-No.
But earlier, we talked about Arisa.
And I told her I liked her.
But no, I didn't say
the meal was for Arisa.
Can I explain my thoughts?
Coming home, I saw you guys
cooking together and thought, "What?"
-That's where I felt that--
-I got that.
The moment you came in,
you both gave me weird looks.
And it made me uncomfortable.
-I thought, "Why look at me like that?"
-It was my fault for not explaining.
And I talked to Arman and found out
that it was just as roommates,
so it was fine.
But if it wasn't,
and it was just you guys cooking together,
then I felt it was wrong,
so I pulled Arman aside.
So it was on behalf of Arisa.
But did you consider
how I'd feel by doing that?
Did I consider? Well, I...
We were just cooking,
and you guys came
and suddenly pulled aside Arman.
And then you guys disappeared,
and Minori started interrogating me.
"Where'd you go today? Why?
Why would you do that?"
That's what it sounded like to me.
-If someone does that to you--
-I do feel bad about that.
I think I didn't word it well.
I honestly didn't know
what Uchi was going to say to Arman.
We weren't trying to gang up on you.
But the tone of voice is revealing.
I think what came out
stemmed from our previous talks
when you asked me why I liked Uchi.
You said things like
how we're a strange couple.
That really made me feel bad.
You tend to be... pretty blunt.
So that was me just honestly asking.
But you kept taking it as criticism.
So what happened in the kitchen
is the flip of that.
Yeah, you didn't consider
Minori's feelings.
Just like you asked
whether I considered your feelings.
Have you considered Minori's feelings?
Is it just all about how we look at it?
There's that too,
and the way I said things in the kitchen,
as well as how you've said things.
We're here because of all of that.
You've just misunderstood each other.
I didn't explain well enough either.
So let's not let this happen again.
Let's all do our best
to not let it happen again.
It's inevitable.
Cheers!
If you brush it off like that,
the friendship
will always remain superficial.