It's been a while, everyone.
It's been a while.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared
is a beautiful home and automobile.
As usual, there is no script at all.
No, there is not.
Terrace House has now
been revived by Netflix.
Wow. Amazing.
It's an amazing thing.
Netflix came to our shores
and showed their interest
in Terrace House.
They may have said,
"We must do Terrace House."
Japanese with a foreign accent.
They were like,
"I want to see Tokui."
Did they actually say "Tokui"?
I'm so honored.
So this studio...
Yes, this is a Netflix office.
I see.
What a great place!
Isn't it?
Amazing.
I would like to greet
a new member to our team.
-This is Ayumu Mochizuki.
-Hi.
-Pleased to meet you.
-He's cute.
-He is.
My name is Ayumu Mochizuki.
I am 14 years old and in grade 9.
Ah, how cute!
-Have you seen Terrace House before?
-Yes.
A-ha.
What do you think of the show?
I watch it with my mother.
I get really emotional.
Oh, you're that type.
Did anyone leave an impression on you?
Let's see.
Well, Ms. Kakei was very determined.
MIWAKO KAKEI, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
CAST FROM MAY TO DECEMBER 2013
I liked her for that.
Oh, stop!
I'm going to melt.
All this brilliance.
Melting from this overwhelming brilliance.
You just can't take it.
-So this is the new title.
-Yes.
Terrace House: Boys & Girls in the City.
And it will be located in Tokyo.
Last time it was in Shonan.
And this house is brand new.
And the members are totally new.
So we'll see what happens.
Tesu is not with us anymore?
TETSUYA SUGAYA, 22, ACTOR
CAST OCT. 2012 - DEC. 2014
A total of 18 episodes.
And so we know
when the final episode will be.
Is that right?
-So let's watch.
-Yes, let's!
Wow!
I'm excited!
Oof...
No one's here.
How huge!
Well...
Seriously?
Amazing.
Really?
I'm the first?
Someone's here.
-Nice to meet you.
I am Makoto.
I am Minori Nakada.
No one else is here.
-Am I the second one?
-Yes.
Phew.
The second one.
-I look forward to living with you.
-Uh, Makoto?
-Yes, Makoto.
-How old are you?
-I'll be 22 this year.
-Oh, you're 21?
-Yes.
-The same age?
-Same age.
I'm glad we're the same age.
This house is amazing.
There's a pool.
Oh, I didn't see it.
Amazing.
Yeah, it's nice.
Are you a student?
I'm in my fourth year in university
and I'm a model too.
-I see.
-I do both.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
-Are you a student?
-Yes, I am.
-University?
-University.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
-Fourth year.
-The same?
Yes. Totally the same.
Which university?
Mei-Gaku. Meiji Gakuin.
-And where do you study?
-Nichi-Dai.
Nichi-Dai?
Were you able to sleep last night?
I didn't really sleep much.
Yeah, that's right.
Someone's here.
I can hear.
It's a guy.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
-Hi.
I am Yuki Adachi.
I look forward to living with you.
Likewise.
-I am Minori Nakada.
-I'm Makoto Hasegawa.
-Makoto?
-Yes.
Sorry for interrupting.
What are we supposed to do?
Were you guys chatting?
Yes, we were trying.
-You're the third one.
-What?
-The third one? Good, good.
I'm glad you seem friendly.
-How old are you?
-I'll be 28 this year.
Twenty-eight.
Could be an older brother.
You're tanned.
What do you do?
I...
-play baseball.
-Baseball?
-Still now?
-Yes, I still continue to play.
-University student?
-Yes, university baseball.
I see.
Do you work?
Work... I tap dance.
I've been active as an instructor
and a performer.
YUKI ADACHI, 27 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
Amazing.
I've never met one before.
-Please come see my performance.
-I will.
-My dancing is all right.
-All right?
Just all right?
A girl.
Your pit sweat is showing.
Oh, damn.
It shows easily with that color shirt.
-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
So this is how it feels.
I am Mizuki Shida.
-I look forward to living with you.
-Likewise.
Now, now...
-Here?
-I don't know. Anywhere is fine.
Excuse me.
What an amazing house!
I'm surprised.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm an office worker.
-Office worker?
-Yes.
I'll be 23 soon.
In clothing?
No, it's a company related to soccer.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
-Soccer?
-Yes.
But I like baseball too.
-I used to play soccer.
-Oh, really?
In high school.
I joined the team but quit right away.
I got too busy with dance.
Ah, I see.
The president of the company runs
various enterprises,
and one of them is a cafe.
I also work as a barista there
twice a week.
What's a barista?
-Oh, coffee.
-Coffee?
-I make them
-A barista.
Just like that.
Another one?
-I was... a little nervous.
-It's a guy.
It's a guy.
-Hello.
A sewing machine?
He seems nice and fresh.
He's holding something.
-It's a sewing machine.
-Sewing machine?
He brought a sewing machine.
Here he is.
Is it okay if I sit here?
Excuse me.
-I look forward to living with you.
-Likewise.
I am Tatsuya Uchihara.
I'm 23 years old.
What's that?
Oh, it's my favorite age.
Really?
-I'm a hair stylist at Daikan-yama.
-A hair stylist.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
HAIR STYLIST
-Why the sewing machine?
-Sewing machine?
I've recently got into sewing.
So the machine is for clothes.
-You make them?
-Yes, I make them.
Separate from work?
Yes, aside from work.
It's just a simple hobby.
Wow.
Someone's here.
It's heavy.
She said it's heavy.
-Should we help?
-Oh, she's up.
Oh.
-Did she see us?
-She hasn't.
She's reacting to the room.
That's right.
-Hello.
Hello.
Phew. It's heavy.
Guys, help her.
Please help.
I look forward to living with you.
Likewise.
Excuse me.
I am Yuriko Hayata.
I'm 23 years old.
What do you do?
I'm in my fourth year of university.
Ah.
What type of university?
It's a medical university.
Wow.
-Medicine.
-A doctor?
Yes, I aspire to be one.
Yes.
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Well, I haven't become one yet.
-But...
-I'm going for it.
Amazing.
Wow, I've never been in a place like this.
There's a pool, too.
-It's amazing.
-Wow! You're right!
-There's a pool.
-A pool.
What?
Let's have fun this month.
-Of course.
-Yes.
Yes! So it begins.
So it starts.
The girls are beautiful.
All of them.
The three girls are quite distinct
from one another.
-Yes.
-You think so, too?
Yuriko is like, you know, girlie.
-Yes.
-And Minori is the lively model.
Yes, with the exotic look.
Right?
And then Mizuki is the career woman.
Very frank.
She also works as a barista.
-Really.
-Wow.
So out of the three,
you would be, more or less...
-Yes.
-...interested in Yuriko Hayata?
-I see.
She is very attractive.
Any guy would be
into someone like Yuriko.
-Any guy.
-For sure.
Generally, though, at first glance,
you can say which person
most guys would be into.
But she could be the type
that would slowly reveal her dark side.
-Yes, well, it was like that before.
-You are right.
What about the guys?
That hair stylist...
-Tatsuya.
-He is so handsome.
-There it is.
-Teacher Triendl.
What is that?
He works at Daikan-yama.
He's invincible.
There's nothing negative about him.
He's tall, too.
And his hobby is making clothes.
I hope he has bad taste, at least.
Then I can laugh at him.
"How could you make this appliqué!"
You need something like that
or he has no flaws.
Wouldn't there be a struggle?
Well, Makoto had those pit stains,
being anxious and all.
Doesn't that come across badly
with women?
-No.
-Not at all.
Really?
He's fine.
He seems to be full of vigor.
Yamasato, you just don't know anything.
You really haven't learned anything.
Is it the tap dancer
that's in trouble, then?
What do you mean, "in trouble"?
Yes, that's all you're talking about.
I want to figure out now who is going
to be my target for the next 18 episodes.
Throughout 18 episodes?
Wow, amazing.
-Fantastic.
-This is great.
This is amazing.
Look at that kitchen!
So who can cook?
Who can cook?
It would be a waste if no one can cook.
-Wow.
-Amazing.
-Do you cook?
I don't cook.
This makes me want to cook.
I think the women
can make good use of this.
The men here aren't too--
I think we've got our hands full
with all of this!
A dishwasher.
We got a dishwasher?
I'm so happy.
Amazing!
I wanted to try it.
This is great.
This is so nice.
It's soft.
-This is nice.
-So nice.
Awesome.
This is great.
How many meters is it?
-Awesome.
-Fifteen meters?
What about upstairs?
Incredible.
Yes, I wonder about upstairs.
It looks very spacious.
Wow, a bunk bed.
Amazing.
-The girls get bunks too?
-Adorable.
Come over here.
Oh, my God!
Wow! Wow!
What is it?
Amazing!
-Wow.
-Is there a Jacuzzi?
-It's there for sure.
-Yes, it's there.
Is that a TV?
A TV!
This is awesome.
There are three shower heads
-so we can all shower together.
-So we can all shower together.
You're right.
Ready, go!
We're the same.
That's mine.
Okay, you're over there.
Rock, paper, scissors?
First time rock.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Right, so I'm over here.
-Do you want to switch once a month?
-Want to? Monthly.
Amazing.
This is great.
Okay, here we are.
This is nice.
Three beds.
It's a cool design.
Who will go where?
I'm not sure which one is the best.
-I want to go up top because I am tall.
-Yeah?
-I don't really care.
-Me neither.
No, really.
Really, is it okay?
Yeah, no problem.
I'll be here.
I get the top?
Yes, it's all right.
Hey, I just realized,
I'll hit my head on the ceiling.
Ouch!
Can we switch?
Where do you want to be?
Would you like to be here?
-Yes, over there.
-Right, so I'll go up.
You can take this one, too.
This is fine.
Does it fit you perfectly?
Well, perfect or not,
you need to try it to see if it works.
Sure.
So...
The next one?
Another room.
This is awesome.
Nice.
-This is like a conference room.
-Check out the cabinets.
This is amazing.
A TV.
There it is.
This is the place where
we bring our stories and talk.
-While we drink.
-Can you drink?
No, I can't.
And you, Makoto?
Yes, I can.
I can drink a lot.
I can't drink at all.
What will you do instead?
I'll drink a cola instead.
-A cola?
-I'll talk while drinking cola.
We need to go shopping.
There's probably no food.
Pots. Kettle.
I think that turns on.
-The women...
-Huh?
Cooking.
-What are you guys doing?
-Are you cooking?
-I'm getting hungry.
-How are your rooms?
The rooms are amazing.
I'm hungry.
-Yes.
-What do you want to eat?
I like omu-rice.
-How cute.
-He's cute.
-So cute.
-Omelet filled with rice?
It's not something
everyone can eat together.
-Yeah.
-You can't make it in a single batch.
Can we let the women
take care of the cooking?
No, I don't think that will be the case.
-How are your skills?
-Not that good.
This is where you can impress us.
No, I don't like this vibe
of being judged or something.
-Tatsuya looks down on people.
-I'm generally strong-minded.
-Well...
-It's just that we're hungry, so...
Let's not get hung up about cooking.
What about hand roll sushi?
-Oh, that sounds nice.
-Yeah, we can make them as we eat.
So we go to the supermarket?
Rock or paper, go!
-Oh, man.
-Okay, let's go with that.
Did the girls talk?
-About what?
-You know, whatever.
Do you think you girls will get along?
-We are fine.
-Yes.
And you guys?
We are totally fine.
Though I think Tatsuya
is a little peculiar.
I mean, something...
I'm so hungry.
What's Tatsuya up to?
Isn't he taking a long time?
Did he say he was taking a shower?
He'll be doing this a lot.
Right now?
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
I took a bath.
What will you do tomorrow?
What shall I do?
-Study?
It's summer vacation, right?
Yes, it is.
You don't cook?
Do you live by yourself?
Yes, I do.
-I sometimes eat out.
-Do you have a specialty?
A specialty?
Let's see.
Traditional?
You can cook traditional Japanese?
Well, traditional simmered dishes.
-Isn't that difficult?
-Really?
Yes, simmered dishes.
So make some for me next time.
Make you some simmered dishes?
NISSIN WORLD DELICATESSEN
AZABU-JUBAN, TOKYO
What was it he said?
Green tea, shampoo...
Sake.
But I don't know much about sake.
It doesn't matter.
Where is the shopping cart?
-Vegetables, this way?
There's lettuce.
Let's get some lettuce.
What about cucumber?
-Yes. Cucumber.
-Tomatoes.
Which one?
This one?
Leafy?
How much?
-This is 2,000 yen.
-2,000 yen?
This is going to be
a really expensive dinner for us.
-It's fine. It's the first night.
-You're right.
-So let's have a toast.
-Good idea.
So, cheers.
Cheers!
-Cheers!
This looks so good.
Oh, you went for the salmon.
Delicious.
When is everyone waking up tomorrow?
Tomorrow we're going for a swim.
-Our group is going to take it easy.
-Yes.
Yes, we decided on getting in the pool.
Tomorrow is my regular working day.
Are you off on weekends?
Usually, yes.
But often there are soccer matches
on weekends.
Then I take a day off
during the week.
I see.
But you like baseball.
-I also like it.
-Earlier you said...
Is there someone you like, Tatsuya?
-What?
-All of a sudden.
-We have to make sure we ask you.
-What do you mean, someone I like?
A hair stylist would be popular.
There's no one right now.
So you're recruiting?
Yes, I'm recruiting a girlfriend.
That's why I'm here.
-That's why you're here?
-Whoa!
Amazing.
Does everyone here
have a significant other?
No, I don't right now.
So, just casually, what is your type?
Just casually...
Maybe it's not a good time
to get a drink right now.
He heard.
He can hear.
I'm listening.
Well, someone who tries hard
and someone I can respect.
-Respect, yes.
-That's important.
-What about appearance?
-Appearance?
I like cute-looking guys.
-Cute-looking?
-Cute-looking guys?
Aren't you a cute-looking guy?
It's hard to tell
once you begin to like them.
You can't tell.
-Someone who tries hard.
-Yes.
-Are you with someone now?
-No.
So everyone is single?
Everyone is single?
Everyone is single.
And what are you into?
Tall people.
-Oh, really?
-Tall people?
Right, you are tall.
That's right.
Do baseball players tend to be tall?
-It depends on their position.
-Right.
Did we ask you what position you play?
-Pitcher.
-Yes, pitcher.
-You got stitches?
-My elbow.
Surgery?
It won't extend.
What?
-Is that baseball elbow?
-Yup.
You know your stuff.
-Oh, it stays like that.
-It won't extend.
-What?
-That's crazy.
Wait, you haven't told us, right?
You haven't told us yet
what your type is.
As for appearances...
cute...
is my type.
-I could see that.
-It's not very interesting, is it?
-What? No, it is.
-Everyone's started eating now.
Everyone started eating.
I lost interest in talking.
Everyone put their hands out
at the same time.
So they're already talking
about what type they're into.
-Yes.
-So...
He's a hair stylist
and has many qualities.
You would think he would be popular,
but it's not the case.
Unfortunately, Tatsuya has a high voice.
He has the tendency to get picked on.
How do you see them?
I think Tatsuya is...
The medical student, was it Minori?
-Yuriko.
-Yes, Yuriko.
I think he's into her.
-Really?
-Right, he keeps at it.
I guess he can tell.
I think in the near future...
Hasegawa...
Makocchan?
...seems interested in Yuriko.
But the barista,
because she works in the field of sports,
-is into Hasegawa.
-Right.
But the barista isn't the type
that reveals her interests easily.
So, even if she likes him,
she won't say it.
Like they've got this common sport thing
and she has this attraction
as a team assistant or something.
-Right.
-A-ha!
But won't say how she's feeling.
Although Makoto
is checking out Yuriko now,
it will eventually happen.
Your prediction is amazing!
Well, I want that to happen.
He seemed kind of happy
that she knew what his injury was.
-Baseball elbow, right?
-She did know it well.
It's also attractive.
I think they'll get closer
by being friends.
-Yes, that's right.
-Right?
-Like, through a mutual connection.
-Oh!
It's like he'll go for Yuriko,
but realize,
"The barista was always by my side."
Can you stop referring to her by her job?
-There's one thing that concerns me.
-Right.
Yuriko keeps saying she's hungry.
-That girl's probably selfish.
-That girl?
Has she already been caught
on your radar?
Yes, selfish.
You know, it's a new season,
but it's already quite fun.
Yes, it's been fun
since the very beginning.
The last group made such an impression,
I thought it would be difficult to match,
yet this group is beginning
to distinguish itself.
-Really.
-I am already thinking
that the previous group is history.
Well, maybe.
It's buried somewhere.
You've got a lot of things there.
Yeah, I just couldn't decide what to take.
I put a bunch of things in,
but I'm still missing something.
-Your shoes!
-What?
-Those shoes.
-Sloppy? It shows my personality, right?
Tatsuya was pretty determined.
Yeah, I thought things
would be a little gentler.
"Well, that is why I came here."
-I wonder if that's true.
-He's so open.
He is really open.
Everyone is so easy to talk to.
I thought people would be
more eccentric here.
What do you mean, "eccentric"?
I wonder what they're thinking
over on their side.
-I'm sure they're talking about us.
-Yeah.
Cute.
She's cute.
Before we arrived, I was more concerned
about the dynamics with the guys...
that I was going to share the room with
than the girls.
It doesn't seem like
we need to worry about that.
Yeah.
I am so glad.
So she's cute?
She's cute.
Well, it was mentioned a lot.
Like, you're into this girl.
It would be Mizuki.
Right, Mizuki.
-Like, the mature woman.
-The mature woman.
-Whoa.
You were hammering questions
at Yuriko, though.
I thought it was obvious.
-Didn't you think so?
-Yes, I did.
Right?
Well, we start from here.
-From here.