Hey!
-You scared me!
-It's only a matter of time until they...
When are you free?
Well, next Tuesday.
Wanna go to Mother Farm?
-Have you been to Mother Farm?
-I want to go.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Mother Farm sounds nice.
We'll be going there, thanks.
Have fun.
Have fun!
-I--
-No way!
-No way.
-No way, a new member.
He's here!
-My heart's pounding.
-What are we gonna do?
Oh, man...
-He's here!
-I'm nervous!
I'm not going to look
until the last second.
He might be hot.
Let's see, let's see.
Hey.
I'm moving in today.
I'm Yamasato.
-Oh...
-Nice to meet you.
You can call me Ryota.
Torichan.
You haven't had much luck in love.
I've been watching.
-Yeah, so Torichan...
-Yes?
...really wants to find love.
So I came at a perfect time.
-Excuse me.
-Sure. I'm Tokui.
-I work at the aquarium.
-Oh, wow! That's great.
I'm working on becoming a firefighter.
-What?
-A firefighter.
-A firefighter?
-You're working on it?
I haven't passed the test yet.
-How old are you?
-I'm 39.
-You're 39 and you're...
-Yes.
-You're trying to become a firefighter?
-Yes, a firefighter.
-I see. You're just starting.
-Yes.
I'm still...
Are you wearing cow skin?
Yes, they're leather pants.
So, you're into fashion?
It's one of my interests.
I love stuff like this.
Since you're here...
Torichan, why don't you sit next to him?
What?
Is that how it's going to be?
-Why not for a little bit?
-Are you sure?
-Are you scared?
-Fine, I'll go then.
Is it such a big deal?
It seems like it took courage.
-So what are you going to do?
-What?
Are you really going to stay?
What? Well, I'm moving in today.
There's a romantic vibe here.
-Yes, well...
-Well, these two are going out.
How is it?
Living here and going out?
They're in the Japanese-style bedroom
every night.
Starting in the afternoon. It's crazy.
-No way! You can hear us?
-Yeah.
Oh, no!
-We can even hear you from the pool!
-Oh, my!
-From the pool?
-Yeah, it's something else.
-That's not good. We should be careful.
-Oh, man...
So... how long are we gonna keep this up?
Let's get started.
-Today's an important day.
-You're right.
-Okay.
-I know you want to mess around, but...
Let's be proper.
-Good evening, everyone.
-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women...
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes. Finally...
Tonight is the last episode.
And we are in Terrace House!
-It's nice. An amazing place.
-It's our first time here.
-It's amazing.
-This house is really amazing.
-There's an elevator.
-Yes, there's an elevator.
The one they kissed in front of.
-That's right!
-That's right, it's that elevator.
It's, like, don't do it there!
It's so easy to see!
Yeah, it's very visible.
It was there!
So, last week...
Let's take a look back.
Last week, the sixth couple formed
since the show started.
-Arman and Masako.
-Yes, Martha.
It made me want to believe in you.
-So, you'll go out with me?
-Yes, that's what I mean.
Don't stare at me!
-They shared their first kiss on the boat.
-Yes, on the boat.
Yes, they did.
And Rikopin and Hayato...
I do like you.
I want to go out with you.
On Monday, in the evening,
I'll wait for you at the restaurant.
If you think you can trust me again...
then I want you to come.
I still like him. But...
I'm very worried.
-You're still 18.
-Yeah.
I think you should date more.
Yeah.
-She came back to Shinagawa station.
-That's right.
-Will she go or not?
That's where we left off.
Terashima made dessert
and is waiting for her.
-And you all think she'll go.
-Yes, I hope she does.
I'm sincerely hoping
she'll stand him up.
-Riko?
-Yes, for Riko to just cut him loose.
Her mom rather...
sort of pushed her to go for it.
-I think she'll go.
-I want her to!
We could have three couples.
I want to drink sake while watching
the scene where he gets axed.
Please!
Make a wish!
-With all your heart.
-I'll put my heart into it.
I want to be with Arman...
You're saying it out loud?
-What's your wish? Share it.
-No, no, no.
-Can I say it out loud?
-Sure.
Never mind. It's okay.
-Congratulations!
-Happy birthday!
Wait, wait.
Seriously?
Oh, no!
-Welcome home.
-I'm home.
-Come sit, Riko.
-Sit down.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Welcome back.
I didn't go to the restaurant.
I'm sure you gave it a lot of thought.
I thought hard about it.
I did think about going.
But I couldn't.
He said three different things.
I want to believe him...
but I can't right now.
You should message Hayato.
-Don't worry. I already have.
-You have?
-Yeah.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 23 YEARS OLD
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
-Hey.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-Good work.
-She didn't go.
-No, she didn't.
Maybe this is a weird thing to ask,
but how are you?
It's tough.
But that's the decision she made.
I have to try and accept it.
At least there's closure.
Thanks for waiting up.
We weren't waiting up for that to happen.
I'm going to sleep.
I'll be okay. I'll be better tomorrow.
Yeah, rest up. Seriously.
I'm sorry I made you guys uncomfortable.
I'm sorry I haven't told Martha either.
-Good morning.
-You're up early.
-Yeah.
You're wearing makeup.
-I have work today.
-It's early.
You thought it over...
and it's the decision you made.
So I'll take it.
I mean...
I'll accept it.
I'm sorry I made you feel bad.
We'll be normal roommates from now on.
I hope we can still be friends.
-Is that okay?
-Yeah.
That would be better.
Okay.
-Friends then?
-Yeah, friends.
-Cut.
-Cut!
-She cut him loose.
-Yeah.
-That was unexpected.
-I thought she'd go talk to him.
But she didn't.
-You were drinking sake happily.
-Sake has never tasted better.
I wavered for a moment
and thought she might go.
But I'm glad I believed in her.
She cut him loose!
I feel like I witnessed a woman's strength
in those moments.
-I know what you mean.
-We did see it.
"We'll be roommates from now on."
"That would be better."
-That was...
-It was good.
-It was very mature.
-Yes.
For an 18-year-old, that much is true.
She made her decision.
"That would be better."
What a great line.
It was a good line.
And then there was the scene
with them sleeping naked in bed.
-That was a surprise.
-Yeah.
But with those two,
-it doesn't seem too graphic.
-That's true.
So it's heaven for the two couples,
and hell for the other two members.
That's what we're going to watch?
-I wonder.
-Yeah.
I don't know what's going to happen.
-Oh, no.
-What?
-It's starting to hit me.
-Yeah, it sucks.
This brings back memories.
The first letter Misaki gave me.
No way! What did I write?
"Thanks for the iron.
Let's go shopping together again."
-That's so cute.
-It's like in elementary school.
-It's really from when I first came.
-Yeah.
I saved it.
It brings back memories.
So what are you going to do, Arman?
-About what?
-With Martha?
I'll be in Japan
until the end of September.
-The end of September?
-No, I meant the end of August.
We'll take it slow.
Yuuki, you're not going to live together?
With Misaki?
Not at first.
You're used to this, though.
You'll probably miss her.
Yeah, we've talked about that.
But I told her she can come over any time.
It's nice that you live close
to each other.
You live close,
even if you don't live together.
-Yeah, that's true.
-You can see her when you want to.
I can see her when I want to.
But I'm going to make an effort.
Nice.
YOMIURILAND
You changed.
Do you still want this?
-Bon appétit!
-Bon appétit.
The flow pool...
-It was fun.
-What?
-Yeah, it was fun.
It's coming to an end.
Terrace House.
Yeah.
-We can be alone now.
-Yeah.
That's something to be happy about.
Hayato and Riko seem fine.
-We can leave in peace.
-Yeah.
We can leave...
smiling happily.
You should stop.
You're going to start crying.
I'll be okay. I'm not alone anymore.
-After it's done, you mean.
-I have you now.
So I'll be okay.
-You went to a water park?
-Yeah, we went to a water park.
-How was it?
-It was fun.
Which water park was it?
-Yomiuriland.
-Yomiuriland?
-Oh, Arman!
-What?
Don't worry about it.
-Yeah, I went a while back.
-That's right!
How are you two?
-The same.
-Yeah, the same.
Nice. There's an aura of happiness here.
You seem okay now.
Yeah, I'm totally good.
So you're roommates and friends now?
-Yeah.
-I see.
-I'm getting sad.
-Yeah, it's a little sad.
Living alone will be so lonely!
Alone? You're staying in Tokyo?
-Yeah, work is here.
-That's true.
Someone's home.
-It's so hot!
-Oh, it's Yuuki.
-It's hot!
We're here to visit!
Long time no see.
It's been a while!
Hansan!
Thank you!
-Riko! How have you been?
-Nacchan!
I can't see your face.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm Natsumi Saito.
-I'm Martha. Nice to meet you.
-What?
-Martha. Nice to meet you.
-Martha? I'm Natsumi Saito.
Nice to meet you.
-She's embarrassed.
-I'm embarrassed because of Hansan.
I've been keeping in touch,
so I invited them.
-Really?
-It's nice to meet you.
Hansan and Natsumi...
-Nacchan.
-I'm Natsumi.
-Thank you!
-Thank you.
Oh, someone's home.
Welcome home.
-Hansan.
-Hey, how are you?
-You're Nacchan, right?
-Yes.
Byrnes?
-How are you?
-It's been a while.
I'm so surprised!
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
How have things been since you left?
-She went to Singapore.
-I want to hear.
-Yeah.
-You live in Singapore?
No, I don't live there.
I've been going overseas for work.
For commercial shoots...
and other little jobs.
-Do you have a boyfriend now?
-No.
-Anyone you like?
-There isn't anyone.
I see.
She looked at me like, "Poor you."
Did you see her face?
"I see."
That's great.
It brings back memories.
It's great. It was totally like this.
It brings back memories?
They're never on the same wavelength.
No, no. We understand each other.
It takes time to reach an understanding.
-What about you, Hansan?
-I've been building as usual.
I just finished a café yesterday.
I've also started doing something
other than architecture.
I'm preparing to sell furniture as well.
-Wow.
-That's amazing.
I can't survive without working.
-And you just graduated.
-Yeah.
But I have to study as well.
What about your girlfriend?
Are things going well?
Yeah, well,
I haven't been able to see her.
-You're so busy?
-You still haven't seen her that much?
I was pretty busy when I lived here,
but now she's busy.
We don't see each other.
-How's work going, Misaki?
-Me?
-It's so-so.
-So-so?
It's not so-so.
You've got things lined up.
You haven't talked about it?
Not really.
-A commercial...
-Seriously?
And a TV drama.
Tiny parts, though.
-I'll watch.
-Even a small part is good.
Terrace House is ending.
We're all moving out next Monday.
-What?
-Yeah.
Really?
-Then I'm glad we came before.
-Yeah.
It's the last day tomorrow.
Did it go by quickly for you?
Very quickly.
But a lot happened to you.
I didn't even like Arman at first.
-That's right.
-Yeah.
-Gross.
-It's pretty bad.
The last day of a luxurious lifestyle.
With that pool...
-I'll leave the trash bag here.
-Thank you.
That helps.
-Oh, Riko. Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-Riko's back.
-You're home early.
Am I?
I thought I was running late.
It's so clean.
What are you doing?
What was that?
I'm taking down the charms.
-Shouldn't Hayato take them down?
-That's true.
Oh, wow.
Is there anywhere that hasn't been wiped?
-There isn't.
-What about here?
Ready?
Watch your feet.
Done.
Let's get in.
-For the last time.
-Yeah, the last time.
-I wonder if it's cold.
-It'll be fine.
It feels so good!
Ready?
That was close!
-Prosciutto?
-No.
-What is it?
-It's meat.
-Looks good.
-Here.
Looks amazing.
Tongue.
-There's tongue, too?
-Yeah.
-Looks delicious.
Feeling better?
-Are you feeling better?
-Yeah.
-It's gotten warm again lately.
I wonder how long it'll last.
I'm really glad.
This has really been fun.
-It was fun.
-It was.
-Seriously fun.
-It's like I was a student again.
The last two months were the best.
We went camping, skateboarding.
I got in an accident, but...
it was really fun.
Let's all work hard starting tomorrow.
It's so sad. I'm really sad.
Everyone who lived at Terrace House
hasn't kept the sink area clean.
Yeah.
Even if you never clean it,
it wouldn't look like that.
-No, it wouldn't.
-What's coming out of them?
The kiss.
-It was so nice.
-The kiss at Yomiuriland.
Oh, the one in the pool.
-Yeah, inside the pool.
-And the tube!
Where the girl's in the tube
and the guy hangs on it like this?
So that's how couples do it.
I'm jealous!
-That's been around since the '80s.
-Yeah!
I guess that's been a thing
since my time.
Yeah, you always see that.
Pools are nice.
That couple is so...
They're so close.
-It's so nice!
-They're going out...
but could you say that?
"I'm not alone anymore, so I'll be okay."
-"Because you're here."
-"I'm so glad you're here."
They say it naturally, not jokingly.
-It's amazing.
-I'm so jealous!
And Arman and Martha, too.
-When they're cleaning.
-When they're messing around?
-That was nice, too.
-Yes, it was.
-Really great.
-It was very cute.
Neither one of those two guys...
really hides anything.
Isn't that nice to see?
That's what you should do.
Could you do it?
-Ken could do it.
-Yeah, I think so.
That's not fair.
I was the worst of the worst
when I was around Kentaro's age.
-I was the worst of the worst.
-What?
-How?
-What were you like?
-I was seeing four girls at once.
-What?
-Four?
-Yes, four.
So since I was always bringing
different girls home, my mom would say,
"Yoshimi, my home is not a love hotel."
I'd hate that.
-That's when I realized how bad it was.
-Yeah, if your mom had to say it.
When did you stop?
Probably two years ago.
-So recent.
-No, no.
-Well, we're at the end.
-It's the end of the end.
That was quick.
We're at the end already?
-Let's toast.
-Cheers.
-This is our last night.
-The last celebration.
-Shall we have Arman lead it?
-Yeah.
-Cheers!
I'm hungry.
-Should we start cooking?
-Let's cook.
What is everyone gonna do?
Ideally, I would live six months here
and six months in Hawaii.
When he asked me out,
he said he'd go back for two months.
That's what he said.
But he's changing what he said.
Beforehand, I would've said,
"That's different from what you said."
But it's Arman's life.
I want to support him.
And I have more things I want to do now.
And there are lots of things I need to do.
So if we can both work hard
and meet where we can...
That's so cool!
-Yeah.
-That's too cool.
We were saying
that we hope to live like that
and still be a good couple.
That's what we were saying.
Wow, that's great.
I'm so happy
that she really understands me.
What about you, Hayato?
I want to open my own restaurant.
My goal is to open one next year.
I'll go.
You never came!
-That's true, I never went.
-We should go.
-You didn't come once. Come.
-Let's go.
Come by after this show.
If you open a place,
Hansan can do the interior.
-It'd be nice if we can all do something.
-Yeah.
-We're all leaving tomorrow, right?
-Let's head out together.
We're all done after this meal.
I'm about to cry.
It's been a long year.
Well, almost a year.
Oh, man.
Let's not talk about this.
Getting off at the same station,
walking down the same street...
That kind of thing.
We won't have that anymore.
It's cool in here.
It's cooler.
That's a nice top. It's cute.
-Isn't it?
-Yeah, when did you get it?
-Need a tissue?
-I'm okay.
It was a really good...
half year.
If we look up at the sky,
we'll all see the same moon.
That was cheesy. Too cheesy.
That was cheesy.
Are we all okay now?
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Here it is.
The day to take my own key has arrived.
It's arrived.
This is also my first time.
I've been using this for ten months.
-I'm off!
-I'm heading out!
-I'm leaving.
-I'm out!
I'm leaving.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.