-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Last week,
there was a discussion about Makoto...
He said he's gonna be serious
about baseball...
-He came to tell us that.
-Yeah, he came to tell us.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
After that, for about three days,
he went to sleep early.
So I thought
he was being good about it, but...
When I get up to go to school,
I've seen Makocchan sleeping...
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
...more often than not.
Actually, the league games
have already started.
I'm trying...
But I get elbow pain.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
So with that...
It's okay if you don't make it.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
If there was evidence of your effort,
I'd think that's great.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD
He clearly displays his annoyance
with his expression.
I love that!
Your favorite?
Both Minori and Yuriko's feelings
for Makoto are fading.
That's right.
-Yeah, and there's the new turn of events.
-That's right.
Uchi, the hair stylist...
I was thinking...
that I want to ask you out.
Part two?
They're going to go to Chichibu.
I hope it pours that day in Chichibu.
Leave them alone!
So in the house, Tatsuya and Minori
seem the most likeable...
They're the oasis of Terrace House.
Everything else is rocky.
And Mr. Tap...
social media broke his heart.
But Yuki and Yuriko have
their Blue Note date...
What?
That Blue Note thing...
She doesn't want to go with Yuki.
She just wants to go to Blue Note.
But I guess anything can happen,
depending--
That's right.
We do want someone to save Yuki.
That's true.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
Hey.
What're you reading?
Slam Dunk?
Yeah, the last one.
The last volume?
I have to finish!
KURUMI NAKADA, MODEL
MINORI'S OLDER SISTER
What are you going to do?
With Terrace House?
Close your knees.
You sit like that all the time.
Your posture must be bad.
I do this with my legs, too.
Yeah, bad posture.
You do that thing with your arm, too.
I keep thinking you need to straighten up.
You're being filmed.
Yeah.
Mom was saying,
"How can Minori live with her sloppiness?"
Am I sloppy?
-Bon appétit.
How is it at the house?
What do you want to do there?
What do I want to do?
You know how Mizuki was chastised
because she was unclear about her future?
How come no one said anything about you?
-You're not sure either, right?
-Yeah, I like modeling now, but...
But you don't know if it's for you.
What about what you studied at school?
Oh, I want to work at a ranch.
I want work...
to be satisfying.
Oh, I see.
So while you're young,
while you're still pretty, you'll model?
-And when you're old and wrinkly--
-That's not it, but...
Since I'm in Tokyo,
and there's something I can do here...
You're not listening.
If there's something you can do?
If I can make money while I'm in Tokyo,
then I'll model.
-Are you getting work consistently?
-Not at all.
-You earn more at your part-time job?
-Totally.
-Why don't you let that go?
-My part-time job?
Well, that's fine, but...
It might force you
to take modeling more seriously--
I did that before, and it did help.
That's good.
Why can't you do that?
But then I started getting
less work again.
But if you keep turning to other jobs,
you're gonna be stuck in that cycle.
Right?
-I'll quit. I'm going to quit.
-You should.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going on a date with the hair stylist.
So you like Uchi?
I don't know.
That's what I'll find out.
So you think you could like him.
-So, the first date was fun?
-Yeah it was.
Well, I didn't see him that way then.
Well, good.
You need a boyfriend.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
KOMATSUZAWA LEISURE FARM
CHICHIBU, SAITAMA
Stop!
-I seriously can't take it.
-What, touching?
No, stop rubbing your hands
on my arm to wipe stuff off.
You're a towel.
Seriously.
Soba eatery.
I think it's here.
It's getting smooth.
Switch!
Good work.
And separate?
You can put it there.
-Wow, it's soba.
-It's thick!
Looks like soba. Good job.
You're doing well.
You've got rhythm.
Oh, you have rhythm.
I think it's getting thinner and thinner.
Looks like soba,
and maybe half udon.
This section is a little thick,
so let's move it here.
The udon's been separated.
Bon appétit.
Tastes like soba.
-Tasty.
-Delicious.
It's soba.
That was fun.
I'm scared!
-Oh, wow.
-Seriously?
This is crazy!
Here I go!
Wow!
What's this?
-Oh, this view is totally Terrace House.
-Oh, yeah, we see it all the time.
We always go far away from the house.
Is that okay?
You like that, right?
I like to, but wasn't sure if you did.
I do! I had fun.
-You had fun?
-Yeah.
I'm glad.
Minori...
is there someone in Terrace House
you're attracted to?
That's right, I'm asking straight out.
No?
I'm not sure.
Well, I asked you out because I like you.
What do you mean, you like...
Oh, I'm so bad with this stuff!
I'm not looking for a yes or no.
I understand.
You get it?
But I wanted you to know how I feel.
He's starting to look cute,
even with his high voice.
It's such a refreshing date,
kind of an ideal date.
Her reaction to his confession,
that means she's happy, right?
Of course she's happy.
-She was so embarrassed.
-"Oh, I'm so bad at this!"
Like that, right?
This is good!
I want this every day!
-That's impossible.
-Even if there's no progress.
Making and eating your own soba.
When he first said, "It's soba!"
I thought he was so stupid!
It's okay!
He was just impressed
that they made their own soba.
That's right.
-Is that what he meant?
-Yeah.
Oh, I thought he didn't know
what he was making until he ate it.
Guess he's not that stupid.
That would be very stupid.
Since we started with such a happy scene,
I feel like we need to prepare ourselves.
I mean, things are messy
at the house right now,
so they want to start us off
with something nice.
Just as a starter.
-So, the main course will be sticky?
-Very sticky.
Why don't you sew the sides?
What about the string?
You can make a hole for it later.
I want to sew it on, too.
-You're gonna sew it on?
-Yeah.
For Minori - A "present"
Let's go running again! - Makoto
-You're doing it.
-Wow!
Make a hole between here?
But isn't it too big?
Vertical, right?
Vertical?
-Welcome back.
-Clothes?
-Yeah, she needs an apron, apparently.
-Apron?
-Apron.
Requested by a friend, right?
-An apron?
-An apron.
Did you eat?
We're going to make curry.
-What's that?
-It ripped just now!
-It's not ripped.
-Look, here.
It's ripped here.
-Oh, this...
-This is...
It's hard to tell where it stops.
Here. Line it up here.
It won't work with this.
-Then how about...
-Minori, do you have plans tonight?
Tonight?
-I'm just staying in.
-For real?
Let's go run then.
-Okay.
-Sounds nice.
-Will it work?
-It should.
You're making curry?
You guys can go run.
Then I'll be...
waiting with my special curry.
Yay!
Amazing!
-Here she comes.
-Yeah?
-Oh, a workout headband.
-What's this?
Nothing.
Just a present.
-Did you try them on?
-Yeah, they fit perfectly.
For real?
I thought they might be too small.
Let's go.
-Have fun.
-Can I wear these barefoot?
Probably.
You're not wearing socks?
Are they too small with socks?
I don't know.
I'm sure they're fine.
Go put them on.
What's your usual pace?
I don't think it's that different.
I'm not sure.
Almost there.
-Finished.
-Done!
I'm hot.
-How are the shoes?
-They're perfect.
SHIBA PARK, TOKYO
-They're really light.
-They are, right?
Yeah, they're good.
How are things going lately?
What does that mean?
Lately?
-Like what?
-Anything.
Anything?
Well, work...
-Oh, did you quit already?
-Not yet.
-At the end of the month.
-End of October?
End of October.
-What about baseball? Over soon?
-October 18th.
-That's the end?
-The end.
And so until then...
as Uchi and Yuki suggested,
I need to focus on baseball.
So I can't...
really do anything for you.
That's why I asked you
to run with me tonight.
And gave you the shoes.
So, until the season is over,
I wanted to close the gap between us.
After the season, when I have more time,
maybe we can go somewhere.
That's what I was thinking.
AOYAMA, TOKYO
I heard you wanted to talk to me?
IMAGE
MINORI NAKADA'S MODELING AGENCY
What is it?
MATSUMOTO ERINA, AGENT
I've decided to quit my part-time job,
and mentally focus on modeling.
Also, financially speaking,
if I keep my part-time job,
I may not focus on modeling because of it.
I figured that wouldn't be good.
I see.
You want to model for fashion magazines?
Well, I'm not sure about shows.
I think you have a chance.
-Height-wise?
-Height-wise and, well,
there are different shows.
I'll have you go to castings.
This first year might be tough.
-But let's work at it.
-Yes, thank you.
The place is pretty well hidden.
-It was so fun.
-Was it?
-I'm still in the clouds.
-Really?
Well, if we see it so up close...
-Yeah, it was close.
-Yeah, it was nice.
AOYAMA, TOKYO
Cheers!
The color changes when you mix it.
It's totally different.
It's been a stylish day.
Yeah, it was fun!
And I knew some of the songs.
-I was surprised you knew some.
-Oh, yeah?
I'll listen to jazz
while studying tonight.
The studying's going to get
harder for you, right?
Yeah, exams are coming up.
I thought by living in Terrace House,
I'd naturally mature,
or be able to change somehow.
But I think I was naive.
Up until now,
I've been kind of passive with everything.
I think I need to change that.
So, I think...
I...
I've been thinking lately.
You remember I once told you about
how I broke up with my ex?
It was a pretty tough break up,
and by coming to Terrace House,
I thought maybe I'd find
a new relationship
and be able to forget him.
But I haven't.
And yesterday,
he messaged me something like,
"Hope you're doing well.
Take care of yourself."
And the feelings I've been holding back...
all of them sort of came out.
I think I should take the initiative
and call him,
and tell him...
I miss him.
Here it is.
I think that's good.
I don't know what he'll think about it.
I'm going to tell him how I feel.
That's good.
Maybe that's weird to say.
You've been...
listening to a lot of my issues, so...
thank you.
I haven't told any of the others.
I wasn't sure
if I should tell you this today or not.
Yeah.
-It's a good day.
-A good day.
A good day.
-Shall we head out?
-Shall we?
Let's go home.
Okay.
-It's hell!
-Out of the blue.
-Oh, Tap!
-Poor Tap.
I know how you feel.
-I feel so bad for him!
-Seriously.
Did you see his expression toward the end?
It was classic.
"I can't show it, I can't show it.
I can't show my shock.
I have to smile.
'It's a good day.'"
He squeezed it out,
that "It's a good day."
He did.
-That was brutal.
-Brutal.
When she was saying
she should take initiative, he thought,
"Oh, maybe she's telling me she likes me?"
I thought so, too.
I really thought so.
It's not a presumption at all.
Anyone would take it that way.
-Any normal person would think that.
-Quite normal.
-Tap is not at fault.
-It's not Tap's fault at all!
She must have known how Tap felt.
That's right!
That really sucks.
-Well, yeah.
-I mean, he kept asking her out.
She built some relationships in the house,
appeared on television,
and then got to go to Blue Note for free,
had dinner, felt him going for her,
so she dropped the ex-bomb.
The end.
-It wasn't like that.
-It's a theory.
One theory.
But for the ex to call at this timing
is so arrogant, right?
Really arrogant.
Arrogant!
He probably saw her on TV and thought,
"Hey, she looks pretty good."
Yeah, he probably thought
maybe one more time.
Just one more time.
Hey.
You mean he wants to see her, right?
Sorry.
But what about Makoto?
He was pretty much saying he liked her.
-That's right, he did.
-He did.
But when Makoto told her
he wanted to close the gap with her,
she had no reaction.
Well, if you're having doubts
about that person...
Yeah.
And he reminded her
that he bought her shoes.
That's right!
Did he need to bring that up?
That's what I don't like about him!
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-Uchi's sleeping.
-He's asleep?
Oh, yeah.
How was it?
It was good.
-The jazz?
-Yeah, the jazz was good.
-For real?
-But after that...
Many things.
No, not many...
What is it?
We ate out.
-Where?
-I'm still trying to process stuff.
What? What?
Stop teasing me.
I'm not trying to tease.
I guess her ex messaged her,
"Hope you're doing well.
Take care of yourself."
Yuriko's feelings have turned to him.
They have?
So she told me.
She said that?
I took it in at first
and wished her good luck.
On the surface, anyway.
But now that I've thought about it,
-it's like, "What?"
-That's true.
So right now I'm at, "What?"
Makoto...
that's where I'm at.
-Right now?
-Yeah.
Right now.
Man, I played it cool.
Totally cool.
It was kind of a classy restaurant.
With a fork and a knife, and everything.
I couldn't say,
"Well, if it doesn't work out with him..."
I cheered her on,
but it doesn't feel good.
I thought that,
if I lived in Terrace House,
I'd be able to forget him eventually.
But I haven't.
So, I think I'll meet with him again.
You asked him?
No, not yet.
-You're going to ask?
-I think I'll ask him.
What's wrong?
That's good.
And you know about Makocchan?
I said I was interested in him.
And that wasn't a lie...
but maybe I was just trying
to force myself to forget my ex.
What about Yuki?
You're not interested at all?
Yuki? Yuki is really...
I can only think of him as a friend
I can easily talk to.
I think I've been holding it back, but...
you know...
I kept trying to forget...
but I guess I couldn't.