-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
So last week...
-a new member moved in.
-That's right.
She's extremely bold.
I liked Hayato.
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD
Why? Why?
What's with that reaction?
Is that bad?
We'll see how she affects
Riko and Terashima's relationship.
-That's true.
-Yes.
Riko was just like, "Oh, Hayato, I see."
That was her response.
Yes, she hasn't said anything yet.
-And there was the legendary doggy paddle.
-That's right.
Arman's only skill.
The one skill Arman has displayed
on Terrace House.
An extremely stable doggy paddle.
Afterwards, he invited Martha on a date.
-When you're free, we should go out.
-Sure.
The fact that he asked caused some issues.
Yes, then Hayato said, "That's good."
"It's good? It's good..."
-That exchange.
-Yes.
Do you cook?
Well...
I'm sure it doesn't compare to you.
-Teach me something.
-Sure.
But for now, since Arman asked,
I'll go out with him.
That's good.
-It's good.
It's good.
It's all good.
-She came on strong.
-It's rather refreshing.
I wonder if Terashima realized it.
Like, "Oh, is she coming on to me?"
I wonder about that, too.
If he was perceptive,
he should've immediately noticed it.
But maybe Terashima is not as experienced
as he seems.
At least that's what my agent said
on the way here.
Even my 26-year-old agent
noticed that about him.
-So maybe he hasn't noticed.
-I see.
Riko needs to make a move.
She's been a little too passive.
But she did tell her friend
that she knew
she had to do something about it.
-But I don't think he'll ask me out again.
-Really?
So I think I'll have to do something
about that.
You're competing against each other
with the denim look today.
We're competing?
-He wins!
-That was too quick! Too quick!
That was way too quick.
-And Kentaro is in a lovely yukata.
-Yes, very nice.
Tokui said something interesting earlier.
-It made no sense at all.
-Will you please repeat it?
I really want to touch his man parts.
What?
-What the heck is he saying?
-Are you crazy?
Seeing young Kentaro in his yukata
makes me nostalgic
for the fleeting summers of my youth.
I remember them,
but I'd like to recall them more directly.
What are you talking about?
I want to connect to them more directly.
Right now, I'm connected to my memories
via Bluetooth.
-Yes, like Bluetooth.
-I'd like to be wired into the circuit.
-We grew up in the age of wired circuits.
-Yes, that's right.
So we'd prefer something more direct.
It's the same as
when I touch Torichan's chest.
-It's the same thing.
-Oh, I see how it is.
If he touches Kentaro's penis,
he'll be like, "I remember now."
-Like psychometry?
-Yes, exactly.
That's how you remember?
-How does that work?
-I can travel back to that summer.
The key is the man parts.
There's something wrong with you guys.
What the heck is this?
-That was a nice story.
-No, it wasn't.
Don't try to find a happy ending.
-She's been taught well.
-I don't think so.
How would Taylor Swift feel having to sing
after this conversation?
Have you talked a lot to the guys yet?
A good amount.
But you don't feel
like you know them yet, right?
Not at all.
-Are you interested in one right now?
-Right now?
Yeah, right now.
-She's got someone.
-I do.
Tell me!
-Tell me.
-I thought you'd have guessed by now.
-I have no idea.
-No way.
Is it Yuuki?
-Is it?
-You're laughing.
Yeah, it is.
I can tell by your face.
It's definitely not Arman.
-She and Arman are friends.
-Yeah, Arman's too close to me.
But they've only gone out once?
Hikaru seemed to like me
in the beginning, too.
But in the end, I was rejected.
I'm scared that'll happen again.
When you're into someone,
do you change into someone you don't like?
-Like overthinking things?
-Yeah, and...
I became infatuated. Lovesick.
Yeah, it's bad.
I haven't heard too much about Riko,
so I wanna hear about her.
Do you like someone?
I don't like anyone...
but I am interested in someone.
Do you know who it is?
If I can ask you back.
I do, but...
I do.
-Then, yes, it's that person.
-Ah, that person.
-Are things going well for you two?
-I'm not sure.
I can't tell.
I wonder.
I can't tell what he's thinking right now.
-Oh, Hayato.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-You're back early.
I got off early today.
-Welcome back.
-Thank you.
Did I interrupt your conversation?
-You're awfully quiet.
-Not at all.
-It's okay?
-We were talking till now.
-Welcome back.
-Did you just get back?
Everyone's coming back.
What are you doing tomorrow, Martha?
My mom's leaving tomorrow,
so I'll see her one last time.
-What about in the evening?
-The evening?
I don't have plans for the evening.
-You'll be home?
-Yeah.
-Want to do the cooking lesson tomorrow?
-Can we?
-Is tomorrow okay?
-Yeah.
-The earlier the better, right?
-A welcome party?
-No, she asked that I teach her to cook.
-Yeah.
-So I told her I would.
-That's why you bought the stuff?
-Yeah.
-You guys are cooking?
What are you gonna cook?
I think we'll make a summer pasta.
-A summer pasta?
-Sounds nice!
-Sounds cool.
-Yeah.
-A summer pasta.
-An easy summer pasta.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
Pasta...
Do you make this pasta at the restaurant?
No. I came up with this dish yesterday.
-I'm so excited.
-Yeah, it's already completed in my mind.
This much.
You cut it like that? In thirds?
-Like this?
-Nice. You know how to use a knife.
-Nice.
-Is it?
This part's important.
-What?
-This part's important.
Add the wasabi and dashi soy sauce.
Only a dash of soy sauce.
Like that.
A little wasabi.
It pulls the flavors together.
It's hot.
-It's ready?
-Yeah.
-You cool it?
-Yeah, and then you toss.
Looks so delicious.
Done!
-Bon appétit.
-Cheers.
It's so good!
I'm glad.
Seriously, thanks.
-You can make it now, right?
-I probably can. Probably.
You got the ingredients yesterday?
You thought of it and bought everything?
You're so sweet.
Thank you.
-You mentioned working in child care.
-Yeah.
What was that about?
I study it when I have time.
Is that what you'd like to do?
I've wanted to
from around the time I was in sixth grade.
So that's where you want to end up?
I do, but now I'm interested
in my job, too, of course.
But I know I can't model forever.
Whenever my motivation drops,
I think of childcare.
I understand how you feel.
-You do?
-I do.
-Were you always a chef?
-No, I used to act...
but I gave it up.
It's easy to dabble in acting...
and to say that's what I'm working toward.
But I had decided my cut off was 30,
so I stopped...
and moved on to the next thing.
-You're 24 or 23, right?
-I'm 22.
Oh, 22.
That's way older.
You're still young, so it's fine.
But it might seem like
you're not committed.
To say you model now,
but that you want to be in childcare, too.
I was like that, so I do understand.
I understand, I'll...
try to give it more thought.
I just creeped myself out.
I was so serious.
-Why don't you pour yourself a drink?
-Good idea.
Break time.
Yeah, take a break.
Let's talk about dating.
Dating? Okay.
We've been talking about goals too much.
How is it?
It's fine.
-What?
-It's fine.
What is?
You've gone out several times, right?
I'm not sure
they could be considered dates.
You mean from your viewpoint?
I really like her as a person.
But she's like a younger sister.
-I'm not sure.
-You don't see her as a woman yet?
Maybe I don't see her as a woman yet.
-So there's no progress yet?
-Yeah, it's a little...
It's on hold right now?
Nothing's ended or started either.
It's in a suspended state.
-Thank you.
-It's so quiet.
No one's home yet.
-Yeah, that's true.
-Yeah, they're not home yet.
You want to just stick our feet in?
Just our feet?
I'm wearing pants.
You got it.
-It's cold!
-Feels like summer.
I also wanna light fireworks.
-We've got fireworks.
-Seriously?
Yeah, rocket fireworks.
This is pretty cold!
It feels nice.
There it is.
You went for the classic move.
-What kind of guys have you dated?
-All kinds.
But none of them would clearly say...
that something bothered them.
It's kind of...
It makes you spoiled?
Most of them would never
be direct with me,
even though it would've been better
if they had.
Like what you said about my goals earlier.
I'm not used to having guys
tell me things like that, like...
-Like, "That part doesn't work"?
-Yeah, because apparently I seem stubborn.
-Maybe they can't express themselves.
-Yeah, it usually just ends with, "I see."
Apart from my agent,
you're the first person to be so direct.
-No way! I'm sorry. Are you all right?
-No, I'm actually grateful.
Seriously.
Work hard toward becoming
a childcare worker.
-Focus on your studies.
-Yeah, I want to.
I should work harder.
-You haven't been studying lately?
-I haven't been.
-You've been slacking?
-I have.
They're living up the summer.
I just heard a phrase
I've never heard before.
-Oh, what old man Tokui said?
-Yes.
Water splashing is summer's foreplay.
Thank you for that.
You're an expert
at incorporating innuendo to everything.
-He is, isn't he?
-An expert.
-It's a skill.
-It is.
I'll add it to my résumé.
But when the girls were talking
and Hayato came home,
he kind of made the first move.
That was kind of cool, wasn't it?
-I really didn't like it though.
-Why?
-Because if I were Rikopin...
-If you were Rikopin, you mean.
I'd rather he ask in my absence.
But she already said she'd only go so far
since they're not together.
She's already put up a wall.
-So she has no right to say--
-But...
-It's painful.
-Painful?
-From Rikopin's point of view.
-What's going on?
He's his usual self.
Seriously.
It's a tough call.
It depends on whether a cooking lesson...
How can I put it?
It's not quite a date.
That's true.
It also depends on whether he realizes
she's coming on to him.
Even I'd realize she was coming on to me.
Maybe he's more clueless than me.
When Martha...
says she's glad he commented
about her goals...
even when she says she's really happy,
it seems like an effort to cater to him.
-It'll make him like her more.
-I see.
-So it didn't really make her that happy?
-No, I'm sure it did, but...
You really...
-You're in trouble. Keep calm.
-She's angry.
Your level of comprehension
is too extreme.
She's showing her female wiles,
acting like she's happy when she's not.
It's not that.
It's like when you have
sansho pepper leaves.
They're aromatic to start with,
but if you smash them...
-Brilliant.
-So stylish.
-That was so stylish.
-It was a stylish simile, wasn't it?
That's on the test
when you graduate comedy school.
-No, it's not.
-Definitely not.
-Not at all.
-Impossible.
Man, am I so obtuse that you guys
have to come up with these similes?
-Good morning.
You're washing dishes?
I saw they piled up, so...
-Want a smoothie?
-Yeah, I'd like one.
-Milk or soy milk?
-Soy.
-Good morning.
-Want a smoothie?
-Yeah.
-Ready?
-Okay.
I'm sure it'll be good.
-Do you think it's ready?
-What do you think?
-How is it?
-I'm going to pour.
-Is it okay? Thank you.
-It's okay.
-Bon appétit.
-You got some on you.
-It's good!
It's good.
-Morning.
-Arman, you're up late.
-Arman, I made some smoothies.
-Seriously?
-Can I have some?
-Sure.
How is it?
-It's good.
-No way!
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
My stomach's starting to rumble.
-That's quick.
-Yeah.
-It always works quickly on me.
-You should drink a smoothie every day.
I've got a fast metabolism.
Thanks for the smoothie.
Of course. You're welcome.
I'll wash up.
-How unusual.
-I think my stomach's rumbling, too.
Oh no, what should I do?
I'm going to the restroom.
Just leave it here.
I need to use the restroom.
My stomach hurts.
When are you going out with Hayato again?
I want to,
but I'm still considering things.
-It's a secret.
-Okay.
-Don't tell.
-I won't.
-Okay.
-What about you? Going to the beach?
I don't know if it'll be the beach, but...
-Have you decided on a date?
-Not at all.
-Thanks, Arman.
-Sure.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go get ready.
-See you.
-Yeah. Thanks again.
Me...
I'm going back to sleep.
-You're going to sleep?
-I'm going to sleep.
-She's gone.
-Yeah, to sleep.
-Did you learn how to make the dish?
-The dish? Yeah, sort of.
I didn't really do much.
He cooked while he was teaching me.
Did you have fun?
I did have fun.
It was fun.
I see...
But the relationship talk
didn't go very far.
-No?
-Yeah, I tried asking about you.
But I don't think he really knows himself.
-Hayato?
-Yeah.
Not that he doesn't know his feelings,
but...
You're much...
-younger than him.
-Significantly.
But he did say that doesn't bother him.
I don't really know how he feels.
He really didn't say much. Seriously.
You're not going to ask him out?
Yeah.
I'd like to go out somewhere with him.
-You're going to ask?
-Yeah.
My stomach's rumbling, too.
-The restroom?
-The restroom.
Everybody else already went.
It wasn't available earlier.
-Later.
-Yeah.
MINAMI-AOYAMA, TOKYO
A-LIGHT
A-LIGHT CORPORATION
Thank you for coming out from Nagoya.
-It's a long way.
-Not at all.
MISAWO NAGAI
RIKO'S MOTHER
I'm sure you have worries being so far,
but we're hoping you'll place your trust
in us and assuage your worries.
YUJI MATSUO - MARIKO KONYA
And mom can sign as the guardian.
This contract will take effect
immediately.
-We look forward to working with you.
-Yes, I'll work hard.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
OMOTESANDO, TOKYO
Finally. Are you relieved?
I am, but this is just the beginning.
That's true.
There's so much going on
at Terrace House.
I thought that after one or two months,
you'd say, "Mom, I want to go home."
-You thought I'd say that?
-I did.
Is anything bothering you?
Um... Hayato?
You saw that?
-You saw it on Netflix?
-I did.
As my mom, how does it make you feel?
How do I feel?
It does feel a little weird.
I didn't think you'd be interested
in someone so much older.
I was surprised.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But I have fun with him.
He's asked me out on three dates.
So I thought this time
I should maybe ask him
because he's stopped asking me.
He's stopped talking about it.
Where do you want to go?
Like a festival around here.
-Is there one in the summer?
-Like a fireworks show.
That's nice. You can wear a yukata.
-A yukata?
-You can wear a yukata
-and go see fireworks.
-In a yukata.
I should ask.
If you're still unsure...
the fireworks will end before you decide.
-Summer's going to end soon.
-That's true.
What should I do?
Yuuki's not home yet?
I wonder how it went.
We're all wondering.
Do you think he passed or failed?
-I'm sure he passed.
-Yeah.
He was studying for it yesterday.
-He studied for it last time too.
-Did he?
-Welcome back.
-Oh, you weren't home yet.
Sorry for interrupting.
-Hello.
-It's nice to meet you.
-You came together?
-We did.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
-Please...
-Come sit down.
Rikopin's mom,
would you like something to drink?
-I can make whatever you like.
-What do I want?
-Tea, water, a highball, anything.
-I'll have tea please.
Tea, water, or a highball?
Why a highball?
-Do we still have tea?
-We may be out of tea.
Water is okay then.
-Are you doing well?
-I am.
It's so spacious.
Amazing.
-It feels strange.
-It does!
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
-Arman.
-Arman's working.
This is the first time, right?
We just signed with the talent agency.
-So it's been decided?
-Yeah.
And then we went out for dinner.
And I decided to bring her here.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's great that you got an agent.
You must have been worried.
She's talked about everyone here a lot,
how you're all such good people.
There's no need to worry.
-He's back.
-Who?
-Welcome back.
-Welcome home.
Hayachan.
I'm home.
-You knew it was my mom?
-Of course.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Hayato.
You caught me by surprise.
What is this?
-Are you drinking something?
-Yes, water.
Oh, water.
Oh, right. Riko got an agent.
-My mom came to sign with the agency.
-Congratulations.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
I can't keep staring at him.
-Maybe you should drink something.
-No, no...
-You're acting strange.
-Do you need a drink?
She's not herself yet.
-Why are you pressuring her?
-We've talked on the phone before.
Yes.
On Riko's phone.
We were both drunk.
She always calls when she's drunk.
Are you okay?
-It's like, "Mom..."
-Yeah, "let's drink in Nagoya."
They're phone buddies.
I'm nervous.
Your face is red.
I'm hot. You're sitting so close.
She's too close?
-Too close?
-She's relieved.
-Where's Yuuki?
-He's not home yet.
We're waiting to hear his results.
That's right! So no one knows yet?
-No, we don't.
-Tell him.
I'm not gonna speak to him
if he doesn't pass.
That's scary. Your expression's scary.
If Yuuki is getting back late,
I'd like to show my mom the girls' room.
Sure. Do you want to go now?
-It's a little messy.
-It's so spacious.
Can you tell which bed is mine?
That one.
-Are all my Hello Kitty things creepy?
-It's cute.
What did you think of the mens?
-"The mens"?
-The mens.
They were...
better looking than I expected.
-Better than what you see on TV?
-Which one? Hayato or Arman?
-Both.
-Oh, both.
Better than I expected.
I've heard a lot about Hayato
from Riko though.
I know they've gone out on dates.
So I was studying him.
But he seems like a good boy.
Easy to talk to.
-It seemed like he tried to be friendly.
-Yes.
So even when it comes to Riko,
he seems to be very caring.
That's the impression I had.
He seems very nice.
-They've been up there for a while.
-Yeah.
I'm sure it's a lot of girl talk.
-Girl talk with the four of them.
-Definitely.
-Hey, Yuuki.
-Hey.
-Welcome back.
-You're back late.
-Yeah, sorry about that.
-What is it?
-What?
-Oh, no. This is a bad vibe.
-Oh, no...
Did it not go well?
-This is between us.
-Sure, sure.
I passed.
-That's great.
-What's with this vibe then?
You scared me.
But I didn't want to tell Misaki yet.
But she knows you took the test today.
She's been really anxious.
I wanted to surprise her.
If you can, keep it between us for now.
-Of course.
-Keep it quiet.
Oh, Yuuki, there's a new member.
Welcome back.
-Welcome back.
It's my mom!
Oh, seriously?
Finally, a reaction.
-Oh, nice to meet you.
-You couldn't tell?
-I was so surprised. Nice to meet you.
-It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Yuuki Byrnes. Nice to meet you.
-I'm Mrs. Nagai.
-She's leaving.
-It's late.
-I'll be going.
-We'll walk you out.
Be careful. Good night.
-Please take care of Riko.
-Hey, we should all see her out.
-Bye. I'm going to take her back.
-Okay.
Click.
That was such a surprise.
When'd you get back, Yuuki?
More importantly...
-What?
-How'd it go?
-How'd what go?
-What?
-We've all been worried.
-What do you mean?
Didn't you take your test today?
I did. I did.
And?
Well, that...
What?
-Did you pass?
-I'll tell you...
-next time.
-What?
-That's fine. Good work.
-Good work.
Cheers.
I'm going to sleep.
Why'd she leave?
She's been waiting up.
That was a mistake on your part.
Yeah.
If we didn't know
when you were getting your results,
and you told us you already know,
that's understandable.
But we all knew you'd find out today.
-You knew I'd get results today.
-Yeah.
For you to know and not say...
I see what you're saying.
-It doesn't really work as a surprise.
-Now that you say it, it makes sense.
Hey.
-Tired?
-Hmm?
-Are you sleepy?
-Yeah.
I really didn't like the way you acted.
Yeah.
It made me think you failed.
Because it was you...
there was a part of me
that wanted to surprise you.
I passed.
I thought that for our next date...
I'd come pick you up or something.
I came up with all these ways
to surprise you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
-I'm happy for you.
-Yes, I passed.
Are you free on Friday?
Friday? I am.
Let's go somewhere.
I'll drive.
-Let's go downstairs.
-Let's go.
-Back to the others.
-Thanks for coming for me.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
They get along so well!
-That scene was too chummy.
-So stupid.
It was nice, the whole,
"Let's go back to everyone!"
So she was just sulking.
But they're both so frank.
He apologized
and she said, "I'm happy for you."
-It's so cute!
-So cute!
He was so bad at surprising her.
Everyone knew he'd know the results.
But he can't say?
-Terrible.
-It's cute!
And Arman says, "Good work."
It's like, good work on what?
Why are all the guys
with chiseled features stupid?
It's only a matter of time
between Byrnes and Misaki.
I'm glad for them.
-It's been a while since we had a couple.
-That's true!
Not since the meat incident.
-The meat?
-That's right, the meat thing.
Uchi and Minori.
The other day, Eiichiro Oda sent me
a message on LINE
asking whether Minori and Uchi
are still together.
-Wow.
-You talk on LINE with him?
Yeah, I do.
-The guy who wrote One Piece? Wow.
-That's right.
He's a huge fan of Terrace House.
-Really?
-That's amazing.
-He watches every episode on Netflix.
-Seriously?
He sends me his thoughts
in the middle of the night.
He's into Terashima right now.
For real?
-As expected.
-As he should be.
We now have a cupid in Riko's mom.
She's creating pressure for Masako.
There's Terashima,
who's not certain how he feels,
and Riko who's hesitant.
But the mom might just come
and push them together.
-That's possible.
-Yes.
Martha and Riko have scary expressions
when they look at each other.
-That morning--
-Sparks?
-After the smoothie.
-There was a weird vibe.
The effect the smoothies had
on their bowels,
-wasn't that amazingly quick?
-It was amazing.
They were all pooping.
How about how things were
between Riko and Martha?
What was that? Was she mad?
It was a little tense.
Riko was like a student
after a private meeting with the teacher.
"I think my stomach is rumbling, so...
I'm going to go now."
Things are starting to get
a little sticky.
NAKAMEGURO, TOKYO
Where are you going for your drive?
I'm seriously considering...
taking her to Yokohama.
-Yokohama?
-Yes.
NOBUYA HISATOMI
Yokohama's streets
are pretty difficult to navigate.
Might be tough for a beginner.
But Yokohama...
is where Misaki's been rejected
once before.
-By another guy?
-Yes.
I was rejected there too, long ago.
-By a woman from Yokohama.
-In Yokohama?
Everybody tells me
I shouldn't go there because of that.
-But it doesn't matter, does it?
-No.
Right?
It's a nice town.
Not to be stubborn or anything,
but I have confidence in the city.
I know I can show her a good time there.
I was going to tell her how I feel there.
What? You haven't already?
-Not yet.
-I see.
You think it'll go well?
-Depends on the date?
-I've got no idea.
-The sound of the waves is nice.
-Yeah.
It's calming.
Look, they're kissing.
Guess it's that kind of place.
-Tomorrow?
-Yeah.
-Where are you going?
-I don't know.
-You haven't heard?
-Is he trying to surprise you again?
Is he?
Is he trying to surprise you again?
The surprises haven't gone well so far.
He hasn't told you even though you asked?
-I haven't asked.
-Oh, you haven't?
Isn't it...
-more fun if I don't ask?
-I suppose.
I like you.
I'd like to go out with you.
That's how I feel.
I feel like you don't know yourself.
You're insecure.
And it's those core elements to you
which I don't really like.
But I don't like you like that.
So, I can't go out with you.