-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week...
The good-looking guy came.
Misaki and...
They seemed to be hitting it off
in Sangen-jaya,
being the same age and all.
He's tending to Misaki's broken heart.
He says all the right things.
I want someone who can accept me as I am.
There's no need for you to change at all.
The reason I was rejected...
He told me I had no core self.
You totally have a core self!
-They made plans for the next date.
-They did.
Byrnes promised to take her on a date
to Hakone once he gets his license.
Also, it's an important moment
in Momoka's life.
Whether you can become a pro or not
depends on how serious
you can devote yourself to ballet.
If you don't have that kind of mindset,
I don't think you'll be able to become
a professional ballet dancer.
So do you have a goal
for this competition?
I need to make the top three.
Out of how many?
I think 150?
So her date with Arman was postponed.
-That's right.
-"Oh, really?" in his monotone voice.
"Yes, good luck" in his monotone voice.
And Rikopin...
Hayato's haunting her.
He's not haunting her.
They went to the Cupnoodles Museum.
They did, but their conversation...
I don't want a date in yukatas.
Only for relationships?
If I'm not in a relationship with someone,
I wouldn't hold hands with him.
-You'd have to be in a relationship?
-I wouldn't hold hands otherwise.
That was the moment she built a wall.
It was cold of her.
Rikopin just expressed
her idea of a relationship.
No, that's just her way
of building a wall.
People who've got game don't understand.
-You think so?
-I know.
Girls do stuff like this.
-Are you naked from the waist down?
-My pants are pink!
-Sorry, I got nervous for a second.
-Me too.
I thought maybe you forgot your pants.
If that's the case,
you could've mentioned it before.
Torichan, it won't help if you squint.
-So true!
-Torichan!
-He does look pants-less.
-Don't turn around!
Torichan!
So we don't really know how she feels.
But when Rikopin came home,
-didn't she say she had fun?
-She did.
I realize I like hanging out with him.
-Oh, good.
-He takes the lead.
He gets excited with me about stuff.
Girls wouldn't say stuff like that
if they were interested.
I wonder...
But yeah, maybe.
So to Rikopin, you're a friend.
Probably.
-But Hayato thinks he was shut down?
-That's right.
I don't get why.
-That's true.
-Why not?
She said she could go on that date
even if she didn't like the person.
She said that to him
while they were there.
-So next time, they could wear yukatas--
-What?
Next time? After what she said?
Aren't you being a little too negative?
Aren't you being a little too positive?
But it's five against one.
I hate majority rule!
If we went by majority on this show,
my opinion would never count!
I talked to Hayato yesterday.
-You did?
-Yeah.
Can I ask about what?
Totally. In fact, it's better if you ask.
-Really?
-Yeah. Hayato thinks that...
you're trying to push him away.
Like, you don't want
to hold hands with him.
Things like that.
Because if someone you like
said something like that to you,
then you might think that
maybe they're not interested.
-Yeah...
-Yes.
So that's why he was acting that way.
-I see.
-You guys both like each other.
But if you put your feelings on hold,
what could happen won't happen.
It's been two years.
I've forgotten what dating's like.
Feels like I'm starting all over again
when it comes to dating.
Anyway, he thinks you're rejecting him.
-I see.
-Yeah.
I see.
GAKUGEI UNIVERSITY, TOKYO
-Are you gonna be in a competition?
-A showcase, for an event.
Am I good enough to solo at the showcase?
-Solos are pretty difficult.
-It's my first time.
DAISAKU KIKUCHI
PROFESSIONAL DANCER
I'm feeling a lot of pressure right now.
It's on July 13th,
so I'll rehearse until then.
-Welcome home.
-I'm home.
-Did you work today?
-Yeah.
-It was busy.
-Welcome back.
-What's wrong?
-Um...
You...
were so quiet the other day.
It's been bothering me.
When we talked about relationships,
you said you wouldn't hold hands
if you weren't in one,
and there are places you wouldn't go to.
You drew a clear line.
I think that's what's great about you.
But the way you said it...
I felt shut down.
At least that's how I felt.
-It made me wonder what the point was.
-I see.
So did that make you consider...
not going on dates with me anymore?
It's fun, but...
Our... I'm not sure anymore.
What I said is how I really feel.
-But the way I said it...
-The way you said...
No! I meant I didn't communicate it well,
and maybe I gave you the wrong idea.
I wouldn't talk about stuff like that
with just anyone.
But maybe I gave you the idea
that I wasn't interested in you.
I hope not.
Because it's not true.
Okay.
Has that been bothering you?
I'm sorry...
Stop.
It's hard to... I mean...
I didn't think I was that quiet.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
No, it wasn't like that.
I realized that I made you feel bad.
-But we do view relationships differently.
-Yeah.
But that's fine.
I think that you should be you.
Always.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 21 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
Studying?
Studying.
Amazing.
Is it?
What's this congratulations letter for?
Oh, that was for my practice exam.
I'll give you a quiz.
Don't do it. No way.
As you attempt a right at an intersection,
an oncoming truck stops
and signals you to go ahead,
so you quickly make the right turn.
-That's false.
-You got it!
When entering a tunnel, you drop speed...
Oh wait, I can't read this character.
Zen... Zen...
You can just skip it.
By turning on so-and-so to see better,
you can enter at normal speed.
-False.
-You're correct!
-Yes!
-You have this all memorized.
Not at all.
These are all the problems I missed.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah, they're the ones I missed.
-Seriously though, good luck.
-Thanks.
-Don't worry.
-I really want to go somewhere.
-Where do you want to go?
-Anywhere! But get your license first.
I'd better study more.
-Every day.
-I'll give you quizzes.
-Okay.
-Do you have work today?
-Yeah.
-At what time?
-A live show.
-I'll be going soon.
-Really?
Study hard. For me.
I will.
-You go work hard.
-I will. See you later.
I'm gonna get ready.
-Good luck.
-I'll see you later.
-Are you coming home later?
-Yeah. It's only Yokohama.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
-I'm super hungry.
-Yeah, I haven't eaten much today.
This is the first time the three of us
are getting together for drinks.
We've done it at home though.
Oh, this must be it.
-This is it.
-Yeah.
-Hello.
We've got the place to ourselves tonight.
Well, the owner is letting us
use the place after hours.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
-Thanks for coming.
How about a starter and then some pasta?
-Yeah, sounds great.
-Okay, I'll go make it.
-We leave it to you.
-Got it.
-Here's the starter.
-Bon appétit.
Looks delicious!
It's great.
You're going on another date with Misaki?
Yeah, so I've gotta get
my license on the first try.
Yeah, if you fail...
-It'd be bad.
-Yeah, embarrassing.
-She'd be my first passenger.
-Yeah.
Until then...
it'd be nice to know where things stand.
Why don't you just tell her how you feel?
I think it's too soon for that.
I think there's a 99% chance
she'd say yes.
What if I get rejected?
Just say something.
Thanks for waiting.
Here's the ragù sauce.
-This is young sardine, roe and zucchini.
-It looks amazing.
This is different from the norm.
So good!
-It's super good.
-It's so good!
I heard you guys talking about Misaki.
All he talks about is Misaki.
Oh, her birthday is next week!
-Yeah, it is.
-Why don't you plan something?
-When is it?
-The 25th.
-Oh, but she said she won't be here.
-Is that the day of the ballet?
Is it the 25th?
Then let's do something
either before or after.
Maybe we can plan something together?
Sure, we'll say you put it together.
You take the lead.
-Nice. She'll be happy.
-Yeah, I'll do it.
How are things going for you, Hayato?
Things with Riko...
-are at a standstill.
-Holding steady?
But are you thinking
of going out with her again? Or are you--
Even if we did, I wouldn't be sure
whether I can take things further.
That's true.
You couldn't even hold hands.
-It'd be like a school field trip again.
-A field trip?
She didn't ask you out
after she apologized?
-No, she didn't.
-I see.
-I wonder what she's thinking.
-I really don't know.
I think you should just clearly say it.
Expect us to move 10% as fast as you two.
You guys are moving pretty quick.
So really, Rikopin didn't shut him down.
-No.
-Or she didn't mean to.
But Hayato thought she did,
which explains what happened.
So she communicated that she's interested.
-She did.
-Right?
-There's no need for him to be uncertain.
-Yeah, why does he feel that way?
I mean, Riko expressed her feelings
as best she could.
Yes, to the point where
it could be taken as,
"I'm interested.
Please ask me out again."
-That's how she meant it, right?
-Yes.
Riko's being harsh.
If she's gonna reject him,
she should just do it.
But she likes him, doesn't she?
-No way!
-Isn't Hayato the one being harsh?
-Why?
-If we're talking harsh...
I mean, he brought it to the point
where she had to say all that...
-and he still doesn't get it.
-Yeah.
It's Hayato's turn right now.
-Right. The ball's in his court.
-It is.
And yet he's like...
"I don't know how she feels..."
So since she said
she didn't want to hold hands yet,
he's afraid that if he asked her out,
she'd say something like that again?
-He should just hold her hand anyway.
-That's right.
Oh, but he wouldn't want
his hand flung off.
Oh, like what happened to Tetsu long ago.
Yes, Tetsu and Rie Kitano.
I watched it over and over.
It's hard to say with these two
until they go on another date.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
On the flipside,
there's no stopping Byrnes and Misaki.
-It's so nice.
-Yeah, it's so great.
When I was about 30,
I forced my guy to do quizzes with me.
-So you can relive the experience?
-Yes, to experience that moment.
Do you understand?
Like, "I don't get this."
"Me neither."
That exchange.
"That's not right."
"Yes, it is!"
"Let's check the answer."
"See! I told you."
"What? That can't be right."
Seems like so much fun.
I can do that for hours.
-I'm gonna have to check out Amazon.
-Please do.
Workbooks are gonna sell like crazy.
What did you think of Byrnes' dancing?
It was wonderful.
That shirt
along with the striped sweatpants,
and his socks with the red shoes?
Only he could pull that off.
-That crazy combination?
-Yeah, maybe just him and Kentaro.
-You couldn't, right?
-Yeah.
But there was a time I dressed like that.
Looking back, I'm embarrassed.
Off to Mito for a tour -Misaki
One day until the competition.
-Tomorrow's a big day for both of you.
-Yeah. We can do it, Momo.
Yeah.
I'll be in Mito thinking of you.
I'll be in Shibuya thinking of you.
Be confident.
Yeah, I need to relax and be confident.
I wonder how it went for Yuuki.
-Oh, it was today.
-His driving test?
-He's not home yet?
-I haven't seen him.
-I'm going to be older in just a bit.
-That's right.
-In 20 more minutes.
-Oh, yeah!
I'm going to try
to stay up until midnight.
Yeah.
Welcome home.
Come on. Hurry.
What?
Oh no, did it not go well?
No way!
Really? You didn't pass?
No way. Really?
You failed?
I'm sorry, I failed.
I just turned 24 right now.
Seriously?
-I'm really sorry.
-You really failed?
Seriously?
I scored an 89. One point away.
One point?
Seriously?
First off, happy birthday.
I'm sorry I couldn't bring good news.
It's okay.
I have something to look forward to.
I'm really sorry, Misaki.
-It's okay.
-I'll get it soon.
As soon as I get it, let's go somewhere.
Seriously.
I definitely want to take you.
I'll always remember this birthday.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
Zero days until the competition.
Keep calm and dance! Good luck!
-Good morning.
-What are you making?
-Coffee.
-Did you see Arman?
-No.
-I think he went to work.
-So early.
-Isn't it early?
-Yeah.
-I want some too.
-Sure. I'm making a lot.
It's my first time making it.
What made you decide to try it today?
I can't go to the competition today.
So I thought I'd make some for Momo.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Are you nervous?
-No.
-You're prepared?
-Yeah, I'm ready.
Dance as if you're the star.
-Even though it's only two minutes long.
-You have to show it in two minutes.
Two minutes will decide my fate
after having danced ballet for 16 years.
The people who know will see it though.
What I've done all these years?
You can tell
the moment someone stands on stage.
-Be one of those people.
-Yeah.
Just coffee today?
Be confident.
Is the coffee ready?
-Looks great!
-Go ahead.
Bon appétit.
It's perfect.
-Good luck. Do your best.
-I will.
Thank you.
-Good luck!
-I'm going now.
SHIBUYA CULTURAL CENTER OWADA
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
SLEEPING BEAUTY
ALL JAPAN BALLET COMPETITION
Here it goes.
We will now begin
with the high school, Seniors B category.
Number 4056,
Princess Aurora variation from Act III.
We will now begin the award ceremony
for the Ninth Annual Sleeping Beauty
All Japan Ballet Competition.
In tenth place, number 4042, Hinako Arai.
In ninth place,
number 4036, Chisato Masuda.
In eighth place,
number 4004, Chisato Suzuki.
In seventh place,
number 4018, Miho Nishimura.
In sixth place,
number 4056, Momoka Mitsunaga.
In first place, number 4011, Aoi Hirata.
She did well.
But I'm sure she's frustrated.
First place in the senior category,
Miss Aoi Hinata.
We present this award to you
for your excellent performance
in the Ninth Annual
All Japan Ballet Competition.
-How was it for you?
-Yeah.
I'm frustrated, to be honest.
I really wanted to make the top three.
So, I'm frustrated.
So what's gonna happen now?
-I mean...
-You mean after?
I'm sort of in a panic right now.
-You are?
-Yes.
You know how the curtains closed after?
Afterwards, I was called over...
and I got an offer from a ballet company.
What?
I'll be a professional dancer
starting next week.
-Wow!
-Seriously?
-Congratulations!
-You scared me.
That's amazing!
-You made pro, but you're down?
-Yeah.
I'm still frustrated.
I wanted to make the top three...
That doesn't matter now that you made pro!
Right?
That's what you were working hard for.
I know, but I still wanted to win.
And if you got the offer on top of that,
then you would've been ecstatic.
That's true.
I have to work harder than ever before.
-It's still amazing.
-Yeah.
-I'm still in shock.
-Amazing.
My dream came true.
That's a serious congrats to you.
Congratulations.
Wow!
It's a happy day.
-Congratulations!
-I'm so glad.
-Yeah.
It sounded like her dreams would end
if she didn't make top three.
But I guess people who know, know.
It's really only a handful
that can make pro, right?
It must be a truly amazing accomplishment.
Now that she's going pro,
what'll happen with Arman?
Yeah, it was supposed to be on hold
until after the competition.
I don't think she should be messing around
with Arman if she's gonna be a pro.
That's true.
He's not a bad guy or anything.
He's not, but we haven't seen
anything cool from him either.
-He's been here awhile now.
-Right?
I don't care
if he's good at making takoyaki, right?
-Anything.
-You want him to show something.
Yeah, he needs to show something.
-Something unexpected.
-Yeah, he needs it.
What's really surprising is
Byrnes failed his driving test.
-Yeah.
-Is the test difficult?
People don't fail too often?
Do people fail the written exam?
But even if he failed,
she said he just has to try again.
I love that.
It's cute even though he failed.
Misaki tells him it made her birthday
more memorable this way.
Beautiful.
He said he definitely wanted to take her
on a ride.
When he said that, I thought,
"Oh no, a lewd comment!"
Even I didn't think that.
"Happy birthday," and then bang.
-I'm--
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-Happy birthday!
-Thanks.
It's so cute! I'm so happy! Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Here it comes.
-Is this the main?
-Yeah.
Seriously, thanks, Hayato.
-Bon appétit!
-Bon appétit.
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
I'm back.
Looks delicious.
-It's so good.
-Yeah, thanks.
Oh, man...
-How about some meat, Riko?
-I want some.
Thank you.
This is amazing. Let's have some after.
-Yeah.
-You want to eat it later?
Then let's do gifts.
Yeah!
Happy birthday.
It's from a brand I like,
and I wanted you to wear it.
Nice!
-Wait a sec!
-What?
-Never mind.
I want you to try it on later.
I'm embarrassed.
-Why? You can do a fashion show.
-Why don't you just wear it now?
Go try it on!
-While we're not looking?
-Yeah.
-This is nice.
-Yeah, it is.
It looks amazing on you!
-It's so cute!
-Really?
It's so cute!
It looks good.
-Really?
-Let's see, let's see.
Spin around.
-It's very feminine.
-Right?
-It's cute!
-I'm so embarrassed!
Come back.
I'll wear it for a special occasion.
-Okay.
-I'm gonna go change. I'm so embarrassed!
Why is she embarrassed?
She looks so good!
It was really cute.
-It looked good on her, right?
-Yeah, it did.
-You wanted to see more?
-I did.
You should seriously wear it
whenever you feel like it.
I will.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Really.
-It really looked good on you.
Your license though...
You don't know when you can get it.
Does that mean we won't go anywhere
until then?
No, let's go somewhere.
As long as it's not Yokohama or Shonan.
You don't want to go there that bad?
I feel like it's bad luck.
Like...
-The bad luck...
-It won't go well if we go there?
Yeah.
Even if you went with a different guy?
You're right. I'm wrong.
-That doesn't sound right.
-You're right.
But it's still scary.
What is?
Never mind.
What are you afraid of? Tell me.
What's so scary?
That even if you like someone...
and even if that person liked you back...
that may change.
So you're worried about that?
Yeah.
-Let's go somewhere.
-Yeah, we should.
Don't stare at me.
I like you, Misaki.
You're kidding, right? Wait...
Why would I kid about that?
Here? I mean...
It's only gonna be on your forehead.
-Just your forehead...
-Wait, wait.
Wait.
-Wait, I'm not ready.
-I'm like the weird guy.
It's been a long time since I...
Oh, man!
Let's go back.
Let's go join everyone.
-You can go ahead.
-Why?
Just go ahead of me.
I'm going.