-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
That's right.
So, a lot happened in the last episode.
-Yes, it did.
-That's right.
First, Makoto and Minori
went for a night jog together.
-It's totally fine.
-Sure is.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
Go running again.
-I might ask you to accompany me.
-Hmm?
I might ask you
to come running with me again.
-There's certainly a good vibe there.
-Yes, there is.
And then the barista is asking
these questions with a little envy.
-The Asano vibe.
-Asano vibe.
Like this.
You're referring to Atsuko Asano
from the trendy TV dramas.
-The influence of Ms. Atsuko.
-Yes, that was there.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
-And then, we cannot forget...
-Yes.
...the tap dancer, Yuki.
He made her speak out about her dream.
Then in return,
he told her "it's not that clear."
Like, I wasn't getting anything
even though you've talked a lot.
It's confusing.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
For me, I thought...
I was doing things with certainty.
What's wrong, Yuri?
Why? Why are you crying?
Mizuki was trying so hard to talk it out.
Can you believe that?
And she cried.
Yes, then Yuriko started to sob along too,
like contagious vomiting.
Not vomiting.
And then while talking intimately,
the tap dancer, Adachi,
explained to Yuriko
that his intention was to be supportive.
You'd think that no one would be fooled by
such a carrot-and-stick approach--
-I like that.
-See?
-Whoa.
-She is so easy.
-She can't help it.
-I'm more concerned with Teacher Triendl.
Right.
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
I wanted to help her clarify
by sharing my vision and dream.
YUKI ADACHI, 27 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
Even if I talked endlessly
to someone who is not as passionate...
something might resonate
within that person.
So I wanted Mizuki to talk about it
and then support her,
whatever it is.
I'm glad we talked.
Well, next time, let's go have a drink.
Yeah, I want to talk again.
For sure.
Isn't it better that she thinks,
"Who do you think you are?"
than to have no feelings at all--
-It's true.
-That's the thing.
There's a better chance
for her to take an interest in him.
-I see.
-It's more likely.
I totally don't get it.
I still don't believe it.
I definitely think
she totally hates him now.
-Hmm.
-Tap?
I think she'll never like him.
And that's it.
-Until the very end?
-Yes!
-Nice and loud.
-It's like, "Hey!"
-Like a "yes" that sounds like, "Hey!"
-Hey!
I haven't been home
at this time in a while.
That's right. You're usually out late.
Is this normal?
As usual, everyone is out late.
I'm bored.
-Yeah, I'm bored.
-Right?
I'm going out for a run again.
-Want to go out again?
-Sure.
When do you want to go?
Before that, what should we do for dinner?
Do you want to make something?
Sure.
-There's a bunch of things in the fridge.
-I'll go check it out.
-So?
-There's only salad.
We don't have anything.
-Do you want to go eat somewhere?
-Sure.
Where?
-I like grilled meat.
-Grilled meat?
-Can you eat that?
-Yeah.
Wanna go?
Meat!
MEGURO, TOKYO
-It's hot
-It's not hot today.
No, it is.
-But summer will be over soon.
-The pool...
-Yeah.
-I wanna go in.
We need to clean it though.
SHUEN
GRILLED MEAT
-It's our first meal out of the house.
-Yup.
Surprisingly.
Without everybody else.
Ouch.
-What would you like to drink?
-Can we drink?
Why not?
-Give up on running?
-What?
-Yeah, forget it.
Got up in the afternoon and did nothing?
-Hey?
-Today.
No, I haven't done anything.
Neither today nor yesterday.
We went to bed late.
It was really late yesterday.
-Cheers.
Yay.
-What was up with that?
-Well, Yuki is an adult.
I mean, what he said was a bit harsh.
I thought he didn't have to go that far.
Like, no one opposed him.
Right. It must have felt like that
on the women's side.
You know, Uchi and I talked
for a while last night.
-After I went to bed?
-Yes, that's right.
-What did you guys talk about?
-Right.
What? What?
-What did you talk about?
-What do you think we talked about?
So, who do you find is the best,
I mean, the easiest, to talk to?
The easiest to talk to?
Is it Uchi?
I haven't really spoken much to Uchi.
I mean, the only time
we talked alone was yesterday.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-When you see us women talking...
-Yup.
...do you wonder if we're getting along?
I do. I do! I really do.
I totally think about it.
I think, like,
"Those girls are holding back."
What should I do about that?
-You are holding back, right?
-Yeah, of course.
It's probably easier to talk to us
three guys than the two girls, right?
That's tough.
-It's not right.
-What?
-Not good.
-We're home.
-Welcome back.
-I'm full.
I am surprised.
Did you cook and eat by yourself?
-You guys went to eat grilled meat, right?
-Grilled meat.
-I'm jealous.
-It was delicious.
What did you do today?
-I stayed at home.
-What about practice?
It was raining today, so no practice.
Right, it was raining today.
And you, Minori?
I was at a photo shoot...
-Oh, right.
-...and was back by around 3:00.
-So you were back early.
-Yes.
Isn't it because you're a good model?
-Exactly.
-Why the praise all of a sudden?
You're not very convincing.
"Exactly."
-You really think so?
-Yes, I do. I do think so.
It's scary.
That must've been so nice
to go out to eat.
We talked about a bunch of stuff.
Well, sure.
You girls have qualms
-and don't talk about certain things.
-Yes.
So we talked about
what that was all about.
What do you think about that, Yuri?
I want all three of us girls to talk.
I think that if all three of us talk,
it won't go anywhere.
You want the two of you to talk instead?
Well, it's not that I want
the two of us to talk...
-Well, so...
-Right, so...
I'm kidding!
No, really. I'm off to shower.
It's like I just booted you out.
-I'll see you later.
-Okay.
So with the three of us,
all we have talked about is...
-Yes.
-...what our types are.
Yes.
And even if we continue talking,
I think that we'll probably
only talk about that.
In reality,
if this was with our other friends,
we wouldn't be limited by time.
Yes.
So I don't think
that we would confide as easily.
But because we do have
a limited time to live here,
I think we need to ask each other things
during the time we have together.
-Yes.
-Yes. Exactly.
-Right?
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Well.
Pardon me. Cheers.
I started drinking without you.
-So, do you think Makocchan...
-Yeah?
...is into Minori?
I'm not sure.
It seems like it.
-They did go out for dinner.
-Yes, they did.
I was wondering if it's mutual.
There's no guarantee it's mutual
just because they went out for dinner.
Of course.
-But it seems like it.
-Yes.
-Oh, welcome back.
-We're home.
-Welcome back.
Oh, wow.
-We got it.
-You got it.
There's so much.
-Thank you. Oh, Jenga!
-Some party goods.
Jenga.
-It's not the usual Jenga.
-I like Jenga.
Oh, Uno! Jenga!
Oops.
How was biking?
-Great.
-I wasn't asking you.
You always go biking.
-Biking is great.
You look happy.
-Oh, here he is.
-Hey.
-A nap?
-I was having a little sleep.
We'll play Jenga today.
Jenga? Really?
What were you up to today, Makoto?
I went and spoke with the coach.
It was okay.
-How did it go?
-Well, I'm not sure.
-What happened?
-Well, it wasn't like anything happened.
-You seem to be in low spirits.
-Well, no, I'm not in low spirits.
-Are you tired?
-Yes, I'm tired.
Isn't Mizuki coming home?
She's at work.
-Really?
-Overnight.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
When will she be back?
-She'll be back tomorrow.
-Tomorrow.
-So, today we'll play Jenga.
-Jenga.
Shall we play Jenga?
-Makoto doesn't seem well.
-Yeah, he seems down.
We'll have to talk to him
to clear the air.
Off to Gunma for work.
Be back tomorrow.
Mizuki
-We were waiting for you, Yuki.
-Oh, really? Sorry.
-That's it for today.
Oof.
-Why are you smiling so much?
-Because you seem a little down.
-Me?
-Yes.
-Seem down.
-You gonna tell us?
Well, it's not that I feel down.
You know how...
-I play baseball, right?
-Yes.
And I don't know what impressions
you get from that,
but I graduated high school and played
during my first year of university.
In my second year,
I wasn't getting along with my teammates,
and I was in a phase where
I only wanted to have fun,
and I wasn't really committed.
So for a year or so,
I didn't go to practice.
So at the beginning of my third year...
I went and apologized to my coach
and asked to start all over again.
So, in my third year I went in
as an entry-level player.
I practiced with the younger players.
I wasn't participating
in the main practice, of course,
and did chores.
My third year was, like,
I was the first person to arrive
and the last person to leave,
kind of thing.
So, just before my fourth year,
they began to let me play.
Because of that gap,
I'm not in the top level of players.
So, when we were talking to Mizuki...
about our ambitions,
and about her dream being vague
and not clear enough...
at that time, I also felt
obligated to talk about where I was,
but I couldn't say anything.
I went along with you two as though I did,
even though I also doubt mine.
So I feel I need to apologize to Mizuki.
Also, my coach is concerned that,
although I'm supposed to
focus on baseball,
I put myself into situations like this...
and that it will affect my performance.
Of course, I want to have fun
and drink alcohol with everyone here,
and my lifestyle has already been
changing into that.
There's only two months left.
What are you going to do?
Well, I have no choice but try
and get into the top level.
We didn't talk about that, right?
Like, where you stand in your team.
I did want to know, though.
When I hear about how the two of you
have figured out your goals and all that,
you both see it clearly.
So I was feeling kind of guilty...
to be honest.
If he apologizes...
I think Mizuki's heart will skip a beat.
Like, if he says to her,
"Yeah, I'm also a little unsure of
my dream, and I wanted to be helpful."
And he comes and apologizes
for not speaking up.
Wouldn't she fall for him for that?
I love you
That's it!
Yeah, so he felt guilty.
-I didn't know.
So, being in his fourth year
but not at the top level,
there's definitely some conflicts there.
He was saying he apologized
and went back to the team.
-It's like that guy from Slam Dunk.
-Hisashi Mitsui.
But you know,
Hisashi Mitsui had this crazy talent.
Man, you don't have to be so passionate.
It was just a small comment.
Also, you know, it seems
as though Tap...
has taken on a role
as the older brother or leader.
-Yes.
-Yes, he has.
But, like, "You seem down.
We need to talk."
-Wouldn't you hate that?
-No, I'd want him to listen to me.
You are totally weird.
There's no way I'd want that.
-It's not weird.
But, you know
along with Minori, there's this issue
-with being open amongst the girls.
-Right.
This time, we see not only
the romantic relationships,
but also the complexity
of the human relationships.
Right.
Well!
-We haven't...
-What?
We haven't seen you for a while.
'Cause you don't sleep up there.
We talk often.
But aren't you sleeping when I come home?
-Or not?
-No, no.
You stay downstairs for too long.
Hi, come in.
-Hey.
-Oh!
Hey.
-I've come to talk.
-About what?
-Come in.
-I'm surprised.
Pardon me.
-This is rather unusual. First time.
-What's up?
-Sit here.
-I want to sit on a chair.
Want this chair? Here.
-Aw, you know.
-What is it?
-What's wrong?
-Well, I'm here to apologize to Mizuki.
Right.
And...
it's not like there's this guilt,
but there's something I didn't say before.
-Yes.
-I got into university
and joined the baseball team.
I practiced hard my first year.
In my second year,
I hit a phase where
I wanted to have fun and all.
So in my third year, I realized
I needed to come to my senses.
So, I went to see the coach,
and I asked to be allowed to play
even if I had to start all over again.
So I was regarded only as
an entry-level player
and not really considered
as part of the team by everyone else.
I would be part of the team
once I continued on to my fourth year.
So now...
I'm finally part of the team.
That said, it felt like
we all kind of ganged up on you.
I left you all alone.
I should've said this
right then and there.
So...
Thank you so much
for coming here to say that.
-Oh, no, it's inexcusable.
-Don't worry.
So for the next two months...
I have to be kind of devoted to baseball
and do my best.
-You need to give it your all.
-Yes, I have to.
-Sorry to take up your time.
-Oh, no, not at all.
-Well, good night.
-Thank you.
-Good night.
-See you.
Good night.
-Are you relieved?
-Yes.
It made me kind of happy to think
that he was concerned about me.
It made me happy.
I'm glad that happened.
Cut it out!
Phew!
Now it's clean.
Pretty much.
You're going out
with Yuriko tonight, right?
We're going out to drink sake.
She can drink.
Yes, it's easier to ask out
girls who can drink.
She scores high.
Easy to ask.
So who are you closest to?
-Or, like, that you can...
-Yuriko probably.
...talk to most easily?
All of them aside from Mizuki...
for now.
-By the way...
-Our schedules don't match.
...me, too.
I wonder if she's going to stay
the way she is now.
The other girls were saying that, too.
EBISU, TOKYO
-Hey there.
-Hey.
-Thanks for coming.
-How was your day?
-Good.
-I've never seen you wear a hat.
-Yes, it's cold. You need to keep covered.
-I see.
Um, I got you something.
-Hepalyse?
-Yes.
-Because we'll drink too much. And you?
-I got one, too.
I got myself the turmeric one.
-Did you drink it already?
-I drank it already.
-Then I'll drink it now. Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Now we can plunge into sake.
-Well, that's it.
Drinking Hepalyse is a smart idea, right?
Yes, it is.
They say it makes a big difference...
whether you drink it or not.
-So, with this, you'll be fine tomorrow.
-I'll be fine tomorrow.
Wanna go?
Let's go.
Let's have a toast.
Yes, let's.
Let's drink.
-Cheers.
So we're going to see you dance
on the fourth of September, right?
I've never seen
something like that before,
so I can't imagine what it will be like.
I'm guessing it's like jazz or something.
Yes, like jazz.
-Oh, is that so?
-You got it.
It developed alongside
the culture of jazz and swing music.
This week, my boss will perform
at the Blue Note in New York.
-Oh, wow. He's that accomplished?
-Yes.
I would like to perform at a place
like the Blue Note someday.
-Yes.
I hope you're looking forward
to the fourth.
-I am.
-I'm all right.
This is fun.
-We don't get to go out to drink much.
-True.
Where do you usually go out for fun?
-Like, the library...
-Right, right.
-...or an aquarium.
Where do you like?
Where do you go?
It depends on the situation.
Like, if it's just guys, you mean?
I like going to the aquarium.
Man, my questions are just
blowing in the wind here.
My questions...
-You like the aquarium?
-I like the aquarium.
-So do you want to go to the aquarium?
-Should we?
Let's go then.
Oh, check this out.
AVAILABLE ONLINE SEPT. 2
7 PRECEDING EPISODES START TONIGHT.
"The beautiful girl that Yamasato loves."
UPDATES EVERY DAY AT 11:00 P.M.
So...
I am going to move.
Do you know Terrace House?
Crazy reaction.
That was a really good reaction.
-And you're cute, too.
-What?
-They can film you any time of day.
-But without makeup...
-Do you think I can go without makeup?
-You are fine. Totally.
-Really?
-Are you okay without makeup?
You are cool without makeup?
I'm totally fine. Totally.
I'll start my research today.
-That's scary.
-Isn't Minori next?
DISCOVER YOUR FAVORITE SHOWS
SEPT. 2
-Next, tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
-Yup.
And it already has a lot of views.
-How many?
-40,000.
It's amazing. "Updates at 11:00 p.m."
It's only been 43 minutes.
-I don't really like it.
-How many views per second, then?
-That's amazing.
-That's scary.
How long ago was your last relationship?
Well, I...
-It's going to take a while to explain.
-That's fine.
-It's okay.
We were together just until...
-before Terrace House began.
-Right.
He's in his first year of residency.
The first year of residency is...
the busiest period...
so we weren't able to see each other much.
As I'm also in med school,
I have to be understanding
of his situation.
I have to be understanding, however,
I just...
couldn't deal with it
in respect to how I felt.
-Of course you want to see each other.
-Yes.
I was totally upfront and told him,
"It's tough not seeing you,
and I also have this opportunity to grow
by being on Terrace House."
So with that, he said,
"Well I, too, am
in the most important period of my life.
I know you put up with a lot
because of my schedule,
and I'm grateful.
And I think the outcome will be
something you won't regret.
I want you to do your best."
It's okay.
We talked a whole lot when we broke up.
-So, that was it. How can I put it--
-I don't think you made a bad decision.
I think what's important is that
you made a decision about it.
Yes.
Well.
Sorry.
-I made you cry.
-Yuki, it's like...
I just open up so easily to you, Yuki.
I mean, I'm glad I talked about it.
-I'm really glad I talked about it.
-Is this a good day?
-It's a good day.
-It's a good day. Today is a good day.
I was really looking forward to this.
Me too.
Thank you!
Let's do this
-on a regular basis.
-Yes, let's.
I see.
We see a big development there.
I think we have mixed opinions about this.
-Right.
-If this was me,
and if I was in a situation where
I liked a person
but had to break up...
and then I told this to someone...
there's a chance that I would cry,
if I still liked that person.
I wonder what her tears meant.
But from the sound of it,
it was a hard breakup either way.
Where she wants to see him,
but he can't because he's busy.
She couldn't take the gap
so they broke up.
And her boyfriend also
agreed to do so.
You're really supportive of her.
Look, she brought Hepalyse
before going drinking.
Yamachan was all intense, like,
"I like her!"
All of a sudden.
Like, "I like her! She's a good person."
In general, any guy
will be impressed by that.
-Yeah, totally done in.
-Hepalyse?
You see, on top of that,
it just so happens that Yuriko
-is so short.
-Yes.
So, this gesture is like, "Here."
Like this, to the guy next to her,
-she can pause like this.
-We get it.
In short, we always think
-that short people are cheating.
-I envy them.
Someone looking up from below you
-is perceived as the cutest.
-True.
-I see.
-Right, so that girl is really
making the best use of Hepalyse.
Like, "Here."
One thing though, that last part there,
there's something
that makes me suspicious.
-I think she might be dangerous.
-Why is that?
She said to Yuki,
"I can talk about anything to you."
Yes, she did.
It's a little like she's putting up
her defenses or something.
Like, "We are not moving
towards a relationship."
As if she is indirectly maneuvering, like,
"We are in a friendship zone."
-Oh, so that's how you think of that.
-I see.
That's twisted.
Well, I--
You tend to think that way.
Wait a second.
What do you know about me?
-Judging me as some good-for-nothing man.
-Well, you are.
That is, you don't want to get hurt,
so that's why you think like that.
-What?
-It's you who is putting up your defenses.
Ask Ayumu there.
Okay, so with that--
"Because it's you, Ayumu,
I can talk about anything."
If she said that, what would you think?
It's like you just got passed over.
I would think that she likes me.
See? Normally that's how it would be seen.
It's that you've been through
too much crap.
You see everything negatively.
-You can't help to be like that.
-That's it.
I would think that person likes me.
-Normally, that's it.
-What?
-That's what it was.
-Really?
You don't really know, right,
trying to go along with adults?
Actually, that was rather obvious.
See?
It was easy to figure out.
Yes, this one is easy to figure out.
That's right.
From a guy's perspective,
you actually need to watch out.
Like, to the point where,
"Hold on! I am getting pulled in.
She's taking the lead,
and I need to slow down."
What?
That's what it could seem like.
So with what happened there,
where she cries a bit
and then immediately after is able to say,
"I can talk about anything with you."
As a woman,
I'm a little wary of how quickly
she recovers and does that.
Like, I think it's a bit too much.
-The alcohol?
-It's tricky.
It seems fishy.
-I think so, too.
-A little.
Like, the sense of heroism, a little.
Her eyes were getting droopy from alcohol,
and she was blinking
kind of like this.
Oh, like she's drunk.
You can attract most guys
with that sort of action.
Well, from her white, lacey,
puff-sleeved shirt
to Hepalyse and her crying.
-And then she confides her interest.
-Right.
Those are multi-combo moves.
There's a jab, then a straight.
Then in with the knee.
Then a high kick,
and the guy is down cold.
-He's got birds singing by his head.
-Birds singing.
-And then, "It was so nice to go out."
-Yeah.
Like, "Today was a good day."
He said,
"Let's do this on a regular basis."
-But yes, it was sweet. Really. Wasn't it?
-Yes.
-Is there still something unsettled there?
-Well, it's just
there's no straight answer yet,
but I feel like
I will continue to fight with this.
-I am not sure yet.
-Yes.
So, you're off for a whole week?
Yeah, I'm off for a week,
about seven days out of eight days.
I'll plan with whoever's around
and have some fun.
That's nice.
-Hey.
-I'm home.
You're up. Hey.
Welcome home.
-You were awake?
-I was.
What are you back from?
I went out for dinner with Yuriko.
Oh, that's right.
-How was it?
-You are smiling.
We just both got drunk...
-And that's all?
-Yeah.
But we did have some good conversations.
Like what?
-So you ask.
-Well, I have to ask.
We are getting to know each other.
Like, even if I went out with you, Uchi,
we would talk about deep, personal things.
-Yeah.
-So it was like that.
Right, you just got closer.
We didn't kiss.
Oh, really?
Wait, you think I did?
Yeah, just with how you came in
all drunk and happy.
Actually, I made her cry.
-Again?
-Man, you make them cry right away.
Were you trying to move things forward?
We're in the process of moving forward.
In the process of moving forward?
It's like we're slowly passing the point
where you no longer indicate
what your intentions are.
Right.
-What do you mean, "intentions"?
-Though I'm pretty clear with what I want.
It's not easy.
Yeah, it's difficult.
Like, after cleaning the pool
and then going out to eat,
I thought it was discourteous.
What was?
What was discourteous?
With Uchi's feelings.
Well, seriously,
I don't need stuff like that.
Like, you don't need to be conscientious
just because I expressed
some interest in Yuriko.
-Like, really...
-Well not so much conscientious--
No, really, I don't care
if it's discourteous.
I want you to go for it.
-So do that.
-Of course, I'll do my best.
Of course, for sure.