-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week...
Hansan...
Of course it's Hansan.
There was a big event.
The birth of a new couple.
Hikaru and Misaki were so cute.
It started a little awkwardly
with the ex-boyfriend talk.
But he apologized.
I'm attracted to you.
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD
-That caught me off-guard!
-Yeah, and...
Hearing you say
you want to get back with your ex...
I didn't like it.
I didn't want to hear it.
I realize that was immature of me.
I tried to end the conversation.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I understand.
I'm glad to hear it.
You could tell
that made Misaki like him more.
Like he knows how to apologize.
The gift was so cute.
-While she was drinking tea.
-Yeah, while drinking tea.
-It was so cute!
-So cute, she was embarrassed.
Was it like that?
The tea's spilling.
The tea's spilling!
Excuse me, the tea's spilling.
It's this angle...
The sushi cake was a nice idea.
Thank you.
-I went shopping with her.
-So it helps you relax, right?
"I'm sorry for saying you're immature.
I'm really happy to have met you
and everyone at Terrace House.
I'm looking forward to my time here.
Happy birthday!
From Misaki."
Thank you.
And at the end,
we got to see Hansan's personality.
That was too amazing.
That was a perfect scene.
That scene was perfect.
If you decide on the placement,
I can make it.
-This is exciting.
-No way.
I'm so stressed about time.
The most interesting results
come from challenges.
-Do they?
-Definitely.
Don't worry.
It'll definitely succeed.
I wonder what she's gonna do?
Natsumi said she doesn't care
whether or not he has a girlfriend.
Hansan, who has a girlfriend...
It'll be interesting to see
how he turns down Nacchan.
-I want to know!
-That's what I mean.
-Maybe he's up to something.
-That's it.
He is a guy, after all.
There's a way of doing it.
There's a way?
-There's a way of doing it.
You two and your experiences...
You immediately refer
to your own experiences.
Like right now.
Don't talk so happily
about how you've cheated
on your partners in the past!
There's a backdoor.
Of course there isn't!
Don't talk nonsense.
But if there were to be such a scene,
depending on how Hansan deals with it,
it could either lower his stock
or make it go higher.
It could go up
even if he does something bad.
Can that even happen?
-It's possible.
Pull this string.
Pull it here.
Pop it on.
Too big?
Your head is so small.
Here.
-Hold on when we're riding.
-Got it.
Okay?
Okay. Ready.
You can get off.
KAMAKURA, KANAGAWA
-I'm tired.
-You're tired?
-It was fun.
-Was it?
-It wasn't scary at all.
-Right?
-Your hands were pretty low.
-No way!
-Really?
-Yeah.
-The whole time?
-You were leaned over like this, right?
The tip of your glove was...
I'm sorry, I'll be careful.
I'll be careful on the way home.
I didn't mind at all.
Will you take me on a ride again?
Sure.
I might get addicted.
The hot springs...
Do you want to take a trip
to the hot springs?
-Bon appétit!
-Please.
It's like what I made.
You can make something like this?
No, I can't.
-Why don't you have someone teach you?
-If I put my mind to it...
You mean Nacchan?
Do you have any requests?
-A hamburger.
-A hamburger?
I think I can make that.
Are you enjoying Terrace House?
Yeah, it's fun.
It's becoming more fun.
I was pretty quick.
Shortly after you came...
I confessed a lot.
-Like how I'm attracted to you.
-I didn't think... Yeah.
What did you think?
I was surprised.
I had no idea you felt that way about me.
Really?
But it made me happy.
ENOSHIMA SHRINE
TREE OF LOVE
TWO TRUNKS CONNECTED BY ONE ROOT
TIE TWO PLAQUES TOGETHER
TO BRING TWO SOULS TOGETHER
Throw it in.
Give me some.
I want some.
Please let me have some.
-I want to climb that tower.
-The tower?
ENOSHIMA SEA CANDLE
It's the ocean!
Yes, it is.
-It's beautiful.
-It's the ocean! The ocean!
Amazing.
-The ocean is...
-Is wide
-Did you have fun?
-I did.
-Are you into motorcycles now?
-I'm into them.
-Did you have fun?
-Yeah.
For real.
-I laugh more when I'm with you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-No way.
Did I do anything funny?
Let's go out again.
Yeah, let's go out again soon.
Soon.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
She said the bike was fun.
That it was more fun than she expected.
And that she wants to ride again.
-She wants me to take her somewhere else.
-Nice.
I want to hear more about the touching.
She's like this while we're riding, right?
This isn't a big deal or anything, but...
But she's like this, right?
I'm sure she didn't realize it,
but whenever her hands would relax...
Her hands would be here the whole time!
So that kinda felt good.
It felt good?
She's going to make me a burger.
-We kind of talked about that.
-Her?
Yeah, since she can't cook,
she said she'd ask Nacchan teach her.
Nice.
I like how she's putting in the effort
even if it's not something she's good at.
It was all kind of easy.
Well, not easy, but...
It went so smoothly.
You never know.
It was like that for me, too.
That's true.
I feel bad.
Sorry, man.
Why? Don't apologize.
She seems like a nice girl.
Not the brightest, but...
Any progress?
Nothing happened.
We said we'd go out again.
-You like him more now?
-I do.
I knew it.
-Was the bike cool?
-It was so cool!
I wanted to stay in that position forever.
No!
Seriously, it was so fun.
The bike is dangerous.
-Did it make you fall for him?
-It did.
Because it was so cool?
It convinced me that I really liked him.
I felt it.
I told him I'd make him a hamburger.
But I can't make it on my own, so...
-will you help me?
-I don't want to.
Please?
Won't he be happier
if you made it by yourself?
You think so?
It's like what happened with Arman.
That's true.
I'll get in trouble again.
Like, "Hey, you..."
You love him?
I didn't think
I'd fall for someone so quickly.
Misaki's having so much fun!
-What a wonderful date.
-So nice.
At the exact spot Tokui took his picture.
-That café?
-I did go to that café, yes.
I believe it may have been that very seat.
-The seat even?
-Yes.
-You sat there?
-Yes, I went and sat there.
And apparently, the waitress there
was interviewed by the media.
She told them I had the cheeseburger
and the lady had a plain burger.
Apparently that's what she said.
But actually, it was the opposite.
I had the plain burger
and she had the cheeseburger.
She had it all wrong.
These things are important.
It was typical girl talk about her crush,
complete with screaming.
Like, "Do you like him more now?"
"I do."
-So fun. Must be fun.
-Must be fun.
This is the best.
It's so fun watching this happen.
"I laugh more when I'm with you."
She did say that.
With the bike...
Triendl, do you ever fantasize about
riding a bike with a guy like that?
I want to do it!
Who did you just imagine in front of you?
I'm not going to tell you.
Really?
It's not Hansan.
I know who it is, though.
I won't ever tell.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-What're you doing?
-Girl talk.
-Random chatting.
Girl talk?
-I'll leave then.
-Did you cut your hair?
-I did.
-Yeah, he cut it yesterday.
I didn't know.
-It's girl talk, but...
-You should join us.
Did you eat already, Hansan?
I have some inari sushi.
-How fitting.
-Yeah.
-It was discounted 30 yen.
-Inari fits your image.
It's a little sad.
How did your entrance exams go?
My exams are done.
The problems...
My predictions for what would be on it
were right.
So it went well, then?
Yeah, I just have to wait for the results.
-I see. When are the results posted?
-Sunday.
-That's soon.
-Yeah, it's soon.
So you won't be able to relax
for the next five days.
I'm off that week though.
-Really?
-For five days.
-How unusual.
-Yeah, the prep school at least.
So I wanted to finish other projects
in the meantime.
Hansan, can you cook?
-No, I can't.
-Can you prep and clean fish?
-I can.
-Really?
Yeah. I'm confident in my skills.
For that at least.
So you can clean fish
the moment you catch it?
-Yes. Well, I grew up near the ocean.
-Oh, really?
I don't know if you remember,
but the first day, I said I liked fishing.
-Right, you like fishing?
-Yeah, I like ocean fishing.
-In a boat?
-Yeah, a boat.
-But from the shore is okay, too.
-Nice.
-Let's go.
-Yeah, let's go.
You guys should go.
-It's super fun. It's--
-Sounds fun. You two should go.
-I have to free up a day.
-That's true.
Is there a day you can free up?
-Let me see.
-Okay.
With the exams,
you're probably not in the mindset.
Yeah, there's a lot going on.
It'll be a reward for all your hard work.
Yeah, let's do that.
Send me pictures.
-Okay.
-Sure.
ICHINOE, TOKYO
-You can put that there.
-Okay.
CAFÉ KIMGURE HIKOSEN
This is a café run by handicapped people.
-This.
-Okay.
They asked me to add another one.
Here are the materials.
So I thought I'd have you paint them.
As you finish, I'll put it together.
Why did you come to Japan?
Well, I really just wanted
to try living in Japan.
I feel like...
I don't have enough time
to do everything I want to do.
There's a part of me that feels impatient.
So your Hawaiian way of thinking
is very appealing, but...
maybe I'm just jealous.
Are you thinking about
when you're going to leave?
No, I haven't thought about it yet.
I do want to stay until the summer,
just because I want to be here then.
That's so Hawaiian.
Do you already know
when you're going to leave?
I'm planning on submitting something
in a competition this summer.
So for that,
after this living experience,
I'm hoping for a change in what I do.
-That was my thought.
-That's so cool.
I think it's great
to try different things,
as long as you keep moving toward
your goal of becoming a firefighter.
You're right.
I'm 25 already.
That's right.
You're 25. You're an adult.
-It's time to do it.
-Yeah.
Come here.
He's sleeping now, so...
You can wake him
and take the car somewhere.
Okay.
I'll say I need to shop
for some heavy things.
Yeah, something like that.
Wake him up.
-Thanks.
-No mistakes.
-You're not allowed to make anymore.
-I'll do my best.
-Your limit is an hour and a half.
-An hour and a half? Okay.
-That's the max.
-Okay.
Wake him up.
Morning.
Hikaru, will you drive me?
What?
Will you drive me somewhere?
I need to buy some stuff.
-Is that okay?
-Okay.
Okay.
Yay. Let's go then.
Let's go.
I'm coming.
Please hurry.
You're not going?
I need to step out.
I see.
Have fun. Drive careful.
Nacchan's waiting for you.
Bye!
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
FROM SAPPORO, HOKKAIDO
2011 GRADUATES SAPPORO SOSEI HIGH SCHOOL
2014 MOVES TO TOKYO, BEGINS WORK
IN THE ENTERTAINMENT INDUSTRY
2014 PART-TIME JOB AT CONVENIENCE STORE
LAST RELATIONSHIP: ONE YEAR AGO
Oops.
Oh, well.
"Sauté...
until it browns.
Mix ground meat and eggs."
I'm going to go upstairs first.
Welcome back.
You made this?
Hamburgers?
I did.
By yourself?
-Yeah, I made it myself.
-Oh, while we were gone?
Wow, thanks.
-Does it look edible?
-The way it looks? It looks delicious.
You were going to say something else.
Where's Nacchan?
Nacchan's over there.
I don't know.
She's not going to have some?
I'm sure she will.
-Nacchan?
-Yes?
You should come.
I made some for you too.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
-She made hamburgers.
-I want to try some.
Have some.
Please enjoy.
Go ahead. Try it.
It's a hamburger. It's good.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's good!
-Really?
-Yeah.
It seems like you guys are lying to me.
It's really good. I'm surprised.
-It's good.
-It's not too hard?
It's not hard?
-It's hard.
-Yeah, it's hard.
Sorry.
-I have to be honest.
-But it still tastes good?
It tastes good. It's good.
-It's not bad?
-It's really delicious, but...
-Hard?
-Hard.
Just a little.
It's really delicious.
-Really?
-Yeah.
The fact that you made it for me...
-This is making me want to cry.
-I'm seriously moved.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Why?
What's wrong?
What? Why?
I'm sorry, it's not hard.
-No, it's not that.
-It's not hard at all.
You were worried, right?
-I'm sorry. What?
-No, no...
It's seriously good. Really good.
That's not what I meant.
-You're just relieved.
-Yeah.
Thank you.
I was really nervous about it.
About making it?
Yeah, I felt so rushed.
What?
I had Nacchan help me
so that I could make this.
But she didn't help you.
She wanted me to take you out.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done it without Nacchan.
Delicious.
I'm glad.
I'm so full.
It was delicious.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Thanks, Nacchan.
I think I'll go take a bath.
I'll see you later.
Are you sure it's not too bad?
How many times are you going to ask?
You don't have to finish it.
Just shut up.
-It's good.
-Thank you.
That was so good.
-So cute!
-Makes you want to be in love.
I want to be in love!
It's amazing, though,
that she cried at the sight of him eating.
She was really nervous about making it.
She was so happy.
-Those were really good tears!
-Really cute.
You don't get those kinds of tears
too many times in a lifetime.
It's different
once you get to know each other.
The very first time...
you made a hamburger for the guy you like
with the help of your friend.
You were able to make something
you thought came out pretty well.
He said he liked it.
Not like it was amazing,
but he told you it was delicious.
So many good moments.
So many good...
-Hey!
-Tokui!
Hey!
What's going on with you today, Tokui?
Feeling a little vulnerable?
-He's been through a lot lately.
-What happened?
My ex married her ex-boyfriend!
He just heard today.
-I'm happy for her.
-It's such happy news.
You said you want to be in love,
but this is what it leads to?
I'm happy for them.
-It's good.
-They're happy.
I'm happy for them.
-Hansan's words of advice.
-Yes, Hansan.
Wasn't Hansan's advice great?
-It was, wasn't it?
-It was great.
-The way he brought it up.
-Perfect.
-Right?
-Yes.
First, he says he admires him.
Brings up Arman's good points.
-"Maybe I'm just jealous."
-"Makes me jealous."
-Even though that's impossible.
-Right?
What do you mean, "Right"?
I don't think
it got through to Arman at all.
-I think it did.
-Really? He was blasé.
"I be here until August."
He didn't say it like that.
He did say that though.
"Aspiring firefighters
who come to Terrace House
don't really end up as firefighters."
TETSUYA SUGAYA, ASPIRING ACTOR
OCT '12-DEC '14
-That's true.
-There's a bit of stigma to firemen here.
When that really thin envelope arrived...
You knew he didn't make it
just by the envelope.
Like, he definitely didn't make it.
-That's happened in the past.
-That did happen.
He's so cool.
His stock was already high,
but after the scene with Arman,
it'll rise even more.
-How high can it go?
-There's no sign of it dropping.
He does have plans to go fishing
with Nacchan later.
-Even there...
-It's going to go up.
-He'll definitely go up.
-Definitely.
He's probably really good
at putting on bait.
-And he'd smoothly help Nacchan with hers.
-He can do anything.
Nacchan seems pretty confident.
She considers it a reward for him
to hang out with her.
Pretty ballsy of her to say.
-Like, "It's a reward for your hard work."
-She just meant to do something fun.
Yeah, going out to do an activity for fun
is a reward.
-Seriously?
-That's right.
Isn't she saying she's the reward?
-Isn't that amazing?
-Will you stop looking at it like that?
We're just trying to make a hole,
so like this.
There's the hole.
-That's it?
-Yeah.
Ready?
It'll probably break somewhere.
Okay, that's it.
-That's it.
-Okay.
Do you enjoy stuff like this?
I haven't done it too often before,
but it's fun.
My dad is a carpenter,
so I used to do this when I was younger.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You know...
I know we're working,
but there's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
To everyone.
Um...
When the exhibit is over...
I'm thinking of leaving Terrace House.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
I've been working
with the exhibit as my goal,
but it's not the finish line.
From then on,
I have to run the business side.
You've worked really hard,
even staying here until the exhibit.
Really.
-Good work.
-Not at all.
Really.
It'll be an amazing beginning.
When I first came here,
I came wanting to meet people
from different fields,
hoping to be inspired.
And I was really inspired.
I was planning on working hard,
and this made me want to work harder.
-Thanks to you all.
-Good luck in the future.
-For now, I want the exhibit to succeed.
-Yeah.
With everyone's help.
I have the most memories with you, Arman.
It was really fun
going on those dates with you.
And even though things didn't work out,
it was fun being friends.
I know you work really hard.
It's the first time
I really admired a woman.
-Thank you.
Whenever I talked to you,
you never treated me differently.
I can only say thank you for everything.
It was fun.
-All of it.
-It was fun.
I went to so many places with you.
Like the gym.
Yeah, the gym.
And Mt. Takao.
And the amusement park.
-Let's still meet up when we can.
-Yeah.
I'll work hard too.
With everything.