-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Last week...
-Finally, Rikopin...
-That's right!
-...and Hayato...
-Right!
-...agreed to go to Tsukiji Market.
-A Tsukiji date!
First they ate meat together,
now they'll eat fish.
Have you ever been...
to Tsukiji Market?
-No.
-Then let's go to Tsukiji.
-It's funny.
-What's funny?
That you're interested in an 18-year-old.
She seems flattered.
She says, "It's funny."
-Totally!
-"You're interested in a girl
11 years younger than you.
That's funny."
-We're getting good vibes from Hayato.
-Yeah!
He taught Misaki how to make hamburgers.
I can't pick on him like I used to.
Arman and Momoka went
to Earth's live show.
-Oh yeah, that's right!
-They did.
I thought she was applauding...
but she's forming a hamburger patty!
I'm seriously scared!
That was about how forming hamburgers
can seem like clapping.
Coincidentally, Hayato taught Misaki
how to make hamburgers.
That's why hamburgers were
such a hot topic.
Momoka seems quite smitten with Arman,
don't you think?
He was surprisingly pure and kind of cute.
No way.
I mean, I was nervous first,
but less than I'd imagined.
He made me comfortable
and I was able to have fun.
Rikopin and Hayato are sort of a couple.
-Then there's Momoka and Arman.
-Yeah.
There are two promising couples,
so this should be interesting.
Sure.
-You go, daddy!
-I approve!
Yeah, daddy!
Did you jump in the pool with Arman
the other day?
-No.
-Why not?
Because...
-being in the pool with a guy...
-Why not?
-Girls get nervous, huh?
-Obviously.
Guys don't?
-Not really.
-Seriously?
-Why would I be?
-We're talking about a pool.
First of all, I've never been to a pool
with a guy before.
-Seriously?
-I'm serious.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-Hey!
Won't be home today. Crunch time!
-Han
-We haven't seen Hansan lately.
-That's true.
-He wasn't here yesterday either.
-Right.
He's busy right now.
Remember when you both came down earlier?
I was so glad.
Why?
I'm not used to being alone with a guy.
So...
I wasn't sure what to talk about.
-With Hayato?
-Yeah.
-But you were okay with Arman, right?
It seems to me
like you're opening up more to Arman.
Think about it.
You're so nervous around any other guy,
but you're totally fine around Arman.
I think that's a big deal.
Arman's a guy,
but you're comfortable around him.
You should go out with him again.
But I can't really ask him out.
Didn't you say
you'd go to the beach together?
-Yeah.
-The beach?
Should I ask him
to take me to the beach?
Yeah, you should tell him,
"You said we would, remember?"
I'll try to find a good time.
I'll try.
How was it with Momochan?
-Oh, right.
-I've been curious.
-Oh, yeah?
-But I couldn't ask.
-It was fun.
-Yeah, you had fun?
What about the beach?
-The beach?
-You don't remember, do you?
I do.
That's gonna happen.
I'm planning on going
after I get back from Hong Kong.
-What's in Hong Kong?
-My friend's wedding.
-Cool.
-I'm going to Hong Kong and Macau.
-That's cool.
-I'm planning on asking her after that.
You should totally show her
your surfing skills.
-That's a good idea.
-Right?
Momochan gets nervous around guys,
even if it's just chatting.
But with you... she said she's fine.
-Oh, really?
-That's what she said.
But that's happened to me before.
Girls tell me I'm easy to talk to.
Ever since then...
I mean, that means I'm like a brother.
I've been kind of worried about that.
-Hey!
-What's up?
-May I come in?
-Sure.
Let's go to the beach sometime.
-Okay.
-Will you take me?
Sure.
-Okay, please take me.
-It's a deal.
-We talked about it before.
-Yeah, that's right.
-You're leaving tomorrow, right?
-Yup.
-To Hong Kong?
-Let's go to the beach next week.
-On Sunday please, if you can.
-Okay, deal.
-I'll make myself available.
-Yeah, you'd do that?
-Okay, cool. Thanks.
-Sure.
-Bye. Good night.
-Good night.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 21 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
-Morning.
You look nice.
-What?
-Dressed up for our date.
-It's cute, right?
-I've never seen that outfit before.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Shall we?
-It's raining.
-Oh, rain...
I'll drive.
-Please.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
-Yeah, let's go.
TSUKIJI MARKET
TSUKIJI HOSPITALITY WITH FINE CUISINE!
Welcome!
-Come on in!
-We have great prices!
-Look at all this.
-They're super fresh.
-Isn't this exciting?
-Totally.
-That melon is such high quality.
-Cool!
-I want some.
-We'll get some later.
-Are you having a good time?
-I am.
There are so many things here.
That looks so good!
-Thank you.
It's hot, but so good. Yum!
So good.
TSUKIJI SEAFOOD-DON
MARUKITA
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
-When's your first day of work?
-What?
-When's your first day?
-Saturday.
You'll finally be working.
-Are you nervous?
-Yeah.
Wow, this is amazing.
-Wow! Prawns!
-This is seriously amazing.
-Fresh prawns.
-Yum.
-It's delicious.
-So good.
Now that you've seen
so many ingredients...
have you been inspired
for what you want to cook?
Totally. I'm super excited.
You were intense.
-Was I too excited?
-Totally.
-But isn't it amazing?
-You were engrossed in your own world.
Oh, really?
You can totally join in.
Thanks, but no thanks.
You know, the other housemates...
like, the other girls...
do you go out with them?
-Should I?
-What?
Do you want me to?
I was just wondering if you were going to.
I'm not really planning on it.
-But I did make hamburgers with Misaki.
-How was it?
-Hmm?
-Did you chat?
Yeah, sure.
-Excuse me. That'll be 5,000 yen.
-Yes.
-I've got exact change. Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
It was delicious.
-Shall we?
-Let's.
Off to find more ingredients.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
I'll make it like an assortment here.
JUNTA ISHIKAWA
OWNER AND CHEF
-It should be set up individually tonight.
-Got it.
-I went to Tsukiji this morning.
-With how many others?
-It was a date.
-Really?
-Did you hold hands?
-No.
-Not yet--
-Is that really a date?
-Or is just more like lunch?
-I'm not sure.
-I wouldn't really call it a date.
-Really?
-When's the next time you're going out?
-Don't know yet.
We didn't make more plans
the last time either.
-You're a bit of a shy boy, aren't you?
-You think so?
Dates aren't a big deal.
You're way too nervous.
So... I asked him.
I asked him about you guys...
and whether he wants
to go out with either of you.
I don't know what he's thinking.
I think he totally just wants you
right now, so...
I totally agree.
-He never asked either of us out.
-Yeah, exactly!
But you cooked with him.
I didn't know much about him then.
Also, I asked him to help.
I see.
-It's Hansan.
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
-Having girl talk, are we?
-Are you tired?
-Hmm?
-No, not at all!
-Liar.
-He's exhausted.
-He really is.
-It's this Sunday, isn't it?
-That's right. It's so soon.
-Yeah.
-It's in two days.
Yeah, I've already set everything up.
What is it for again?
It's called a graduation design.
I have to design an architectural piece
in order to graduate.
To graduate from university?
Yes, every architecture university
does it.
Two students from each university in Tokyo
get chosen for this.
And you're one of them?
Yeah, from the University of the Arts.
-That's amazing!
-Thanks.
It's a competition
that takes place in Tokyo.
The piece that we designed
is being assessed right now.
So I have to do a presentation for that.
So if you win in that competition,
the next step is national?
Exactly. I'll kind of be competing
at a national level.
-I'll come if I can.
-Great.
-I wanna come, too.
-It's super small.
-Riko and Hayato went to Tsukiji today.
-Oh, you finally went!
-Today?
-Yeah, we did.
-It was raining.
-Yeah, it was.
It was so crowded too.
Weather was bad,
and there were lots of people...
but?
It was fun.
I see.
I'm happy for you.
I want a new bathing suit.
Yeah, me too.
I need to get one.
The grey one's cute.
I always end up wearing black.
-Yes?
-May I come in?
-Wow.
-Did you change your hair?
-Yeah, I went on a date today.
-Oh, I see.
-I get it.
-Can I sit here?
-How about over there?
-There?
- Yup.
-You're too close.
-Okay.
Did you say "You're too close"?
I came to ask Riko out again.
-What?
-What will you do?
-It's all right.
-What? Why? No!
-What?
-Hmm?
-Don't ask me!
-I can't?
It's summer.
Let's go somewhere.
Is that okay?
-Yeah, okay.
-Really?
The lady has spoken. Goodbye!
All right, I'll think of some place to go.
Okay, let's talk about it.
All right then. See you later.
-Bye.
-What's the matter?
-Hmm?
Riko?
Does that mean he had a good time today?
-Of course.
-That's why he asked.
Are you happy?
Yeah, I'm happy.
Have fun!
-Riko totally panicked.
-Totally.
It's been a while
since a couple has formed.
-I know!
-How nice.
-Agreed.
-They're practically together.
-You think so?
Do you think they might be
together by the end of the week?
It's up to Hayato now.
It depends on how things go
when Hayato acts more masculine,
-and how Riko reacts.
-I see, I see.
Will Riko reject Hayato
when he shows his masculine side?
Or is she going to be able to accept him?
I feel like she might be scared
if he comes onto her with hungry eyes.
And let's not forget,
Hansan is super cool this episode.
Yes, Hansan!
When he got home,
everyone could see how tired he was.
-He pulled an all-nighter.
-Exactly. "Are you tired?"
"No, not at all!"
The way he stretched out on the couch...
If I were his girlfriend,
I'd want to squeeze him!
-He's so cute!
-Right?
I'd cook everything I know for him.
And then Riko said, "But it was raining,
and it was crowded..."
And as he listens...
"It was raining, it was crowded... but?"
Yeah, the "but"!
The way he said that was so cute!
I'd strip his pants off right there!
Time out!
-Mommy went crazy.
-He's just too cute.
-No, you can't.
-But I just cooked him a fabulous meal.
Hey, that has nothing to do with it.
She's dangerous!
TAMACHI, TOKYO
SHIBAURA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY
TOKYO STUDENTS
GRADUATION DESIGN CONTEST 2016
There he is!
-Hey.
-Where? Oh, Hansan!
Thanks you guys for coming.
This is it right here.
What is it exactly?
My design is for building facilities
for physically disabled people.
You see this model right here?
It's Harajuku at 1/500 scale.
It's at the end of Cat Street.
There actually are facilities
for physically disabled people there.
My design is a reconstructive idea.
I'm suggesting to open these up
to the public.
-You don't usually visit them, right?
-No.
I've proposed an idea to open these up.
There are going to be
nice fashion stores in these spaces.
-Oh, that's cool.
-You see?
Because these facilities will allow people
from the inside and outside to mingle.
When you think about creating
a new Harajuku,
I think facilities like this one
are necessary.
That's my idea.
-You came up with this?
-I did.
-I didn't end up winning, unfortunately.
-Oh, no!
Anyways, everything I've done as a student
has culminated in today.
I see.
-Good job!
Really good job.
It'd be awesome if they build
something like this in Harajuku.
I'd brag about you.
Just you wait.
Someday my designs will be out there.
What do I do if I screw this up?
I've never made it before.
-I'm sure Hansan will laugh it off.
-True.
-Wow, awesome!
-Does this look right?
-Paella is supposed to be dry, right?
-Yeah.
-I'm home.
-Welcome home!
What's this?
It's for you.
Hayato made these, didn't he?
Right?
-Wow! Really?
-We did.
That's amazing.
-Want a beer?
-Yeah.
Wow, thanks!
"Good job, Hansan."
Misaki did all that.
Thank you.
I can't guarantee that it tastes good.
This is great.
It smells so good.
Delicious.
-Really?
-Yay, Riko!
-Thanks! Have as much as you like.
-What is it?
Takikomi rice?
Wait, what's it supposed to be?
It's delicious.
-Well...
-This is actually paella.
Oh, seriously?
Sorry, I didn't mean to offend you.
No worries.
From now on, this is takikomi rice.
Have you cleared everything up
at the contest?
Yup. I wasn't able to wow them though.
-What?
-The judges.
Right.
But to us, you're number one.
Yup.
Thanks, guys.
Sometimes doing my best is not enough.
I have to get credited somehow.
That's the only way in architecture.
You won't get paid
unless you're number one.
Because there's only going to be
one building.
So I've got to be number one.
Someday... I will be.
You will be.
What's next for you?
Well, I should put everything together
into a portfolio...
-and prepare to study abroad.
-Okay.
Will you be going to university abroad?
-Grad school.
-Right.
Well, I'm glad we were able to do this
for you tonight.
Yeah, I really appreciate it.
-You always work so hard.
-Exactly.
Thank you.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
Thank you!
PICK UP HERE!
Here you go.
-Thank you very much.
-How was it?
-I was more nervous than I thought I'd be.
Just remember, smile and be cheerful.
YASUHA ITO
MANAGER
Also, speak a bit louder.
Okay.
-If you do that, you're good.
-Okay.
And how are things lately?
-At Terrace House?
-Yeah.
Are you having fun?
Yeah, I am.
Does everyone get along?
In the past, some previous members
had fights.
But there aren't any right now.
How's your love life?
Well, I went on two dates with a guy.
Oh, yeah?
I like him,
but I don't know if I like-like him yet.
Well... he's 11 years older.
Hey, that's cool.
What do you think about that?
-I'm totally okay with it.
-Really?
Take my parents, for example.
My dad's 11 years older
than my mom.
Wow, really?
-I think it's more common now.
-You think so?
That changes things for me.
Is he cute?
I think he is.
So you don't know if you like him yet,
but are you willing to give it a chance?
I think so.
He asked me out for a third date.
-I'm definitely nervous.
-Aw, I'm jealous!
Oh, hey, Hansan.
What are you doing?
I'm making marinated peppers.
-A pepper?
-Marinated pepper.
A friend of mine runs
a barbecue restaurant.
-He asked me to think of an appetizer.
-Oh, cool.
-Aren't you drinking tonight?
-Once I'm done, I will.
-I need to submit a quote today.
-Oh, I see.
I'd love for you to help
with the interior design
-once I have my own restaurant.
-Totally.
Your future restaurant, right?
A pasta specialty restaurant?
Yeah, exactly.
You wanted the interior
to look like a burger joint.
-That's what you said, right?
-Yup.
And also to have the feel of a resort.
That's cool. It'd be fun to design it
because you don't see anything like it.
Exactly.
-Welcome home.
-Thanks.
-What are you doing?
-I'm browning the pepper.
-I'm not playing.
-It looks like it.
Well, I'm not.
-Are you working, Hansan?
-Yes.
I only have about 40 minutes
until I have to send it in.
I'm pretty screwed.
-You are.
-That thing you're working on now?
I'm gonna have to seriously tackle this.
-Good luck.
-I've got 42 minutes.
-Come get me when the peppers are done.
-Okay.
-So...
-Yeah?
-About our date.
-Uh-huh.
-I thought about it, and I googled it too.
-Cool, thanks.
The thing is,
I don't know much about dates.
So I couldn't figure out
a good place to go.
So I'm a little stuck.
I see.
Out of curiosity, what did you search?
Just...
-I just googled "date."
-That's good.
-And what did you find?
-There were too many things.
I'm totally confused.
So what should we do?
What did we decide
with regards to Yokohama?
-What?
-Yokohama.
Remember when we first talked
about Yokohama?
What about Yokohama?
What's in Yokohama anyway?
The Cupnoodles Museum.
That sounds like fun.
You get to make your own
cup noodles there.
And... you get to eat it?
-You can have it.
-Cool!
So, let's say we go to the museum.
We go to the Cupnoodles Museum
and that's it?
There's Chinatown.
-What do you think?
-The museum sounds fun.
Would you have fun though?
Of course I would.
Let's go there.
There are other things to do there.
-Other places to go?
-Yeah.
Let's think about all the other things
we can do in Yokohama.
Deal.
Okay? There might be some.
This totally works.
Easy-peasy.
Yeah, it looks cleaner.
Totally.
-Let's take a break.
-Sure.
-Cleaning adjourned.
-Cheers.
It's too hot.
I'm going under the shade.
I'm moving out tomorrow.
-You're kidding!
-No way.
You're not serious, are you?
-Seriously?
-Yeah, I'm moving out tomorrow morning.
Why?
Remember the other day...
at my presentation?
It really felt like it was
the end of a chapter,
and that a new chapter's beginning.
So from now on,
I'm my own person.
Both for my career and other challenges,
like studying abroad.
I want to thank you both for everything.
I thought about letting you know sooner...
but I didn't want things to be depressing.
I don't like this.
-Don't cry.
-Please don't go.
-I'll come visit Hawaii with Hikaru.
-You should.
-I will.
-Me too.
You should.
I'm sure you already know this, Arman.
I'm sure I don't have to say this.
Stay the way you are.
Thanks.
I think your true calling
isn't to become a firefighter.
I think it's to stay happy,
just as you are now.
Stay that way.
Live life as the happy man that you are.
I think that would be awesome.
-It's not a title you're after.
-I guess.
Change of plans.
My dream job: Happy.
I think that's cool. Really.
I've learned a lot during my time here.
All right then.
I'm gonna do it.
Do it.
Yeah, do it.
Why is everyone so quiet?
So he's leaving.
Give it a second.
The women are all too shocked to comment.
Are you okay?
What's the matter with everyone?
Seriously!
That's not good.
Why?
This isn't the first time
someone's leaving.
It's called Han Loss.
What's Han Loss?
Did you see Tamosan
genuinely not wanting him to go?
A single tear ran down her cheek
as she said "Please don't go."
He's a legend!
That was intense.
I've never seen anything like that
in real life.
Seriously!
I can't believe
there's actually a man like him.
I seriously don't want him to go.
Oh, right. I should just go with him.
Come again?
That was close, Tokui.
Yeah, she had a deranged
look on her face.
-Remember that bit about Arman's dreams?
-Yeah.
-I thought someone wrote a script.
-Seriously.
He said some really good stuff there.
"You're happy, not a firefighter."
-Yeah, but...
-I wanna say something like that.
What is it?
I'm talking here!
I'm sorry.
You're scaring me.
-Yu isn't usually like that.
-I know, right?
I've never said anything like that before.
-He was perfect from beginning to end.
-He was amazing.
-He hasn't made one mistake.
-Not one! That's perfection, right there.
So next up must be when he's leaving.
He's leaving!
Oh, no, that's right.
-Our last Han.
-Let's see our last Han.
-Wait a second.
-Let's see how he'll part from everyone.
Let me make one thing clear.
Don't talk.
Wow, that was cool.
Before we start eating,
I have an announcement to make
to you three.
I'm leaving Terrace House tomorrow.
Seriously? I'm still cooking.
I'm no longer a student.
I have to start working.
-I don't want you to.
-Sorry.
But...
It's okay. I'll leave quietly tomorrow.
Let's eat.
Let's eat!
-Let's try not to be sad and eat.
-Agreed.
-Thanks, guys.
-Let's just eat.
This feels like
a very cheerful goodbye party.
Right?
We decided to send him off happy.
Riko, take those dumplings.
Sure.
Thanks, guys.
-Those look amazing!
-Oh, yeah!
-Hansan balanced this group out.
-I know, right?
You brought this group together.
It's hard to not be sad.
This is the universe telling us
to be stronger.
-We've all been relying on you.
-Yeah.
All of us.
You girls are like sisters to me.
All of you.
Take care of them for me, will you?
Wait a minute.
Well, if you girls ever want to talk...
come to me.
-He's pretty...
-Unreliable?
No, he's pretty good.
Don't underestimate him.
Is there anything you want to do
before you leave?
Do I?
-Let's do something.
-Good idea.
It's so cold. For real.
I didn't think I was going to end up
in this pool again.
So thanks, I guess?
-Oh, yeah?
-Get in there.
-Is it really cold?
-Actually, it's not bad.
-Are you sure?
-I'm coming in!
Ready, set, go!
It's so cold.
-Is it really cold?
-What are you doing over there?
-No, please!
-Come on!
This is scary to watch.
-Goodbye party's over!
-Really?
-Morning.
-Hey, good morning.
Hansan...
-You're cleaning.
-Yeah.
You don't have to!
-I'm sorry we were up late last night.
-No worries at all.
There's a ballet competition this month.
I'm going to get into the top three.
I'll be rooting for you,
Momoka Mitsunaga, 21 years old.
-Okay.
-Stay happy, like Arman.
See you later.
-Okay, I'm gonna go now.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, too.
-See you.
-You're gonna carry all that?
-I've accumulated a lot.
I remember that bag.
Oh, this? The grass bag?
It's literally a grass bag.
-Hansan, here.
-What?
We made it together.
When did you do that?
Really?
Thanks.
Thank you.
I'm going to treasure this.
Don't make me cry, guys.
I have to leave now!
Sorry.
I promise you that...
one day you'll hear about me
as an architect somewhere.
Watch me.
-Watch me, okay?
-We will.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
I'm leaving now.
-All right then!
-Thank you!
See you around, Hansan.
Okay, see you around!
That was so anti-climactic.
He's gone.
He really is.
-There's no one to lead us now.
-True.
Are we gonna fall apart now?
What?
-Already? Isn't it too soon?
-Seriously?
Wow, my heart stopped just now.
What is it?
Seriously, it's too soon!
What should I say?
-Arman, Arman!
-Yes?
I'm moving in today.
Come in.
-What's happening?
-Hey, there.
You were bawling your eyes out
when Hansan was crying.
I was like, "How much can she cry?"
Yu, seriously?
-She's bawling.
-Really?
She's bawling.
I never met the guy,
and I'm absolutely smitten by him.
She said it.
You know how alumni sometimes come back
in later episodes?
Like, "Let's ask Hansan
if we need his help" type of thing.
Like, "Ask Kojimasan."
That's a good idea.
Why do we have to console you?