-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
-Let's see, last week...
-That's right.
-An unexpected man came in.
-Yes.
-Yuto Handa
-Handa.
You sound like women in love.
Yuto Handa.
She's using her narrating voice.
I'm in the architecture department
at the Tokyo University of the Arts.
I'm studying architecture.
I'm 27, trying to become an architect.
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD
-He's older!
-You seem happy.
-You're super happy.
Twenty-seven years old,
studying architecture
at the Tokyo University of the Arts,
and aiming for Harvard Graduate School.
Even his name, Yuto Handa...
If his last name had been more...
If it had been something really cool...
it may have been a little annoying.
But it's Handa.
The coolness of "Yuto"
is offset by "Handa."
-Yes, well-balanced.
-It keeps things in check.
-Keeps it from being too much.
-It's kept in check.
He seems invincible.
He's invincible, but there is one concern.
He has a girlfriend.
He came to Terrace House despite that.
Of course he has one.
And the way he was sawing the wood...
He's got a manly side to him as well.
That's what's nice about him.
What are you thinking about?
What are you thinking about over there?
When they were on the sofa,
he'd lightly throw in some teasing
into the conversation.
That was so nice.
How long have you been together
with your girlfriend?
This is the second time you've asked,
but two and a half years.
He's so mature.
The way he answered that.
It seems that Natsumi may have a crush
on Mr. Handa.
It doesn't matter if he has a girlfriend.
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD
If I fall for him, that is.
-Seriously?
-It doesn't matter at all.
It doesn't matter to her
whether or not he has a girlfriend.
She did say that.
We feel the same way over here.
Maybe we can have a new rule.
If we find someone we like,
we can crash the house.
The new crashing rule.
What do you think?
-I like it.
-Only once per person.
-I love it.
We keep talking about Handa,
but other things happened.
Oh, like Hikaru and Tamori...
-Right, Misaki.
-They have a motorcycle date.
It can be anywhere.
Far or close.
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD
-It's easier when it's up to me.
-Really?
I can do whatever I want, right?
That's right.
What's going to happen this week?
Is it just going to be
Handa's one-man show?
Is there any part for Arman to play?
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
-Probably not.
-I wonder...
Maybe No-man.
Will Arman be Yes-man or No-man?
-No-man.
-Good morning.
-No one's here today.
-Yeah.
Where's Nacchan?
She's... at an audition.
Oh, I see.
And Arisa's probably at work.
Yeah, I saw her this morning.
-What were you doing?
-I've been making problems.
-Problems?
-For the prep school.
Prep school?
You do that too?
I teach at a prep school.
-No way!
-Yeah.
-Did you eat already?
-I did.
-What did you eat?
-I had an egg sandwich.
-You're not hungry anymore?
-Maybe for lunch.
I ate this morning.
Do you want to grab a bite then?
Sure. Shall we?
Nice. What do you want to eat?
-A hamburger.
-A hamburger?
-Okay. Yeah.
-It's okay?
You know it's yakiniku night?
Should we not do yakiniku for dinner then?
That would upset Hikaru.
SHIBA, TOKYO
How are the guys?
The guys are easy to get along with.
-It's nice.
-You like them?
-Yeah.
-What about Arman?
Every time I have to do something,
he offers to help.
"Just let me know," he says.
-That sounds like him.
-He's always offering to help.
-And Hikaru?
-He's a rascal.
-A rascal?
-He's spirited.
He acts all mature in front of us, though.
Yeah, I can see that.
I thought he was just a kid at first.
Has Hikaru said anything about me?
Hikaru? Yeah.
He did?
He said he asked you on a date.
I kind of don't understand why.
So you don't mind the age difference?
I don't mind at all.
But...
I'm probably not Hikaru's type.
-I wonder what type of girl Hikaru likes.
-Well...
he said someone mature and patient.
-I'm the complete opposite.
-Are you?
I'm not patient...
and I'm not mature.
I don't know, but...
-Didn't he say he liked Arisa?
-Yeah.
What happened with that?
I don't know.
I saw that on TV, too.
He said Arisa was cute.
And even now...
he still steals glances at Arisa.
It's bothering you.
Maybe he likes her.
So that's why...
I was wondering what he's thinking.
EBISU, TOKYO
YAKINIKU TORAJI
It's a welcome dinner for the two of you,
so order whatever you want.
Nice.
-I want liver.
-No.
You'll get some color back.
-I'll get my color back.
-You'll look healthier.
-Did you all come from home?
-Yeah.
-Hikaru too?
-Yeah, I did.
-Was it raining?
-No.
It was. Don't lie.
When I came, it wasn't raining.
Sorry.
-That sounded mean.
-Seriously?
-You were definitely mad just now.
-I wasn't!
Why do you guys think
I'm mad all the time?
They say guys are mean to girls they like.
-Really?
-That's in elementary school.
-That's only up to elementary school.
-That's true.
-Boys would make fun of girls they like.
-Yeah.
The two of you went out today, right?
Your girlfriend doesn't mind?
It's just lunch.
I'm sure it's fine.
-Does who you have lunch with matter?
-I don't think that matters.
More my...
my attitude and words.
How long have you been single, Tamosan?
About a year.
I do think about my ex from time to time.
And when I stop thinking about him,
he calls.
It's because it wasn't a clean break.
If you're going to break up,
you should break up.
Even if you start seeing someone else,
but if he's really meant for you,
I'm sure you'll get back together.
This middle ground, where you see him...
-You still see him?
-Only with other people.
You should tell him you're not over him
if you still like him.
But you can't help
keeping in touch sometimes.
-Yeah, even when I know I shouldn't.
-I totally understand.
-This is way too long.
-Yeah.
Bored?
I just felt like
the topic's gone on too long.
Do we even need to talk about this?
That makes me think you're immature.
-What?
-Nothing.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
-What's wrong?
-What do you mean?
-What?
-You're frustrated.
I'm not.
What about?
About Misaki, right?
Wow, straight to the point.
When Misaki said you're immature...
-Yeah.
-How'd it make you feel?
All that talk about her ex...
was that even necessary?
-You mean after you asked her out?
-Yeah.
I felt like...
Whatever, I didn't like it.
So you're attracted to her?
Yeah.
I guess that's what it means.
-Your attitude is a little rough.
-Whose?
-Mine?
-Yeah.
I'm the same as everyone else.
I was wondering
why the girls were picking on you.
-Did something happen?
-What do you mean?
They've been frequently asking you
if you're mad.
-Lately.
-Yeah.
Maybe it's the way I say it.
But when they keep asking if I'm mad
when I'm not, and I say I'm not,
then it seems like I really am.
Since you're roommates,
you should be nicer to them.
-We're living together, after all.
-Am I that cold?
-A little.
-I'm not mad...
Even to me, you seem a little cold.
Like you have an attitude.
Since we're living together,
I think it would be better
to not upset them.
Maybe this is strange for me to say...
but my sense of pride is probably strong.
I don't like being ridiculed.
I don't care if it's someone
I don't care about.
But when they are roommates...
I think that's part of it.
Nacchan and Misaki especially,
since I've been thinking about her...
When they say that,
I have a strong reaction.
He's immature.
-He was upset.
-It was uncalled for.
So when just the two of us go out,
what are we supposed to talk about?
And today, Hansan was so easy to talk to
when I had lunch with him.
That's right; you had lunch with him.
Especially after lunch with Hansan,
Hikaru's reaction from just a few words...
The difference between 18 and 27.
That little argument
about whether he's mad or not
did make me think he's young.
A little.
You liked him,
so what he said left a big impact?
I'm just surprised
it's bothering you so much.
It's easy for me to fall for someone
at first sight.
You mean from first impressions?
What do you like about Hikaru?
His face.
You're terrible!
You're kidding, right?
Seriously?
He's so hot!
I've never heard a girl blatantly say,
"I like his face."
-Arman is passable.
-Passable?
That's a little rude.
She liked him.
I like Arman's personality, of course!
If a guy had Hansan's personality
and Hikaru's face, he'd be perfect!
-So, Misaki likes Hikaru too.
-Yeah.
The two of them are attracted
to each other.
They match. They're just...
-I think so, too.
-Just clashing at the moment.
It's because he's attracted to Misaki
that he's sensitive to what she says.
Hansan's personality
and the face could be Hansan too, right?
-Yes!
-So, it's all Hansan then.
It's Hansan.
-Yes, Hansan.
-So it's Hansan.
Not just half, but the whole.
Does "Han" stand for half then?
-Yes, it should be the whole.
-Yes, the Whole Yuto.
Misaki would say,
if she got into an argument with Hikaru,
"If it were Hansan, he would have said--"
"Then why don't you go out with him?"
-Oh, so dramatic!
-Wouldn't you love to see that?
-It'd be so good.
-It'd be nice.
And then Hansan would say,
"Wait a sec, hold on."
-It'd be great.
-So cute.
It's like a stylish script.
It might happen.
It might.
It's a more modern take
on what happened with Seina.
SEINA SHIMABUKURO
It's more like Orange Days...
-That type--
-Nice.
That's true.
EBISU, TOKYO
MAISON COULEUR CATALOGUE SHOOT
I just added some color here.
If you want to add more,
we could use this color...
And by adding or not adding a highlight
around the eye,
-her expression can be changed.
-That's true.
Yes.
Morning.
-I took the day off.
-What?
-Let's go to the gym then.
Let's go later.
-Where's Han?
-I think he went to work.
He said he had an early day today.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
-Are you off today?
-I'm off today.
You're going to be home all day?
No, I'm thinking of going out
with Nacchan.
I think I'm gonna get coffee.
-Can you get me an iced latte?
-Sure.
-Arman, can I get--
-Do you want anything?
An iced latte, please.
I can't hold all of them.
I only have two hands.
Too bad.
-Oh, but you have to get it there.
-Yeah.
-Will you be able to hold it?
-I'll buy it if I can.
If you can, I'd appreciate it.
-It's fine. I already had one.
-Okay.
So I wanted to apologize about yesterday.
-Yeah.
-When we went out for yakiniku...
Yeah.
When you were talking,
I interrupted
and said the topic was pointless.
Sorry about that.
It was a little uncalled for.
I was wondering what would make you say
something like that.
I was just...
I don't know.
I'm attracted to you.
-That caught me off-guard!
-Yeah, and...
Hearing you say
you want to get back with your ex...
Well, not get back together...
That I think about him?
For me, that was a little...
Like, "What?"
I didn't like it.
I didn't want to hear it.
I realize that was immature of me.
But I didn't want to hear it
and tried to end the conversation.
-I see.
-Yeah.
For that...
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I understand.
-I'm glad to hear it.
-Yeah.
And you frequently ask if I'm mad.
I'm really not,
but maybe my tone is rough.
-Yeah.
-I'll work on that too.
I'll try to be gentler.
-That's right.
-To everyone else and Nacchan too.
Okay.
Hey.
-Good morning.
-He apologized.
-What?
What'd he say?
Out of the blue?
I was about to ask him about it,
but he said it first.
-Like, "I've got something to say"?
-Yeah, like, "Sorry about yesterday."
And he said he's attracted to me.
-Really?
-He said he was attracted--
-What?
-He said he was attracted to me.
And because of that,
he was annoyed I was talking about my ex.
And...
that's why he said
the topic was pointless.
So that was it?
Yeah, so that's what happened.
For real?
Crazy!
You must be ecstatic.
It did make me happy.
Yesterday's concern is all forgotten.
You know, yesterday
I said I only liked his face.
But he really thought things over
and apologized.
Talking with him made me think
he's a good guy.
So quick!
-So you're going on a date with him?
-Yeah, I am.
-Of course.
-Of course I'm going.
Being in a couple.
That was quick.
We don't know what'll happen.
I don't know...
-And tomorrow is Hikaru's birthday, right?
-Yeah, the first.
You have to get a gift.
-Let's all get one together.
-What?
Hansan left a note.
"Tomorrow is Hikaru's birthday.
What should we do?
I'm going to pick up a gift
on my way home.
If you could prepare something,
that'd be great."
-I see.
-When did he come in?
-Isn't that scary?
-Yeah, scary.
I'm sure he took something.
You're so quick to suspect people.
-Shall we get something then?
-Yeah.
-Let's go look.
Hansan, can I interrupt?
-Sure.
-Oh, are you doing homework?
-Homework? I guess it's homework.
-It's not homework?
It's for school.
My final project.
I met with the interior designers,
but I couldn't decide on anything.
I wanted to make the display from scratch,
but I don't know if there's enough time.
-Let's make it.
-Is there enough time?
I designed a really efficient system.
It's strong, inexpensive and stylish.
-It's all those things?
-Yeah, and it's about 600 yen for one.
It's this big
and strong enough to hold a person.
About 600 yen for one.
-What's the material?
-Steel.
I think it's possible
because I've got a worker named Arman.
That's true.
Here, it's a little cut off, but...
Here, it's a net supporting concrete.
The bottom portion, not the top.
-It's like thick steel wire?
-Yes!
It's like a thick steel wire.
I'll draw it.
It's like a net.
I love nets.
You're free to paint it any color,
if you want color.
What I want to know is
what's the best angle to display a hat?
I want it to be seen from various angles.
Kind of like this.
This is a little low, but...
So a stack of these?
Or creating height with those nets.
I like how you could change the height.
If you decide on the placement,
I can make it.
I'll give you a visual, a 3D model.
Amazing.
-This is exciting.
-No way.
I'm so stressed about time.
The most interesting results
come from challenges.
-Do they?
-Definitely.
Don't worry.
It'll definitely succeed.
That's encouraging.
"The most interesting results
come from challenges."
-Wow!
-This is terrible!
Who wants to crash?
Anyone?
-This is...
-Damn it!
Amazing Professor Handa.
That line...
needs to be written and framed.
I'm going to use it starting tomorrow.
Like, to my son, "Don't worry."
"It'll definitely turn out interesting."
The line could've easily been like,
"Don't worry. I'll take care of it."
But Professor Handa says it lightly
and even says it'll be fun for him.
-Yeah.
-Girls love that sort of thing.
And he was staring at his screen,
looking at his own work while explaining.
And he said very naturally,
"This'll definitely be fun."
He said it while looking at the screen.
If he was at all interested in Arisa,
I think he would have said it
while looking at her.
Someone with an ulterior motive
would've done that.
But he said it while working.
He's so hot.
That's true.
If he had said, "It'll definitely be fun,"
like that, it would've been shady.
But he was staring at his PC.
And Arisa was staring at him
staring at his PC.
-This was even more...
-That's exactly right.
-It was well done.
-He's so hot!
It's too late for Arisa.
She can't cut in.
Yeah!
But Arisa and Professor Handa,
they have the creator thing in common.
Too good to be true.
This is just to showcase
the greatness of Hansan.
-That's not true.
-No, it's not.
Are you forgetting about Arman today?
-Was he on?
-Yes, he was.
Hikaru's and Misaki's story
is about to start.
-It was cute.
-They were cute!
-They make a nice couple.
Like during the meat incident,
Hikaru is young, but he's able to honestly
admit and apologize for his mistakes.
It's healthy!
-It really is.
-So healthy!
Organic.
-It really is.
-Yeah.
Is there such a thing
as being organically in love?
He's organic.
As you grow older,
additives get incorporated.
-That's right.
-I see.
We turn fluorescent.
Slowly.
-A color that can't be consumed.
-That's right.
We get used to the strange color.
-Is that what happens?
-That's what happens.
-Wait, you didn't hear?
-What?
What?
What? Did something happen?
-Nothing.
-What?
-She likes Hikaru.
-"Likes"?
-I didn't know.
-Not "likes"!
-You didn't know?
-I didn't.
Starting last night at around 11:55 p.m.,
she'd say,
"Oh, it's almost Hikaru's birthday!
Almost...
Oh, it's his birthday! Happy birthday!"
To herself.
How cute!
He's just going to play me and it'll end.
Why? He said he was attracted to you, too.
-They totally message each other.
-Oh, really?
With voice messages.
-They send each other voice messages.
-For real?
It's already started then.
-It started?
-It started.
-When are you going to get together?
-It hasn't started yet.
-Aren't you guys going out soon?
-Oh, yeah.
He didn't say when.
He's probably going
to make it official then.
That was so quick.
Hikaru and Misaki.
Well, I've been watching the show.
That's right.
You were interested in him to begin with.
Really?
Like, "Hikaru's so cute!" kind of thing?
I did think he was good looking.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
That's so cute.
I'm back.
-Did Hansan do this?
-Makes you question his style, right?
How is it?
Wow.
-Amazing, right?
-Amazing.
-I thought of it.
-You thought of it?
Hikaru doesn't like whip cream, right?
-Or sweets.
-That's right.
Yeah.
Let's say "happy birthday"
when he arrives.
-Happy birthday.
-Are we okay here?
-This is exciting.
-When it opens.
Oh, I think he's home.
-Happy birthday!
I'm so surprised.
Sit, sit!
-Cheers!
-Please sit.
Happy birthday!
-Bon appétit!
-Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Is this because I don't like sweets?
-It was Misaki's idea.
-Thanks.
Thanks, I was so hungry.
Delicious.
The sushi cake was a nice idea.
Thank you.
-Why are you laughing?
-It's nothing special.
-How cute!
-Don't play it down.
It's just to throw on...
Explain it to him, explain it to him.
-I went shopping with her.
-So it helps you relax, right?
-Supposedly.
-That thing works.
She was like, "What would Hikaru like?
It's his birthday. Happy birthday."
The entire time to herself.
I didn't say happy birthday.
-You were saying it the whole time!
-She was doing that?
-Thank you.
-I wrote details in the card.
I'll use it.
Should I read the card now or later?
Whenever.
-Nice.
-So I can read it now?
If it were me, I'd read it out loud.
Why? That's so embarrassing!
I'm just saying if it were me.
Happy birthday.
Why don't you read it to him?
-No way!
-Nice.
There are shows like that.
There are shows like that?
No, I'm going to turn red.
It's just normal stuff.
Wait. Hold on.
"Dear Hikaru,
Happy birthday.
-Happy birthday."
-This is really embarrassing.
"Yay!
Please use the roller
to roll away your daily stress.
I'm sorry for saying you're immature.
I'm really happy to have met you
and everyone at Terrace House.
I'm looking forward to my time here.
Happy birthday!
From Misaki."
Thank you.
Oh, man.
Thank you so much.
Seriously, thanks everyone.
-Happy birthday.
-I'll treasure it.
Happy birthday!