-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Last week, Minori and Tatsuya
became a couple.
Congratulations.
-There was also a goodbye kiss.
-The kiss was nice.
You're not gonna kiss me goodbye?
-You want me to?
-I do.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
I want to see them fight.
-Me too.
-A lovey-dovey fight.
And "I'm sorry" written on omu-rice after.
Cute!
That's so cute!
Why are they communicating by omu-rice?
It's like a bulletin board.
There were happy moments,
but not all of them were.
The development
of Arman and Arisa's relationship.
Maybe everyone's ditching.
-No, they're not!
-They must be ditching.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
Okay.
-We made it?
-We made it.
Holding hands, feeding him bento...
It's as if Arisa likes Arman.
-What? She does.
-She does.
That hasn't been decided yet.
Wait, did you not see them holding hands?
-Didn't you see it last week?
-I did.
Arisa seemed really surprised.
"Oh, he's holding my hand."
What? No, they were swinging their arms.
Arman started that.
If she resisted, she'd hurt her arm.
-I don't think that would happen.
-That's not quite...
So I don't think it's decided yet.
You're not the only one who thinks that.
-Mizuki is probably thinking that, too.
-That's right.
-Arman, let's go out to eat sometime.
-Sure.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
It's set then.
"I'm always supporting
other people's relationships,"
is probably what she's thinking.
Inside.
"Are you okay with that?"
She asks herself in the mirror.
"Are you okay with that Mizuki?"
That's how it is.
So, thankfully, the time at Terrace House,
-has been extended, right?
-Yes, it's been extended.
But I'm sure
they're feeling the pressure of time.
So I'm sure
the attacks will be more aggressive.
-That's true.
-It'll be aggressive.
A complete love triangle.
The ring of love is a triangle.
Read all of Mr. Tokui's works
published for Margaret.
-So, abstinence...
-Abstinence.
-I can't drink for the next three weeks.
-No way!
-Until the match?
-Yeah.
I'm so sad.
Well, good luck preparing for the match.
Last day!
Here she is. We're drinking.
-Drinking?
-We are.
Cheers. Is this your last day
for drinks, Arman?
Yeah, last day.
Did you go hiking?
Oh, yeah, how was it?
And the bento?
-Yeah, thanks.
-Oh, you made an bento?
Arisa made it the night before.
It was super cute.
You did that?
It's the first time
someone made me an bento.
Really?
-Was it good?
-It was. It had spam musubi.
Lucky.
What are you doing Tuesday or Wednesday
next week?
-Arisa?
-Me?
I'm working Tuesday and Wednesday.
But I finish early I think.
Around 7:00 p.m.
If the timing works out,
let's go grab a bite or something.
A bite?
You should ask more clearly.
-It was a little vague.
-I see.
Let's drink. Should I bring more?
-There's no ice.
-I'll go buy some.
I can't believe we're out of ice.
I'll be right back.
-You okay by yourself?
-Yeah.
-I'll go with you, Arman.
-Thanks.
How was it yesterday?
It was fun.
And then?
Same as usual?
We held hands.
What?
We said, "Let's hold hands
until the summit."
What? From the start?
No, just before the summit,
and then we said, "We made it!"
To celebrate reaching the summit, I guess.
-And after?
-After?
He apologized for his sweaty hands.
So I said I'm sorry for my dry hands.
You're laughing.
What about Yuki?
-Yuki?
-Yuki.
You're having dinner with him, right?
Dinner?
Just the two of us?
I think he wants to.
-The two of us...
-I think so.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
Babachan has come around.
This is the important part.
-Oh, he said he liked her.
-He did?
He said he liked Minori...
-This is embarrassing.
-I know.
Why are you watching that specific part?
It just happened by accident.
Is it work?
-I'm going to an exhibition.
-I see.
-I'm hungry.
-You're hungry?
-I'm hungry, too.
-Minori, I'm hungry.
-What would you like?
Anything.
-You can make it with whatever we have.
-Okay.
You totally think it's a hassle.
Not at all.
It's ready!
Is it any good?
-Let me try a bite.
-Okay.
It's okay?
It's a mish-mash.
A complete mish-mash.
It's delicious.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
Crepes. Maybe it's not that popular now.
But there's a really good crepe shop.
They have sweet crepes
and more savory ones.
-Like, for a meal?
-Like ones for breakfast.
It's really good when you wrap
your breakfast in a crepe.
Like sausages?
It's located in Kailua.
We said we were going shopping today,
-but it turned into a walk.
-Yeah.
-Let's go again sometime.
Bon appétit!
-Let's go eat crepes next time.
-Yeah, let's.
You're going to eat two, right?
-If we share, we can have two.
-Good idea.
But before that, I have to find a job.
It's already been a month.
Teaching English?
-Have other places...
-No, I haven't heard yet.
When are you going to dinner with Yuki?
-Tuesday.
-Tuesday?
Where are you going?
He messaged me earlier
saying he'll pick a place.
Are you going on a date with Mizuki?
We're going to dinner.
I don't know when.
-It hasn't been decided?
-No.
-Have you been here for a week now?
-Yeah, just over a week.
Is there anyone you're interested in?
Yeah.
I do, I think.
And you?
I do, too, I think.
There's someone.
Isn't that too much?
-Yeah, too much.
-It's green curry. That's spicy, right?
I was just curious.
What is this?
That was a conversation
between two people who like each other.
"Do you?" "Yes, I do."
"And you, Arman?" "Well, yeah."
"It's you."
Definitely an, "It's you."
It was like they were apologizing
for their other dates.
-Like they're obligated.
-Both of them.
Like, "You too? Me too."
It's terrible!
It's like,
"Then let's meet up afterwards."
That's right.
I'd hate it
if someone talked that way about me.
-Yeah, if you're on that end.
-Yeah, that's true.
I'm like Adachi, so I understand.
I invite people knowing
they might be thinking that way about me.
But what's important
is if you like them or not,
not what they think of you.
Exactly!
-A sound argument.
Arman... should find work.
-That's right.
-So true.
-It's about time.
-He hasn't passed any interviews yet.
He's an active bum.
That's true.
He's a very active bum from Hawaii.
Not anti-social, but anti-solitary.
-Like introducing a new style.
-Yes, like that.
Like an outgoing anti-social.
Isn't that just a normal person then?
We're all that.
We're all outgoing anti-socials.
SUGAMO, TOKYO
ITO TAKASHI
CEO OF TARGET
RAOUMARU
4TH PLACE ON RISE HEAVYWEIGHT RANKING
Hello.
I'm Arman.
It's nice to meet you.
Come in and change.
Thank you for seeing me.
Now jab.
Nice.
Do it hard.
Don't hold back.
Now knees.
Hit hard.
If you do it hard,
it'll show in the match.
Hard knee! Hard!
Hard!
Give it your all. Keep your guard up.
Give it everything.
More!
Three hooks.
Hard!
-Ten hard ones.
-Make it 15!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Now a hard one!
Harder!
Again!
-Okay, good.
-Thank you.
Okay.
Not bad.
-He's got stamina for an amateur.
-He does.
Thank you.
-Thank you for today.
-How was it?
-It was tough, but fun.
-Was it fun?
But watching you practice,
I think you'll be okay for the match.
-Really?
-If you continue this way.
In the match,
attack before you're attacked.
-If you're hit, hit back harder.
-Hit back harder.
You get hit once,
hit them back two or three times.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
-Come again.
Thanks again.
EBISU, TOKYO
Bon appétit.
-It's good.
-Delicious.
-Have you been in the car yet?
-Hmm? Yeah.
At the house?
The yellow one?
No, I can't drive that one.
The big one, right?
I haven't been in it either.
-You can drive?
-I can.
I've been wanting to take it out.
I haven't driven in it yet.
-Let's use it sometime.
-The car?
Everyone said they wanted to go to Costco.
-Costco?
-Yeah.
-Not Costco?
That wasn't a moment for Costco.
I was asking you out on a date.
A date?
-You brought in Costco.
-I see. I thought it was a Costco moment.
Well, that and I want to drive the car.
A day trip in the car, maybe.
Yeah.
Let's go somewhere.
Shall we go somewhere?
We do have a car after all.
Yeah. Exactly.
I'll think of where we can go
for a day trip.
-A day trip?
-Yeah, with the car.
-Let's drive somewhere.
-Not Costco?
Anywhere.
I want to go to Costco.
-You want to go to Costco?
-Yeah.
Errands?
-Minori said she wanted to go, too.
-Okay.
The popcorn's good there.
Is there any popcorn left?
There were about two left.
I haven't eaten any recently.
Where are you inviting her to?
Well, I haven't driven the car yet.
So I wanted to go somewhere with the car.
-On a date?
-Yeah.
-A day trip?
-Yeah, a day trip.
I've been looking up places.
And, well, this time of year
it'd be nice to see Christmas lights.
-When are you going?
-We haven't decided.
But we were talking,
and she didn't seem that excited.
She wasn't into it?
She was like,
"Let's go to Costco with everyone."
Oh, she changed topics?
Yeah, she threw in "everyone."
If she's not into it, then I'm...
Well, I don't know,
but if she's not interested,
she would say so.
-She would? That's true.
-She would.
You should just go for it.
Ask her out. Maybe just ask her now.
-Better not to have regrets.
-Yeah, I agree.
Do it! Go!
I'll go now.
Thanks.
I'm gonna do it.
Go do it.
That's set.
-Sequences.
-You love that.
I pass.
Pass.
Here.
I win.
-Really?
-I won.
-That's the card, right?
-Yeah, the card.
Let's use the full deck.
That's set.
Everyone wants to play.
Hey.
Can I talk to Arisa for a bit?
-Of course.
-Okay.
I'm stepping out, then.
-Wanna sit there?
-I'll sit there.
Sorry to interrupt the card game.
That's okay. I was losing.
I wanted to talk to you
because I didn't get to properly
ask you out earlier.
I wanted to go somewhere with you.
So I wanted to invite you.
-Not to Costco with everyone?
-No.
I said I wanted to take the car somewhere.
With just the two of us.
-The two of us?
-Yeah.
I see.
I don't mind if it's with everyone...
instead of going with just the two of us,
like a day trip.
I'd rather go somewhere with everyone.
-Right.
-Yeah.
Well, I'm sure it'll be fun with everyone.
What's wrong? You look down.
Of course.
-What happened?
-It was not good.
She said, "With everyone."
So that means no?
I guess she has feelings for Arman.
Either that or...
I wonder what it is.
Maybe she's not in relationship mode.
-But she did go with Arman.
-That's true.
-Right?
-She did go with Arman.
-That's right.
It just didn't work out.
Why did you decline before you went out?
Even if the two of us went out,
I just can't see Yuki
as someone I'd be attracted to.
And right now,
I have someone else I'm interested in.
So to go out with someone else...
-Feels like you're two-timing?
-I guess so.
OMOTESANDO, TOKYO
HAKATA
TREE OF NAGI
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Did you wait long?
-Not at all.
-Cheers!
Short hair looks good on you, Mizuki.
I cut it!
I said before I didn't like short hair.
That's right! You did say that.
-But it looks good on you. I like it.
-Yay!
Uchi?
-Yeah, Uchi.
-He's good.
-I was pretty worried though.
-It looks really good.
How are things going?
Not bad.
-Do you know who you're going to fight?
-I don't know.
You won't know until the day of?
Yeah. They weigh us the day before.
I'll know then.
Yesterday?
Did Arisa go with you yesterday, too?
Yeah, she did.
That's nice.
-Since she's a member now.
-Oh, a member.
-So Arisa kickboxes too?
-Yeah.
Wow, sounds fun. I see.
How was it?
You went to Mt. Takao for hiking, right?
Yeah, it was good.
That's good. Did you hear?
-What?
-About Yuki?
-I haven't heard.
-You haven't?
-Then maybe I shouldn't say.
-Why not?
Tell me.
It's probably good news for you.
-For me?
-Yeah.
To be honest, since Arisa came...
I've been attracted to her,
and we've gone out a few times.
You like her?
I think I'm starting to.
-Right now.
-That's great.
I'll be rooting for you.
Did she say she was coming on the 13th?
I asked her about it once.
-She seemed okay with it?
-She seemed okay.
You have to show her how cool you are.
-Yeah, I can't lose.
-No, you can't lose.
That's painful!
-She's going to root for them.
-She's going to support them.
She realizes he doesn't have feelings
for her anymore.
Arman said what he did because
he knew he had to convey that to her.
And Mizuki cut her hair
as if she already knew.
Oh, that's right.
"I already knew.
I'm rooting for you."
"Since I'll have to cut it sometime
in the near future."
-It's so deep!
-It's so sad!
I guess people still cut their hair
when love doesn't work out.
The feelings linger
in the ends of your hair.
-That's beautiful!
-That was beautiful.
-That's why women cut their hair.
-That's so cool.
What about Tap?
I feel so bad for him!
"Costco? With everyone?"
She said it three times.
He should get it.
Tap probably thought
Arisa was a Costco fanatic.
So he should've realized at that point?
I guess it was obvious
she didn't want to go.
At that point, yeah.
She repeated Costco
because he kept asking.
With everyone.
The spell to end things,
"Costco! Costco! Costco!
It's not working! Costco!"
That's what was happening.
Like the spell of destruction from Laputa.
Is that being nice though?
I found it really painful.
When he said,
"Let's go, just the two of us,"
she says,
"Um, Minori said she wanted to go, too."
Isn't that embarrassing?
That's probably the result
of trying not to hurt him.
Is that what it is?
When he suggested the day trip,
she said, "Day trip?"
Like it was the most horrible thing.
"Day trip" isn't usually repeated
so many times.
It's like she's solving a crime,
"Day trip?"
He's asking lightly,
but the question was heavy.
-Hey.
-Hello.
-Hello?
You're like an old man.
Nothing wrong with "hello."
-Welcome home.
-I'm back.
What are you going to do?
-The program is extended.
-Right.
Well, yeah...
-It doesn't end the 18th week.
-No.
We're in the losing group.
Losing group? Yeah.
We lost two battles in a row.
Two battles, two losses? Was it?
Maybe the last one wasn't really a battle.
Two tries, two losses... I guess.
We have one more month.
-And I wanted to stay until the end.
-Yeah.
But if it extends another three
or six months, then what'll you do?
Eighteen weeks for you?
You're going to leave after 18 weeks?
I might leave now.
Really?
The next step after Arisa, I guess.
Maybe it's time for me to move on.
-I've wanted to go overseas.
-You did say that.
And then after that,
I'll think about my future.
For me...
I didn't gain any insight
on what I want to work towards.
And it's not like I've reached that goal.
And I haven't found a boyfriend.
You know...
Yeah.
I am considering leaving.
I don't need to be cool...
and have some big reason to leave.
That's true.
I'm thinking that it's okay
to just say, "I had fun. I'm satisfied."