-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Not at all.
-Well, well, well... So last week...
-It's here.
It's here...
Ugly drama is back at Terrace House.
-Yuuki Byrnes has now joined.
-The new member is very handsome.
I'm a dancer.
-A dancer?
-Yes, a dancer.
What kind?
-The style is called Krumping.
-Krump?
Oh, like the band Exile?
I also model once in a while,
when I feel like it.
Now that Byrnes is here,
Terrace House is experiencing
the calm before the storm.
-That's right.
-Two couples were nicely paired up,
but now we've got a love triangle,
or even a love square.
-Maybe even a love hexagon.
-Yes.
I think Misaki...
is really pretty.
-Misaki also finds Byrnes attractive.
-Yes.
-But...
-Rikopin also finds Byrnes attractive.
He's her type. But since she's not his,
she's decided to sit on the sidelines
and observe for now.
She feels she's got the disadvantage.
He's tall and half-Japanese.
He's totally my type.
So he's perfect then!
Yeah.
But he...
seems to be into one of the other girls.
Really?
No, I'm not going to stop.
So you do like him.
I meant I'm not the type
to stop liking someone
just because a friend likes him too.
When Byrnes said to Misaki
that they should go somewhere...
She asked if it'll be the two of them,
as though she was testing him.
Did you see Rikopin's expression
when he said yes?
That was the face of a woman
about to make a move.
Let's go grab food when you're free.
Just the two of us? Or with everyone?
It could be either.
The question is
what Terashima's next move will be.
Is he gonna flounder?
Or will he be mature and quietly withdraw?
No way! It's the start of a new act,
starring Terashima.
-Oh, you mean in Yokohama?
-Yes, in Yokohama.
I wonder if there's gonna be
a Yokohama scene.
It's gonna be quite the show this week.
It's like Yokohama's a scary place now.
Something's gonna happen...
Nothing good has ever happened
in Yokohama on Terrace House.
-So true.
-I detect something foul.
NAKAMEGURO, TOKYO
Yuuki, can you grab the lid?
Thanks.
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD
'02 BEGINS DANCING
'03 JOINS ENTERTAINMENT INDUSTRY
'11 GRADUATES HIGH SCHOOL
'14 BEGINS WORKING AT GOLDEN BROWN
LAST RELATIONSHIP: ONE YEAR AGO
How are things going?
KIKUNO KURIHARA
CO-WORKER
-What do you mean?
-I mean at the house.
It's pretty fun.
-Have you made friends with the guys?
-Yeah.
Any cute girls?
Cute?
Yeah, actually.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
There's one girl...
Her name is Misaki.
I asked her out.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
-How old is she?
-She's the same age as me.
-Nice.
-Twenty-three.
Just for dinner?
Yeah, just for food.
What about a movie
or something beforehand?
Isn't that more of a date?
I hadn't thought of that.
I was just thinking if we go out to eat,
we could talk and get to know each other.
-That's a good start.
-Yeah.
I guess that's better
than trying to do a bunch of stuff.
SANGEN-JAYA, TOKYO
-Hey, were you waiting long?
-Not at all.
Really? Sorry I'm late.
-I'm so hungry.
-Yeah, me too.
What are we having?
Yakitori.
Yakitori? Yay! I love it.
TORIJIRO
What's good here?
I think everything is good here.
Right.
-Cheers!
Yum!
Yeah, a beer after work is the best.
-That's right, you had work today.
-Yeah, until 5:00 p.m.
Want some?
Thanks.
I don't usually do this for someone.
-Is this good?
-Yeah.
-I wanna talk about personal stuff today.
-Sure.
What type of guy do you like?
Someone who cares about others.
That's important.
I don't really have a type.
If I like someone, I just like him.
Even if I'm asked why,
I wouldn't have an answer.
-You wouldn't?
-If I like someone, I just like him.
What about at Terrace House?
Is there someone?
-There was.
-That's right.
Oh, that's right.
And now I don't like hot springs.
Why?
On our first date,
he mentioned he wanted to go
to the hot springs with me.
But later on, he said he didn't want to go
in the co-ed baths with me.
I see.
So now when I hear hot springs,
that's all I think of.
-I see.
-I've been traumatized by hot springs.
I was talking with Riko.
She asked me where we'd be going.
I told her Hakone.
But I wasn't thinking
of the hot springs there.
-I see.
-I didn't mean the hot springs.
I was thinking of taking you
to a great soba place there,
and taking the gondola up the mountain.
-My plan was to have a relaxing day.
-Sounds great.
But I thought
maybe I'd give the wrong idea.
That sounds great.
You can take me there next time.
Let's go after I get my license then.
When will that be?
-Next week, I'll pass the test for sure.
-Oh, that's right.
-Ride with me then.
-Okay, I will.
-Is it your first time?
-Yeah.
I drive safely, so don't worry.
You seem like a good driver.
Have you gotten over the guy you liked?
Oh yeah, totally.
We all get together as a group sometimes,
but I'm fine.
Honestly!
I think of it as a good experience.
-I was initially attracted to his looks.
-His looks?
Yeah, he was really good looking.
What did he look like?
I guess it'd be hard to describe.
Well, he was half-Japanese.
I'm half-Japanese.
-That's true, but so is Arman.
-That's right.
Arman is half-Japanese, too.
But I'm not attracted to Arman at all.
-I mean, if someone...
-What about me?
Right now...
-Am I a possibility?
-Right now...
Yes, for now.
-I am?
-Yeah.
Why are you embarrassed
when you're the one who said it?
Never mind.
-I feel so tight.
-You do?
I'm gonna unbutton the top button.
That's totally fine with me.
I love that about you. It's hilarious.
Excuse me.
I promise my zipper is still closed.
Girls are usually shy
about things like that.
I don't need that shyness.
Oh, that reminds me!
I want someone who can accept me as I am.
There's no need for you to change at all.
In my opinion, anyway.
The reason I was rejected...
He told me I had no core self.
No core?
-Why?
-I don't... Well, maybe I am like that.
But since I was told that before,
what you said made me happy.
You totally have a core self!
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 21 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
-Hey, Yuuchan.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back!
Are you drunk?
I was so nervous that I drank too much.
-Nice.
-I was attracted to her from the start.
Now... even more so.
What was her reaction?
We talked about whether she could see me
as a potential boyfriend.
And she said she could.
That was quick.
-Yeah.
-Aren't things moving pretty fast?
-So you're happy.
-Yeah, it made me super happy.
It made me happy.
She does seem interested in you.
-Right, Arman?
-Really?
-It's pretty obvious.
-Right?
-No way.
-For real.
-Lucky you.
-Yeah.
Seriously, I am interested in her.
-You guys make a good match.
-Yeah.
-Did you drink a lot?
-Yeah, I drank a lot.
-You did?
We talked about relationships and work.
You look like you had fun.
We made plans for another date.
-The next one?
-Yeah.
He asked me if I could see him
as a potential boyfriend.
I said I might.
I'm so happy today. So happy!
I'm so happy!
I'm just gonna...
Are you gonna sleep like that?
Don't worry. I'll just change in here.
I really had fun today. It's been so long.
-I'm happy for you.
-Yeah.
They look really happy.
-It has begun for them.
-It certainly has.
Both of them want to just be themselves.
They're alike in that sense.
And to have their date in Sangen-jaya?
Great choice.
It is.
Sangen-jaya is the place
to bare your soul.
-Really?
-Yes.
He refuted everything
that hurt her before.
She laid out all her dissatisfactions
with Hikaru Ota.
HIKARU OTA
And when Byrnes came home,
Terashima tells him how that sounds good
in his lounged position.
The ridiculousness of it!
The way he acts like he knows it all...
I can't get enough of it!
I mean, he can't even tell
what the girl he likes is thinking.
-Terrible.
-I love it!
I mean, she's trying so hard
to contain herself from her perfect guy.
And she looks back to Terashima.
Of course she's gonna question
her decision.
Terashima is really not that bad.
Really, Riko has only gone out with him
a few times.
But Terashima is in love with her.
He is, and he acts like she's his.
Hold on.
Until recently,
you were calling him Hayato.
But now you disparagingly refer to him
as Terashima.
He's setting things up for us.
We'll know how Rikopin really feels
when she's on that date in Yokohama.
It'll be interesting to see
how Hayato acts.
He's gonna come on strong.
Right now, Riko is putting on the brakes
for her interest in Byrnes.
So, if Terashima plays it smart,
then he can come across as the good guy
in Riko's eyes.
Right.
But the wrong move
will turn Riko away from him.
That's true.
Riko's been concerned about
their age difference the entire time.
So if he says something like,
"I knew you'd put that in your noodles..."
If he says it like that,
she might think it's because he's old.
It's all over if she thinks that.
YOTSUKAIDO, CHIBA
KAORI BALLET STUDIO
When are you performing?
-Next Saturday.
-Saturday? Oh, I see.
KAORI KAWABATA
INSTRUCTOR
If it's right before your competition,
you might want to put more effort into it.
-Yes, that's why I'd like you to see it.
-All right.
Let's begin.
Hold the turnout.
One.
Two.
Three. Very nice.
Turnout.
Raise your arms. Now tighten.
Core, core, core.
And last move, up.
And the finish.
-Wipe yourself off.
-Yes.
Now...
Do you feel focused on ballet right now?
I feel like I'm doing what I need to do,
while still having fun at the house.
Whether you can become a pro or not
depends on whether or not
you can give your all to ballet.
If you don't have that kind of mindset,
I don't think you'll be able to become
a professional ballet dancer.
So, everything you do throughout the day
should be for ballet.
It's something you need to decide now,
considering your age.
I know that this is my last chance.
You also should lose some more weight.
Yes.
You're not eating the same things
as everyone else, are you?
As a ballerina,
you need to be able to restrain yourself.
Yes.
-Can I do this nail?
-Sure.
You're good at this.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-You look tired, Momochan.
-I am.
You've got ballerina head.
Yeah, I showed my competition piece
to my teacher today.
I've been taking lessons from her
since junior high school.
And... well...
-She had a lot to say?
-Yeah.
She said it'd be tough to make it as a pro
if I don't change my ways.
Maybe it was naive of me
to have a lifestyle outside of ballet.
She said she could tell
from seeing me dance just once.
So do you have a goal
for this competition?
I want to produce results,
so I need to make the top three.
Out of how many?
I think 150?
There aren't too many 21-year-olds
in competitions.
-You mean it's too old?
-Yeah.
By the time you're 21,
you either quit or you're already a pro.
So if I can't make it into the top three,
then I probably won't be able to
become a pro.
At least in my mind.
Then I guess your future depends
on what happens.
-Yeah, it will.
-I see.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
HJ COMPANY LIMITED
MISS HIGH SCHOOL JAPAN
Last time I mentioned about modeling
for the cover of Gravure magazine.
The cover of a shonen magazine...
KEITA MIYAGI
DIRECTOR, HIGH SCHOOL MODEL MAGAZINES
I think we talked about whether
that would be something you wanted to do.
Have you given it any thought?
I don't feel comfortable about
the fact that I'd be in a bathing suit.
-You must've been working really hard.
-Yes, well...
I can tell you've lost weight.
That's how I feel.
I do think this is a job that's necessary
to further your career.
It's my personal opinion that
you should take any job
that comes your way for now.
This is the first time
I'm actually conversing with you.
What's wrong?
-What's funny?
-What's wrong?
-Am I being weird?
-Yeah.
-No, it's normal.
-What's wrong?
-He's your type?
-No, no.
-Do I have a weird face?
-No, no, you don't.
Are you nervous?
Actually, I wanted to talk to Arman.
-Me?
-Yeah.
You know how we talked about going--
Oh, I'm sorry!
-It's okay. Would you prefer we left?
-No, it's okay.
-It's so serious.
-Sorry.
It's okay.
We talked about going to the beach,
but now I have practice on the weekends.
The show's going to run for a while.
And if I go before the performance,
I'll be thinking about it
and won't be able to have fun.
I totally understand. Good luck.
We can go after.
-After you're done.
-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
I won't know what to do if you apologize.
Please wait a little longer for me.
Sure.
See you tomorrow then.
-See ya.
-Yeah.
-Good night.
-Good night. I'm sorry.
I used to do performances, so I get it.
-It takes focus.
-Yeah.
If she makes a mistake,
I don't want her to regret
missing a practice.
So you understand.
-Good morning.
-Ready?
-Ready.
Is it gonna rain today?
It's not raining right now,
but it might later.
It's starting to rain.
Oh, no!
How much longer is it?
Another hour.
Wake me up in 45 minutes.
What?
-You're going to sleep?
-Yeah.
You can sleep.
-No, I'm not going to.
-You can.
You're sleepy, right?
You can lean back.
It's okay.
Oh, I'll take a shot of Tokyo Tower.
-I'm like a tourist.
-You are like a tourist.
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
CUPNOODLES MUSEUM
-Isn't it cool?
-Like Hansan said.
Yeah.
-What'd he say, that a designer built it?
-Yeah.
Someone famous.
-Are you good at drawing?
-No, I'm not.
When you're done drawing,
please head to the counter.
Okay.
I'll make one for you.
Then I'll do yours.
Is that okay?
ARMAN
-Looks good.
-Ready.
Please spin the handle six times.
Wow!
There it goes.
That's six. Thank you very much.
-Ding!
-Here are your noodles.
-It went "Ding!"
-Here you go.
-Which one do you want?
-You can pick for me.
The normal noodles please.
Cheddar cheese, egg and egg powder.
Nice and colorful.
Please move over to this side to wait.
-Thank you.
-Wait, that's only five.
Wait, what? No, there it is.
Entrance fee?
-Oh, wanna go to the kid's party?
-Yeah!
Really?
-I'm hungry.
-Doesn't this look cool? Wanna make one?
That's okay.
-Do you know what this is?
-I don't know.
It's a Thai taxi.
-Bon appétit.
Oh, it's good.
Want to try some?
Yeah.
It's sweet.
Sweet and spicy.
-It's good.
-Yeah.
What are we doing after this?
How about the shopping center?
Okay.
How's the third date?
It's fun.
So for you,
is there a difference between...
a date when you're in a relationship
and one where you're not?
If I'm not in a relationship...
-then I don't want a date in yukatas.
-No?
If we weren't in a relationship.
-That's for when you're in a relationship?
-Yeah, and theme park dates, too.
But this is okay?
-Just barely.
-Just barely?
And?
If I'm not in a relationship with someone,
I wouldn't hold hands with him.
-You'd have to be in a relationship?
-Yeah, I wouldn't hold hands otherwise.
But maybe holding hands is normal?
I don't know.
I probably would,
even if we weren't in a relationship.
-You would?
-If I liked the person.
I see. If you liked her.
What about for you?
Is there a difference?
Something you're okay with
even if you're not in a relationship?
Even if I'm not in a relationship...
as long as we had feelings for each other,
I'd be okay with anything.
Anything?
-Anything.
-Anything?
I'd treat her like a girlfriend.
Are you drinking this?
I'd be okay treating her
like a girlfriend.
I would.
I see.
YOKOHAMA WORLD PORTERS
Is there anything you need to buy?
No, not really.
Me neither.
Shall we go then?
-Yeah.
-What?
-Should we go?
-Should we go home?
-Should we?
Why?
I want to spend more time
in Yokohama sometime.
That's funny.
-What?
-The sign.
It said to move slowly,
both in cars and in love.
That is funny.
Why is it so funny?
Why are you so quiet?
I'm not.
-You are.
-Am I?
Maybe because I'm thinking.
About what?
What are you thinking about?
I was thinking I'd let you sleep
because you're sleepy.
-I'm not.
-No?
-Hold on.
-What's happening?
-What was that?
-Their last conversation about
how he's okay with anything
if he likes someone...
She was taken a little aback by that.
-Their paths missed each other there.
-Rikopin seemed to be holding off
from moving on to the next step
of the relationship.
At least it seemed that way.
She did say the museum just barely passed.
She said she could go there
even if they weren't in a relationship.
That must have been a shock to him.
But they're not in a relationship yet...
But they've been on several dates already.
If someone said that to me,
I'd think I'm only one step away.
I think I understand how Terashima feels.
-Why?
-Well, Riko is attracted to Byrnes.
Also, with it still raining
after a date like that,
I would feel like that too.
I see.
They both might be
reading into things too much.
It's not like Rikopin isn't having fun.
But Terashima is making assumptions
and reacting to them.
And Rikopin sees that
and asks why he's so quiet.
Just a small...
-A misunderstanding.
-Mutual.
They need a reminder
from that comedian Esper Ito.
Yeah, it's a little too serious right now.
They need bigger misunderstandings
and some more flailing.
They need to stuff themselves in a bag!
He should be in a bag in the girls' room.
And come out. Ta-da!
-That'd be scary.
-Yeah.
-She'd scream.
-Scream!
He'd be like, "Aw, Riko..."
There was one nice thing.
There's no more date with Arman.
-That's not nice.
-Why is that good?
It's like her teacher said,
the competition can determine her life.
She should take it seriously.
That's true. She's at a turning point.
She has to work hard.
If she wants to make it
to the top three out of 150...
-She has to do her best.
-Yeah, it'll be tough.
-I wonder what we'll get to see now.
-I wonder!
-Yeah, this is it for today.
-It feels dark.
There won't be a happy ending today,
that's for sure.
-I wonder!
-There's no way.
-Misunderstandings...
-What's gonna happen?
What's gonna happen?
Oh, Adidas.
It's been awhile since I've worn Adidas.
-It brings back memories.
-You're back early.
Is it? It's just past 7:00 p.m.
But you left in the afternoon.
I expected you back later.
-Really?
-Yeah.
The Cupnoodles Museum place was amazing.
Oh, the Cupnoodles Museum?
Yeah, that part was fun.
That part?
What does that mean?
On the way home...
he was really quiet.
-He was?
-Yeah.
Did you do something?
Did I?
Is there anything you can think of?
Well...
I did think we had differing views
on relationships.
-With Hayato?
-Yeah.
Our views on relationships
are total opposites.
Any progress?
For me, it's the third date...
-Already the third?
-Yeah.
I was planning on making a move.
But she doesn't even want to hold hands
if we're not in a relationship.
Theme park dates,
fireworks and yukata dates,
for her those are all things
she'd do with a boyfriend.
It's like she closed the door on me.
-She shut you down?
-Yeah, kind of.
We have differing views on relationships.
Yeah.
What should I do, Arman?
That's the problem. Not much you can do.
Not really. Is there nothing I can do?
If Rikopin got along with a girl,
she wouldn't say it out loud.
I wonder... But yeah, maybe.
So to Rikopin, you're a friend.
Probably.
Did anything change for you
after three dates?
I realize I like hanging out with him.
-Oh, good.
-He takes the lead.
He gets excited with me about stuff.
-Actually...
-He was more excited than you?
Yeah. Usually it's like, "Calm down."
There was nothing I didn't like, but...
I think there were things
that bothered him.
I think you guys should just get together.
Relationships are all about timing.
You're letting yourself miss it.
I see.