-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
-Let's see, last week...
-Oh, yes.
Minori and Tatsuya finally got together.
Oh, they kissed!
Remember the legendary missile?
She wrote "coward" on Tatsuya's omu-rice,
because even though the mood
was right for something to happen,
he just fell asleep.
-That's right, the cushion.
-Yes, the notice-me missile.
Are you ready now?
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
That's why I wrote "coward."
-You seemed so experienced.
-I'm not.
-What?
With that kiss, we all realized
that all of Tatsuya's previous actions
were just a reflection
of his inexperience with love.
All of it came together in that moment.
It was refreshing to watch.
Now that they've kissed...
They're young.
It's gonna be hard to stop.
It'll be hard.
-They'll be making babies.
-They won't stop.
And on the flipside...
That's right.
-Though things looked good for Mizuki...
-Then she came.
Sometimes I miss being in nature.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
Like, recently, I climbed Mt. Takao.
Is that close to Tokyo?
-Do you want to go?
-Let's go somewhere like that.
I want to join a gym, too.
You should come to Target.
But he's already invited Mizuki
to his match on December 13th!
Oh, Arisa from Kagoshima.
Maybe this new environment in the city
is clouding her judgment.
Guys like you, Yamachan,
tend to just assume
a girl is pure and innocent.
And when you find she's really not,
you say, "You betrayed me!"
That's not good, Yamachan.
It's a characteristic of a stalker.
I know this girl's not like that.
She's not one of those wanton women.
Oh, so you've met her before?
No, I've just seen her here.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Look at your expression.
How'd it go?
We kissed.
Wait, wait a sec.
How? How did it happen?
He asked me if I liked him.
I told him I do.
-And?
-And then...
Then it just sort of...
happened.
Oh, man, that's so great!
Was he smooth?
No, not really.
Well, he said it himself.
I see.
But that's good.
Yeah. I'm happy, I think.
These heart-pounding moments
before the relationship are the best.
-Relationship?
-You're going out now, right?
We didn't talk about it.
We only talked about how we felt.
French? How many seconds?
-Nothing that intense.
-You used your tongue?
I didn't.
Dude, no.
I didn't do that.
-Not deep? A pretty one then.
-Yeah.
-Use your tongue on the next one.
-I won't.
-I won't
-You won't?
She's gonna write "coward" again.
Now that you've kissed,
are you guys in a relationship then?
We didn't talk about that.
So you're not officially a couple yet.
I guess not.
But we have feelings for each other.
Going to Korea with my co-workers!
Uchi
Mino.
Morning.
-You slept out here?
-I fell asleep.
You're awake.
I'm going to Korea.
Have a good trip.
For how long?
I think three days.
-With co-workers.
-You're so lucky.
Before I leave for Korea,
there's something I wanted to clarify.
Why are you laughing?
That kiss means
you're okay with us being exclusive?
You're asking me now?
I just thought I'd better make sure.
I wanted to know.
-You want me to ask?
-No, no.
Will you go out with me?
Yes, I will.
Don't sound so excited.
-Can I get some enthusiasm?
-Yes!
-It sounds lackluster.
-No, it's not.
It's embarrassing.
-So we're together now?
-We're together.
I see.
All right.
Guess I'll be going then.
Have a good trip.
You're not gonna kiss me goodbye?
-You want me to?
-I do.
See you when I get back!
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
-Hi!
-Hey.
-Shall we go?
-Yeah.
-Did you bring your gym clothes?
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Hi, it's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
DAIKI MIYAGI, 25 YEARS OLD,
ACTOR, TARGET SHIBUYA OWNER
-This is my friend Arisa.
-I'm Arisa.
Nice to meet you.
-So you want to kickbox?
-Yes, I want to relieve some stress.
Jab, straight.
One, two! Again.
One, two.
Four times.
One, two. One two.
Very good.
Last one.
Okay, let's take a break.
-You're good.
-Am I?
-Am I, really?
-Yes.
Wow, I think I might get into this.
Go Arman!
Begin!
Nice!
Get a kick in. Nice!
Just throw punches if you're tired.
Attack.
Good. Move in.
Last 30 seconds.
Don't go down, don't go down.
Move in.
Okay.
-Are you all right, Arman?
-Yes.
You seemed like
you were going to throw up.
Been drinking?
-A little.
-A little?
I need to quit.
I have about one a day.
One a day?
Well, you have another month.
-But the last two to three weeks...
-Nothing for the last two or three weeks.
I understand. I won't.
-Thank you.
-See you next time.
-Man, I'm tired. Rain?
-It's raining.
-Just a little.
-I don't have an umbrella.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-That was hard work.
-Yeah.
It was amazing.
For the match...
Yeah, that was about 60% effort.
I wonder if I can watch.
They're together!
Congratulations!
-Couple number four.
-That's right.
One out of very few couples from the show.
I guess it's difficult for couples
to get together,
especially when living together.
You see things you don't want to see.
So, it's not very easy.
There isn't always an attraction either.
But with the guys' conversation,
Arman was pretty vulgar.
"Did you stick your tongue in?"
And he officially asks her out
sitting on the sofa.
They shared another kiss.
Oh, and what's with the hood thing?
It's nothing, just a little embarrassment
after the kiss.
Oh, to hide her embarrassment?
But the girls were just saying
they'd want the guy to pull up the hood,
and with the eyes covered they'd say,
"What's going on?"
and the guy would drop a kiss.
Oh, I see.
Triendl likes the hood idea as well.
I'd want him to pull the hood down
with a "wham!"
A "wham"?
-A "wham!"
-Sounds powerful.
Did you mean to use that term?
If you have a foreigner for a dad,
it's "wham."
Like "bow wow"?
I see.
So it's "wham!"
My mistake.
Oh, Babachan's wearing a "wham" jacket.
Wham!
Congratulations to them,
but what about the other members?
Yeah, what's with that?
Arman and Arisa are almost...
When Daiki, the trainer,
was explaining things to Arman,
she was standing next to him with water
as if she was already his girlfriend.
You can tell me if I'm wrong.
-You're wrong.
-You think so?
Arman seems like he'd come on strong.
Guys from Hawaii have that impression.
And the first kiss has tongue, right?
I will stop him. Yes.
What can you possibly do?
What can you do
from this side of the screen?
For now, after this episode,
I'm starting a 2-chan topic from my phone.
For what?
About how Arman is a player.
Are we in elementary school?
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
What are you doing?
-I'm making bento.
-Wow.
-For tomorrow?
-For tomorrow.
I'm going to Mt. Takao tomorrow.
You're going to eat it at the top?
Yeah, at the top of the mountain.
Do you cook often?
I do when I have a boyfriend,
but I haven't been recently.
How is it with Arman?
-Arman?
-Yeah.
He was great at the gym.
Well, you know...
-He looked good?
-He did.
He was good, like he could survive
on a deserted island.
When you said that,
I totally thought of Arman.
He seems wild.
I'm going to go take a bath.
Later.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
Oh, wow.
Is that bento?
Are you going somewhere tomorrow?
I'm going to Mt. Takao tomorrow
with Arman.
Mt. Takao? Wow.
So that's your bento
to eat at the summit?
Mountain hiking, huh?
Yeah.
Hopefully the weather will be nice.
-So last time...
-Yeah.
When we were playing table tennis,
you mentioned
you were interested in Arman.
I find Arman really easy to talk to...
so I made plans with him
to go to Mt. Takao.
I've wanted to tell you.
Go have fun.
You should go have fun.
There's always tomorrow.
I think I'll take a bath and go to bed.
I'm going upstairs.
I'm not sure what to think.
Did you see downstairs?
-I did.
-You did.
-I don't know.
-Is it jealousy?
-Jealousy?
-Or not?
I'm not sure.
I thought it'd be okay at my own pace.
But maybe it's pressure?
But Arisa came...
I know she's a nice person.
And cute.
And I know she's interested in Arman.
She told me that again.
So I'm not...
Maybe it is jealousy, I don't know.
MT. TAKAO STATION
HACHIOJI, TOKYO
-We're here.
-Here.
Oh, there's a map.
Which should we do?
-The red trail?
-The red?
-That south side is the hardest part.
-Oh, really?
Let's do an easy one then.
Oh, these maple leaves are red.
It's the same tree, too.
Yeah, it's green over here.
I wonder why.
I've never been on a suspension bridge.
Oh, it shakes.
Stop it!
-It's shaking.
-Yeah.
Everyone's doing it.
Wow.
Oh, it moves a lot.
Watch your step.
We still have a long way to go.
But that looks like the top.
Oh, that's true.
I guess we're close.
MT. TAKAO SUMMIT
We came at the best time.
A little crowded though.
Is it a holiday today?
-No?
-It's a regular weekday.
-It's crowded for a weekday.
-There's school too, right?
Maybe everyone's ditching.
-No, they're not!
-They must be ditching.
Okay.
-We made it?
-We made it.
Finally.
Wow.
-There's a Ferris wheel there.
-Is that Odaiba?
No, that's totally not!
It feels nice.
It was worth the hike.
Let's go on another adventure sometime.
Yeah.
-I'll go to the gym, too.
-Yeah, definitely.
I'm looking forward to the match, too.
-I'm hungry.
-Do you want to go eat?
-I made lunch for us.
-You did?
-Is that why you were up so late?
-Yes.
That's why I said, "Don't come in!"
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Ta-da!
Looks good.
Spam musubi!
-From Hawaii.
-Yeah, thanks.
It's good, the Spam.
The Spam?
-Yeah, the Spam.
-I bought the Spam.
It's good, seriously.
-We keep doing active stuff.
-We're always moving.
Kickboxing, hiking, what's next?
I want to go somewhere more relaxed.
Sounds good.
-Like where?
-Like...
Like shopping?
Yeah, like running errands together.
I do need winter clothes.
-I'll help you look for some.
-Thanks.
You can help me find a good hat.
-Work?
-Yeah.
-Tired?
-Yeah, a little tired.
Of course.
-The mountain.
Did Arman like it?
The bento?
You stayed up late making it.
How was your first outing together?
The first outing?
It was really easy being with him.
-The whole day?
-Yeah.
You must be cold.
Maybe I'll go take a bath.
-The hot water is ready.
-Thanks.
I'll go first then.
-Okay.
What is this?
He did it so naturally.
Holding hands in Japan is a big deal.
But he just did it.
Is it just a normal thing
for Westerners or what?
I'm sure that's part of it.
But girls notice it
when a guy takes their hand, right?
-She's aware of it.
-Yeah.
Maybe she's not the one.
Who? Arisa?
She's not who I thought she was.
She's different from what you thought?
She was taken by Arman.
Well, nothing's decided yet.
Let's decide after we see what happens
in the next couple of weeks.
They hiked holding hands
and made plans for the next date.
-She said that.
-Arisa did.
I'm going to decide about Arisa,
after this week, or next week.
He's scary.
We've seen this pattern before.
The kind that makes headlines...
She's not going to betray
my image of Arisa.
That's creepy.
It's okay.
She's being led astray for now.
She'll come back to me in the end.
How creepy!
-How creepy!
-So creepy!
But Mizuki seems...
Her feelings are apparent in her behavior.
-That can't be helped.
-Of course, that'll happen.
Oh, maybe this is Tap's chance!
-For Mizuki?
-Yeah.
He's gonna stick his shoes in?
"Oh, what is that soothing sound?"
Tap's feet appear under the girls' door.
Don't be ridiculous.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Your breakfast is so healthy.
It is, isn't it?
You're not eating?
-Oh, I ate already.
-I see.
I got up early.
-Work today?
-Yeah.
-Where?
-In the office today.
-At the office?
-Yeah.
-Arman, let's go out to eat sometime.
-Sure.
-It's set, then.
-When do you want to go?
-The weekend maybe?
-The weekend? Okay.
-Are you free on Sunday?
-I am.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Let me know the details later.
-I have to go to my training session.
-Oh, yeah.
-In the afternoon?
-Just weights today.
-And kickboxing at night.
-At night?
Have a good session.
See you.
THE SEASON HAS BEEN EXTENDED.
TERRACE HOUSE IS NOT FINISHING YET!