-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
So last week...
Hayato and Martha cooked together.
-He was teaching her.
-Yes, he was.
How is it?
It's fine.
You've gone out several times, right?
But she's like a younger sister.
-You don't see her as a woman yet?
-Maybe I don't see her as a woman yet.
After the summer pasta...
came the summer foreplay.
-That's right.
-Yes.
-Riko's mom visited.
-That's right.
She seemed to get along rather well
with Terashima.
They had previously spoken over the phone
and had a little conversation.
She was giving off a vibe of,
"Look how he gets along with my daughter."
So even when it comes to Riko,
he seems to be very caring.
That's the impression I had.
He seems very nice.
Misaki and Byrnes
might make it official this week.
-It's so cute.
-I wanna see it happen!
He finally got his license.
But his attempt at surprising her
was terrible.
Are you free on Friday?
Friday? I am.
Let's go somewhere.
I'll drive.
Everybody tells me I shouldn't go
to Yokohama because of that.
-But it doesn't matter, does it?
-No.
I was going to tell her how I feel there.
What? You haven't already?
-Not yet.
-I see.
I wonder if they'll date this week.
He did some research
by watching Netflix.
I wonder what kind of date he'll plan
after having watched that.
He purposefully chose the place
even though she may not like it.
It's like, "Go ahead and remember.
I'll take care of you."
-He's so cool!
-Well, he hasn't said that yet.
That was me. That was me.
The mom! The mom!
-You're leaving soon?
-Yeah, I am.
At...
noon.
-Good morning.
You look so cute!
-Nice.
-Good morning.
It looks amazing.
Thanks. Is this for me?
I made it.
I figured you'd be coming down.
-You know...
-You wore the dress.
It looks good on you.
You look different.
-It's a totally different look.
-Yeah, totally different!
-You got a hair cut.
-Thanks.
-Are you ready?
-I'm ready.
-He was ready way earlier than you.
-Yeah.
Shall we?
Shall we go?
Do you have your license?
Hold on...
What?
I've got it.
-The beginner sticker.
-I have to put the sticker on.
-On the back, too?
-Yes.
I'm excited.
It feels kinda strange.
Are you sure you're okay?
-And we're off!
-We're off! Let's go.
I'm so happy that I'm finally driving.
Yeah, you worked hard.
-The highway!
Already?
-You'll be okay.
-Totally.
Believe in yourself.
You're totally fine.
This leads to the Rainbow Bridge, right?
It does.
-Oh, no!
-The Rainbow Bridge!
Yes! The Rainbow Bridge!
Here comes the Rainbow Bridge.
-I wanna see--
-It's super pretty.
Wish I could see.
Where are we going?
-You can't guess, can you?
-No.
YUIGAHAMA, KANAGAWA
-Too bad it's not sunny today.
-Yeah.
What are you doing?
I was making a funny face!
-Not at all.
-Really?
You weren't.
Oh, you were.
-Wow!
-It's so nice here.
-We're here.
-We're here!
I'm glad I didn't know the consequences--
Consequences? I didn't mean that.
Not consequences...
-You mean where we're going?
-Yeah.
I had to think about it, though,
since I messed up last time.
-The surprise?
-Yeah.
But looking back at it all,
it'll be a nice memory.
Yeah.
-Here it is.
-You can start.
-Can I?
-Of course.
Bon appétit.
-Tasty?
-Yeah.
Is this all we're doing today?
Are we going somewhere else?
-Is it okay if we do?
-Sure.
So many secrets today.
Sorry for not telling you
where we're going.
It's okay. I'm having fun.
-Are we almost there?
-What?
-I don't know.
This is...
Yokohama.
-What?
-It's Yokohama.
Yeah.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILD CARE WORKER
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
I had so much fun today.
-Did you have fun?
-I had fun.
-Did I seem like I wasn't?
-No, not at all.
It was super fun.
-I'm sorry I brought you to Yokohama.
-I'm totally fine.
It's already in the past for me.
Yes.
And...
There's something I wanted to tell you.
Hanging out with you...
is so much fun.
I find myself wanting to come home
after work.
Because we live together...
I see so many of your good qualities.
I like you.
I want you to...
go out with me.
I like you, too.
Yeah.
-What?
-I'm looking forward to this.
You laugh too much.
-Did my stubble hurt you?
-It did.
I'm so glad. I like Yokohama now.
-Do you really like me?
-I really like you.
Seriously.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm glad.
-They're back.
-What? No way.
-Here they come.
-They're here.
-Welcome back.
-Hey, you-- I mean Misaki.
-"You"?
-Sorry.
That outfit... You went in that outfit?
-It's so cute!
-I did.
It was so much fun.
So where did you go?
-Yokohama.
-Yokohama?
-You told him, didn't you?
-Why?
I asked her to go steady with me.
-Seriously?
He asked me to go steady.
-Wait, wait.
-Seriously?
But your reaction...
gives away the answer.
We're going out now.
Congratulations!
-That's so fun.
-It's hilarious.
Congrats!
-I'm happy for you. Congrats.
-Why didn't you say that right away?
-We're together now.
-Nice work!
Right?
She said yes.
So you're moving
to the Japanese-style room?
Not tonight.
-Not yet.
-Not yet?
I'm so glad!
I'm so glad for them.
There were several moments
that made my heart pound.
-Which ones?
-They were already having fun in the car.
When they were walking with their phones,
their shoulders would brush.
Even that's...
Yeah, that would recharge me by 86%.
-Yes, I was recharged.
-Powerful...
And after their talk,
during their walk back,
the way he said he really likes her.
Like, "I really like you."
The way he said it!
For those of you who couldn't see,
Tokui was standing up and pacing.
He was going wild over here,
practically dancing.
Totally wild.
Just prancing around.
This is the good stuff!
And when they were sitting
with the Ferris wheel in front of them...
-It was so pretty.
-It showed the time,
so I'm sure they'll remember that moment
down to the minute.
"We started going out on this day,
at this hour and this minute."
The way Byrnes said he likes her,
it really feels like
it's overflowing from him.
-Yes, it did.
-It was so natural and nice.
What?
I'm sorry--
You're always over
in our living room watching TV...
Why?
Maybe I should go home then.
Should I go home?
Going camping with everyone!
-What should we do?
-Should we take it?
We should put beer in the cooler.
Meat?
Wait.
-Should we take that?
-Yeah.
-Good morning.
-Where's Yuuki?
-Yuuki?
Good morning.
You're already wearing a hat?
What's wrong with that?
Oh, do we need this?
-Let's take the garlic.
-Do we need it?
-Why don't we...
-We can put the meat there.
I can't understand
when you all talk at once.
It's sunny, sunny. The sun is out.
It is sunny.
What do you want to do?
Jump in the water.
-And maybe fireworks?
-Fireworks sound nice.
-Fireworks are so fun.
-I've wanted to do that.
-Guys look good when they're driving.
-Yeah.
Thank you very much.
You too, Hayato.
-Oh, you mean Yuuki.
-Yuuki.
-I see what you're doing.
-She's doing it.
Lovey-dovey already.
I'm looking forward to camping.
You're taking pictures?
-Looks good.
-Does it?
Everyone's looking good.
I'm gonna snap away.
FOREST SONS NAGATORO
NAGATORO, SAITAMA
Oh, man...
It's nature.
Negative ions.
-Negative ions?
-Yeah.
Are there negative ions? I guess so.
-Is this it?
-This is it.
We take off our shoes, right?
-We're here.
-Home sweet home.
-It's nice.
-It smells like my grandma's place.
Wow!
Crazy.
It smells like wood.
-Wow.
-This is crazy.
Wood smells amazing.
-Wow.
-There's a lot.
-It's nice.
-Yeah.
-Oh, the beds!
-Wow, wow, wow!
Amazing.
-Wow, there's a balcony!
-It's the new girls' room.
Nice.
Put your weight on it. Yes, yes.
-Are you ready? I'm letting you go.
-Wait.
Stay centered.
Put your weight on the center.
Look!
Look, look, look!
I did it!
Good job.
I can kick flip.
How cool!
She said he's cool! She keeps bragging.
We heard it.
-We heard it.
-It's been heard.
Be careful. Go slow.
-Can you go?
-Yeah.
I can go.
What's that?
They're going down the river.
-Oh, man.
-I want to do that!
Wave to them, Riko.
They're waving back.
Hey!
-That looks ready.
-Looks so good!
Cheers.
Should we welcome Martha?
-Oh, yeah.
-That's right!
It's also a welcome for Martha.
Welcome to Terrace House.
-Welcome!
-Thank you!
-Cheers!
Is it on me?
-It's on your face.
-Bon appétit.
Delicious.
-Hey, the watermelon is drifting away!
-What?
-Oh, the watermelon!
-Arman!
-Get it, Arman!
You got it!
Hey, stop that! Seriously!
He's being annoying!
Seriously, stop!
It's hot.
The water's nice, huh?
Stop grinning so much.
-Is it done?
-I think so.
-It's good!
-Still a little warm.
Delicious.
I need to use the restroom.
I'll go with you.
Wanna go? We're going to the bathroom.
-I'm okay.
-You're joining the girls?
A bathroom break.
What's going on?
I don't have a clue. Doesn't matter.
-She's pretty mad.
-She's mad about something.
She's mad about something.
-Do you know, Arman?
-What?
Not really.
You know how Yuuki's got his camera?
There was a picture of his ex on it.
Yeah, from four years ago.
It's from when I first bought the camera.
-Misaki saw it.
-She just did.
That's why she's acting like that?
It's my fault for not erasing it.
Seriously.
Why did this happen
while we're having so much fun?
What is it?
I don't know why I'm crying.
I don't know.
I don't know. Is it jealousy?
-I get it. I totally get it.
-Is it jealousy?
You're upset at yourself
for even getting upset.
Yes, that's it! Yes!
-You're crying from that frustration.
-Yes!
-I get it.
-I'm so frustrated!
The timing isn't good either.
I'm so frustrated!
I know the past is the past,
and he told me he likes me.
So that feeling...
I need to just accept it.
And I realized I really like him.
So I'm...
I'm frustrated and sad...
and jealous?
-Cheers.
This is seriously the best.
Today was fun.
-Were you able to have fun?
-I did.
All of us usually don't get to hang out.
-It's the first time.
-Yeah, probably.
-What are you going to do, Yuuki?
-I'll apologize.
You will?
Yeah, you should.
-I just want to see her.
-Shut up!
-You've been saying that.
-Go see her.
You guys already started.
Hey.
-Hey.
-Hey. It's warm here.
-It's hot.
-Wow.
We didn't bring our drinks.
It's hot.
It's warm.
But it's nice for the evening.
-Are you drinking?
-I am.
-Want some?
-Sure.
-Bug spray?
-I haven't put on any.
Let's go talk, Misaki.
Let's go.
Sorry, we're gonna step out for a bit.
-The sparks fly.
-It's dangerous.
-We should scoot back.
-It was fine earlier.
Really?
Wanna go inside, Martha?
Where?
To the house.
Okay.
-Want a beer?
-You're leaving?
Bye.
Why isn't anyone else coming?
-How's the campfire?
-It's nice.
I haven't sat around one
since junior high.
It's really burning.
Sorry about earlier.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I promise that kind of thing
won't happen again.
I want to believe you...
but there's still a part of me
that doesn't.
And that frustrates me.
The more I like you...
I'm kinda...
The more insecure I become
about different things.
After you left,
I wanted to see you so bad.
I realized...
how much I really like you.
Me, too.
-I realized how much I like you.
-I really thought that.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-I just have to believe you.
Why did everyone leave?
I don't know.
Look.
What did they say they're doing?
I don't know.
Are we...
going to go on another date?
-What?
-Don't you think about going out again?
Why?
I was just wondering. There's...
somewhere I want to go.
-Somewhere you want to go?
-Well, I mean...
a festival or to see fireworks.
-That's where you want to go?
-Yeah.
With who?
With you.
You said we'd have to be going out.
That was my ideal situation.
It was just...
something I had in my head.
-You've changed your mind?
-Yeah.
You sure you're okay it's with me?
Yeah.
There are better guys for you.
Not right now.
I want to go with you.
Let's go then.
Then let's wear yukatas...
and either go see fireworks
or go to a festival.
Sure.
Let's go.
-It's nice.
-What is?
-What's nice?
-It's nice. It's fun.
It is fun.
It is fun, but...
Since I got here, I've only met girls
who try to cater to the guys.
Of all the girls I met here,
not many would say what's on their mind.
Living with you,
I realized you're the first.
-You mean my personality?
-Yeah.
And you're cute, too.
Out of all the girls that have been here,
I think you're the cutest.
I'm serious. Why are you laughing?
-Arman!
-What?
So...
let's go somewhere together.
Will you?
Will I?
Don't get all embarrassed after asking.
I'm okay with that.
-You are?
-Yeah.
Thanks.
I'll think about it.
I didn't know you were like this.
You'll think about it?
Oh, you mean where we'll go.
I wonder what Riko and Hayato
are talking about.
I don't know.
Oh, for Martha this is...
Wait, wait. Let's start at the beginning.
-We have to organize.
-Yes.
-Summarize.
It's like you said.
No matter what happens,
it's all just spice.
-Things have gotten hotter.
-Yes.
"I realized I really like you."
"Me, too."
-It doesn't happen like that too often.
-It's amazing.
And Riko...
We thought she might withdraw,
but she bent her own rules.
-She's maturing well.
-Hayato tried to play games with her.
-Games?
-He was just embarrassed.
I wonder what it was.
He told her there are better guys for her.
Why do guys say things like that?
When do you say that?
It's the whole, "With who?"
"With you."
He wants her to say it.
It's a little effeminate.
At the end, he was like, "Let's go."
Yeah, abruptly.
-Are you sure?
-Who do you want to go with?
-With you.
-You sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Let's go!
What happened?
It's so abrupt!
That was a little abrupt.
I thought that maybe his feelings for her
had changed,
that maybe he was starting to like Martha.
But the way he was saying "Is it on me?"
What do you think?
-The way Riko stuck out her arms was cute.
-It was so cute.
Although it's dangerous to do
so close to the fire.
Well, yes. You've got a point.
You should really keep a safe distance.
Stop the lovey-dovey stuff.
He's got to notice the details.
He's an adult after all.
Are you from the Boy Scouts?
It can be dangerous if it sparks.
I understand. I'm sorry.
As long as you're aware.
Otherwise, enjoy camping.
Okay.
And then Arman,
using consideration as an excuse,
took Martha aside.
That was tough for Martha.
It must have been hard on her.
Arman's being unusually aggressive.
His timing is bad.
-It's probably because of the flames.
-Yes.
Flames from a campfire
can lead people astray.
It helps boost things
that are already going well.
But it also got hot
in unintentional places.
It makes you think you can go for it.
-It's summertime.
-It is summertime.
-It's summer.
-We're being shown summertime.
Can I end this summer
without doing anything?
Should we light fireworks?
I'll go get them.
I'll go, too.
What's wrong?
Does it have to do with Arman?
Yeah...
It's nothing.
He asked we go somewhere
after we get back from camping.
He asked, but...
Well...
And you, Riko?
-Did you talk to him?
-I did.
I asked him out on a date.
I see.
Then...
he asked if it's okay that it's him.
So he still had Yuuki in mind?
He said there are better guys out there.
Or so he said.
-But you told him there isn't.
-I told him there isn't.
I see.
-Just rip it open.
-How do I open it?
-Fireworks!
-Let's start with an easy one.
Hold it at the bottom.
Go, go! Let's all do it.
Let's do it together.
-You're gonna start with that one?
-Oh, wow!
-Wow, scary.
-It's safe.
-Beautiful.
-Yeah!
Smells like fireworks.
The smoke's coming this way.
Here are some sparklers.