-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show
about six strangers, men and women
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared
is a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
In the last episode,
Tatsuya and Mizuki had a date at Odaiba.
It was a good date.
-It was a good date.
-Good date.
Next will be my turn.
-Okay.
-I'll think of something.
I look forward to it.
I'm so sorry about that.
Oh, I'm so sorry, too.
-This isn't good.
-It's not good.
CLOSED FOR TODAY
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU AGAIN
This feels really new to me.
New?
I've never been out for dinner
with someone dressed so beautifully.
It took a lot of effort.
-You did?
-I did.
-Why?
-It's not like it was Yuriko's fault.
I think it was the way I approached her.
Among other things.
So Tatsuya regrets that it didn't go well
because he had to put in a lot of effort.
-Right.
And what happened behind his back
was shocking.
Makoto's tattling and the LINE incident.
That's right.
His date with you was carefree and fun.
But it seemed he was
quite tense on our date.
Uchi told him something like that.
So, I heard that from Makocchan.
After that, Makocchan texted me,
something like,
"I don't want to see you sad."
I kinda forgot.
So awkward.
What we don't know is
whether Makocchan is stupid,
or in fact a truly malicious schemer.
That hasn't become clear yet.
What did you think of
the whole turn of events?
I thought Makoto was such a coward.
-You said it.
-I told you.
I told you so.
-Acting with seniority.
-Showing seniority to him.
You said you were rooting for Makoto,
didn't you?
-Yes.
-That's the real him.
Don't get so puffed up.
Sorry.
Everyone makes mistakes.
You don't look that cool.
Uchi, are you up yet?
-Morning.
Already ready?
Well, there's something...
I need to talk to you about.
I've been thinking about it.
Telling you...
what Makocchan told me
doesn't feel right, but...
You told him you could have
a fun date with Mizuki
without any effort,
but that you had to be cautious
a great deal during the date with me...
is what I heard.
And it made me feel pretty down.
Well, it's true, I was really cautious.
I'm just being honest.
But...
it wasn't your fault.
It was me.
I couldn't find the best way
to get to know you.
I was thinking of using
a different approach next time.
If that's the case,
I understand completely.
Makocchan shouldn't have told you that.
But I thought
I had to have a talk with you.
So I went to the boys' room,
but Makocchan was there.
I wonder what was on his mind.
So I wanted to explain to you
and apologize about yesterday.
-That's why you're here.
-Yeah.
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, no.
I'm sorry, too.
Shall we go out, then?
I'll get ready.
I'm glad we talked.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
-Bon appétit.
Everyone tells me
that female doctors can't get married.
Why?
First, they're too busy to meet anyone.
Same with hairstylists.
You aren't allowed to ask
customers out, right?
Not that we aren't allowed,
but I won't date customers.
And we work long hours.
Plus, our days off are irregular.
So we tend to date within the profession.
How many girlfriends have you had?
Not many.
What? You can't...
-More than you can count?
-Not that many.
Four or five.
Me too. Five.
The first relationship was long.
My first girlfriend was
when I was a freshman in high school.
We went out for four years.
-That's long!
-It was crazy.
I erased all the other girls' addresses.
-Co-ed?
-Yeah.
We saw each other between classes.
-Wow.
-I walked her home every day after school.
I thought that was normal.
-She was my first girlfriend.
-I see.
"This is what dating is like."
Since you're popular with girls,
I thought you went through them quickly.
But you're not like that.
-The first...
-I feel bad.
It was fun talking about your love life.
Well, I wanted to talk about it.
The day before yesterday,
all I did was listen.
You got me.
Are you coming home late?
I finish around 8:00 p.m.,
so I'll be home around 9:30 p.m.
-Shall we go?
-Yeah.
Let's go.
-Yo.
-Hey.
-Sit down.
-What?
Come sit.
I think I know what this is about.
That wasn't cool.
I wanna know what you were thinking
when you told Yuriko.
Well, what I said...
I don't blame Yuriko, but--
I heard that Yuriko asked you.
So...
I feel this is like a boy's club,
so I'm being frank.
So, if someone tattles...
I just think it's not right.
But,
it was the first date for you two.
It's normal to feel tense.
But it was thoughtless of you.
If I were Yuriko,
I'd also get upset...
if I heard that someone had to be
cautious around me.
But is it such a bad thing
to put in effort for someone?
She had also heard
that the date with Mizuki had been fun.
You told her that I hadn't needed
to put in any effort with Mizuki,
but that I had with her.
She thought that I compared them
and found her more difficult...
It'd hurt to know, wouldn't it?
Well,
I'll get angry next time. Really.
I may kick your butt.
I'll be careful.
Well...
Don't be so serious.
-I have to.
-No need.
Mizuki woke me up late last night
and told me--
Well, that's...
It's important to be told clearly once...
Man...
Yuriko was pretty hurt.
Mizuki told me to apologize to you two.
Yeah, I want an apology from you.
Do I need to apologize to Yuriko?
You need to talk with her about that.
I don't know.
You should think about how others may feel
before you say or do something.
-Okay.
-Well...
I got it.
I'm gonna hit the showers.
I'm starting to feel sorry for
the hairstylist that I've been loathing.
It wouldn't be easy to speak up, either.
He didn't want to, but he had to,
so he said it,
and that was the reaction he got.
Yeah, and the expression on his face said,
"I'm really repressing my anger."
That twitch between his eyebrows.
-That reaction is hard to take.
-It's too much.
I don't think it's because he's stupid.
-What is it?
-Is he simply a jerk?
Perhaps he lacks empathy.
He might have meant well,
but if someone doesn't like it,
it's wrong.
I agree.
So he needs to realize
that he owes apologies.
Exactly.
-You're so right.
-What's bad is bad.
It may have felt right to him.
You sound like a bossy mom.
If someone says it's wrong, it's wrong.
Even if you think it's right.
-Big mama.
There was a political candidate like you.
-What's bad is bad.
-Bad is bad.
"I will fix this city. So vote for me."
What made me think he's a jerk
is when he said,
"I don't want to blame Yuriko, but..."
What's obvious here is,
even though he says
it's his fault and not hers,
what he really wants people to hear
is that it was Yuri's fault.
That kind of tactic is something
only a jerk would use.
I know it because I'm a jerk myself.
-You use that method?
-You're a jerk too?
I do. I use it when
I don't wanna admit something
or when I'm dissatisfied with something.
So he's a jerk just like me.
-Same jerk?
-Same jerk.
Not all athletes are innocent.
I'm certain he's even worse.
How exciting!
-You want more juicy stuff.
-I want more.
This is not the end of it.
You can squeeze out more good stuff.
Squeeze out good stuff...
-More good stuff?
-Much more.
TAKESHIBA FERRY TERMINAL
Welcome aboard.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
We made it.
-Nice.
-This is great.
First date?
-Huh?
-Your first date?
Do you consider running together a date?
-Yes, I do.
-You do?
-Then this is my second.
-Okay, second.
Did you two reconcile?
Reconcile?
We weren't on bad terms.
We weren't fighting or anything.
My impression of Makocchan changed a lot.
What? How?
-Huh?
-How did it change?
I thought he was calm and collected.
-He isn't?
-He isn't. Not at all.
He's revealed his true colors.
What will he do now?
IZU OSHIMA
-There it is.
-I wanna fish.
Wow! Amazing.
The ocean.
-Gorgeous!
Amazing view.
Have a good day.
-Amazing.
We're off to Izu Oshima! Uchi & Minori
I'm off to a lesson in Sendai!! Yuki
So cold!
How come nobody's here?
-We can't catch anything.
-Nothing at all.
-The end.
-No. One more chance.
Too close.
What? What?
-You've got something. Pull!
-Help me pull!
It's coming!
On the very last one?
You did it!
-We got it.
-We got it. One fish.
Wow, what a smell!
Cows.
-They are gobbling.
-Amazing.
I hope they'll come near.
Cows!
You like them?
-I hear you want to work at a ranch.
-Yeah.
-To take care of them?
-I want to.
-Cows?
-Yeah.
Cows.
Cows!
CAMELLIAS - SOCIAL AREA - RECREATION AREA
Let's eat the lunch that you made.
-Bon appétit!
-Good?
-Good. Delicious.
Very picnic-like.
You're a good cook.
-You noticed?
-I noticed.
This is very nice. This...
Nature surrounding us.
Feels date-like?
The most date-like date so far.
Out of the three,
this is the most date-like.
Did your impression of Mizuki change
after the date?
It did.
Did she become a girl?
-She is a girl.
-So am I.
You're more like a little brother.
In my eyes, you're my little brother.
-Why not a little sister?
-You're boyish.
But you're the most comfortable one
to be with.
-I'm probably the most comfortable type.
-You are.
-What?
-It makes me happy.
-Does it?
How was the Uchi Week?
A lot happened.
I heard bits and pieces from people.
What happened? What--
Something else happened
between Makocchan and me.
What? A fistfight?
I made a negative comment about
how I had to cater to someone.
But it's not something
the person needs to know about.
But it's not something to hide, either.
Did you try to hide it?
Not necessarily hide it,
but there are things a person should know
and things you don't want them to know.
Earlier, we all talked about
how we should share our thoughts
about who likes or dislikes whom,
about which girl we're into or not into.
But if it's just going to leak out,
I'm not going to share my thoughts.
If you don't want to share,
you don't need to.
What was that sneer?
-Huh?
-What was that sneer?
I won't share anything then.
OSHIAGE, TOKYO
There you are.
-How are you?
-Sorry for making you wait.
All right, let's go.
It's huge.
Amazing.
-Beautiful.
-Yeah.
It'd be nice to have this
on the wall of my house.
Even Terrace House
couldn't put this on the wall.
They sure couldn't.
They're all looking in the same direction.
At the perfect angle.
I wonder what they're looking at.
I feel the strong determination.
-They look like you.
-Why?
Seems like they're looking
straight into the future.
There. There they are.
Tonight's highlight is garden eels!
Amazing!
I've never seen such long ones.
What does the color difference mean?
These are splendid garden eels
and these are spotted garden eels.
I wonder how they breed.
Maybe they do things under the sand.
Under the sand?
You're nasty!
ASAKUSA, TOKYO
BENTEN
OKONOMIYAKI MONJA
-Thank you so much.
-For what?
-The aquarium.
-You're very welcome.
-I had a lot of fun.
-Spotted garden eels.
Yeah, but I liked the penguins.
But that wasn't the highlight.
You wanna have them cook it?
Let's cook it ourselves.
-It already looks delicious.
-Does it?
I'll definitely spill it.
We'll make it work.
-Bon appétit.
Have you danced since the last tap event?
After watching that event,
I understood why, on your birthday,
you talked so passionately.
Really? Well, I did make you cry...
But now I really understand.
I heard Uchi was going to take you
to an aquarium,
so I thought,
"That'll overlap with my plan!"
You said you liked jazz,
so I thought maybe Blue Note, then...
I love Blue Note!
But isn't that place expensive?
One of the staff...
I know a guy who works as the bartender.
I talked with him,
and he gave me a schedule.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I love Blue Note so much!
It's nice, isn't it?
Do you dance there too?
It's one of my goals.
If you perform at Blue Note,
you'll be unapproachable.
-Not at all.
-No?
I want to go to Blue Note.
What? Blue Note?
Let's go.
You mean it?
OMOTESANDO, TOKYO
Thank you very much.
-Hi.
-Sorry for the unexpected visit.
-No problem.
-Can we talk now?
-Welcome.
You look cool.
What would you like?
-Hazelnut.
-Hazelnut. Okay.
Cute!
-So amazing!
-Here you are.
Thank you.
-Looks good.
-It's best when it's fresh.
Tasty.
What brought you here?
Huh?
I haven't checked out
everyone's workplace, so...
We saw Yuki's.
Right.
Yuki looked so cool.
I thought of going
to Makocchan's place, too.
-Makocchan?
-The practice field.
Right.
Let's go together.
-I'll go.
-Yeah.
We can invite Minori, too.
Minori...
What?
I just wondered about her.
Remember, at first,
-all of us liked Makocchan?
-We did.
The other day,
I brought trouble to you and Uchi.
I thought my feelings might change
after that incident.
-Toward Makocchan?
-Yeah, yeah.
But they didn't change.
-I see.
-They didn't.
I don't know how to put this.
-He's still...
-I know you don't dislike him.
He's still at the top.
-The top?
-The top.
Seriously?
But...
If Minori has feelings for him too,
and if I go to him knowing that...
I can't, after all this.
After everything that's happened,
asking him out
seems so odd.
You heard Minori might like him,
so you can't make a move.
I understand.
But if you think you like him,
pretending that you don't
seems like a shame.
Thank you.
I'll take it here.
Thank you so much.
-Why?
-What does she like about him?
-Wait a minute.
-I don't get it.
Shall we try figuring it out one by one?
But I like what Minori said.
Makoto "revealed his true colors."
-That's something we'd say.
-Right.
She must be really disgusted with
his saying something like that.
Since she liked him at first...
He looked calm and collected,
but in reality he's just a child.
If Makoto started singing a song
with a guitar, he would be that guy.
YOSUKE IMAI (30)
JULY 2013 - MARCH 2014
-That guy. Once again.
-It'd be bad.
That conversation in the boys' room...
-"Then you don't have to."
-You can't say that.
That was bad!
The worst thing to say.
It would make anyone say,
"Then I'll stop sharing things with you."
I could see that coming.
"Okay, then.
You don't have to say anything."
Sounds like an ugly girlfriend.
-Indeed.
-But, at that moment,
Tap should've said something.
If it's not about dreams and stuff,
he's like...
Is that so?
"I don't know."
"I don't care what happened in the past."
But Yuriko still likes him.
-Why?
She says Makoto's still at the top.
But she went to the aquarium with Tap
and ate monja.
I don't get that either.
And Blue Note?
She whispers that she wants to go.
"I wanna go to Blue note."
It's amazing she could do such a thing.
She must really want to go.
That must be the reason.
-She really wants to go to Blue Note.
-She does.
But in that situation, guys would think,
"She wants to go with me."
We would.
-They would.
-We would.
She could've used a normal voice.
The first word was very crass.
-Remember?
-What?
-She said "expensive."
-Right.
-"Isn't it expensive?"
-She said that.
I thought, "Oh man, she's good."
She has probably wanted to go
for a long time, but it was too expensive.
That's not a juicy part.
I drooled.
Thinking she's a schemer, too.
So juicy, you thought.
What's so attractive about Makoto?
She hasn't seen
that disagreeable scene yet.
She only knows that she told on him.
Right. She hasn't seen that.
Plus, she's got a LINE message,
"I don't want to see you sad."
That's true.
She doesn't know his true colors yet.
She doesn't know his retort yet.
What do you think, Ayumu,
about Makocchan,
who you were rooting for in the beginning?
What do you say?
I'm being influenced by your opinion.
Good boy.
Is that so?
It's a comfortable place, isn't it?
What are you watching?
The previous season of Terrace House.
Can we...
talk downstairs?
-What?
-Let's talk.
Is the playroom okay?
Okay.
Sorry.
So people won't hear us.
What is this?
What's the matter?
Well...
Since the other day,
I've been feeling a little confused.
I'd been thinking...
I liked Minori a lot at first.
My feelings then, and my feelings now,
are completely different.
-Is that so?
-Yeah.
The reason is,
there was the Uchi Week, right?
He announced that he was gonna have
a date with each of you.
He said he wanted to observe each of you
when he was alone with you.
Back then, I thought it was okay...
I accepted the situation.
But later,
I felt that it was wrong.
How can girls,
without thinking too deeply,
go out with him after that?
I couldn't understand it.
Minori and I were pretty close,
and I think she knew how I felt.
But I saw her making lunch for the date.
That kind of thing
made me lose interest in her.
I honestly thought it was weird, too.
But Uchi said
that he wanted to get to know
each of us individually
and see how the relationships play out.
I was like,
"So that's what he was thinking."
-So I understood it.
-You understood it?
Minori gets along well with Uchi,
and Minori said,
"I don't think Uchi thinks that way."
Something like that.
So I thought if Minori said so,
it must be true.
After I heard that,
I thought maybe I was overreacting.
And so, now,
I have no feelings for her.
I liked her at first, but...
Nothing.
How do I put this?
But, Makocchan,
I thought you liked Minori, so I'm...
-Really?
-Yeah.
Well, I did, but...
I did...
I see...