-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week...
Misaki confessed her feelings to Hikaru,
but was rejected.
I feel like you don't know yourself.
You're insecure.
And it's those core elements to you
which I don't really like.
-And that night...
-Yes, the incident that night.
The rejection was completely overshadowed
by the incident.
Natsumi became infuriated
when Misaki said she reeked of alcohol.
I don't understand that explanation.
You're a little drunk, aren't you?
You totally reek of alcohol.
I can't help it!
I couldn't wait otherwise!
Seriously, what time is it?
-I'm sorry.
-It's 1:00 in the morning.
Then she started saying she didn't want
to be labeled as a drinker.
She doesn't want to be thought that way
because it might affect her career.
Natsumi can't seem
to control her emotions.
We found Fuyumi, the evil Natsumi,
inside her.
-Yes, her alter ego.
-She comes out at times.
She doesn't want to seem like a drunk
in front of her fans?
Well, she is an actress.
So she doesn't want
that image attached to her name.
Isn't the association with Fuyumi worse?
-That's true.
-Yes.
-You're right.
-Yeah, Fuyumi seems worse.
After that,
they had a serious house meeting.
I've been trying to change.
But it's hard to change.
Natsumi then announced
that she'll be leaving Terrace House.
I think I've figured out...
what I've been missing.
-And during the barbecue...
-That's right.
-Hikaru...
-Hikaru, too.
I'm... leaving Terrace House.
-What?
-Really.
-Seriously?
-I'm serious.
-You're lying.
-I'm not.
-So two members will be leaving.
-Yeah.
-Also...
-Yes?
Terrace House has been extended again.
Yay!
It was supposed to end after week 36,
but ten weeks have been added,
so there will be 46 weeks.
Oh, ten weeks?
Shouldn't the show just go indefinitely?
It'll air until August for now.
Life at Terrace House will continue
until the end of summer.
I see.
When the show is close to ending,
wanna go beg them not to end it?
-"Please continue the show!" Like that?
-Yeah, like, "Please!"
-Seriously.
-Really?
-For real.
-When did you decide?
Um...
a while ago.
I still can't believe it.
I hate to add more bad news, but...
I'm leaving too.
-What?
-Tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
Seriously?
This is... What?
I'm so surprised to hear
you're leaving too, Hikaru.
It's too sudden. I thought I knew
everything going on with you.
I thought for sure
you'd tell me something like that.
I didn't tell you
because I thought I could just leave.
I thought it would be easier.
Why are you leaving?
My reason for moving in
was just to have a new experience.
I just wanted a different experience.
I feel like I experienced a lot...
and I learned a lot.
So I feel like I need to be
on my own now...
and work on my modeling
and acting careers.
I want to work on those.
So let's drink tonight.
Let's drink.
-Oh man...
-You're leaving tomorrow, too?
Yeah.
I took your being around for granted.
There's so much more
I wanted to do with you.
It's not like we can't see each other.
-It's not the same.
-It's really not.
It's totally different.
Let's have a good time
while you're still here.
Man...
This is the saddest I've felt here.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
HIKARU OTA, 19 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
-Just the dishes.
-Don't clean up.
-We'll do it tomorrow.
-Stay, stay.
-Come on, drink up.
-You're always doing that, Nacchan.
Don't worry about it today.
-Yeah, Natsumi. Arman will do it.
-I'll do it.
-I'll do it!
Stop, Nacchan.
-Let's do it together.
-No, you sit.
-Maybe you should go to bed, Misaki.
-I'm not going to sleep!
Are you sure you're okay, Misaki?
I feel like you're gonna break something,
so you should just drink.
-You're already drunk.
-I'm not!
You are. You definitely are.
-You're drunk. Totally drunk.
-I'm not!
Let's hang out after you leave.
But seriously, you made me happy.
About what?
-You were right.
-About what?
When I confessed my feelings to you...
you said that I didn't really know myself
and that I was insecure.
I was really bitter about that.
Like, "What do you know about me?"
But I think you're right.
I'm glad that I fell for you.
Even though you annoyed me a lot, too!
Words from the person you like,
whatever they may be...
really affect you.
-Oh, am I being criticized?
-Yeah.
So that's why, in the future...
when you meet someone you like...
-you should be keep that in mind.
-Okay.
I'm sorry.
Let's both do our best.
-Yeah, do your best.
-I will.
Next time we meet, you'll be like,
"Wow, you've changed Misaki."
Yeah, I'll be looking forward to it.
I'll work on it.
You don't have to change too much.
I do like this part of you.
Thank you.
-I think Arman feels the saddest.
-Yeah.
You should talk to him.
-I'll get him.
-No, it's okay.
Don't! It's okay.
Seriously, I don't get it.
Arman! Your turn to talk to him now.
It's not like he's my girlfriend.
-What'd she say?
-I don't know.
-It's not anything.
-What's wrong?
I just said I was sad about leaving you,
and she said we should talk.
She acted on her own.
Isn't this kind of weird?
-Don't be embarrassed.
-Embarrassed?
Man, what's she looking at?
I'm glad we got to do this at the end.
Thanks, Arman. Seriously.
-Seriously, thanks.
-No. Thank you.
I'm the older one,
but I couldn't have done anything for you.
I'm the one who should thank you.
You really have it together.
-You can do anything.
-I still have a ways to go.
-Really.
-Thanks.
I wish we could've used the pool.
We'll have to go to the beaches
in Brazil or Hawaii next time.
I'm seriously going to visit you
in Hawaii.
-Shall we go in?
-Yeah.
That was unnecessary, but thanks.
-Bye.
-See you.
-You too, Tamochan.
-Thanks for everything.
-Thank you.
Bye, Arman.
Nacchan, thank you.
See you. Thanks.
-Come visit.
-Yeah.
Hansan.
-Be well. Good luck.
-Thank you.
You too, Hikaru.
I'm leaving with you, though.
Bye.
-Seriously, thank you.
-Bye!
YOTSUKAIDO, CHIBA
KAORI BALLET STUDIO
Okay.
Make it big.
Yes, and jump.
-Thank you.
-Good job, Momochan.
I'm going to move
into Terrace House tomorrow.
-You're moving tomorrow?
-Yes.
For someone my age,
the fact that boys will be there
-is a little worrisome.
-Yes.
I've danced with men in a pas de deux...
but that's about it...
-You've had no exposure whatsoever.
-Yes.
-I'm very nervous.
-I'm sure you are.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
You know how
I was talking about Terrace House ?
-It's been confirmed.
-Seriously?
Living with a lot of people will be tough.
Yes.
-Lucky you.
-Lucky?
If I were younger, I'd do it too.
Your cooking tastes better
when you're in love.
-Is that true?
-Yeah, of course.
Terrace House has a huge kitchen.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
Great. That means you can cook.
-I'd like to cook for everyone.
-Nice.
-It's ready.
-Good. Bring it over and let's eat.
Okay.
New members!
Did our mood change too quickly?
-Each of us has an evil Fuyumi side, too.
-Yes.
Last night,
the way Tamosan acted in front of Hikaru?
-That was really great.
-It was.
It's amazing.
How did she do it?
She was so honest.
"I'm going to work hard to change.
When we meet again, you'll be surprised."
It's not easy to say something like that.
When a girl says it like that,
it makes a guy think
that she's a classy girl.
If things are going to end,
we should all end them like that.
We should!
-If it's going to end anyway.
-Right?
It should end that way.
A bad example, though,
is when a girl brings it to that point,
and when the guy says,
"I like that part of you,"
the girl, swept by the mood,
could say she likes him again.
If she does that,
he'd have to reject her again,
and things would end awkwardly.
But instead, Misaki called Arman
and ended the conversation.
That was a good moment to end it.
I see. She gains some points there.
-She did good.
-She did.
She did good.
-And now we have a ballerina.
-Yes, a ballerina.
And she seems especially sheltered.
It sounds like
she's never really gone out with a guy.
Maybe she's a little prudish.
"I've only danced with a man
in a pas de deux."
When can you say something like that?
"I've only been with a man
in a pas de deux."
I don't think I've ever used that word.
Pas de deux is when
a man and a woman dance as a pair, right?
I'm getting some signals from the chef.
-Seems like he'd be popular.
-I have a feeling he's a hottie.
Feels different
when it's just the four of us.
-It's quiet.
-Yeah.
-It's lonely.
Oh, it's Rikopin.
-Come take a seat, Riko.
-Okay.
Can you cook, Riko?
-I can't.
-You can't? Well, we can work on it.
-It's my turn to cook on Monday.
-Oh, that's right.
-You cook well.
-I made yesterday's.
-It's Misaki's turn next.
-I'm scared.
It's delicious.
I heard her hamburger was really tough.
-Maybe I'll go to sleep.
-What?
Oh, my nose is running.
-Seriously?
-Let's go, Hansan.
Ding-dong.
-Oh, man!
-The doorbell rang.
Yes, the doorbell.
Uh, oh...
-Yes?
-I'm moving in today.
It's a girl.
Come in.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Momoka Mitsunaga.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Your head is tiny!
-Excuse me.
-Your head is really small.
-It is.
-I feel like I can grab it.
-Like you can grab it? What?
Yeah, like I can grab it.
-What was your name again?
-I'm Momoka Mitsunaga.
-So, Momochan?
-It's Momoka, but yes.
-How old are you?
-I'm 20.
-You seem older.
-Yeah.
Really?
Yay!
What do you do?
I'm a ballerina.
-This?
-Yes, that.
I'm trying to make it my profession.
I'm currently
at a professional training facility,
-and practicing in order to move up.
-Wow.
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 20 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
No wonder your posture's so straight.
-Is it? It's out of habit.
-Very ballerina-like.
-Amazing. Where are you from?
-I'm from Chiba,
but I spent five years
in Kyoto for ballet.
-Wow.
-And I just came back this April.
What about college?
No, I dance from morning to night.
-It's the first time we've had an athlete.
-Oh, that's right.
When did you start ballet?
I started gymnastics when I was three
and ballet at five.
A long time. About 15 years.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, not for a while now.
It's been one, maybe two years.
Do you drink at all?
-I'm very weak.
-You are?
One drink is my limit.
-But generally--
-What?
It's the guy.
The girls should greet him.
-Can I go too?
-Of course.
Go, go.
It's my first time doing this.
-Yes?
-I'm moving in today.
-Please come in.
-Don't make a move on the new girl.
No, I won't. It's you.
She looks like someone you'd like.
Yeah, she looks cute.
-This is very nerve-wracking.
-It is.
-Hello.
-Come in.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Can I put my luggage here?
Of course.
Please.
I'm Hayato Terashima.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-You're very tall.
-I'm 178 cm.
-Do you mind if I sit?
-Please.
-How old are you?
-I'm 29.
Twenty-nine?
-Older than me.
-Wow!
You seem younger.
-What do you do?
-I'm training to be a chef.
Wow!
Last night, we talked about
who might be coming,
and we said maybe a chef.
Really?
-What type of cuisine?
-Italian.
-Italian?
-Wow.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-No.
-Since when?
-It's been about a year.
It's been awhile.
Are there any couples here?
-No, no one.
-No one.
So cupid's arrow might be pointing
in specific directions already?
-What, now? You think?
-Don't you think?
What do you think, Momochan?
-You move quick.
-You're so quick.
-Did I jump the gun?
-He seems like a player.
He's definitely a player.
We bought drinks.
Shall we have some?
Yes, let's!
Are you okay?
-I'm fine. I'm used to it.
-Used to it?
She usually drinks water.
Welcome to Terrace House. Cheers!
-Cheers!
-Nice to meet you.
So you're not a model or anything?
I was an aspiring actor.
I intended on pursuing it until I was 30,
but my plans changed.
I've been cooking part-time for a while,
so I thought I'd become a chef.
I also work part-time
at Lindt in Omotesando.
Have you heard of Lindor chocolates?
-They have one in Shibuya too?
-Oh, yes.
-I know it.
-It's the chocolate shop.
-I work there.
-How stylish.
-Do you make it?
-No, I just greet people.
Seems like you could teach ballet.
-I did in Kyoto.
-Kyoto?
I'll start teaching here this Saturday.
-An instructor then.
-Yes.
Instructor Momochan.
Wow.
-So mature.
-Yeah.
She must come from a good family.
Learning ballet seems really expensive.
Yes, it is.
Pointe shoes can be expensive.
Are they?
They get destroyed in about two weeks.
-One pair costs about 10,000 yen.
-Whoa!
What do you do with the shoes after?
-You throw them out?
-Yeah, to the garbage bin.
Did we ask?
What type of girl do you like?
No, we haven't yet.
Someone pure.
She should be active
and relatively social.
Something along those lines.
And you Momosan?
Someone who...
you can't grasp what he's really thinking.
-Mysterious?
-Yes, it makes me want to know him.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I often tend to get that.
So, what do you think?
What about age difference?
You're okay with that?
I like older men.
How many women have you dated?
I've had about four relationships.
Yeah, four.
But he seems experienced with women.
I have a twin sister.
She's the older one.
So she had her girlfriends over
at the house all the time.
So maybe I'm experienced in that sense.
-I see.
-I grew up like that.
I think there are lots of pretty women
from Hokkaido.
That's true, there is that impression.
I often hear that people who work as cooks
don't like cooking at home.
I'm sure the girls would love to learn.
Cooking? I think I would like that.
Does anyone cook?
-Nobody.
-Do you?
I lived alone, so I can cook a little.
If you don't mind, we look forward to it.
For me to cook for everyone?
-That makes me nervous.
-Thank you very much.
-Here they are.
-Momochan is cute.
I mean, her name is Momoka Mitsunaga.
-So cute.
-She seems so pure.
-She's got a nice figure.
-Her posture...
I thought a ballerina would be super thin.
But she isn't too thin.
And her chest,
the stripes were stretched just right.
-It's perfect.
-Yes, very nice. Very nice.
-Um...
-Yes?
This whole time...
I've felt unsettled since I saw the chef.
Is it just me?
He looks like he's full of cilantro.
People who like it, like it.
He's got a really strong gaze.
It's just like Esper Ito
after his punchline.
"Ta-da!"
That's right!
At 29, he's an adult,
so maybe he felt like
-he needed to talk to lighten the mood.
-Trying to be social.
It would be hilarious
if his cooking was terrible.
They'd all whisper about it
behind his back.
"Does this taste kind of bad?"
But when he serves it,
he'd be like, "Ta-da!"
"Ta-da!"
Something could happen
between Hansan and Momoka.
Maybe.
Like, Momochan could fall for him.
-For the first time.
-Yes, she could fall for the first time.
A passionate un, deux, trois?
-A pas de deux?
-Yes.
"Will you dance a pas de deux with me?"
"I can't dance a pas de deux with you!"
"What?"
And the pointe shoes fall.
"Ta-da!"
Seriously?
"Don't come this way!"
But he'll pop out from the pointe shoes.
-Oh, man.
-You must be exhausted.
-I am. It's this strange--
-But you don't seem nervous.
I am, though.
I'm looking forward
to tasting your cooking.
What is your restaurant like?
The owner-chef was
in Italy for eight years.
-It's a really small place.
-Really?
It maybe fits 20.
About four to five tables.
How many people work in the kitchen?
Just the owner-chef, and I assist him,
and there's also a server.
So three in total.
-I want to go.
-It seems intense.
-That makes me want to go.
-Yeah.
Yeah, whenever.
-What do you think of the house?
-It's nice.
-What kind of girl did you say you liked?
-Pure.
So that's her personality.
-But guys tend to factor looks, too.
-You mean physically?
I like a balanced figure.
Momochan seems to fit
with her small head.
I'm not sure if I felt it with Momochan.
The way she looked at me...
We're both new, so maybe it was nerves.
Out of curiosity...
-what did you think of the new guy?
-He seems like he'd be your type, Riko.
He's good-looking, but he's 29.
-And his flirtiness...
-He seems like a player.
-But he is good-looking.
-Yeah.
I went to an all-girls high school.
-Oh, I see.
-So I'm not sure how to act around men.
Do you get nervous
when you talk with guys?
-If it was just the two of us, then...
-You'd get nervous?
Even if it's not a guy you like?
I've never even been on a date before.
I'd get really nervous.
-What did you think of Momochan, Arman?
-Yeah.
I think she's cute.
-She's in your strike zone?
-She's active and dances ballet.
I tend to like girls
who take care of their bodies.
-Nice.
-Arman.
We've never had an athlete before.
-That's true.
-So good first impression.
Nice.
Yeah.
She seems like a good person, too.
-Very pure.
-Yeah, she's overflowing with it.
That'll be interesting.