-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week...
-The meat crime.
-Yes, the meat crime.
The biggest crime in the history
of Terrace House.
It truly was a crime.
Watch out.
Looks amazing.
-Is it good?
-It's delicious.
Wow, is this for real?
It's not my favorite.
-This?
-Yeah, it's a little fatty.
Yeah, it's got a lot of fat.
-You're mad?
-Yeah, I'm pretty upset.
That meat was from a client who came
all the way from Nagoya to visit Blast.
And they sent the meat from Nagoya.
There's value in the gift.
I'm very sorry.
Whatever.
-He was pissed off.
-He was really pissed.
He thought he had told Minori
how important it was to him.
Right, beforehand.
The youngest guy,
tired after working construction,
went to apologize for eating the meat.
You'd think he'd say,
"No, it wasn't your fault."
Instead he said,
"I'm too upset to talk now."
Not yet.
I know it's just meat to you guys.
But it was something
that meant a lot to me.
Either way, I'm sorry.
I need to zone out for a bit.
I don't want to think about anything.
I'm really sorry.
I know it's all I can say, but I'm sorry.
I can't calm down right now,
no matter what you say.
I'm looking at his name, Uchihara,
but all I see is Meat-hara.
A first in the history of relationships,
where a couple breaks up over meat.
-Break up caused by meat.
He had told the guys the day before
that it was better
before they started going out.
Things don't seem great lately.
Yes, and then this happened.
When you have different priorities...
-You have different priorities?
-Yeah.
It would've been great
if we were just friends.
But if we're going to be
in a relationship...
then I think...
You quit your job
so that you can focus on modeling.
But I feel like you were more focused
when you were working.
Is being with me
different than you imagined?
A first in the history of relationships.
I wonder if we'll get to see
a couple break up because of meat.
You were out.
-What happened?
-I drank...
-and went to a club.
-A club?
While you were drinking,
we were getting in trouble.
-What?
-I was getting in trouble.
-With whom?
-Uchi.
Uchi got mad at you?
-Oh, because of the meat.
-Yeah, how'd you know?
-That's hilarious.
-What? You ate some, too!
-He got mad about that?
-Yeah.
Seriously, he was pissed.
-For real?
-Yeah, pissed.
That's funny.
-Why are you wearing your jacket?
-Good morning.
Your eyes are bloodshot.
I was sleeping.
-Good morning.
Work?
-Going to work?
-Yeah.
-Are you coming back late?
-Today? Yeah, I'll be late.
It's my last spurt.
The exhibition is in February?
-The exhibition got pushed back.
-It did?
Yeah, some things happened.
It'll be from March 15th to the 17th,
for three days.
But since your exhibition got pushed back,
does that mean you have more time?
-Or is that not it?
-It's because I didn't have enough time.
So it was extended
because you were too tight on time?
I see.
Well...
I'd better get going.
-Work hard!
-Thanks.
-Bye.
-Yeah.
-Take care.
-I'm off.
We watched the latest episode
of Terrace House together, right?
-Yeah.
-My sister was in it, right?
She's coming today.
-Where?
-Here.
What? Your sister?
What, now?
-My sister is coming over now.
-What?
Your sister is cute.
You should tell her that.
Don't be bothered by things she says.
-Am I in trouble?
-No, I don't know.
-I haven't done anything.
-That's true.
Maybe not someone she just meets.
Arman, my sister is coming over.
-Today? Seriously?
-Yeah.
This guy is so nonchalant.
KURUMI NAKADA, 24 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, MINORI'S OLDER SISTER
Hello.
-It's been a while.
-Long time no see.
Oh, new members.
Nice to meet you.
-Wow.
-Nice to meet you.
This is my older sister, Kurumi.
Hi, I'm Kurumi.
-I'm Natsumi.
-Natsumi?
-I'm Hikaru.
-Hikaru?
He's like the complete opposite of Tap.
-Arisa's not here?
-She's been busy with work lately.
And Uchi?
-Where is Uchi?
-Oh, he's just come back.
I think he's home already.
-I wasn't home.
-That's right.
We got in trouble.
-Got in trouble?
-With Uchi.
-Because of your lack of consideration?
-No, not like that.
There was some really nice meat
he got from a client from Nagoya.
We thought it was to share.
The night before last,
we thought we'd have it for dinner.
We didn't have any main dish besides rice.
But we had the meat,
so we decided to eat it.
-Uchi's meat?
-Uchi's meat.
So the three of us cooked and ate it.
Natsumi had already eaten dinner.
So yesterday, when I came home...
he was really quiet.
He asked, "How could you guys do that?"
He was pissed.
That's so petty.
-But the meat--
-Well, we hadn't asked him.
Yeah, we hadn't asked,
and we didn't tell him after.
Well, then you should've just hugged him
from behind and apologized.
-That's good. That would've solved it.
-Seriously, right?
-No, no. It wouldn't have.
-Why?
You can't?
That's the power of a girlfriend.
I don't think that would've been enough.
It would have.
-It would've put that matter to rest.
-Yeah.
Should we get Uchi?
-I see.
-Should I?
Uchi.
My sister is here.
-Did you know?
-Not today.
Are you still mad?
Not today.
I'm tired.
-How are things going, Arman?
-Good.
I'm just hanging around.
It's fun.
What about Arisa?
Are you two together?
No, we're not.
I was rejected.
What?
What? Why?
She said it was too soon.
We talked it out.
What? Really?
How could've it been too soon
at that point?
And since then, she's been really busy.
You should write "I'm lonely"
on omu-rice.
That's right.
I can't make omu-rice.
But that's a good idea.
How'd it go?
-He's not coming?
-What are you smiling for?
-No good.
-What do you mean?
-He won't get up.
-What?
What do you mean?
I asked if he's still mad,
but he only said, "I'm tired."
I told him you're here,
and he said,"Not today."
What?
-He should say hello.
-Yeah.
He's not even going to say hi?
If he's really this upset over the meat,
that seems pretty extreme.
Maybe I should go.
-You didn't eat the meat?
-No, I didn't.
-So he can't get mad at you.
-Right.
I'll go ask what he's thinking.
Nice.
Excuse me.
It's Nacchan.
Good morning.
Sorry to wake you.
-What's wrong?
-Well...
the two of us have never talked before.
-No, we haven't.
-No.
You seem a little depressed.
I'm not depressed.
But...
everything that I've been holding back
came out.
Because of the meat incident?
I just felt like, "That's it. who cares."
I don't wanna deal with anything anymore.
This is about Minori?
Everything.
So that's why you don't really care
that Minori's sister is here.
Yeah, it's like whatever.
Up until now,
did you and Minori often argue?
Lately, yeah.
We're so different.
The way we look at things...
is different.
It's just not what I want for myself.
It was great to be friends.
But as partners...
we're not facing the same direction.
Like, Arisa's working really hard now.
I want her to work hard alongside me.
Yesterday, I came home from work,
and the meat I was saving was gone.
-I see.
-Of course I'd be upset.
It just confirmed my thoughts.
So, are you thinking of breaking up?
I don't know. I'm really confused.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 24 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
Everyone was wondering
why you aren't joining us.
-You don't want to come up?
-Why?
Why can't I be alone?
Kurumi's here,
but you don't want to say hi?
It's all bothersome.
Then, I'll give you three options.
Kurumi will come here,
or you come upstairs,
or you stay here, sleep, and do nothing.
-Have Kurumi come here, then.
-Okay.
That's your choice?
I don't feel like talking with everyone.
-Good work.
-So...
Wait...
-Where's Uchi?
-He's not coming?
-No, he's not.
-What?
-But...
He did say a lot.
Everything he's done to live here...
He's worked really hard.
But the meat incident
just knocked loose
everything he's held back.
And now he just doesn't want to bother.
He doesn't want to put the effort
of hanging out with everyone.
It's fine that he's upset,
but he should say hi.
So, I gave him three options.
What's that?
To come talk with everyone upstairs,
or to have Kurumi go to Uchi...
or just sleep.
He chose option two.
Me? Really?
Why didn't he just tell me?
-I don't know! Ask Uchi.
-That's true.
That's a little...
Why does he talk to Minori the least?
He says it's a bother.
-That's the end then.
-We're done then.
What else?
-He talked about Minori...
-What else?
But I don't think it'll sound right
coming from me.
-Do you want to know?
-Yeah.
I do.
He said that Arisa's working hard
right now,
and seeing that inspires him to work hard.
It's fine if you're just friends,
but as partners...
He wants you guys to motivate each other.
You can say, "Then we don't match,"
and just end things
if you're fine with that.
Or is it something you can work out,
find a solution,
and take your relationship
to the next level?
It's up to you.
So it's not about the meat,
-but about things before?
-Yeah, it's an accumulation.
The meat just pushed it over the edge.
So, Minori...
maybe it's different
because I'm your sister,
but aren't there moments
when you, as friends, want Minori
to really convey her thoughts?
Yes, definitely.
-Now's that time.
-I believe now is that time.
Is it okay?
-I'm off then.
-Good luck.
Good luck.
I'll be back.
Mr. Uchihara.
Good evening.
Sorry, I made you come down.
Well...
So, I heard about the meat.
I must have been pretty stressed.
I was very stressed.
So I'm sure for them it was more like,
"Yay, meat for everyone!
Thanks, Uchi."
But that was a little different
from what you thought.
I think that's all it was.
I didn't say it was for everyone.
But from everyone's viewpoint,
if you came back with meat,
-it was like, "Oh, he brought meat--"
-I said...
I said, "Look at what my client gave me."
That's all I said.
I didn't say they could eat it.
-What did you want exactly?
-It's just...
It was taken so lightly.
And the attitude.
Let's say it was just a misunderstanding,
and then they found out how I really felt.
But it didn't feel like they were sincere.
-You didn't?
-No.
According to Hikaru,
he didn't understand what the problem was
with eating the meat at first.
But after hearing your explanation,
he said he felt really bad
and sincerely apologized.
I don't want to compromise anymore.
With anyone?
It's all such a bother now.
What you said now is exactly
what Minori usually does.
Why should I have to bend?
When others don't try to understand me,
why should I bother?
It took a lot of courage for Minori
to come see you.
Okay, she had the courage to see me.
But her words...
I couldn't feel her sincerity.
Well...
she doesn't want to just leave things
the way they are.
I think that's why Minori came here.
-It was too much of a shock for me.
-It was too much?
I was so upset...
I couldn't hold it in.
If you don't hold back,
you won't be able to explain.
I did explain, but...
I'm so fed up.
I don't even want to bother explaining.
Minori can be like that, too.
She doesn't want to bother explaining.
There's a lot that will bother her
during an argument,
but she'll just say, "I understand,"
because she doesn't want to bother.
You don't like it
when she does that, right?
Of course.
You're doing exactly the same thing.
I know it's just meat to the others.
But someone's thoughts are there.
My feelings were a part of it as well.
How that was dealt with was a shock.
I can't just say, "Okay..."
so soon.
Minori would rather talk to you in person.
The fact you're not telling her directly
is just her frustrations right now.
What normally bothers you
and what normally bothers her
should come out.
Right now, I think she'd be able to say
what she normally holds back,
and in fact, she did a little upstairs.
I think now is the time to tell each other
how each of you really feels.
I think that can lead to
the kind of motivating relationship
you're looking for.
Am I wrong?
Right.
I feel much calmer now.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I will.
The meat was more significant
than we had ever imagined.
-He's still mad.
-Yes, still.
Things with Minori just added up.
Kurumi got things moving.
-She's really amazing.
-Yeah, amazing.
I was impressed that she listened
so attentively to the meat story.
-She's such an adult.
-She's impressive, this sister.
Natsumi was amazing, too.
Explaining it all.
I think it's okay in this case.
-Really?
-Yeah, because it's all true.
But still, when she said,
"He talked about Minori.
But...
it won't sound right coming from me."
Of course she's gonna say it.
In that case, it's the same as saying,
"Please don't twist my arm."
When she came back and said,
"He told me a lot about you,"
she shouldn't have said it that way.
That's true.
-I wonder what will happen.
-Will he come to the living room?
Maybe Minori will go downstairs?
Is everyone just going
to take turns apologizing?
-One at a time?
-Yeah, one at a time.
-She's back.
-Welcome back.
Welcome back.
He said he'll talk to you.
-When?
-Now.
-Now?
-What?
And just so you know,
Uchi says he doesn't wanna talk to anyone
because it's a bother,
and that is exactly
what Minori would normally do.
Like, you don't want to bother explaining.
That's why you should tell each other
what each of you is bothered by.
We should talk it out?
This is probably the best time to say it.
Thank you very much.
You too, Nacchan.
I haven't done anything.
Go, me!
Good luck.
Wake up.
Hold on a sec.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Why are you crying?
Everything I've held back until now
broke loose.
Until now?
From this shared living situation.
It's been tough for you?
I'm tired of it.
I think.
I heard what you talked about
with my sister and Nacchan.
I heard, but never directly from you.
That upsets me.
You should always...
tell me what you really feel,
like you are now.
I know that you're really tired.
You usually just go to sleep
when you get home.
So even when you're home,
I feel like...
we don't really talk.
I can't tell if you're even interested.
Sometimes I make dinner
before you get back.
Before, you said...
if I cooked, then you would too.
That hasn't happened lately.
I feel like maybe you don't care anymore.
It made me feel that way.
I cleaned the Japanese-style room,
vacuumed, aired the futon and more...
but I don't think you even noticed.
I'm sorry.
I don't work every day, so to you,
I know it doesn't seem like
I'm working very hard.
So coming home tired
and just falling asleep
has become the norm for you.
You hang out with everyone downstairs.
You play cards with them and stuff.
I'm sorry, but I want to sleep.
What do you mean?
About talking...
It's rare that you initiate conversations.
I was afraid you'd just say you have work.
I'm sorry for that.
I don't like...
how you're too passive at times.
What's happening now...
is mostly because I'm just tired.
You, your sister and Nacchan
have all come to talk to me,
and I feel really grateful.
I'm okay.
-Don't cry.
-I'm okay.
Let's make up.
Your hands are sweaty.
-I'm sorry.
-Thanks.
I'm okay.
-Are you crying?
-I'm not.
I'm not.
It's my first time seeing you like this.
ZUSHI, KANAGAWA
You can pull all these down-facing leaves.
Start from the bottom,
and take them off in turn.
HISATO KOJIMA, OWNER
-This is the bottom, right?
-Yes.
If you pull it, it'll come off.
-All the ones facing down?
-Yes, pull all of them out.
-It feels good to pull them out.
-What?
-Feels good, right?
-Yes, it's cathartic.
-That looks good.
-Got it.
-Don't leave any behind.
-Understood.
So, Arman,
people in Hawaii don't really work.
-That's true.
-When I was in Hawaii...
I looked at the stones
lining the streets of Waikiki.
I even watched
the gardeners in the hotels.
-But they go home around 3:00 p.m.
-They do.
-They're often called slackers.
-Really?
But really...
no one works as hard as you.
-You do good work for us.
-Thank you.
How's Terrace House going?
Having fun?
-Yes, it's fun right now.
-Is it?
-You said something happened?
-Yes.
What happened with that?
She's been really busy with work lately.
We haven't really had time to talk.
I'm thinking, eventually...
I can take her to lunch or something.
But before that, you dated Mizuki, too.
It's hard to fall in love
if you keep dating around.
-That's true.
-Maybe you shouldn't date so many girls.
-It's fun to date different girls.
That's for sure.
But it's more fun to love one girl.
Especially since you look like a player.
I have a feeling it's not gonna happen.
-You're not going to sleep?
-I will.
-After I relax.
-What do you mean?
I'm going to relax here and then sleep.
-Good night.
Oh, there's tea.
Hey.
-Good night.
You're not going to bed?
Don't you think Minori's demeanor changed?
Has she?
After the meat incident?
She's happy because they made up.
She's exuding happiness.
By the way...
has anything happened with Arman?
-What? No, nothing.
-You haven't gone out after?
-No.
-Oh, you haven't.
If it's just two people,
does it mean it's a date?
It turns into a date?
If you know
you're just hanging out as friends,
then it's just an outing.
The possibility isn't zero percent, right?
Isn't it zero percent for me?
It's zero, right?
You mean you and I?
You're asking
if it's zero percent on my part?
You're asking me that?
-Why?
-I'm just surprised.
-I can't ask?
-Well...
it's not zero.
It's not zero?
-You thought it'd be zero?
-Yeah.
So it's zero on your part then?
-Two?
-Two percent?
What? For real?
Because I thought it was zero for you.
On my part you mean?
Your personality is totally my type.
-My personality?
-Yeah.
You're very much a guy's guy.
-You are.
-I don't know.
-I think I'm normal.
So, I was hoping
there'd be someone like that.
-Why do you laugh?
-I'm just embarrassed.
-Oh, I see.
-Yeah.
But it's two percent.
Then...
seventy percent.
I'm 18 though.
You're not concerned about age?
That's exactly it.
-You are concerned?
-Yes, of course.
-Wanna go somewhere?
-Where?
Maybe dinner sometime?
When you're off.
Then tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
-Yeah.
I'll cancel everything
and take the day off.
When I have construction work,
I'm done at 5:00 p.m.
We can see what day works,
and we can do dinner?
Sure.
It was a crisis.
-He was a little broken.
-It was a meat cry.
So everything, life at Terrace House,
issues with Minori
and maybe some things from work.
Everything has built up...
and exploded.
-So it seemed.
-Yes.
If that's the case, it's understandable.
-On the other hand...
-What?
If it was really just about the meat...
For the first time, we're going
to have to close the door on them.
You mean the door right here?
-Yes, from this side.
-Seriously?
But I may be curious and want a peek.
"Let's make up."
-That's right.
-What was that?
There was a power imbalance
in which Uchi kept berating Minori.
But by crying in front of Minori,
they became equals,
or maybe power tilted to Minori.
So she comforts him.
The power balance may have shifted
into a good place.
And toward the end, what was that?
-What was that?
-Natsumi and Hikaru...
It was like a scene from a bar.
Things like that happen every night.
That's true.
"Do you go out to dinner pretty often?
After work?"
"Well... tomorrow...
do you have work?"
-"No?"
-"No, not really."
-"Just gonna chill?"
-"Yeah, just taking it easy."
"You?"
"Tomorrow? I work at night so..."
"Oh, I see..."
When you guys do re-enactments,
it's totally from personal experience.
-It's too real.
-Yeah.
Those pauses...
A lot is said in those pauses.
-Do you want me to take it?
-Let's take one together.
Wow, it's really pretty.
-So lovey-dovey.
-Wow!
Is it bad?
What's with the arm move?
You guys are so close!
No, it's just normal distance.
Things look like they're going well here.
I really like you right now.
Will you be my girlfriend?
It's like...
Family? Brother? Like friends...
The more we hung out,
the more my feelings tilted that way,
I guess.
-Shall we go?
-Yeah.
It's sad.
So you were rejected?
No, I don't know...
It's vague.
It ended.
Oh, man...
Good night.
-Good night.
You approached her because you liked her.
And she said she liked you, too.
That she liked you
and wanted to go places with you.
But she hasn't said anything since, right?
-You haven't talked since then, right?
-No.
It still felt vague though.
It didn't end clearly.
Are you okay with that?
Arisa.
Are you awake?
-I just woke up.
-You did.
Can you get up?
You getting up early tomorrow morning?
About 10:00 a.m.
Can we talk?
We just watched
the latest episode on Netflix.
Where Arman told you how he felt.
I've only heard about it.
-Are you okay?
-That scared me.
That scared me.
-Can I come in?
-Come in.
I wanted to talk to you.
You were awake?
I thought you'd be asleep.
-Did she leave?
-Minori left. She's gone.
I'm tired...
and falling over.
Well...
I still have feelings for you.
You said before you still wanted to date
and continue our relationship.
But we haven't seen each other
at all this year,
and nothing's changed.
I know you're busy.
But if you feel something for me at all,
you could spare even ten minutes a day
to talk to me.
That's what I think.
So I wanted to ask one last time
how you feel about me.
I don't think I can think about you.
I have my hands full
with myself right now.
I'm not really in the mood
for a relationship.
I guess...
I don't have time to think about
anything else right now.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you cleared that up this time.
Good luck with your work.
But let's continue...
to be good housemates.
Good night.