-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week--
-There's a lot going on right now.
-There is.
-A heart-fluttering turn of events.
-Yes.
-The bike date was so nice.
-So nice.
-Hikaru and Misaki...
-Their bike date.
HIKARU OTA
MISAKI TAMORI
It was sexy.
-Are you into motorcycles now?
-I'm into them.
-Did you have fun?
-Yeah.
For real.
-I laugh more when I'm with you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-No way.
-And she made him hamburgers.
-She did.
-She even cried.
-Yes, those tears!
It was so cute.
-This is making me want to cry.
-I'm seriously moved.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Why?
What's wrong?
-What? Why?
-I'm sorry, it's not hard.
-No, it's not that.
-It's not hard at all.
It's seriously good. Really good.
-You're just relieved.
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-The two of them are so pure.
-Yes.
-It's going well for them.
-And Natsumi...
-She made a move on Hansan.
She invited him fishing.
That's right, that's right.
I like ocean fishing.
-In a boat?
-Yeah, a boat.
-But from the shore is okay, too.
-Nice.
Let's go.
With the exams,
you're probably not in the mindset.
Yeah, there's a lot going on.
It'll be a reward for all your hard work.
Yeah, let's do that.
"After all your hard work...
I'll go out with you as a reward."
She made a statement
that speaks highly of herself.
She meant going fishing would be a reward.
So it's not the fact
he gets to fish with her?
I don't think so.
She'd be a terrible person otherwise.
Oh, and Arisa...
When the exhibit is over...
I'm thinking of leaving Terrace House.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
I wonder if she's leaving this week.
I wonder.
If you were asked
to draw a clear object...
what would you draw?
I'd leave it empty.
No, you have to draw something clear.
-It's so hard.
-How about a glass?
No, not that kind of clear.
-Something more abstract.
-I know.
What about your music?
-My music?
-Sound.
Draw something that expresses sound
without drawing notes nor instruments.
But draw sound.
That, I can draw.
I don't get it.
The music inside me.
I thought of something!
See ya.
-Where are you going?
-I've got to work on my thesis.
I have to read.
I'll bring my drawing when I'm done.
Don't look.
It's nice.
It reminds me of elementary school.
-Is that a compliment?
-Yes.
-Hey, Hikaru?
-Yeah?
-Will you take me out?
-What?
Take me out somewhere.
Take you out?
I've been wondering
when you'd ask me out again.
You haven't said anything.
Yeah...
-On your bike.
-You want to go on my bike again?
Yeah, it was really fun.
Yeah, but...
You don't want to?
No, it's not that.
You don't seem like you want to.
-Did you have fun before?
-Yeah, well, I like bikes.
That's not what you're asking.
-No, it's not.
-It was fun.
-Really?
-It was.
-It doesn't seem like--
-I told you I had fun, too.
I can't tell with you.
You're a mystery to me.
-What do you mean?
-You're a mystery.
I can't tell what you're thinking at all.
It's hard to know who you are.
That means
you're thinking about me too much.
I am?
It's why you're reading into it too much.
But you're obviously thinking something.
I don't know what it is, but...
Let's decide now then.
Where do you want to go?
-Anywhere specific?
-The hot springs.
Sure, we can go to the hot springs.
Okay, it's decided then.
It's decided.
DAIKAN-YAMA, TOKYO
I wanted the girls to work on the details,
like putting on the stickers
and wrapping the catalogues.
-If you don't mind taking care of that?
-No problem.
Are you on schedule, Arisa?
-I'm catching up more every day.
-Really?
Since everyone is helping me,
I feel like I need to work harder.
If I were on my own...
-You wouldn't have?
-I would've slacked in some areas.
-Like, "Well, that's good enough."
-I see.
Tired?
A little.
-It was pretty heavy.
-Yeah.
My arms are sore.
-I hope it goes well.
-Yeah.
As long as Arisa says she's glad,
it went well in the end.
Yeah, that'd be nice to hear.
Have you talked to Nacchan lately?
-To Nacchan?
-Yeah.
Yeah, normal conversations. Why?
-You heard about the fishing?
-Oh, yeah.
She said she's going fishing with you.
I asked her if it's just the two of you,
and she said yeah.
I don't think I can go fishing with her.
-The two of you? Oh, you don't want to.
-Yeah, I don't want to.
I gave my girlfriend
a gift the other day,
a fishing rod and reel,
and I told her we should go fishing.
But I live here,
so I haven't been able to take her.
So if I go fishing now, it would look bad.
-It would be the worst.
-I think I should cancel the fishing trip.
I feel that, knowing Nacchan,
I think it's better to make things clear
rather than just pretend
it didn't happen.
Has your girlfriend said anything?
She said she misses me.
-That's it?
-Yeah.
She hasn't tried to stop you?
Like, "I can't take it"?
She might be thinking it,
but she'd never say it.
At my place the other day...
I mean the studio...
When I was working on
the mock-up for Arisa,
or rather, the model for her...
my girlfriend came over,
so I asked her to help.
She said,
"No, I refuse to help with that."
-'Cause it's for Arisa?
-Yeah.
Crazy.
-So she was jealous.
You guys are lovey-dovey then?
I'm not really sure.
There are three women in closer vicinity
than my girlfriend right now.
It's hard to ignore.
The moment I find myself
attracted to any of them...
in my mind, that's cheating.
If that happened,
I'd probably break it off.
-If it were you, you wouldn't tell her?
-Who?
-To your girlfriend, I mean.
-I wouldn't.
Not at that point anyway.
Yes?
-Can I come in?
-Sure!
-Are you by yourself?
-Yes.
-Oh, good.
-Good?
-I wanted to talk to you.
-What is it?
-Can I sit here?
-Yes.
-What we talked about the other day...
-What we talked about?
-About going fishing?
-Oh, yes.
-Well...
-Yes?
I can't go fishing with you
if it's just the two of us.
-I can't.
-Okay.
I had promised my girlfriend...
-What do you mean?
-That I'd go fishing with her.
I had promised her,
but hadn't taken her yet.
Oh, I see.
So I don't think
I should go fishing with you.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
But like you said,
I would like to talk with you more.
Okay.
-Since we haven't talked much.
-Yeah.
So...
What's wrong?
Oh...
It's nothing.
And?
-What's wrong?
-Nothing. Don't take it the wrong way.
I'm sorry.
I had other things on my mind.
I thought maybe
you'd like to go out to eat sometime?
-I came to ask you out.
-Thank you.
You did? Thank you.
I'm almost done with my work right now.
So, afterwards.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Something's bothering you.
Yeah, I am.
Store it for now.
-I don't know if I can anymore.
-I'll...
I'll lend you my ear.
I don't know if I can help, but...
Why are you crying?
-Why are you crying now?
-I don't know.
-What is it?
I don't understand
what I've been feeling lately.
Let's go now.
Let's get a drink.
-Right now?
-Yeah, let's go now.
Okay.
-That makes me so happy.
-Let's go.
It's an emergency.
Now I feel like drinking.
Let's go.
Thank you.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 19 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
EBISU, TOKYO
TEPPAN BUAISOU
What's going on?
Seriously.
When I came to Terrace House...
in the beginning, I'd speak my mind
without really taking others
into consideration.
I used to do that
without really worrying about others.
But after everything
that happened with Minori
and after I realized
how different other people are from me,
I couldn't really speak my mind anymore.
It's been really tough for me lately.
I see.
So when you said
you couldn't go fishing...
it felt like, "Now you, too?"
Not to say you were my last hope.
But at least with you,
I wanted things to be honest.
So when you said you couldn't...
I felt a little overwhelmed.
And it all came pouring out.
-I'm sorry.
-No, it's okay.
But...
What do you want to say?
You said you can't really speak
your mind anymore.
What sort of things are on your mind?
I've never been really good
at smiling for the sake of politeness.
I wouldn't normally join conversations
I have no interest in, personality wise.
But with shared living,
if I'm with everyone,
even if I'm not interested
in the conversation...
-Yeah, I get it.
-Yeah.
It's hard to just even laugh.
I'm not usually interested
in other people's relationship issues.
Really? I wouldn't have guessed.
I thought you enjoyed that kind of thing.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It seemed like you were trying really hard
to get Misaki and Hikaru together.
Yeah, that kind of thing.
-I've never done anything like it before.
-Really?
-That's unexpected.
-Yeah.
I think you should be more confident.
With what?
-With myself?
-Yeah.
In how you think.
How, if something is wrong,
you think people should say it's wrong.
It's great.
It's really an amazing thing.
Everyone's scared
of what others think of them.
I'd like to be able
to clearly speak my mind more, too.
Like you.
I think you can be more confident.
You should speak up.
You've cleared things up for me.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm glad.
We can grab a drink anytime.
Thank you.
What?
Hold on.
-Tokui...
-Hold on.
First of all, Hikaru...
Oh, right, that happened first.
I thought they'd be lovey-dovey, but...
If someone said that to me,
I'd think he wasn't interested anymore.
I mean, she asked if he had fun,
and he said,
"Well, I like bikes."
He purposefully said it was fun
because of the bike, not her.
-He's doing it on purpose, right?
-Yes, I sense an ulterior motive.
Maybe the date wasn't what he expected?
Like he's not totally sure yet, but...
But she touched him and everything.
I'm talking with Kentaro now.
And she didn't touch him.
She didn't mean to anyway.
That's not what we're talking about now.
Shut down.
Either he felt like she wasn't the one,
or his feelings have cooled off.
Maybe he doesn't like
that she's coming on so strong.
He could be that type.
I can see how Hikaru may be turned off
by her coming on too strong.
-So ungrateful.
-Do you feel the same way, Tokui?
I think most guys feel that way
to some degree.
Someone doesn't.
He's probably never had a woman
strongly come on to him.
It hasn't been triggered yet,
but he does have that switch.
I guess you have it, too.
-I have that switch?
-You do.
A switch where a woman is coming on to me,
but I won't like it?
I don't want to push a switch like that.
No one's asking you to.
You're losing interest.
Scary.
-But it's what happened after.
-Yes, after.
You all finally see
some discrepancy, right?
The exchange between
Hikaru and Tamosan was rather young.
We suddenly switch
to one that's more grown up.
-Completely more mature.
-Yes.
-From young fawns to seasoned deer.
-It did.
It certainly did!
-We suddenly became worried.
-Yes.
-From the girls' room.
Nacchan initially invited him
to go fishing.
But after thinking it over,
he decided not to go
since he had previously promised
to take his girlfriend fishing.
Not that he doesn't like Nacchan,
but just out of principle.
He should first take his girlfriend.
He went to the girls' room to explain.
He told her rather honestly
why he can't go fishing with her.
Handa did what he needed to do
and said what he needed to say.
And Nacchan cried
and he wondered if she's okay.
Handa, in his maturity,
realized something must be bothering her.
It's not because of the fishing.
-Yes, he understood that.
-Yes.
She revealed what's been bothering her.
He told her she should be who she is.
He reaffirmed her values
and she felt better. Right?
This is how affairs begin.
This is the process
from which affairs begin.
I see.
It's totally viable.
This is cheating!
Right.
It's the worst kind, actually.
-I totally get you.
-Because neither of them intends to cheat.
And then suddenly,
"Wait, I'm cheating now?"
Because after that kind of conversation,
both sides feel it's safe being friends.
And as they go to each other
to talk out issues,
feelings for each other
begin to accumulate.
Then one night, when they're both drunk...
Thank you.
I didn't realize.
I want them to stop.
-You never know. It's Hansan.
-I don't want them to see each other!
That's impossible.
They live together.
-And he said...
-No!
-"Let's go right now."
-Yes, yes.
That was already the first step
to having an affair.
-That was?
-It was a big move then.
If he had waited,
the situation wouldn't be as dire.
This is if we're discussing cheating.
-If it's cheating.
-Only if it's cheating.
Then he's very skilled, isn't he?
Hansan had dinner with Nacchan yesterday.
-What?
-You had dinner with Nacchan yesterday.
Yeah.
-How come?
-She said she was losing sight of herself.
She's having trouble
with some aspects of shared living.
-She was bothered.
-But she said she had fun.
It worked out.
-Problem solved?
-She said it was solved.
-I wonder why she told Hansan.
-It just happened that way.
But you'd think she'd talk to me.
Don't you think?
Shouldn't she talk to me?
I don't know.
Maybe she couldn't because we're close.
But I would've rather
she told me about it.
And the fact she can't talk to me
means there's a barrier between us.
-Welcome back.
I'm home.
-We were just--
-Welcome back.
-What?
-We were just talking about you.
I heard Misaki's cries.
Misaki is frustrated.
-I'm not frustrated.
-With Hikaru?
-Not with Hikaru. With you.
-Me?
-I'm sorry...
She asked what we talked about last night.
I told her a little bit.
She's upset you didn't tell her.
I pretty much tell you everything.
So I'm wondering
why you couldn't tell me how you feel.
If I always tell you
about every little thing that piles up...
you wouldn't like it.
But you're...
not saying enough.
Yesterday,
after talking to Hansan about it,
he made me feel okay
about talking more openly.
So I was planning on telling you.
It just so happened Hansan was there.
It's not because I felt like
I couldn't open up to you.
Okay.
He winked at me.
I wanted to ask Arman something.
Seeing Arisa, who's the same age as you,
work extremely hard,
and to hear
that she's leaving Terrace House...
have you thought about
what you're going to do?
I wanted to ask you, too.
Did you have a goal in mind?
No, my life has been about
going with the flow.
-I like it.
-If there's a wave, I'll ride it.
-You'll ride the wave if it comes?
-So Hawaiian.
That's so Hawaiian.
But I respect Arisa
for working toward her dreams.
I think it's great.
But my happiness isn't based
on material things or money.
What is it then?
If I can surf every morning
and be able to come home to my family...
then I'll be happy.
That's true.
That's enough for me.
-That's true.
-This is my first time hearing that.
Yeah, but it's nice.
DAIKANYAMA, TOKYO
EXHIBITION
There's a lot we couldn't finish,
but my goal is for the guests
to enjoy their time here.
Let's not forget to smile and interact
for the next couple of days.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
-It's done.
-Yay!
-It's done, but...
-I'm excited.
-Maybe you shouldn't look.
-I want to see.
-It looks so cool!
-Squint when you look at it.
Thank you so much.
I think Hikaru and the others
will be here soon.
-I'll go in as a guest with everyone.
-That's true.
No more backstage work!
-Thank you!
-Good job.
-Thank you, Hansan.
-Good luck from now on.
-I sold one earlier.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-That's great!
My first sale.
-Amazing.
-That's great.
Saria.
Welcome.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
-Can I try these on?
-Of course.
-Doesn't she look cute?
-It's so cute!
-Come look.
-It looks good on you.
I want to pick one, too.
Don't be too critical.
It's cute.
Cute!
-That was quick.
-Don't smile.
-It's a good shape.
-She's gonna laugh.
-Saria?
-That's the second time.
What about me?
What'll look good on me?
For Hikaru...
-This is amazing.
-Wow!
-A white space.
-Yes, it's what you all painted.
-It's the ones we made!
-Yeah.
-Wow.
-Yeah, it's what you all made.
-It's amazing.
-It's so stylish now.
It's nice, three guys with hats.
You guys look good.
No one's taking it off.
Yeah.
-They look good.
-Yeah.
-Amazing.
-Incredible.
It's amazing.
You made so many.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
Thank you.
-I'm glad.
-Yeah.
-The exhibit is done.
-Yeah, it's over.
That means...
I'm trying not to think about it.
How are you two doing?
Nothing's happened.
-You haven't gone out since then?
-No.
But we've been talking about
going somewhere.
Where are you going?
Have you decided yet?
Maybe the hot springs.
But I don't like co-ed baths.
-You don't? Why?
-No.
I don't want to go to a co-ed hot spring
when we're not even going out yet.
I'm sorry.
I think that's normal.
Is it?
You wanted to go to a co-ed bath?
No, I wasn't thinking about it.
I'd be pretty hurt if it were me.
-No way.
-Yeah.
This is what I mean!
What is that supposed to mean?
You need to learn more from Hansan.
You really should.
So you don't like co-ed baths.
But isn't it okay with someone you like?
Did I say I like her?
I wouldn't know.
That's between the two of you.
-He hasn't.
-No?
He hasn't said anything,
so I have no idea how Hikaru feels.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go shower. See ya.
-Good night.
-See ya, good night.
It's been like this
between the two of us lately.
No way.
Really.
Are you okay after what he said?
There were at least two things
that would've bothered me.
At least two.
I don't think he likes me.
-Why don't you just ask?
-I don't want to.
Why?
I don't want to think about it right now.
None of it.
What should be done, Tokui?
If the two of them continue to fight...
Misaki might say she's tired of it.
Hikaru says the wrong things
when he's upset.
That personality won't change easily.
That's true.
He's too sensitive.
As for the co-ed baths,
he didn't need to say he didn't want to.
That's right.
Misaki is cute.
She should be more clever
about directing him and making him
want to do things.
I think someone older
would be better for Misaki.
-She needs a 60-year-old.
-A 60-year-old?
-That old?
-Yeah.
-Otherwise...
-Retired?
Both of them are immature.
They fight over every little thing.
So the two of them make a perfect balance
to the love triangle between Natsumi,
Hansan and Hansan's girlfriend.
-I want to see both.
-Me too.
Yes, but what about
Arman's life philosophy?
-He said it very clearly.
-Yes, he did.
"I go with the flow
and ride the wave when it comes."
"It's enough to have a family
waiting at home."
Maybe he has something we've forgotten
growing up and living in Japan.
-As someone who grew up in Hawaii.
-Hansan got that, too.
That's why at the end
he said, "Yeah, it's nice."
But I wonder if I could say nice.
Oh, but it was a rather dramatic night.
Wasn't it?
All three girls cried.
It was very emotional.
But Arisa will be leaving.
-Yes.
-The exhibit is over.
She worked hard.
Will a new member appear now?
Hot!
Thank you for your help.
-Looks good.
-Lasagna for my gratitude.
-Wow.
-Smells good.
It looks delicious.
Thank you, everyone,
for helping with my exhibit.
Of course!
It helped me a lot.
Ready? Bon appétit!
Have some.
Did you make this from powder?
No.
-What do you mean by powder?
-It's tasty.
It's good.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
What's this?
It looks super good.
It's my way of saying thank you
for helping me.
Really?
This isn't enough then.
I knew you'd say that.
I'm glad I got to see the exhibit.
-You really came alive.
-It was really cool.
I thought it was like
a grand gesture of departure.
But you worked really hard
and made it happen.
And I know you were busy,
but seeing the final result
made me really understand.
I've decided to leave.
But every day has been fun.
At times I wasn't sure
if coming here was a good idea,
but right now I'm truly grateful.
It's like I have another home.
I'm so happy.
To be honest, I never thought
I'd not want to leave.
I'm going to keep working hard
so you'll say that I'm doing my best.
I hope you guys work hard, too.
Thank you.
We all made this for you.
-What's this?
-It's for you.
I don't remember when we took these.
It brings back memories.
Arman, I can't read English!
Will you read it, Arman?
No, not in English!
In Japanese!
"Thank you for all the great memories.
Continue to pursue your dream.
Good luck."
Thank you.
-See you, Arisa.
-See you!
Thank you.
Good luck.
-Bye, Arisa!
-Bye!
-See you later!
-Good luck.
-Bye!
NAGOYA, AICHI
-You've packed everything?
-Yeah.
-Will you double-check for me later?
-Sure.
You'll be okay in Tokyo?
I didn't think I'd leave you so soon, Mom.
Seriously.
You can come home anytime.
Yeah, I will.
Will you be okay living with boys?
I won't be okay.
I wonder if you'll find someone you like.
That would be nice.
If I can grow in some way
or gain something there...
-I think you will.
-I think so, too.
And then if I can come home,
I'll be happy.
-Be careful.
-Yeah.
I'll go now.
-Call me anytime.
-Yeah.
Come home if you don't like it.
-Bye. Be careful.
-Bye.