-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
That's right.
So as of last week,
Terrace House began its new season.
Yes, yes.
Our location moved to Tokyo
where six new members moved in.
The first one was Makoto Hasegawa.
No one's here.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
Well...
He's on the university baseball team.
He's 21 years old.
Oh, he's still on the team?
His elbow is injured.
-Yes.
-He's a pitcher.
He seems popular among the girls.
Yes, he does.
He seems to be a mighty man
with a tender heart.
And then we have Midori Nakada.
That's Minori Nakada.
That was close.
-Nice to meet you.
-I am Makoto.
-I am Minori Nakada.
She's a model, and she's 21 years old.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
-And then Yuki Adachi.
-There it is.
Do you work?
Work... I tap dance.
I've been active as an instructor
and a performer.
YUKI ADACHI, 27 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
Amazing.
I've never met one before.
-Please come see my performance.
-I will.
My dancing is all right.
-A professional tap dancer.
-Yes.
He's 27 years old.
He's the oldest out of all of them.
And then Mizuki Shida.
I'll be 23 soon.
In clothing?
No, it's a company related to soccer.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
The president of the company runs
various enterprises,
and one of them is a cafe.
I also work as a barista there
twice a week.
Well, the barista here is 22--
Her name isn't "barista."
It's "Ms. Shida."
It sounds like a foreign baseball player.
Barista!
-Then Tatsuya Uchihara, the hair stylist.
-There he is.
-Hello.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
HAIR STYLIST
-He's holding something.
-It's a sewing machine.
-I look forward to living with you.
-Likewise.
I'm a hair stylist at Daikan-yama.
Why the sewing machine?
I've recently got into sewing.
So the machine is for clothes.
So he's pretty hip.
And he works at Daikan-yama.
Not a single bad trait.
But Mr. Tokui pointed out
his voice is a little high.
Yes, he's been rather active
with opening things up.
Yes, he's been asking
some pertinent questions.
Like, you're into this girl.
It would be Mizuki.
And finally, Yuriko Hayata,
a fourth-year med student.
Yes, that's right.
She'll be a doctor.
I am Yuriko Hayata.
I'm 23 years old.
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
What type of university?
-It's a medical university.
-Wow.
A doctor?
Yes, I aspire to be one.
You know girls with names like "Yuriko,"
where the Chinese character "Yu" is--
Like the famous lyricist.
I've been told to watch out for girls
with that character "Yu" in their name.
Something tells me
things will be tricky with her.
You think?
Things will move a bit this week.
People have stated their interests.
"Oh, I like her."
-Things should move.
-Yes.
I'm off to practice.
-Makoto
She's coming?
What do you want to drink?
-Orange juice.
-Orange juice is fine?
I also want some cereal.
-Thank you for this meal.
There she is.
-Good morning.
-Oh, hey...
Only the girls?
The only one left is Yuki.
-Thanks for the cereal.
-Anytime.
That's so difficult. What are your hours?
Usually until 7:00 p.m.
-Oh. 7:00 p.m.?
-10:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m.?
Yes.
It must be nice to have a day off.
You'll go into the pool today, right?
TOKYO
DAIKAN-YAMA
What about the girls?
The girls are pretty cute.
He's laughing.
He's smiling.
I see.
MIKI TAKEUCHI, DIRECTOR OF THE SALON
-So is there someone you like?
-Well, we just started, so...
Yes, there is.
Just by looks?
Yes, just appearance.
It's still early.
We'll see what you say in a month.
I might start going out
with someone or something.
You should cut their hair for them.
And they will all like me.
I am greedy.
Yes, right this way, please.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA (23)
HAIR STYLIST. FROM CHIBA.
WORKING AT BLAST HAIR SALON SINCE 2012.
SINGLE FOR 4 MONTHS.
TOKYO
SENDAGAYA
MIZUKI SHIDA (22)
OFFICE WORKER. FROM IBARAKI.
WORKING AT EUROPLUS INTERNATIONAL
SINCE 2015.
SINGLE FOR 2 YEARS.
The event attendance is not very good.
I want to increase the exposure.
Will the athletes be there?
No, they won't.
Why don't you make a proposal?
Can I ask?
Sure.
This is for the washing machine.
Is it in the basement?
-Should we put them by it in the basement?
-Yes.
I'm home.
He's home.
-Welcome back.
-We're here.
-Hey.
Baseball from head to toe.
-Welcome back.
It's hot.
You're home early.
Yes, I am.
It's early.
What?
-What time is it?
-1:00 p.m.
1:00 p.m.
It's so hot.
What were you doing?
-We bought stuff.
-We bought a bunch of stuff.
Like containers and stuff.
-Ah, I see.
-Slippers and stuff.
-Makocchan.
-Yes.
Can I use my hand?
How's the taste?
-It's so loud.
-The inflating sound.
-That looks good.
-Thanks for the meal.
Delicious, delicious.
Yummy.
Was your practice just in the morning?
-Just the morning.
-Oh, right.
Okay then, I will eat that.
I can't eat any more.
-Can I leave the shiso leaf?
-Yes.
Is this how you eat normally?
I eat well when I do eat.
But, generally, I...
dance and then I eat a lot in the evening.
You're heavy if you eat too much?
I guess so.
Can I eat all of it?
Please.
So I'll tidy up.
Right.
Meanwhile, the women will get ready.
Please.
-Are you sure, it's okay?
-Of course.
Thank you.
Then I'll go.
Okay.
-Are you curious?
-About what?
Tits?
Yeah.
I like asses more than tits.
-You like asses?
-Yes.
-Really.
-Yeah.
I like tits.
What kind of ass do you like?
Really perky.
It'll get all weird.
Then tell me which one you like,
-just quick so I can understand.
-Okay.
-I'll say the color of the bathing suit.
-Hey?
If it's blue, let's say like, "Cool!"
-I'll say, "Blue!"
-Blue!
It's hot.
You're good.
It's cold.
It's awesome.
Here they are.
We've been waiting.
It's fun already.
For sure.
I wonder if it's deep enough.
Should be okay.
It's cold.
Blue!
It's a nice blue.
It's cold.
The look on your face...
after you said, "Blue!"
It's cold.
-Lady in blue.
-Yes.
Here comes the sun.
It's out.
Yeah!
Look at this.
-Look at my hair.
-It looks like seaweed.
Look.
Woops.
Just great.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 27 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
We just hung out yesterday too.
It's like we've got too much free time.
Things will resume next week.
Are you busy with school?
-I'm busy before tests.
-Do you have lots of tests?
I have one every month or so.
When are you busy?
I have my thesis,
so I will be busy with that soon.
So for your thesis,
do you research then write it?
I do experiments in the lab,
so I present the results.
What kind of experiments?
Fish experiments.
-Fish?
-Fish.
We keep a bunch of killifish at the lab.
And we make them learn to do things.
Like conditioning?
-Yes, yes!
-Yeah, I get it.
-That's what it is.
-I see.
You're the first person to get it.
Like if they do something, they get food?
Do you experiment on animals?
-What...
-Do you?
I've done dissections.
On mice?
Frogs and mice.
And humans.
I guess everyone does that in med school.
Yeah, I think so.
We're home!
Welcome back.
-What?
-It's hot.
-He's awake.
-Wait a minute.
Just the two of you?
-Just the two.
-Everyone's awake.
Happy?
I'm done for today.
I'm in a good mood.
-Is there a Minori bowl for me?
-Yes, there is.
I'm gonna eat.
-What's a Minori bowl?
-A Minori bowl.
Is Uchi asleep?
-I don't think he's home yet.
-He's not back?
It's late.
-What time is it?
-It's just before midnight.
Thank you for the meal.
-Yum!
-She's low on energy.
-Yeah, low on energy.
-Delicious!
Are you okay?
Are you really playing baseball?
I am.
It doesn't look like you're being careful.
-When you have the game...
-Do you even know the rules of baseball?
-I do.
-Oh, really?
I told you I was an assistant
for a baseball team.
Really? You can keep score?
Yes, I can.
Yeah. Do you need me to?
But you probably have one already.
Yes, we do.
-I think I'll go.
-It's not that we need...
It's different when someone
wants to do it out of kindness.
-No pressure.
-Hmm?
I'm off to bed.
-Good night.
-Good night. Sorry.
-It's okay.
-Good night.
Good night.
So you're rather familiar with baseball.
Yes, I am. That's why...
-I do still go to ball games.
-Really?
I went to boys' school.
I envied teams with girl assistants.
-Here, this is yours.
-By the way...
I don't know how to keep score.
Want me to teach you?
I'm not sure if I can remember exactly.
-I might have forgotten.
-Oh, I can't.
Check it out.
A game?
Really?
I am in my uniform.
-Are you there?
-Yes, I am.
-Furthest to the right?
-Yes.
I'm sure you're judging.
I'm not wearing any make-up.
-It says October 31st.
-Who did you lose to?
-Let's see. Ura-Gaku.
-Ura-Gaku? From Saitama?
-They're really good.
-Yes.
-Are you okay not sleeping?
-I guess I will go.
We can talk forever about this.
-Yeah.
-So we'll do this again.
Yeah, there's a good vibe there.
Yeah?
It's the late '90s...
-Yes, the late '90s.
-Kind of vibe.
It's like the post-trendy vibe
from the late '90s or something.
Just a bit.
-She said they could talk forever.
-Yes.
"So we'll do this again."
"Again."
That's the vibe from the late '90s?
Yes, where the woman is
a little tougher.
I see.
Do you think they'll hook up?
But didn't Tatsuya say who he's into?
-That's right.
-Yes.
Oh! He knows that his friend likes her.
Man, you really get it.
He totally remembered it.
Something we adults have forgotten.
He may be thinking of her
just as a friend.
I don't know. Friendships between
men and women don't really exist.
Are we in space?
-Sorry.
Sorry.
Everyone probably thought,
"Who is he to know something like that?"
That's what that pause was.
That's why I had that choking feeling.
Just... "Ack!" You know...
By the way, Minori's body.
Body?
-It's spectacular.
-It really is.
The tap dancer might also have been
knocked out by that.
-I think Tap has.
-Yes,
Tap did seem to be in
a good mood at night.
-He must have danced hard that day.
-Tap?
Like, the others would notice,
"Hey, your tapping sounds chipper today.
-What happened?"
-"Oh, really?"
-"Hey, something sounds different."
-"I think you are in love."
By how he sounds!
Yes, all by his tap moves.
Like, "Hey, how's it going?"
Tap talk?
-Tap talk.
-Tap talk!
I want to see him talk with his tap moves.
"I like you."
And then...
"What?"
"I can't hear you."
By tap!
So trendy!
We've gone back to the '70s!
YURIKO HAYATA (23)
MED STUDENT. FROM FUKUOKA.
SINGLE FOR 1 MONTH.
TOKYO
TAMA
TAP DANCE CLASS
Faster now!
INSTRUCTOR: YUKI ADACHI
Ready, and one, two, three,
four, five, six.
Synchronize with each other.
Eight... One, two, three, four...
And one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
And one, two, three, four...
Okay, from the single time step, everyone.
Okay. Ready.
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah.
Five, six, ready...
YUKI ADACHI (27)
TAP DANCER.
FROM TAMA, TOKYO.
STARTED TAP DANCING AT THE AGE OF 7.
No jumping. Ta-tah, ta-tah...
To the side.
WON TAP DANCE BATTLE JAPAN OPEN
3 YEARS IN A ROW. SINGLE FOR 9 MONTHS.
To the back.
Step firmly.
The other side.
Hey.
-Hi.
-Oh, he's back.
-All done for the day?
-I've been home.
-I was in the bath.
-Oh, right.
Thank you.
-Is it done?
-Not yet.
A bit more.
Like a mom.
-What?
-Like a mom.
-Like a mom?
-A housemaster.
Hey, now that we're here,
let's figure out the birthday.
-It's almost his birthday.
-That's right.
What is everyone's schedule like?
Do you have something?
I'm off on the 19th.
I'm working.
-That, I know.
-I'll go look.
I'm off the 18th.
That you can't change.
It's finally ready.
-Thanks for the meal.
-Thanks for the meal!
Delicious.
It's good.
-I'm glad.
-What was this again?
-Grilled fish?
-It's cod.
It's been a while
since I've had a meal like this.
-He can't do the 18th.
-No?
-So the 19th.
-The 19th.
What will we give him?
We don't know much about dance.
He said he wears his swim trunks
for his rehearsal.
What kind of swim trunk was he wearing?
-A fish pattern.
-Fish?
-Were they green?
-No.
-Not that?
-White and blue.
As expected, you are observing well.
You too are buddies.
-What color does he like?
-Stop teasing me.
I wonder what would be good.
-If you said, "Yuri picked it for you..."
-Then he would wear it.
He would be happy for sure.
-Maybe Minori could pick.
-You just need someone cute.
No, not me.
Girls often have
this issue of being too modest.
-Definitely.
-It's not good.
-You think you're pretty cool, huh?
-I do.
Yes, I do.
-That was good.
-I'm full.
-I'm full. Thanks for the meal.
-Thanks for the meal.
-So, for now,
as a plan,
we'll go with that.
I'm gonna go do my laundry.
I'll...
You do it every day.
Teach me.
Sure.
You do a lot of laundry, Makocchan.
Yes, I have a lot.
Do you wash your practice uniform by hand?
-Or throw them in a machine?
-Yes, I throw them in.
When I was in the laundry room,
there were two big piles.
That's before the wash, right?
-That's done.
-Those were washed?
-Where do you dry it?
-It was really smelly.
-She said it was smelly.
-It was stinky.
No, really?
-It was really smelly.
-That's trouble.
I'm screwed.
Oh, you're done.
I didn't say it.
Oh, you did.
"It's smelly."
-I did.
-Yes, Yuri said it, too.
-The women on the right and the men, left.
-Ah, that's the rule?
-But I am using both machines.
-Oh, that's fine.
Let's see.
-This one?
-Yes.
Phew.
Which do you put in?
He knows what he's doing.
-He's good.
-And?
-Start?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Everyone seems decent at cooking.
Mizuki's pretty good.
Is it that thing?
It's about being modest at first.
-Why?
-At first you said you couldn't cook.
Well, just not good enough
to treat other people.
-I see.
-Yeah.
I wonder why...
women are so modest.
When I say that someone's cute,
they all squeal or make a fuss...
then praise each other.
Well, that's all we can do about it.
Why, isn't it about
whether you really are cute or not?
It depends how well we know each other.
So if we are close,
we can say, "That's not cute."
-But if not, we say, "Oh, that's cute."
-You say that?
That's harsh.
It's cool in here.
So?
What do you mean?
-What is it?
-Oh, you know.
-Like, what? Really.
-How is it?
-Nothing yet.
-No?
-Just checking it out.
-Right.
Things have changed since the beginning.
-It's changing?
-Yeah.
Really?
Such as?
Unexpectedly, actually.
-Like, Yuriko was around here.
-Yeah.
But now she's going off like so.
She's come a long way.
Don't you have feelings like that?
-No?
-Not yet.
-It hasn't been a week yet.
It hasn't been a week yet,
but you can kind of see.
-Their silhouettes are starting to show.
-Yes, slowly.
-We start from here.
-From here.
That's the most romantic
laundry room ever.
That's true.
Yes, two washing machines in the dark.
He was saying something there.
You know...
Yes, about Yuriko.
Yes, Tatsuya did.
Yes, he's someone who rates people.
The typical attitude
of a handsome guy is coming out.
But he also works hard.
It's attractive.
Although, the client would be thinking,
"He's attractive,
but his voice is too high."
"I have a bad feeling.
It's just, a little too high.
I have a bad feeling."
"I have a bad feeling.
It's too high."
Why make it sound like a ghost tale?
Yeah, why do we mimic Junji Inagawa?
JUNJI INAGAWA
"There's something strange.
He's tall and good looking.
But I have a bad feeling.
I just can't place it.
His voice is too high."
What about the cooking?
They don't really know each other, there,
and then the barista makes that fish meal.
That, for you, is a bit too early
to make that kind of meal?
Well, from a guy's perspective,
that comes off as a really good quality.
It's not excessively fancy.
But it was a simple way of saying,
"I can cook."
Also, to tell you the truth,
cooking with foil is super easy.
-You don't need to do much.
-Oh, really.
I think she knows that.
-I see.
-I think she's brilliant.
Even for the women,
it's not something extravagant.
-Right? The best choice.
-Yes.
So for women,
there is a dish that is extravagant?
A quiche.
Just now...
when I put on my pajamas, Yuri said,
-"Is that from soccer?"
-Which?
-Lakers.
-That's basketball, right?
-Basketball.
-You know that?
-Duh! Really?
-It says "Basketball" on it.
I saw it from far away.
Then she said,
"Aren't basketball players kind of cool?"
Yeah.
Aren't basketball players the coolest?
-I think soccer.
-Soccer?
Okay, here we go.
-This is Monk Grab?
-Yes, Monk Grab.
So you like boys who play basketball?
Boys in the basketball team--
I had to think!
Were you dating someone
from a basketball team?
I had feelings for this one
since elementary school.
In high school,
it's pretty important
which group you're in.
What kind of guys did you date?
Soccer players, the whole three years.
-Oh, really?
-Me, too.
-The soccer team?
-Soccer's cool, yeah?
-What club was Uchi in, you think?
-I think he said soccer.
He seems like a soccer guy.
He seems comfortable with women.
Let's play President.
Something we can play slowly.
What were we talking about?
Oh, right, from this.
-So what's your type?
-Right, from the Lakers.
Just like I said before.
-Tall.
-Yes. And calm.
-And calm.
-You know, people that are calm...
Well, there are only three of them.
Which one would it be?
I guess Makocchan seems calm.
Right.
If you're thinking about marriage,
you can't just casually date anymore.
-Anymore?
-Yes.
Even more so
if you're already in the work force.
You don't think about it?
Don't you think about getting married?
-I want to get married already.
-Already?
-Well, I'm in my fourth year.
-Oh, right.
I guess after graduation.
Well, if you want marriage to happen then,
you've got to start dating now.
What type were you into again, Yuri?
-Out of the three of them?
-Yeah.
-Makocchan.
-He's number one?
Right.
But isn't that the same with everyone?
-Makocchan has two votes.
-He's easy to like.
His general vibe is nice.
Makocchan?
He got all three votes.
-Wait, so we're all into him?
-I am surprised.