-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week...
Oh, yes, the loungewear incident.
They made up in the end.
-Yes, even after Rikopin's talk...
-After the talk with Hansan.
...she still didn't understand
until after talking to Hansan.
However you may feel,
the fact Misaki got angry means
you didn't consider her enough.
It depends on each person.
She didn't look like she accepted that.
But they did have dinner together.
-They did.
I think I did say things
without considering your feelings.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
There's another big incident.
The one that's been dragged out until now.
Yes.
I like you, Hikaru.
So, if you feel the same way...
I'd like to go out with you.
That's how I feel.
But going by Hikaru's expression...
-It might be a no.
-Yeah.
Throughout the entire date,
we all said Hikaru's heart wasn't in it
Yeah, going by his attitude...
The level of excitement was uneven.
-He hasn't given his answer yet, though.
-That's right.
We're just making assumptions.
-He might say yes.
-Yeah, it could be the opposite.
-It might be "Me too."
-What?
I invited you out today so that...
I can tell you...
how I feel.
Thank you.
I was attracted to you at first...
so I invited you out on my bike.
And as I got to know you,
there were good things,
but I saw the bad, too.
Like...
I feel like you don't know yourself.
You're insecure.
And it's those core elements to you
which I don't really like.
So I didn't invite you out a second time
because I put my feelings on hold.
But you asked me out,
and it genuinely made me happy.
And I thought, "I want to go," so I came.
But I don't like you like that.
-I understand.
-So, I can't go out with you.
I understand.
But for you to suggest
what is core to me...
makes me really sad.
So I...
I'm going to try my best
to show you otherwise...
from now on.
I appreciate you telling me
how you feel.
Okay.
Shall we go home?
It's so pretty.
I guess Yokohama is a city of rejection.
-Is it? Has this happened to you before?
-No, no.
-Already experienced it?
-No.
Maybe people who see the city lights
get rejected.
What? I've never heard that before.
-Welcome back.
Welcome back.
How was it?
You seem exhausted.
-You're so down.
-Yeah, really down.
She confessed her feelings to me.
She told me...
but I rejected her.
You couldn't see her that way?
She's just a friend to you?
As I got to know her...
it never occurred to me...
that I wanted her to be my girlfriend.
There's no need to feel so down.
But for her to be so forward
and tell me how she feels...
I've never experienced that before.
I've never given a second thought
to rejecting someone.
It's always been like,
"Sorry, I'm out."
I've been pretty cold.
But I live with Misaki...
and it's not that I don't feel anything.
I can't explain it.
Oh, no!
Hold on, I'm scared.
-I'm scared.
-You're a little drunk, aren't you?
-She is.
-I'm scared.
Hold on.
Wait, hold on.
Oh, no, don't! Hold on!
Don't cry.
Hold on!
-I'm scared.
-Come here, come here.
-I was rejected.
-No.
-Are you okay?
-I'm okay. I'm okay.
You're scaring me.
I've been anxious all day.
-You're drunk, Nacchan.
-I'm not.
-You said to have drinks ready.
-She's been worried.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys...
for all your support.
It's okay to cry.
Thank you, guys.
He said I was insecure
and didn't have a strong sense of self.
Or that's what he thought.
That's what put an end
to his feelings for me, I guess.
Are you okay with that?
It made me...
want to prove him wrong.
It was hard to hold back the tears.
You're totally drunk, aren't you?
-Wanna drink, too?
-I mean, it's fine, but...
you totally reek of alcohol.
I can't help it!
I couldn't wait otherwise!
Seriously, what time is it?
-I'm sorry.
-It's 1:00 in the morning.
I'm sorry about that.
That's my fault.
I've been so anxious,
I had to have a drink.
-Seriously.
-I didn't know that you were.
Sorry.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
HIKARU OTA, 19 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
-It's so cold today.
-Is it?
Oh, is that coffee?
Oh, sorry.
I bought this since we're out.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
I should've asked you.
Have you talked?
-With Nacchan?
-Yeah.
No.
-Do you remember what happened?
-Yeah, totally.
-Really?
-Yeah, I mean, I was balling.
It sucks.
I get rejected and...
Nacchan was drunk or buzzed.
Then she started saying she didn't want
to be labeled as a drinker.
So she didn't like that I said
she smelt of alcohol...
or that she seemed drunk.
She doesn't want to be thought that way
because it might affect her career.
So then I told her not to come home drunk.
Then she got mad
and told me she drank
because she was so anxious for me.
Remember when she said
she chose the outfit for me?
-She did.
-That's right. She did.
And how she came home for me?
So why would I say things
like that to her?
And you cried
after she said that a couple of times.
You were like,
"Why can't you let me go today?
I was just rejected.
I'm depressed.
I can't think about anything else."
Yeah, I really couldn't.
Plus, I apologized, like, three times!
You did.
You kept saying you were sorry.
Then she told me I was lucky
I didn't have to think about anything.
-Of course you think about things.
-Yeah.
She saw everything I went through.
I've actually talked to her
about this before.
But this time, she did exactly
what I told her she shouldn't.
That means she didn't really take anything
from our conversation.
She's repeating her actions
even though she said she gets it.
Yeah, she can't just say it.
She doesn't understand the issue at all.
But if she can't...
then she can't, right?
If you've already talked to her.
We're not rejecting her as a person.
She has so many great features.
-She does.
-So let's keep that in mind.
-Then let's have a meeting to talk it out.
-Yeah.
What she said made you feel bad, right?
Yeah.
It started
because I didn't like what she said...
Well, Misaki came home
after she confessed her feelings, right?
We got ready for it together.
I was really rooting for her.
I felt really anxious for her.
To be honest,
I thought it would turn out well.
So for her to tell me...
I reeked of alcohol...
It really upset me.
I didn't say it then, but...
Well, it couldn't be helped
if you smelled of alcohol.
Misaki told you that you smelt of alcohol.
So if she really thought that,
there's nothing wrong with her saying it.
Yeah, I didn't say she couldn't say it.
I just didn't like it.
I thought you and I...
have talked a good amount.
You've asked
how you can relate to other people.
I thought that you had made
progress in the right direction.
But this made me think
you didn't really hear what I said.
Misaki was crying,
saying she was just rejected,
and she couldn't really think about
anything else.
But you didn't let things end there.
You mean how she asked me to forgive her
and I didn't?
You didn't.
You demanded to know
why she'd say something like that to you.
You asked her to stop
because it would affect your image.
I think we have talked about
how there are times
you need to restrain yourself.
I understand.
You're that kind of person,
and I admire you for it.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-You cut your hair?
-I did.
Why don't you use the restroom, Misaki?
Go use the restroom.
I'm sorry.
-Excuse me.
-Sorry, you were saying.
But this time...
I don't feel like I need to apologize.
I just said what I felt.
I'm telling you
because you didn't just say it.
It's your attitude and the way--
Well, I had drank.
But...
everyone was heated then.
But things got heated
because it was so bad for Misaki.
We had to intervene.
-Yeah.
-It was a bad situation for Misaki.
That day anyway.
Was I really being that demanding?
-You were.
-Yeah, you repeated it twice.
She was balling...
and she was apologizing to you so hard.
That's why I said it was fine.
But the conversation wasn't over, right?
Sorry, I need to step out for a smoke.
It just feels like
this might happen again.
This is the second time, so it might.
Even if Misaki's careful,
it could happen again.
So how can we fix it?
When you guys went out for dinner,
did you guys talk things out?
We understood each other then.
But...
after the alcohol thing,
now I'm not so sure.
Like, how you can say
I don't have to think about anything?
That part.
Just that part?
Friends don't usually say
things like that.
You knew what I was going through.
I think it would better if I weren't here.
I'll go.
I apologize for the things I've said.
I drank too much.
I don't feel like it's sincere.
I do really feel that way.
I was drunk and said too much.
I'm sorry.
Please continue for now.
I'll go. Good night.
But this is for you.
So, do you feel like it got through?
I give up.
-Too awkward?
-I give up.
It's just gonna happen again.
That was...
scary.
It must have been really bad.
We're supposed to be getting worked up
about Hikaru's rejection...
But instead we get another incident.
The rejection was overshadowed
by the she-said-I-reek-of-alcohol trouble.
"Don't say I reek of alcohol."
"I didn't reek of alcohol."
Like that?
"Yes, you did."
That exchange is like
something from Cops.
"Have you been drinking?"
"Of course not.
I took a two-hour nap. I'm fine!"
When someone is hurt or depressed,
you usually try to give that person
all of your attention.
But she tries to add
all her issues on top of it.
-Why?
-"You made me so worried for you!"
Would you be able to say that
to someone who was just rejected?
Yeah, she just said to someone
who came home rejected and crying,
"It's 1:00 in the morning!"
It's unimaginable.
Natsumi tends to say, "I did it for you.
I helped choose your outfit for you.
I waited until 1:00 a.m. for you."
Then she gets upset
when someone doesn't show appreciation.
Isn't this the third time
this kind of thing happened with her?
The rate of repeated offenses is high.
That's true.
If she stays for all the episodes,
then everyone would understand
that she's just like that.
She should just convince everyone
by sneering at them.
She could say to Arman,
"Hey, go back to Hawaii."
-That'd be interesting.
-Right?
In the end, she'll be like Takeyama
and just get angry at everyone.
"What's wrong with you?"
They should have a spin-off
where Natsumi just goes berserk.
Yeah.
"We've got another
short-tempered person for you today."
I'm wondering about Hikaru's statement
that Misaki doesn't have a core.
Oh, when he rejected her.
Would you rather talk about that?
-Yeah.
-That's true.
That was an all-out rejection.
"I don't like your core."
That was cold.
Because he lives with her
and cares about her,
maybe he felt like
he needed to give a reason.
Tamosan is an optimistic girl
and wants to prove him wrong.
So it's taking
a positive direction at least.
I'm sorry.
All I can think about is the drunk.
Like, who cares about that?
It's stuck in my mind.
Rikopin...
can we ask you to get her?
Sorry. Because if we go...
Wait. I think it's better if I'm not here.
-You should be here.
-Don't worry.
-It's okay?
-You should be here.
Sorry, Natsumi.
I think it'd be better to talk it through.
We're not rejecting you as a person.
I really want you to know that.
Misaki came home rejected and hurt.
You understand that feeling best,
especially because
you thought it would work out.
She came home depressed.
Because of that...
you needed to hold back
some of your own needs.
And helping her with her outfit
and anxiously waiting for her...
it's really great of you.
There's no need to say it.
It's already understood.
Are you even listening?
I am. Of course I'm listening.
I have to try to get along.
I know I have to put in the effort.
I know that's the best solution.
But being here, trying to get along...
is that fun for you?
-Are you just forcing yourself?
-I don't know.
After Hansan talked to me...
when we talked at his atelier...
since then...
I thought it over
and tried to act accordingly.
But in that situation...
I guess that part of me came out again.
I feel like it's just gonna happen again.
She's probably back to herself again.
I'm trying my best to change.
But if I slip even a little
in that kind of situation,
someone says, "Oh, she's reverted."
I know that the solution
is for me to change.
I'm saying it because I think it.
I've been trying to change
since Hansan talked to me.
But it's hard to change.
I am really sorry
about the things I said the other day.
So please don't say,
"Oh, it's just gonna happen again."
I'm proud of you for apologizing.
But to be honest,
I don't know you anymore.
I don't know what's real and what's not.
Right now...
I don't know you.
What do you mean by what's real?
I'm thinking
that everything you showed me...
wasn't the real you.
Her emotions really came through
in her apology right now.
She didn't just say it.
She apologized and tried to change.
-I felt the emotion.
-Yeah.
Is it still not enough for you?
You're still not sure?
I'll act the same way I have been.
But if it's so hard,
I don't think you need to force yourself.
I don't think
you have to try to get along.
You shouldn't have to force yourself.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to you too, Hansan.
The end!
I think we're done here.
Let's all make the effort...
to get along.
Cheers.
Again?
-Good morning.
-It smells good.
-It's scrambled eggs.
Riko said her throat hurts.
It might be a cold.
A cold?
I wonder if it's our fault.
That's what I was thinking.
I couldn't apologize yesterday, but I...
It's between you and me,
and I played a part, so I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
It's not just us living here.
It really made me realize
I must think about the people around me.
If I were in Riko's place, I would've run.
Yeah...
Hansan.
Hey.
How's your work?
I thought I'd have a break,
but it's piling up again.
What's wrong?
I think I'll be leaving Terrace House.
Seriously?
Why?
Well, since the last house meeting...
or the talk...
I've thought...
many things over.
Not long after I moved in,
I had issues with Minori.
Then things happened with Misaki.
I think I've figured out...
what I've been missing.
People can't change overnight.
But now that you're aware...
good things may happen.
And so, I really appreciate you.
You're welcome.
We should all do something together.
Yeah, at least have dinner together.
Didn't we say we wanted to barbecue?
-Yeah, that would be nice.
-Let's do it tomorrow.
-Here.
-Seriously?
We can use the grill.
We'll do it tomorrow.
Thank you.
That makes me really happy.
The teen is out with a cold
because of all the stress.
She absorbed all the ugliness.
-Poor girl.
-Poor Rikochan.
She's probably thinking
she shouldn't have auditioned.
Yeah, so far nothing nice has happened.
Those heart fluttering moments
of Terrace House,
-she hasn't experienced any of them.
-Not at all.
Only the fights.
But things did get resolved that day.
That was crazy.
The way she just said, "Hansan."
-That was scary!
-That was crazy.
But that...
that's a real part of her too.
She's not trying to act cute or anything.
It's like there's another Natsumi inside
she has trouble controlling.
-It's Fuyumi. The evil Natsumi.
-Fuyumi!
-There's a Fuyumi.
-That's right!
I mean, the expressions are
completely different.
Fuyumi?
She kept saying
how it still comes out sometimes.
She was talking about Fuyumi.
So by joining Terrace House,
Natsumi was able to confirm
Fuyumi's existence.
-That's right.
-That's it!
She can't tell in normal life.
But on the show,
she was able to see Fuyumi objectively.
She did say she realized
what was missing inside her,
and that's why she's leaving.
Wow! I didn't realize this was sci-fi!
The battle between Natsumi and Fuyumi
begins after she leaves.
-Spin-off time!
-Spin-off!
Do they realize it?
She's probably going
to tell her boyfriend...
"Keep filming me."
He's going to have one here.
A GoPro?
-Wouldn't it be more discreet?
-Right here.
I hope Fuyumi makes
another appearance before she leaves.
As she puts her keys down,
Fuyumi will appear
and beat up everyone with the keys.
"Stop it, Fuyumi!"
"Don't do it, Fuyumi!"
-Bon appétit!
Delicious!
-It's delicious.
-So good!
Our first barbecue.
Barbecues are nice.
-We should do this more often.
-It's happy.
-We should.
-And we bought a grill.
That's true.
I'll go get more.
The A5-ranked beef?
Here it is.
Wow!
What?
Whoa, it's a solid block!
We haven't had such high quality meat
since the meat incident.
-We can really just cook it as is?
-That's what Arman said.
I said we should cut it.
We might waste another A5.
Wow, are you sure?
-It's like it's not meat.
-Amazing.
I wanna ask a Truth or Truth question.
What question?
Let's go with the craziest experience.
Craziest experience?
A crazy experience...
-You must have a lot, Hikaru.
-Yeah, I do.
It can be anything,
like a bike accident.
-Okay, I've got one. My crazy experience.
-Please.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
What? I'm scared.
I'm... leaving Terrace House.
-What?
-Really.
What?
-Really. I'm serious.
-Seriously?
-You're lying.
-I'm not.
THE SHOW HAS BEEN EXTENDED AGAIN.
TO BE CONTINUED!