-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Let's go over what happened last week.
-Let's get to it. I know she's itching to.
-I am.
Tatsuya told Minori how he feels.
I really like you Minori.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
I want you by my side.
It's moving a little fast for me.
I want to be surer of my feelings,
so I feel like I can't give you
an answer until then.
-I thought she'd say yes for sure.
-She asked him to wait.
She wants Tatsuya to step out
of his comfort zone and make a move.
-And we have a new member, Arman.
-That's right.
He had a job interview
and joined a boxing gym.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
DAIKI MIYAGI, 25 YEARS OLD,
ACTOR, TARGET SHIBUYA OWNER
Arman is rather...
Well, he's made a good impression
on the ladies.
-He seems to have no faults.
-For now at least.
Him and Mizuki have something going.
-Yes!
-Their date in Kamakura.
Wow.
It's like old Japan.
Will you try this one, too?
-That's cute. Maybe too cute.
-It is.
It's freezing!
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
It feels good!
Mizuki turned into a whole new person.
Her voice changed.
The tone of her voice is higher.
Arman invited her to his match.
December 13th.
-I wonder what'll happen.
-A confession of love maybe?
Terrace House is known
for the ringside kiss scene.
-That's true.
-Yes, for sure.
And Yuriko told her ex-boyfriend
how she feels.
Last time, I told you how I felt.
I told you then
that I couldn't forget you.
I'd just like to know
your honest feelings.
TADAMICHI KAWANO, 25 YEARS OLD
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
The episode ended
before we could find out his answer.
But his expression...
He's being forced into marriage
with his boss's daughter.
Yuriko said she wants
to get back together,
but he can't say yes
because the boss's daughter
is right there waiting for him
-in her red convertible.
-That reason, right?
The sound of an engine right now
would get a reaction out of us, huh?
I'd just like to know
your honest feelings.
I'm surprised to hear
you're leaving Terrace House.
But getting back together...
isn't an option.
The reason...
is the same as before,
when we first agreed to break up.
The situation hasn't gotten any better.
I'm even busier than before.
-Now?
-So even if we get back together,
I don't think it'll make you happy.
There's something else I haven't told you.
I'm thinking of going back to my hometown.
I'm at a crossroads in my life...
and if I'm in a relationship,
I'd have to think about marriage.
I'm feeling very limited in my options.
These are my honest thoughts.
I don't plan for us to get back together.
I understand.
I'm not a student anymore.
I'm gonna go now.
Thank you.
Good luck on your exams.
See you later.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
It's Yuriko's last day,
so let's give her a nice send off. Cheers!
Cheers!
-Bon appétit!
-Tasty!
-Hot pot was a good idea.
-Delicious!
-How was your interview, Arman?
-I haven't heard a response yet.
I passed the first interview,
and I went in for a second.
How do you feel about it?
-I'm not sure.
-You're not sure?
Did you tell everyone about your match?
Did I tell you?
-I told everyone.
-Yeah. So, yeah.
-Yeah, we heard.
-December 13th, is it?
-That's only a month away.
-Yeah, only a month.
We can witness you being cool.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
-Oh!
-So? The result?
-The result?
-What happened?
-You announced it already?
-No, not yet.
We've been waiting to hear.
I...
was rejected today.
-For real?
-Seriously?
It was almost refreshing
how clearly he said no.
It's his loss for turning down
such a cute girl.
Arman, thank you!
-Did he say anything?
-Give you a reason?
After he said no,
I was in shock for the next few minutes.
I think he gave an explanation.
-But you don't remember?
-Yeah.
He said getting back together
was not an option.
Wow.
I think it was better than
if he tried to word it nicely.
Do you feel like you got closure?
-Yeah, I do.
-That's good.
What are you going to do now?
Well, in December, there's
a big national exam for med students.
-So you're going to focus on that?
-That's my plan.
That's good.
That's a big portion.
I think I deserve it.
-Eat, eat!
-Yeah, let me eat.
-Good morning.
-That's a lot of luggage.
-Looks heavy.
But you got everything into two bags.
Yeah, barely.
Minori helped me last night.
Phew! Thank you for everything,
the last three months.
Thank you.
-Thank you for the last ten days.
-Thank you.
I guess I'll be going.
I'm going.
-Your key?
-Yeah, my key.
Bye!
-See you!
-Bye!
-Oh, man.
-Wow.
He completely cut her down.
It's so sad.
-It's Sad Triendl.
-Sad Triendl?
I'm a little shocked.
-"Not an option."
-They were strong words.
Strongly worded rejection
can garner criticism,
but vague rejection is similarly bad,
if not worse.
I don't get it.
Very true!
That might have been the best way.
But he said
he's going back to his hometown?
Does that mean he's opening a clinic?
Maybe he's actually
the son of a hospital director.
So, the boss's daughter scenario
never existed?
The reason being
that he was the boss's son.
What's going to happen now
that another person has left?
But there are relationships developing.
-That's true.
-Mizuki and Arman.
And we'll have to see what happens
between Minori and Uchihara.
It's the last spurt.
Did you have dinner, Yuki?
Not really.
-Wanna go eat later?
-Later?
-He said he wanted to go to Fuji Soba.
-I was thinking that, too.
-Tonight?
-Yeah, did you eat?
I ate already.
-Wanna eat again?
-No.
We went with Arman before.
He was saying he had too much to drink,
and that he wanted something with broth.
So we went to Fuji Soba,
but he ordered a Ten Don.
He didn't order something
with broth at all!
What I really wanted was tempura soba.
So when I saw "Ten" on the menu,
I just ordered it.
-Oh, you thought you were getting Tensoba?
-Yeah, but they put rice in front of me.
I only ate half of it.
It was disappointing.
Can I get the door?
-Yeah. Should I get Mizuki?
-I'll go, too.
Maybe it's Mizuki.
Wait, here she is.
What's going on?
Should I open it?
-I wanna open it!
-Wait, me too!
-Hello.
-Good evening.
-Let's invite her in.
-Come in!
This moment is always nerve-racking.
Good evening.
Hey!
-Good evening!
-This is the turnout?
KURUMI NAKADA, 23 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, MINORI'S OLDER SISTER
-Oh, don't do that!
-What?
I wasn't expecting this.
What?
You thought I was the new member?
We totally did!
-Here's a little something.
-Thank you.
Oh, Makocchan isn't here.
Weird!
This is for anyone who drinks.
And some cookies.
-Thank you.
-Because, you know, wine and sweets.
High-quality selection. Wow.
I just saw the episode that aired.
It was so sad!
Yesterday,
after we all watched it together,
she called and said, "Poor Tap."
Yeah, Yuriko was horrible!
-We didn't say that!
-But she was!
Why?
That's not just being oblivious.
That's being horrible.
-It's not horrible.
-Just oblivious.
That's just a cover.
-She represents the voice of the viewers.
-It's refreshing.
Minori says you always give your opinion.
-You wanted to complain, right?
-Oh, yeah, when Tap was lecturing Mizuki.
They talked about that a lot
and said how annoying that was.
I was like,
we don't all have the same priorities.
-Don't tell us that.
-I get tons of comments about that.
And you,
from a viewer's point of view,
-it's what we want to know the most.
-What do you mean?
-What was it like after?
-That's what you're wondering?
-Oh, you haven't heard?
-I haven't told her.
She wanted to watch it.
I saw her before we went to Odaiba.
She told me you guys were going on a date.
She was expecting your confession of love.
She knew what was coming!
Hey, that's unfair!
-Yeah, Uchi...
-So, you don't know what happened?
-I don't know.
-I've been put on hold.
Oh, yeah, she did tell me that.
So I asked her if she's making you wait.
Yes, that's how it is.
I'll be more expressive.
I like Uchi.
You've never pursued a guy, have you?
-No.
-Right?
-Never?
-Yeah.
Make her work for you.
Actually, I haven't pursued
anyone before either.
That's why it's taking so long.
-Excuse me.
-Please come in.
-Oh, it's really spacious.
-Yeah.
Minori and her sister's personalities
are nothing alike.
She's strong.
-The strong big sister.
-Yeah, she's straightforward.
-So, how's Uchi?
-We're going there?
-Of course.
-So you want him to be more expressive?
Not expressive, per se.
Like, embracing you
because he can't hold back anymore?
-Yeah, that'd be...
-That's totally what you want!
Wouldn't that make you happy?
I was totally going to ask him,
"Why don't you just hold her from behind?"
That seems completely unlikely.
So you're afraid
his feelings aren't at that level?
Yes, that's exactly it!
You won't believe his feelings are sincere
until he reaches that level.
-Amazing.
-Maybe he's never done that though.
-So maybe he just doesn't know?
-Even if he doesn't...
Even if he doesn't,
you don't mind going out with him, right?
Well, that came out wrong.
But if he pushes for it,
you're thinking you wouldn't mind, right?
I want to go out with him
with the best feelings.
-"Best feelings"?
-Like, you love him?
Why don't you put yourself
in that mindset?
I am.
Why don't you make him lunch every day?
No comment.
You can write "Still?"
with nori on his rice ball.
A noriben?
-I hope it works out for you.
-I'll try my best.
-You too, Mizuki.
-Yes, me too.
I do like Arman for now.
Her sister should just stay over.
They have an open bed.
-It's an amazing house.
-Is it?
-Was it messy?
-Super messy.
It shows people have really settled here.
Can I show her the playroom?
-Yeah, of course. Right?
-Of course.
She wants to see it.
-Maybe I'll have Uchi show me.
-Oh, really?
Surprised?
-We've got nothing to hide.
-Nothing to hide?
-The playroom is totally clean.
-He's very confident.
Are they gonna be okay?
-And here is the playroom.
-The playroom.
-It's surprisingly clean.
-Right?
Yeah, but there's a ton of dust.
Here are Minori's glasses.
She likes to leave them everywhere.
-Her glasses represent her lifestyle.
-How is she?
-Minori, um...
-I came to ask about that.
I see, well...
-You really like her?
-I do.
-Really?
-Yes.
Watching you,
I know you went on that date to Chichibu,
but I don't think you like her
as much as Minori is hoping.
Am I not coming on strong enough?
She's the person I love most in the world.
-You said that?
-No.
-My feelings aren't coming across.
-You should just say that.
But I'd rather prove myself
through action rather than words.
-Such as?
Such as...
Well, you know.
I think what she wants from you is...
that feeling of,
"I can't restrain myself around you."
-Minori?
-Yes, I think so.
So seeing her sleeping face
doesn't make you want to kiss her?
Seeing her sleeping face
does make me want to kiss her.
I do.
I do, but I can't bring myself to do it.
But if you do something like that,
it'll make everyone think,
"Wow, you like her that much."
I'll try my best.
That was good advice.
-Next time...
-I'm looking forward to it.
-I hope you'll be her boyfriend.
-Thank you, Kurumi.
I can't wait.
DAIKAN-YAMA, TOKYO
I'm trying to decide on the label.
Which one do you like?
-If you had to pick.
-This one.
You like this one?
You're right.
Actually, I'm going to Terrace House.
-You don't have a boyfriend?
-Not for two years now.
Finding love would be nice,
but it would also be nice to make friends.
I'm very nervous.
And worried.
-She looks pretty.
-She looks beautiful.
Beautiful!
Really clear skin.
Yes, she looks like
she takes care of herself.
She seems like your type.
What do you think of that, Tokui?
I was just thinking she seems my type.
The sister is so cool!
She's like an action star.
So true.
-Really blunt.
-"So? Why don't you just say that?"
So cool!
The sister really gave a big push.
-It was probably really good for Minori.
-It really was.
She basically told them both
to make a move if they like each other.
Her words really reached Tatsuya.
That he should convey to her
that she is his only love in the world.
Wasn't that a little creepy?
He's giggling.
It's making me all itchy.
I think I'm allergic.
I think that Uchi,
when he gave that head massage,
he already feels like
he reached second base.
But it means nothing for the girl.
And we've got a new member coming.
This is probably
the last chance for Yuki.
-The next one's coming in.
-We'll get to see the full face soon.
I hope she has tiny eyes.
That'd be hilarious!
Or super wide-set eyes.
She won't look like that.
-What if her eyes are at her temples?
-Stop making fun.
She's about to make an appearance.
Who has eyes up at their temples?
When someone stands in front of her,
she'll be like,
"I'm sorry, I can't see you."
Even when dining together, she'll turn.
-"This is delicious."
-When did she turn into a fish?
Nobody like that exists!
But she'll see if you talk to her
from this angle.
There's no one like that!
I wonder
what your sister and Uchi talked about.
Hopefully something good.
Probably exactly what she said
in our room.
That's true.
-She has no qualms.
-That's what's so great.
She's just happy if she's entertained.
She's probably thinking
it doesn't affect her.
Is Arman home in the afternoons?
-I wonder if he got the job.
-It's been a while, right?
Oh, Arman.
-Welcome back, Uchi.
-I'm home.
What are you guys doing?
-Nothing really.
-Working.
Working?
-Just Mizuki.
-Oh, yeah, just me.
-She's here!
-Why don't you get it, Yuki?
-I'm going to wait.
-She's here!
Yes?
Hi, I'm the new roommate.
-Oh, wow.
-She's peppy.
-Good evening.
-Should we help with her luggage?
-Let's wait a bit.
-You can go.
-You're so nice.
I'm not trying to be nice.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Wait, what?
-I've met Mizuki before.
-What?
-Through a friend of a friend.
-That's right!
Like a second cousin?
-It's nice to meet you.
-Wow.
I'm Arisa Ohata.
-Arisa?
-Arisa Ohata.
-Where are you from?
-I'm from Kagoshima.
The twang.
-Your accent.
-Yes, from Kagoshima.
-She's here, Arman.
-I'm new, too.
-It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Arman.
-I'm Arisa.
-Arisa?
Yes, Arisa Ohata.
What do you do?
I used to design clothes.
I'm now getting ready
to start my own hat brand.
-Your own brand?
-Yes, my own.
-Nice.
-That's amazing.
How old are you?
-I'm 25 years old.
-Same as you, Arman.
-The same?
-Yeah. 1990.
-Do you have a boyfriend?
-Yes, that's important.
I don't have a boyfriend.
Why did you come to Terrace House?
I've been in Tokyo for six years.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
HAT DESIGNER
I was so motivated in the beginning,
but lately, everyday...
has become repetitive.
If it continues like this,
there's no point of me staying in Tokyo.
I wanted to meet more people
from other fields, hardworking people,
and I wanted to remember
what that felt like.
Can I ask what's your type?
Someone who can survive
on a deserted island.
A deserted island?
-A deserted island?
-What do you mean?
Someone I can rely on.
Oh, if the two of you were
on a deserted island?
Yes, even if the environment changes...
-Someone you can rely on.
-...that person wouldn't.
-You can live together.
-Yes, and the place wouldn't matter.
Why don't you show her upstairs?
Do you need help with your luggage?
-Wanna go?
-Yes.
Please come in.
-Isn't it clean?
-It's always clean.
Wow, nice!
It's so clean.
It's spacious.
-Excuse me.
-Your bed's here, Arisa.
I'm so happy.
-I'll leave it to you guys.
-Bye.
-Thank you!
-See you later.
I should've dressed nicer.
You're worried about that?
Is she your type?
Not completely, but she's cute.
-She's cute?
-Yeah.
It's gonna be fun for you then.
If she can drink, she'll be perfect.
-What do you think, Yuki?
-She's really cute.
-She answered my question immediately.
-Which one?
What she came here for.
She said she wanted
to start her own brand.
-Yeah. That was appealing.
-It's a good day.
I don't know,
but I'm going to make it a good one.
The fact that she tries to hide
her accent is great.
But yet the Kagoshima accent
still comes out.
I love it.
-You love it?
-You're so excited.
-That black hair... I love it!
-There it is. The black hair.
It's been awhile since I've felt this way.
That's so cute!
Terrace House
may have just pulled my fangs.
Darn it.
-This is a first.
-Yes, it is.
Since Season One.
I want to join the house.
I want to join Terrace House now!
I want to join!
Adachi doesn't stand a chance.
-No.
-Not at all?
He was trying to be cool again.
"She answered
when I asked about her dreams.
So she's all right."
-What's with that dream boss?
-I know.
Why is he so tough
on other people's dreams?
If they answered,
"Hmm, there's no specific reason."
Then it's an automatic rejection.
Yeah, what's wrong with that?
I'm still unsettled.
Maybe because of the ceiling?
There's so much space.
I hope I can sleep.
You should take a long hot bath.
Arman and Yuki are probably drinking.
-They drink every night.
-Yeah.
-Together?
-What do they drink?
-Pretty much beer.
Is anyone in love?
-Love? Are you looking for love?
-Yes.
Did anyone attract your attention?
Arman seemed easy to talk to.
He seems like he'd be able to survive
on a deserted island.
He's definitely that type.
I totally thought Arman
when you said that before.
Yeah.