-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
SIX STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
LIVING TOGETHER
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
-So, last week...
-Yes, yes.
-It was the biggest shock we've had.
-It was shocking.
-It caused a panic.
-Yes, a panic.
A system error.
Seriously.
Riko and Hayato acted as if
they couldn't even hold hands.
Like an innocent couple
taking little steps.
But simply put, they were doing it.
-That's right.
-They were acting innocent,
but Byrnes had already seen them kiss
and couldn't hold back anymore.
So he makes the big reveal.
You meet after the rest of us are asleep.
When I ran out of the elevator
the other day,
I saw you guys kissing.
What you're doing
and what's being said is too different.
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD
There's a gap.
That in itself is fine.
It's just that they were lying about it.
Arman was a witness as well.
Starting about a month ago,
she'd come in the guy's room
when everyone was asleep,
and leave before everyone woke up.
I noticed you disappearing
about a month ago.
When I'd wake up around 4:00 a.m.
sometimes Riko would be there.
They're upset because she said
she didn't want to hold hands
and that she wanted
to cherish the relationship.
So if Hayato held your hand,
would you have liked it? Or no?
I didn't want him to.
I want to save things like that.
Especially because we've been
going out on dates.
I felt like I wanted to save that.
Normally, you'd want sleep with her
or kiss her or something, right?
You feel that desire toward a woman.
I don't really feel that for her.
-That's right.
-He clearly rejected her.
He has to retract it all.
So today, we'll get to hear
what's going on with the two of them.
That's right.
If they can be honest here,
that they were scared
of what would air on Terrace House
and that he was worried
about Riko's career...
I'm sure they'll say something like that.
He's anticipating their move.
That's impossible.
They should've kept it outside.
I'll end it in one move.
But...
let's watch.
But there's also Arman and Masako.
-Tracing back to Arman's accident.
-Yes, the accident.
-Thanks to that...
-His miss.
...it seems to have brought them closer.
It's fun hanging out with you.
I wonder why?
I feel comfortable with you.
You're going back to Hawaii?
-Well, I haven't decided when.
-So someday.
It's been more fun recently.
-Recently?
-Yeah.
Why?
The train.
-Masako doesn't know what happened.
-No, she doesn't.
-That's right.
-She's away for work.
It's the guy she liked.
It might be the most shocking for her.
By then, they were already doing it.
-This will make Martha dislike him.
-Yes.
-I'm scared.
-It's scary!
I'm afraid.
I can't help...
but be aware that I'm on TV.
I don't want to think of it this way,
but I think of it as work.
I want to say something about that.
Then you really should have
done it more secretly.
So no one would know.
If you're going to do it,
you should've done it outside the house.
Because we know,
we're forced to play along.
It makes it hard for us, especially
when you're putting on an act.
You haven't been able to hide it.
And for me to have to pretend
to give advice, is just plain stupid.
When you decide to live here,
relationships, arguments...
you expect things to happen.
-We're here with that expectation.
-Yes.
You have feelings for each other,
but to be secretive about it
because of your career...
is the biggest problem.
Yeah.
There is that.
I couldn't help but think about the fact
that my actions would be seen.
What about you, Hayato?
I mean Riko's the only one
who's said anything.
I was thinking about Riko's career...
and felt now wasn't the right time
for us to be together.
But I still like her, so things happened.
I overanalyzed things.
But you didn't really think it through.
That's true.
Since things ended up this way.
If you're going to do it, you should
just go to a motel or whatever.
I don't know,
but somewhere none of us would know.
If you do things halfway,
of course we'd find out.
We live together.
You guys don't like each other?
I do.
But...
we don't trust each other...
100% yet.
You didn't talk about
your feelings beforehand?
You're together so much.
Well?
No, maybe not.
I'm amazed you guys can do it,
not knowing how you feel
about each other.
You said you couldn't
even hold hands with him.
I thought you guys were kissing
because you've shared your feelings,
but you haven't.
I'm just wondering
how can you even be kissing?
After hearing everything,
it just sounds like the two of you
are convenient sleep buddies
who get to make out when you're home.
That's what it sounds like to me.
-That's...
-I don't like how you're putting it.
-It's really--
-But that's what it sounds like.
It's...
It's not like that.
Making out and all,
when you're not together,
is just friends with benefits.
I do like him.
But you said you weren't sure,
even when it's the two of us.
-Like you said here earlier.
-I do like you, but...
So this is what I mean.
If you're still in this status,
how could you kiss her, Hayato?
If you're aware,
then you shouldn't have.
You're right.
-Riko shouldn't have either.
-Yeah, both sides.
But maybe Hayato
should've considered that for her.
-Right.
-Yeah.
Before you kissed her.
Yeah.
Kissing her may have caused
Riko more confusion.
What we're wondering
is what's going to happen now?
What are you going to do?
But I thought they already knew.
They make out
because they like each other.
But because of her career,
they can't officially be together.
-If that's the case...
-I thought that's what it was.
I do think that's what it is.
I really wanted to be honest.
But as things progressed...
I couldn't say anymore.
You should really talk about it.
Figure out your true feelings
for each other.
You should confirm them with each other.
Because this is tough for us to say, too.
Sorry.
Talk it out.
That's what I think.
You coming, Misaki?
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
I'm sorry, Riko.
I said we shouldn't go out
because of your career.
But I guess we made our reputation
a bit worse anyway.
Well, we can't help that anymore.
It's done.
We need to think of what to do.
What do you want to do?
Even if we liked each other...
is it better if we didn't go out?
Or if we really like each other,
is it better if we just go out?
I don't know.
I like you, but...
when I consider your career,
maybe now is not the time for us.
That's what I think right now.
But what do you want?
If you think we shouldn't go out,
that's fine, too.
Even if you like me,
going out isn't everything.
And you're not even sure, right?
It's not that I'm not sure,
maybe I'm just running away from it.
Maybe so,
but that's how you feel right now.
Then we shouldn't go out right now.
And the fact we've kissed
and hung out at night,
we didn't establish boundaries.
Yeah.
So we won't do things halfway anymore.
We won't go out right now.
We'll tell everyone that.
And if your feelings change...
then you can talk about it.
With everyone...
and with me.
That's all we can do, right?
Is that all right?
Yeah.
He's leaving too much to her.
He always asks, "What do you want?"
"What should we do?"
"What do you want?"
This is tough on Riko.
-She's 18.
-He's 29, right?
Yes.
The worst part was
when they were all talking.
He didn't say anything.
He made Riko talk.
All of that is a little...
He should've tried to protect her.
It's not like Riko was the one
kissing him and going to the room.
Even if Riko was the one who liked him,
and she was the one initiating
the kisses and such,
Hayato should've said
that it was the both of them.
He couldn't say that it was because
he considered Riko's situation.
I wanted him to take the blame.
Yes, that he took things too far.
I wanted him to say that,
even if it's a lie.
And what was really cold
was when he said,
"This might ruin our reputation,
but that can't be helped."
He was suddenly from her agency.
It's like, are you serious?
He's even pettier than Yamazato.
Yeah, we've got a small guy.
We're talking micro-small.
The fact he got up and left first
makes me want to punch him.
Did he go to get the others?
-No, no...
-He just left?
I think he just left.
-I think he went to get the others.
-Really?
He said, that's what we'll tell everyone
and then left...
If not, I'm going to put him a big bag
and send him off.
We'll drop him off at a random place
and be like, "Here you go!"
-Hey!
-Hey.
-Welcome back.
-Thanks.
I brought souvenirs.
-Thank you.
-It's been awhile.
-It was only two days.
-It was two day, but...
-Look, look.
-What is it?
This is the one from before.
-You've got a big smile.
-Can you tell which one's me?
Second from the right.
-Can you tell?
-Yeah.
-You went to do PR for Kagoshima?
-Welcome home.
-Welcome back.
Long time no see.
You look tired.
I'm not tired.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I lost my voice.
-You have a cold?
-Yeah, I caught a cold.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
What? What's going on?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Let me sit here.
You wanted to talk to me?
My relationship with Hayato...
had been progressing.
What does that mean?
As to how far things have gone...
we've kissed.
Seriously?
My feelings...
I've been lying about them.
I've been lying to myself and to everyone.
But Hayato...
what was he thinking when he kissed you?
I'm unsure of his feelings ever since
you guys came back from the fireworks.
So it's hard for me to say.
That was a lie.
Hayato's been lying, too.
Seriously?
I'm in shock.
All that time...
I've agonized over things.
What was the point of me
trying to consider how others felt?
I'm sorry.
What I did was
really disrespectful to you.
And yesterday,
I really thought things over.
But no matter how much I think about it,
I feel like I know even less.
I can't sleep.
My head is just full.
It feels like my life is over.
You told him you liked him?
For the first time yesterday.
What did Hayato say?
He's always told me he liked me.
What are you going to do?
But Hayato said yesterday
that even though he likes me,
considering my career,
we shouldn't be together.
I couldn't really accept it.
No.
It's not very manly of him.
I'm starting to think
he just wants to escape.
Yeah, it's not a good reason.
After making the moves,
and then when you say you like him,
he says no because of your work?
-That's for you to decide.
-Yeah.
Are you okay with that?
You're not going to tell him?
I'll think it over.
I'll talk about it with Hayato.
Good morning.
-Long time no see.
I'm so hungry.
How was Kagoshima?
It was fun.
I wanted to apologize to you.
-A little late, no?
-Yeah.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
You were doing this behind our backs.
Who made the first move?
I did.
How do you feel about Riko?
I feel really bad for her.
Why do you feel bad?
I mean, you like her, right?
I said I was I thinking
about her career
and I really was.
You did,
but you still kiss her behind the scenes?
It turned out the opposite
of what I was thinking.
So you guys are going out now?
I don't know about making a decision...
about that now.
If you're so worried about her career,
you shouldn't have made a move.
And if that's the reason,
I won't be able to accept it.
You're just running away.
At least from the girl's point of view.
That's all I have to say.
I'm sorry.
You should talk with Riko.
Yeah.
-See you.
-Thanks.
-Welcome back.
-Hey.
Welcome, I'm back.
-Is Hayato here?
-"Welcome, I'm back"?
Is Hayato here?
-Is he downstairs?
-He was downstairs.
-He's downstairs?
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Are they going to talk?
It's been awhile
since they've seen each other.
Seriously?
Well, it's better to talk soon.
Yes?
Riko...
-Alone?
-Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
-You want to talk?
-Yes, that's why I came.
I wanted to talk too.
I thought it over,
but I liked that I felt like...
I could depend on you
because you're older.
And how when we're with everyone
it felt like you treated me special.
I liked that.
I liked it...
and I was okay with going out with you.
But...
When you said we shouldn't go out
because of my career...
I thought maybe you were
just running away.
And when we were all talking,
I was the only one talking.
You didn't say a word.
All that wasn't manly at all.
It's not that I wanted you
to protect me...
or take my side or anything,
but you just stayed silent,
which was a shock for me.
Seeing that side of you...
even though I wanted to be with you then,
I became unsure.
And now, I'm not sure what to do.
I see, I'm sorry.
I should have explained then.
From now on...
I want you to think about
what you want to do.
Because you're always...
asking me what I want to do.
Yeah. I couldn't speak up then,
but I was really thinking about it.
And the fact I didn't protect you...
wasn't manly of me.
I know that.
Right now, I really feel...
that we don't have to decide right now
whether or not to be together.
We both have things we need to focus on.
For you, your career.
And me...
I need to focus on
my chef training.
I felt we need to focus on other things.
I had fun,
but I know my actions were rash.
I'm really sorry about that.
After thinking about it
with a clear head...
going out right now...
isn't right for either of us.
I see.
That's how far your feelings went.
You acted like you were thinking of me,
but you didn't understand me at all.
Which part?
You're still using work as an excuse.
It's not that I'm running away,
it's just when I thought about
what I really need to do right now...
for me, you didn't come first.
-Yeah.
-Work came first for me.
For you, too.
What you need to do...
I don't think I'm first for you either.
For me, there's no first or second.
Work is work.
I know what I have to do.
You told me how much you like me.
But to say I'm not first for you...
To put a number on it...
I did like you.
I still have those feelings...
But to go out because I like you,
it's not as simple as that.
So...
you were just messing around with me.
Even if that wasn't the case...
I'm really sad right now.
I can't accept it at all.
I'm going now.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, bye.
Hell.
He's the worst.
So Terashima initiated it.
And he'd been telling her he liked her.
This wasn't right.
So he didn't really like her then.
If he did, work wouldn't matter.
He said kissing her was rash.
Disgusting.
He knows the premise of Terrace House.
But he did what he wanted,
and kept it a secret
so that it wouldn't affect their image.
But when Riko said it'd be okay
if they went out,
he says, "Well, we don't have to go out."
His reasoning was that they both
have other things they need to focus on.
It's not like he's in love with her
and wants to go out with her,
but he couldn't help himself.
I totally get it as a guy.
Like Yoshida from the comedy duo
Black Mayonnaise says,
the brain and penis are constant rivals
for a man.
The brain and penis are constant rivals.
They're always battling.
Sometime the brain wins,
and sometimes the penis wins.
According to Yoshida.
I have to agree with that.
-How difficult for you.
-Yes.
So I get it.
But his behavior when they all talked,
all of that was not very manly.
The way he did it was bad.
Do you think the girls
are talking about it?
-Like, "Isn't he the worst?"
-Yes, definitely.
The girls definitely feel that way.
So it's five against one.
I want to see a five against one.
Good morning.
We're wearing matching shirts.
-What?
-We have matching shirts.
-Does it look bad?
-No, it looks good.
-I've never seen you dressed like that.
-Seriously?
Are you hungry?
-What?
-Are you hungry?
No, not really.
Did I tell you where we're going?
-No.
-I haven't?
-Then it'll be a surprise.
-Okay.
KAMAKURA, KANAGAWA
KAMAKURA STATION
It's so hot!
-It's so hot.
-Yeah.
-There are so many people.
-Breezy, though.
It's super hot.
YUIGAHAMA BEACH
We should get a drink.
-You want to drink?
-Ice cold beer?
-I don't want to.
-I want to.
I drink every day,
so I don't want to.
You should drink though.
-It's hot. It's beautiful though.
-Yeah.
I want to do that!
Yeah!
THAI VILLAGE
-Cheers.
-Sorry, I drank already.
-No worries.
Can you surf here?
I think so.
But I've never done it here.
-We should go together.
-What?
-We should go surfing.
-Surfing?
You can teach me.
-Looks delicious.
-It looks so good!
There's only a week left.
It's sad.
-Don't say it.
-Sorry.
We should keep it fun.
But, what are you going to do?
I need to decide.
Either at the beginning of September,
or the middle...
I might go back to Hawaii.
I haven't decided yet though.
I see.
-Should we walk around some more?
-Sure.
When you're done.
TENNOZU ISLE
Let's go on a boat.
-A boat? Seriously?
-A boat.
-Where is it?
-On a cruise. I'm not sure.
Seriously?
We get on here?
I'm okay with that.
-Thank you.
This is nice.
-Oh, man.
-It's nice.
Man...
This is cute.
Arman, your eyes are half-closed.
Your eyes are half-closed!
-Your eyes are half-closed.
-I look dead.
It's nice.
You look good in casual wear.
-Who?
-You.
What?
It's funny
because you say it out of nowhere.
It's sudden.
It's amazing we're on a boat.
Thank you.
-Kintaro.
-Oh, thank you.
On the rocks.
-Cheers.
We both have dark features
-but our choices are traditional Japanese.
-There's definitely a gap.
Oh, the Tokyo Tower.
Where?
-That's the Sky Tree.
-Oh, the Sky Tree.
That's the Sky Tree.
When the sun sets more,
it'll be even more beautiful.
-When it's darker?
-Yeah.
I'm sure it'll be beautiful.
Yeah. It's pretty now, too.
I was going to say this
when it got darker.
But today...
The airplane.
We've been hanging out more lately.
It's been really fun for me.
Right now, we're like friends.
It's how we started.
I...
want to take things further.
-So...
-What?
It's fun being with you.
Will you go out with me?
Right now?
You're asking now?
-Was it too soon?
-No, it's not, but...
I've been wanting to ask.
I like you too, probably.
I like you.
-Me?
-I like you, Arman.
But you're going back to Hawaii.
That bothers me.
I do wonder what you think about that.
I have things
I need to take care of there.
I can always come back after.
I can go for a few months and come back.
But I really like you.
If we went out for a month
and if I felt like I can't leave,
then I won't leave.
I can stay in Japan.
-You like me that much?
-That much.
I've thought it through.
Will you believe me?