-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
A lot happened last week...
-Yes, indeed.
For the issue between Rikopin and Hayato,
Rikopin apologized
and practically said she likes him.
But maybe I gave you the idea
that I wasn't interested in you.
I hope not.
Because it's not true.
But Hayato...
He's a little scared off right now.
He says they're on hold.
Even if we did, I wouldn't be sure
whether I can take things further.
That's true.
You couldn't even hold hands.
It'd be like a school field trip again.
-And Momochan becomes...
-Congratulations.
...a professional ballerina.
We're so happy for her.
I'll be a professional dancer
starting next week.
-Wow!
-Seriously?
-My dream came true.
-That's awesome.
Now she can enjoy her time
at Terrace House.
That's right. And now...
-The brand new...
-Misaki and Byrnes.
A simple occurrence.
He fails to get his license.
-On Misaki's birthday.
-I suppose it was significant.
But later at the party,
he gives her a dress.
-That was nice.
-But afterward...
That was great.
Let's see it again.
They're unstoppable.
-Can we see that part again?
-Can we?
Can we run that scene?
As long as it's not Yokohama or Shonan.
You don't want to go there that bad?
I feel like it's bad luck.
Even if you went with a different guy?
"Even if you went with a different guy?"
The title for Kazumasa Oda's new single.
-Here it comes.
-It's happening.
"Don't stare at me..."
Don't stare at me.
And then...
I like you, Misaki.
That carried weight.
It was the real deal.
-It was real.
-It was that thing where it just came out.
It just came out.
What a great moment.
I like you.
She's gonna file a complaint.
Oh, man! You lied, Byrnes!
It doesn't work!
I'm sure it drove the older ladies crazy.
And he tried to lead it into a kiss.
But he was rejected.
It's only gonna be on your forehead.
-Just your forehead...
-Wait, wait.
-Wait, I'm not ready...
-I'm like the weird guy.
But Misaki seemed happy.
She was like, "Wait, you go ahead."
Isn't it a bold move
to go for a kiss so soon?
Isn't it a turn off?
Like, "Who does this guy think he is?"
Didn't she say something like that
at the end?
-Not at all.
-No?
I see.
I guess I am clueless.
What's wrong?
There Triendl goes again.
I was just playing it over again
in my head.
-What?
-Byrnes and Misaki?
-It's so nice, isn't it?
-It is.
The golden days of summer.
-Summer is here, old man.
-It's summer.
-Good morning.
-You're cleaning up?
-Yeah.
Thanks. I'll help you.
I'm gonna have some cake from yesterday.
Seriously?
You can eat that now?
Totally.
-Did I seem drunk yesterday?
-Yeah.
Do you even remember what you said?
I do.
I see.
It looked really good on you though.
-Thanks.
-The dress.
Really good.
It...
it just occurred to me...
it just occurred to me
that I was really happy.
-I'm gonna go shower.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Thanks for cleaning up, too.
-Of course.
-See you.
-Bye.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
What about the new member
you were talking about?
The new guy...
definitely likes one of the other girls.
So no real potential there?
AYAKA NISHIDA
PART-TIMER
None.
Did you go somewhere with the 29-year-old?
-I did.
-Seriously?
We went to Yokohama.
Did he make any moves?
Not at all.
If he asks you out again...
would you go?
I would.
-But I don't think he'll ask me out again.
-Really?
So I think I'll have to do something
about that.
I think that if you ask him out,
it'd make him happy.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What if he says no?
-Then...
-Like, "Sorry, I'm not feeling it."
-But things aren't awkward, right?
-Not at all.
So?
Yeah, I need to do something.
-Yeah, something.
-Something.
-I have to take action.
-Yeah.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 21 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
ASAMI MAKI BALLET
NAKANO, TOKYO
KYOZO MITANI
ARTISTIC DIRECTOR
-Good morning.
-Hello.
-Congratulations on the other day.
-Thank you so much.
-Please sit.
-Excuse me.
What did you think of the competition?
I wanted to make the top three...
I still feel a little frustrated.
Then your frustrations and your desire
to make the top three
can drive you further.
Watching you dance,
I felt that if you work hard,
you could potentially be better.
You have presence and you have the height.
That's what made me decide to accept you.
What you have inside of you,
you can express to the audience
through your dance.
So please work hard on your dancing.
Thank you.
Please do your best.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it too.
Your first class will be tomorrow,
so I'll come by to see.
Okay.
So...
tomorrow morning...
I'll be leaving Terrace House.
-What? Tomorrow?
-Tomorrow?
I went to the new dance company today.
I went to talk and sign the contracts.
From now on,
everything's going to be ballet for me.
I need to be in an environment
where I can focus on dance.
I'll do my best.
-I understand.
-Yeah, your dream has come true.
If that's why you're leaving,
then we support you.
-We'll be rooting for you.
-Thank you.
I've only done ballet my entire life.
So my time here was so much fun.
Thank you.
Over these past two months,
you only had one day off.
Thank you for spending it with me.
-That's right, I only had one day off.
-Yeah, no fair.
-No fair!
-It's not fair, Arman.
-I didn't get to go out with you.
-Yeah.
-Thank you. It was fun.
-Thank you.
I've gone pro,
but I'm at the bottom of the ranks.
If I ever get to the middle...
I'll invite you guys to a performance.
So please come see me.
I'll go even if you're at the bottom.
Yeah, totally.
-We want to see.
-Really?
I'm off.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
See you.
-I'll be going.
-Good luck.
-I'm going.
-See you.
-I'll be going.
-Thanks.
Thanks.
I'll be going.
-Do your best.
-Thank you.
He's carrying all my stuff.
-See you.
Thank you, guys.
-Work hard.
-Do your best!
EBISU, TOKYO
-Starting this week, I won't be alone.
-Are you going somewhere?
-I'll be living at Terrace House.
-What?
-You think I'm lying, don't you?
You think I'm lying.
Are you serious?
That's unexpected.
-I haven't had a boyfriend for a year.
-That's true, you haven't.
-I fall for guys pretty quickly though.
-Yeah, you do.
-You didn't have to agree.
-You do, though.
But somehow it never works out.
-Seriously though?
-Yeah.
Are you gonna be able to get along
with the others?
-Because I'm a brat?
-Yeah.
Don't agree with me!
But yeah, I do fall for guys easily.
-I have a feeling it'll happen quickly.
-Oh, yeah?
Yeah, real quick.
I see. I thought she'd stick around
to enjoy her time at Terrace House.
But she is a professional now.
There's no need for her to stay.
They mentioned it in passing,
but I didn't realize
she only had one day off
during her two months there.
What a waste!
I mean, she spent it seeing
the comedy duo Earth with Arman.
What a waste.
-What a waste!
-Such a waste!
And things between Byrnes and Misaki...
I guess things are good.
I didn't need to worry.
Very natural.
That exchange of, "Do you remember?"
"I remember."
And the way he said it.
It wasn't just, "I remember," but...
"I remember."
The tone shows that he meant what he said.
Right?
Yes, he said that part seriously.
But he then lightened it up with,
"You looked good in the dress."
He's made us forget about Hansan.
-So you've recovered from the Han-loss?
-I have.
-We've got a new member.
-Yes, a new member.
She might not fit in with the group.
Yes, she's energetic, like Hana Imai.
Seems like we've got a crass one.
If she falls for guys quickly, then...
-What if she goes for Byrnes?
-It'd get complicated.
It'd be perfect if she went for Arman.
-You want her to go for Arman?
-Yeah.
You're a fan of Arman.
-Yeah, you root for him.
-You like him?
Isn't he good?
He doesn't usually say anything wrong.
He doesn't,
but only because he doesn't say anything.
I hope we get to see her friend more too.
Yeah, to come visit the house.
She looks like she'd own a chameleon.
She does seem like she would have
a pet reptile!
"They feel so good because they're cold,"
she'd say.
What happened with the license, Yuuki?
Oh, no!
I'm going back next week.
-It's stuck.
-It's sticking.
You should push it back once.
I want to hurry up and drive.
The doorbell rang.
Let's all go.
-Everyone?
-Just Yuuki and me then.
-Is it a girl?
-Of course it's gonna be a girl.
Yes?
I'm moving in today.
Sure, come on in.
Wait, I'm gonna sit here.
How about we immediately
play a game with her?
Like, "Here, roll the dice."
-Hello, sorry for interrupting.
-Hello.
I'm sorry I'm so slow.
My luggage is very heavy.
Don't worry about it.
-You can leave it there.
-Is it okay?
-Good evening.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Masako Endo and I'm 22.
-What do you do?
I usually model.
-Thanks for having me.
-Nice to meet you.
-You seem nervous.
-I am.
-You are.
-Are you from Kansai?
-From Fukuoka.
-Oh, Fukuoka.
-Fukuoka's nice.
-You've got the accent.
-Yes, I do.
-Yeah.
How long have you been in Tokyo?
This is my fourth year.
-You were in Fukuoka before that?
-Yes, in Fukuoka.
I'm actually half-Japanese as well.
I'm half-Filipino.
We're getting more people
with strong features.
-Very strong features.
Would you like something to drink?
-Maybe a highball?
-May I?
-How about a beer?
-We've got beer.
Oh, thank you.
-Was it Endo...
-Masako Endo.
It doesn't match my face, I know.
You just smirked.
-He totally smirked!
-I was just thinking of what to call you.
I go by Martha at work.
Martha?
Masako, Martha, either is fine.
-Then here's to Martha.
-To Martha.
-Thank you. It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to have you.
-Your drink's almost done.
-It's okay.
-To Martha.
-Martha.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Can you speak Tagalog?
Yes, I speak Tagalog.
-Any plans for the future?
-The future?
-You're asking that, Arman?
-It's so sudden.
-What? I'm curious.
-Future goals...
My goal is to be happy.
Happy? That sounds familiar.
Who said that?
She's the girl version of Arman.
-Nice.
-I think we'll get along.
I studied childcare for three years
in high school.
I went to a junior college
and dropped out after a year.
I had to move to Tokyo
for my modeling career.
So I did have the dream
of working with kids, you know?
-Your dream.
-Yeah, my dream.
I heard you can get certified
without going to school,
so I wanted to get certified--
So you want that,
but you're modeling in the meantime.
-That's right.
-I see.
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
-She has it planned out.
-Yeah.
Do you like to clean?
I'm not OCD, so I'm not super clean.
-That's good.
-Yeah, that's good.
-Do you like things neat?
-Not really.
I cleaned a little when Nacchan was here.
-Oh, she said it.
-Quietly.
Say it out loud, Riko.
-Say it out loud.
-It's okay.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I haven't had one for about a year.
What's your type?
None of the guys I've dated
were the same type.
So I don't really have a type.
But if there's even one thing
I can admire about him...
then I'd find him attractive.
-But someone I can be comfortable with.
-That's true.
-So whoever you fall for is your type.
-Yes.
-Thanks.
-Do you want to see the girls' room?
-If you don't mind.
Need help with your luggage?
-We have the elevator.
-Okay.
-I'll take you.
-I'm going to go see the room then.
Thank you.
Thank you?
Are you leaving or something?
My luggage is crazy heavy.
-It's nice to meet you.
-It's nice to meet you too.
I'm so nervous.
Is this your first time
living with others?
I have lived with a friend before.
We fought almost every day.
Because of a difference in lifestyle?
Apparently I'm pretty whimsical.
Apparently.
Um, so...
-You go ahead.
-It's okay.
Inspiration... Is it inspiration?
Or how do you say it?
-First impression?
-Yes! Yes that's what I meant.
My first impressions?
At a quick glance...
I liked Hayato.
Why? Why?
What's with that reaction?
Is that bad? Am I not allowed?
No, no...
She's laughing like crazy.
-No, I thought maybe it was Arman.
-Calm down.
How old is he?
-Twenty-nine?
-Twenty-nine.
That's totally fine.
-You like older men?
-I tend to like older guys.
-So the guys you've dated before...
-Mostly older.
What about you two?
I wonder...
Is it better if I don't ask?
We'll take it one step at a time.
Hayato's attractive.
Isn't he?
You keep laughing.
-Good morning.
-Are you cleaning up?
-Yeah.
So many dishes...
There are so many dishes.
-Can I help?
-It's okay.
-You sure?
-Don't worry about it. Please sit.
-Do you want some coffee?
-I'd love some.
I couldn't sleep at all.
I've got a hangover.
-It's my own fault.
-Your own fault.
-Good morning.
-Oh, coffee.
-Want some?
-Yeah.
-Is this okay?
-Sure.
Good morning...
-Arman.
-My head hurts.
I'm fine.
I couldn't sleep much though.
-The first day...
-What?
I can't hear.
-It's hard to sleep the first night.
-Yeah, it is.
-Do you have work today?
-No.
-My mom is visiting from Fukuoka today.
-So you're gonna see her?
-Yeah, I'm gonna see her.
-Nice.
-Do you have work today, Hayato?
-I do.
You start late, right?
Yeah, I'll leave around 3:00 p.m.
3:00 p.m.? Wanna have lunch then?
It's a nice day today.
We should all go in the pool.
Will the other girls join?
-Let's ask them.
-Okay.
Ready?
They're here.
Let's all go in.
-I'm scared.
-I'm starting to get nervous.
-No way.
-A little bit.
Are we all going in together?
Ready?
It's my first time.
I hate this part, having to jump in.
-I'll help you.
-That's okay.
It's freezing!
It's super cold.
It's not warm at all!
Can you doggy paddle?
It's really like a dog.
It's been a while for me.
-A race?
-Yeah, doggy paddle race.
Ready? Go!
He's good.
Is that normal swimming?
What? That was fine.
I lost.
Should we head back in?
It's freezing.
What's your schedule usually like?
My schedule's all over the place.
Sometimes I get called in
at the last minute.
It happens pretty often.
-When you're free, we should go out.
-Sure.
Where do you normally go?
Nowhere in particular.
Depends on how I'm feeling.
Okay.
You can leave it to me.
-Masako Endo.
-She's here.
-She's bright and cheerful.
-She's cute and energetic.
-And her goal is also to be happy.
-Yes, her goal for the future.
Who would've guessed?
But she likes Hayato.
But Arman asked her out.
-I wonder if she's Arman's type.
-He did seem interested.
-Love triangle?
-Things have been steady until now.
Speaking of steady,
Arman's doggy paddle...
That was impressive.
His head never wavered.
Just like that.
It's like there was a motor underneath.
Yeah!
The doggy paddle looks a little scary
when it's done too well.
Scary.
But maybe...
Masako talked about how she might find
one thing she could admire in a guy.
Maybe that qualifies.
-No way.
-You think she admires that?
The steadiness of his doggy paddle?
Would she really?
Admirable doggy paddling, happy...
-Nice physique.
"I meet all her qualifications."
-Oh, you mean Arman thinks that.
-Yes, from Arman's view.
What will Rikopin do now?
-It might push her to ask Hayato out.
-Hopefully.
And if Hayato makes any strange moves,
then Martha's friend is going to appear.
Like, "Hold on a sec, hold on.
I just heard."
I want to go in the pool every day.
-Maybe I'll go again today.
-But it was surprisingly cold.
It was warm at first, but it got cold.
It feels like a vacation.
Are you off?
You're going to work, right?
-No, I'm going to see my mom.
-Right, your mom.
How many siblings do you have?
-I'm an only child.
-An only child.
What do you usually do on your day off?
I usually go to the gym.
Oh, you work out.
We should go together next time.
-Is there a gym close by?
-Yeah.
I want to go.
Maybe I'll head to the convenience store.
-For breakfast?
-Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
See you later.
I'm gonna go shower.
I'm going to do laundry.
-Earlier...
-What?
Earlier...
I didn't expect Arman to ask me out
on a date on the first day.
Is that usually how it is?
-Like, to do something?
-To go somewhere.
I think.
I don't remember exactly.
-Did he say where?
-I asked him where he usually goes.
He said it depends
and to just leave it to him.
-Really? So you said yes?
-What?
-You said yes?
-Yeah, I did.
There's no reason for me to say no.
Right?
A date...
-Is it?
-So you're going.
Is it a date?
But yesterday, you know how girls talk?
They asked me who I liked
based on first impressions,
-and I said you.
-No way.
-But they laughed at me.
-Who did? Misaki, right?
-She was laughing so hard.
-Misaki?
I was like, "Why are you laughing?"
-I see.
-Yeah.
Do you cook?
Well...
when I used to live with my boyfriend,
-I did most of the cooking.
-Really?
-But I'm sure it doesn't compare to you.
-No...
Teach me something.
-Sure.
-Let's see...
What would you recommend that's easy?
I'll think about it.
But for now, since Arman asked,
I'll go out with him.
That's good.
-It's good.
It's good.
It's all good.