-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-No.
-Unfortunately, Ayumu is absent today...
-Yes.
for reasons related to his being young.
-"His being young."
-I see.
Newspapers referred to him
as a genius child actor.
-Wow.
-Is that right?
Who will lead the movie industry
in the future.
-Really?
-Wow.
So, I was afraid I'd be nervous
if I saw him.
-It's a good thing he's absent.
-I'm glad.
-I'll have time to mentally prepare.
-Yes, you have time.
In the last episode,
Makoto and Minori
had grilled meat together.
-Yes, yes.
-They had.
They're moving quickly.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
However, Mizuki, the barista,
showed hostility towards her.
-The barista.
-Yes, she did.
-She launched her attack.
It began when Makoto apologized to Mizuki
at Yuki's birthday party.
-That's right.
-"I also had issues about baseball.
I didn't talk about it. I'm sorry."
So, Mizuki,
it felt like we all kind of
ganged up on you.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
I should've said this
right then and there.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
Thank you so much
for coming here to say that.
-Oh, no, it's inexcusable.
-Don't worry.
-Good night.
Good night.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
It made me kind of happy to think
that he was concerned about me.
-Love triangle.
-Right.
And then, Yuki and Yuriko had
Japanese sake together.
Ah, Yuriko brought Hepalyse.
-Oh, that.
-Hepalyse!
That knocked me out.
-She said, "Here."
-That's it, yes!
Just like a commercial.
-True.
-Exactly.
We talked a whole lot when we broke up.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT
Sorry.
I just open up so easily to you, Yuki.
They promised to have a drink
together again.
-That's right.
-Yes, they did.
I think they're solid.
-I think they are.
-Is that so?
They get on my nerves.
Tap showed us many sides.
In the boy's room, Yuki was
sort of worried about Tatsuya's feelings.
He said, "Sorry,"
and Tatsuya was like, "Don't."
Like, you don't need to be conscientious
just because I expressed
some interest in Yuriko.
-Like, really...
-Well not so much conscientious--
No, really, I don't care
if it's discourteous.
So, we have two love triangles.
That's right.
-That's true.
-Beautifully.
Isn't this the first time?
Two love triangles.
-That's right. No one's left out.
-That's amazing!
Come to the pool with me.
Pool, right.
Mizuki's swimsuit.
-That's not what I mean.
-I gotta see Mizuki in her swimsuit.
I hear you've brought several swimsuits--
-But I haven't worn much.
-That's the rumor I heard.
I do have several.
It'll continue raining for the next week.
-I'll make some coffee.
-Yes, sure.
While you're drinking alcohol,
I'll drink coffee.
Six...
seventeen.
-Welcome home!
-Here he comes.
-What towel is that?
-The Giants towel. It's for Chono.
-Ah, Chono. Looks good.
-Who won?
Yakult. We lost.
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
-Amazing. Great timing.
-People are coming home.
-Who wants coffee?
-I want some.
Okay, then I'll make more.
You won't be able to sleep again.
I'm okay. I'll stay up.
-Who else is home?
-Minori.
She rented another scary movie.
I won't watch it.
I'm scared of horror movies, too,
so let's go see a movie together.
Which one?
-Amazing!
-He goes right for it!
-I'll be on summer break.
-Right, summer break.
More like fall break.
As of the second, right?
-Just the two of you?
-Yes, the two of us.
Really? Sure.
-What's that about?
-What?
-Well, I wanna go, too.
-I wonder if it's ready.
Next time.
Thank you. Is it sweetened?
Not yet. I'll get sugar,
so serve yourself.
By myself?
Please put it for me.
-I have practice tomorrow.
-It is getting late.
I think I'll go to bed.
It looks like it's going to be long.
-Good night.
-I'll leave her to you.
-You're going?
-I'll be relaxing downstairs.
I'll go.
Okay.
-Where do you wanna go on the second?
-Are you off on the night of the second?
-How about in the morning?
-I can take a day off.
-So let's go in the morning.
-Okay.
You make plans then.
-You want me to make plans?
-Yeah, on the second.
-For real?
-Yes.
-I'll think about it.
-Think about it.
-Something I can enjoy.
-What?
Isn't it usually the other way around?
-No, no. Please make plans.
-I'll come up with something.
Have you talked with Minori?
We haven't been able to talk at all.
You'd better.
Minori sleeps over there
because she says the bed is too hard.
But for sure there's an issue there.
-You think so?
-Among you girls.
She comes downstairs
and has guy talk with the three of us.
-Is it really that bad between us?
-Hmm?
I was wondering
if the vibe was that bad between us.
I think it is. Already.
I see.
Wow. Isn't it a little too hot?
I'm gonna make more bubbles.
This is good.
Feels like being in some resort.
We took a bath
on the first and second days.
-The second?
-Did we all go in?
-We took one together.
-Right.
Seems a long time ago.
-All clean?
-Not yet. Still on the eyelashes.
The reason I called you out
for a bath is...
-Someone told you something?
-I got called out.
So, do you always sleep
in the living room
because of the problems between us girls?
-That's not true at all.
-Really?
We're making you feel unwelcome--
-Uchi said that?
-Yup.
-Why did he think that?
-I'm not sure.
We didn't talk about that.
He told me you said something like that.
-Makocchan's been sleeping downstairs.
-Is that so?
-He's focused on baseball.
-And has to get up early.
-He says he won't stay up late.
-Right.
Makocchan asks me out
at every chance he gets.
Even though he asks me out so much,
I don't know what he's thinking.
What do you mean?
We keep in contact regularly.
You like him, don't you?
-That's not quite right.
-No?
We could be just good friends.
I don't know.
What could it be?
When we talked about
who made the best first impression,
we all said Makocchan.
So, I wonder
if that feeling is increasing,
or, like, it's going in
a direction that you want.
Well, I think...
Has it remained the same?
Has the impression stayed the same?
It's the same, I guess...
Well... that's...
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Let's eat.
-It's risotto.
-Is it good?
It tastes good.
-Uchi, I wanna get a haircut.
-Come to my place.
I wanna do it before the summer break.
-Our salon before the summer break--
-Booked?
We're open only on
Saturday, Sunday and Monday.
Maybe if you come Monday.
-Are you shaving your head?
-You want it shaven?
No, no. I want it short, though.
I'll ask if there's
an open slot on Monday.
What was the day we're getting together?
Is everyone available?
I'm free on the second.
I'm going out with Mizuki in the morning.
-Really?
-A date?
I asked her to make plans for me.
Oh, you're here. Good timing.
What is this? Some kind of dish?
Minori made a bowl of something?
-Minori's risotto bowl.
-Risotto bowl?
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
I'm back.
-Eggs.
-From the convenience store?
-Yeah. I love it.
-It's super delicious, isn't it?
Yuriko, are you free
on the third or the fourth?
I'm free on the third.
After school, I'm free on the third.
Wanna go somewhere?
In the evening?
Then I'll make plans.
-Really?
-What?
-So, for Yuriko...
-Why, Uchi?
-You, make plans?
-I feel a bit...
No, no. You're wrong.
It's not like that.
I believe you should communicate
differently with different people.
-True.
-Yes.
I'll go out with Minori, too.
How about you, Minori?
-I...
-We'll discuss.
-Discuss?
-After we've discussed...
-You'll make plans together.
-Yeah, yeah. We'll plan.
-It's all different.
-It's different.
-Maybe it's time for bed.
-I'm going to bed.
Coming?
-Good night.
-One by one.
-Yes.
-Dating all of us.
-All of us.
-It's funny.
-It is.
What a fucker!
-He's unbelievable.
-Isn't he?
-Totally new.
-He's making moves.
This is a new tactic.
I asked for stimulation,
but this hit me straight in the stomach.
What a fool!
He's too quick.
How does that make women feel?
I don't like it.
It's like,
"You wanna go out with me, right?"
I bet he's been like that all his life.
He thinks every girl he meets
is happy to go out with him.
But he differentiates,
letting Mizuki make plans.
"With you, I'll make plans.
With you, we'll plan together."
He shows that he thinks of
each one differently.
He's open in that way.
-No, no, no, no!
-He is.
No, no! Open?
He's nasty.
-The girls said yes.
-Why?
Because of his looks?
If so, this country is done!
-Country?
-That's going too far.
Surprisingly, girls who fall for guys
who are open about everything,
don't get angry with them.
A friend of mine is like that.
At his birthday party,
all his ex-girlfriends gathered there.
-He was unbelievable.
-Unbelievable.
But he was so open about it
that everything settled nicely.
I wondered how he could build
such a kingdom.
He might be the same type.
Son of a bitch!
Please have a seat.
-Well, well, well.
-How would you like it done?
-What should I do?
-It's really long...
-Really long...
How do you want it?
Leave the top part a little...
That's what everyone says.
"Leave the top part."
-Let's shampoo, then.
-Let's do it.
-Can I really cut it?
-Yeah, go for it.
Don't get mad.
I won't get mad.
Because after I cut your hair
and we go home...
Your reputation is at stake.
-I'm sure there will be talk.
-Especially from the girls.
-What's funny?
-I'm really nervous.
I'll be on summer break starting tomorrow.
Cool.
I'll have lots of dates.
-Where are you taking Yuriko?
-Well...
to Enoshima Aquarium.
Night Aquarium.
Minori and I will go somewhere big.
-What do you mean, big?
-Mihara-yama.
-You'll climb the mountain?
-We'll climb the mountain.
It's a day trip though.
-Day trip?
-We'll take a ferry to Izu Oshima.
Yeah, we'll go there.
-Does it look okay?
-It looks okay.
What will Minori think?
-That's the focal point?
-Aren't I right?
You're right.
I can't wait to see Makoto's new style.
What if he shaved his head?
If it's horrible, I'll blame Uchi.
-How about saying nothing about his hair?
-That's a good idea.
I'm sure he wants your opinion.
-Why?
-He doesn't care what I think.
What would be a good comment?
"Looks good"?
-Here I am.
-Here he is. He's back.
-Welcome home.
-Back from practice?
-Not practice
-Oh, right.
-I got it cut.
-Cut?
-What?
-At Uchi's.
-Did he cut your arms?
-No, Uchi cut my hair.
Uchi cut your hair?
-Right.
-Oh.
It got shorter.
-Isn't that a little slow?
-You got a haircut?
It got much shorter.
-Where?
Here. The back.
It's hot.
Tell him what you think.
-It looks good.
-Really?
I'm glad.
-Looks good.
-Uchi was skillful, but nervous.
-He was nervous?
-He was.
He was glad his first customer was a guy.
It got a lot shorter.
-He cut a lot.
-It looks great.
Is your makeup different today?
A different shade of lipstick gives
a totally different image.
I don't know anything about makeup.
-But you noticed this, right?
-That I did.
But you didn't say anything.
I don't bring up stuff
like shades of lipstick.
But it makes girls happy.
-It does.
-Right?
What do you wanna do now?
Wanna go somewhere?
If we eat out, I want something
we don't cook at home, like fish.
I have an idea.
What?
A place where you eat the fish you catch.
You don't know it?
Sounds fun.
You eat the fish you catch?
-Where?
-It's true.
MEGURO, TOKYO
ZAUO
FISHING BOAT TEA HOUSE
We're gonna fish.
-What do we catch first?
-Let's see.
I want horse mackerel.
-Yeah, horse mackerel.
-Horse mackerel?
Then this tank.
You can catch lobsters too?
I want lobsters and turban shells too.
CATCH AND FISH
(2 - 4 FISHING POLES)
Which ones are horse mackerels?
-That white-colored one.
-That one.
Come here, horse mackerel.
Come, Mr. Horse Mackerel.
I'll put the hook in front of it.
Come get the bait.
We can't catch any.
Wait.
-Here it comes!
-You got it?
You got it!
-Good catch!
-Thank you.
-How would you like it cooked?
-Sashimi and nigiri sushi?
-Nigiri sushi?
-Nigiri, okay.
Oh, I got it! I caught one!
Good catch!
-What's this?
-Horse mackerel.
-Is this it?
-Yeah.
Incredible.
-What's this?
-It's a chicken grunt.
Not a horse mackerel.
Nice chicken grunt.
FISHING MENU
Here you are.
Sea bream sashimi and sushi.
Amazing.
Awesome.
Looks delicious.
-How is it?
-Delicious.
Do you know the market price?
I don't know what that means.
Lobsters are priced as quoted.
It depends on the day.
Depends on the cost price.
Market price. I'll remember.
Any interesting stories lately?
What a direct question!
When you weren't here,
I asked him how things are.
What things?
-What he thinks of you.
-You asked that?
-In a different way.
-Very straightforward.
-What do you think of me?
-Seriously?
"What do you think of me?"
Amazing.
I don't love her or anything,
but I want to get to know her better.
Very simple.
So boring.
Boring?
Like, as if she's just one of the three?
So boring.
It's not like...
Boring, yeah.
-I'll tell everyone.
-Did you expect something more?
-Yeah?
-Definitely something more.
-There was no feeling to it.
-Nothing.
-I think highly of her.
-Highly?
Highly?
You don't think of
all three of them equally?
-You don't, do you?
-Huh? What?
Why are you two talking through me?
No, no. We're talking to you.
-The conversation is directed--
-What's my role here?
It was going this way and that way.
And this way.
-What did you ask?
-You're asking me?
-I don't think that way.
-What do you mean?
I'm interested in Yuriko.
She's up here.
-And I'm here, right?
-What's that?
That's not true.
Why doesn't anybody think of me as a girl?
-I do.
-No, you don't.
I do too.
-She doesn't feel it.
-I don't.
Are you and Yuriko going out somewhere?
-Huh?
-In the future.
-The aquarium.
-You're going to the aquarium?
When?
September.
After my show.
-She's going there with someone else, too.
-Someone else?
-Who?
-Uchi.
Is he taking her there?
He said he was taking her to the aquarium.
Should I have said that?
Does she like the aquarium that much?
But you're taking her first, right?
-No, later.
-What? Later?
He said on the third...
But you asked her first.
-I don't know.
-Uchi did this intentionally?
It seems Uchi was the one
who chose the aquarium.
He did this intentionally.
What?
But wouldn't she decline to go?
So Yuriko is comparing Yuki and Uchi.
That can't be true.
What... is this feeling?
What are you saying?
I'm a confused 28-year-old.
-This is good. Fun.
-Interesting.
It's getting interesting.
It's getting complicated.
-Indeed.
-Not good.
Uchi knew Yuki and Yuriko were going
to the aquarium,
but he asked her to go with him
before she goes with Yuki.
-But could he have known?
-Is it a coincidence?
If it was a coincidence,
for Yuriko to accept it...
she's very...
But Uchi hasn't told her
about the aquarium.
-He hasn't?
-I see.
So no one is to blame.
I see.
So, Yuriko is in for a surprise.
-Right.
-And she'll go, "You too?"
"This again?"
But he makes a lot of moves,
so he may simply say, "I just knew."
It depends on which one successfully
entertains Yuriko at the aquarium.
He may say things like that.
I want him to have
an overwhelming sense of defeat.
Overwhelming.
I wish we could add
another charismatic hairstylist.
-Makocchan's hairstyle is very good.
-Thankfully.
Man, he has skill, too?
Unfortunately he does.
I wished he'd been just a shampooist
pretending to cut hair for TV.
But no, he can actually cut hair.
Yes, he can actually do it.
Makocchan and Minori are going well.
-Very well.
-It seems good.
That dinner scene was good.
That's how love grows.
"What did you say?"
"Huh?" "Huh?"
-We know you heard it.
-Very cute.
And while he's leading the two of them
in the right direction,
tragedy hits him.
"What? The aquarium? What?"
"My aquarium!"
"My aquarium..."
It's not Monopoly.
-Isn't it getting complicated too soon?
-It's fun!
It's because they know
they have only 18 weeks.
It gets more interesting
if the time is limited.
-You're right.
-We've learned.
If we don't tell them,
they don't do anything.
Where are you going, Mizuki?
Have you decided?
Oh, um... let me think.
-Spo-cha.
-Spo-cha. Sounds good.
Uchi hasn't told you yet,
but he's been thinking about it.
-Really? He's been thinking about it?
-Yeah, it's a nice place.
Very date-like.
-It's very, very nice.
-Wow, really?
How was Makoto today?
Did you like his hair?
It was good, it was good.
I freaked out while I was cutting it.
You told him about Uchi week, didn't you?
-Uchi week, yeah.
-Which starts today.
-It starts now.
-Now, right.
Are you going to the aquarium
by any chance?
I am.
Me too.
-With whom?
-Yuriko.
-We made the same plans.
-That's right.
Makoto just told me.
-When are you going?
-Next week.
-I'm going on the third.
-You're earlier.
I'm earlier, so I win.
-I win.
-I'm not sure who wins.
Should I postpone?
Because you already made plans.
We ate out together the other night,
and we talked about the aquarium
in our conversation.
Then I'll change my plan.
It doesn't matter either way.
But if we take her to the same place...
-It's not right for her.
-Which aquarium?
-The one in Sky Tree.
I'm taking her to Enoshima.
Different aquariums.
What kind of duel will this be?
Right.
-So how is it, Minori?
-How's what?
-Makocchan.
-What do you mean?
Well, the three of us had dinner together.
-Right.
-Naturally, the conversation led there.
-What did he say?
-What did Makocchan say?
He said, "I don't love her or anything".
-He did?
-That's a lie.
From where we stand,
Makoto's totally in love with you.
Really? I'm sure he isn't.
-Really?
-I don't think he's in a hurry.
I think so.
Minori, you don't have to change.
I mean, if he's not acting like
he's really in love with you
and he doesn't admit it,
at least he's fond of you.
But you look so cute.
You look happy.
Nobody thinks of me as a girl...
-Wrong.
We talked about it over dinner.
Makoto said he thinks of me as one.
He's honest on that point.
Unless he says it clearly, I don't know.
Just make him say it clearly.
You're fun to be with,
and he knows you like him.
So the rest is up to him, right?
Right.