-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Many things happened last week.
First, there was
Uchi and Minori's very nice date.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD
Well, I asked you out because I like you.
What do you mean, you like...
Oh, I'm so bad with this stuff!
He told her he liked her.
Minori didn't answer, but was embarrassed,
like, "Oh no, what should I do?"
-And Makoto...
-You almost forgot, didn't you?
Ma-ko-to.
He gave Minori sneakers as a present,
and they went for an evening run together.
And gave you the shoes.
So, until the season is over,
I wanted to close the gap between us.
After the season, when I have more time,
maybe we can go somewhere.
That's what I was thinking.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD
He said a line that will go down
in Terrace House history.
"And gave you the shoes."
The way things ended
for Yuki and Yuriko...
-That was shocking, right?
-It was shocking.
You remember how I once told you about
how I broke up with my ex?
I haven't been able to forget him.
I think I should take the initiative
and call him,
and tell him I miss him.
That's good.
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
-It's a good day.
-A good day.
"It's a good day."
What a good day
And Mr. Chou would appear and say,
"How about an ending to love like this."
You guys are terrible.
Aren't you getting sick of people?
-That's not true, right?
-No, not at all.
Just a little bit more.
That's what a monster would say.
"See, humans are no good."
I think I might see a tail behind me.
GIRLS AWARD AUDITIONS
Is this your first time
auditioning for a runway show?
-Yes, it's my first time.
-Your first?
Then imagine
30,000 attendees watching you.
TOSHIYA UO
DIVISION DIRECTOR
Please walk with that image in mind.
You're entertaining 30,000 people.
What did you think?
The clothes for this show,
Jill by Jill Stuart, are a little...
We have this image of the models
wearing something chic.
So that image, and as I mentioned earlier,
30,000 attendees will be watching you
the entire time.
So we want your walk to be fun,
and still express our brand.
In that sense, you're still too stiff.
But I hope you work at it.
I'll work on it.
-Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
She could be good.
She has long limbs.
She's got a clean look.
She's still too stiff.
-But the clothes look good on her.
-Yes.
Hello? This is Yuriko.
It's been awhile.
I'm sorry for calling so suddenly.
I'm sorry.
Oh, thank you for the LINE message.
And...
I thought it'd be nice...
to see you again.
Could we meet?
-Hey.
-Game?
-Can I come in?
-Yeah.
-By yourself?
What's up?
-I wanted to talk to you.
-What is it?
We went running the other day, right?
I've been thinking about stuff since then.
I was wondering about your timing.
I thought if I let things be,
you'd lean toward Uchi.
I'll take that to mean
that you're interested in me.
But the next time we decide to hang out,
it's not intended to mean
I'm responding to your feelings toward me.
That's how I feel right now.
We got along so well at first.
I said I was interested in you.
I liked you, but...
to be honest...
I had no idea what you were thinking
or what you wanted to do.
You'd say you were going to ask me out,
but wouldn't follow through.
And so I went on a date with Uchi,
but then you got upset,
and wouldn't talk to me.
Well, it wasn't that
you didn't talk to me,
but you were obviously avoiding me.
I wasn't avoiding you.
It was just plain jealousy.
But that happened...
and it would be an overstatement
to say I was disgusted...
but I didn't like it.
And so at this time,
I don't want to go out with you again.
So that's where you're at?
Got it.
-Sorry to bother you.
-Later.
-Good night.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
-Hey.
-Hey to you.
-Everyone's still awake today?
-Yeah.
I was...
talking with Minori downstairs.
I told her we should hang out
after my season ends.
-Yeah, I remember you saying that.
-You asked her out?
But then...
she said something about bad timing.
What timing?
Us going out after baseball.
But she said she didn't want to.
-She rejected you?
-Yeah, she said no.
Really? Why?
She knows I like her
but can't reciprocate, or something.
She said something like that.
She didn't say it outright,
but I guess she dumped me.
-Dumped?
-Yeah.
-Without telling her you liked her?
-I never told her.
You never clearly told her your feelings.
So I don't think you'd get a clear answer.
-So you were wrong?
-I was wrong.
Wow, so Makoto finally admits
that he was wrong.
-I'm glad.
-He was wrong?
-He was wrong.
-But when he was dumped,
how did you want him to react?
In the guys' room,
I wanted him to say, "Good luck."
-To Tatsuya.
-Oh, I see.
-"It didn't work out for me, so..."
-"Good luck to you."
Man, you're so thoughtful
to come up with something like that.
I was thinking
Uchihara was laughing hysterically inside.
Not hysterically.
No, not laughing hysterically.
I thought he was pinching himself.
Too obvious!
-It was good Minori spoke up.
-It was.
Because she feels his interest,
even though he hasn't said anything,
and she tells him clearly
that she won't reciprocate.
-Why couldn't Yuriko do that, too?
-I knew you would say that.
Even her call to her ex,
wasn't it kind of nasty?
-I think it was normal.
-What?
I felt like I was watching a reenactment.
From what she said, it's obvious
that she wants to get back together.
Yeah, for the guy, it's just a matter of
when and if he wants.
It was too obvious.
But if Yuriko was the one
who dumped him in the first place,
then the guy must be happy
that she came back.
Busy day?
Yeah, it was crazy.
A girl from Hokkaido came to see me.
-I was moved.
-Wow, she watches Terrace House?
-Yeah, she saw the show.
-Wow!
-What a nice day.
-Yeah, it was nice.
-You know how we practiced walking?
-Oh yeah, we practiced together.
Together? I don't understand.
-I was practicing for the audition.
-Yeah, I watched as she practiced.
-It was for Girls Award.
-The one you mentioned before?
-Oh, really?
-You said you were going.
I did, and I passed the audition.
-That's a big one. Congrats! Wow!
-Congratulations!
-That's impressive.
-I have to practice.
Is there something we can do to help?
Hmm, something we can do?
Come get your hair done.
-What?
-Come get your hair done.
Treatment and head massage.
I want a head massage!
-Oh, nice!
-Sure.
I want a head massage!
-It's a nice day today.
-Yeah, it's a nice day.
BLAST
DAIKAN-YAMA, TOKYO
-Good morning.
Let's start the morning meeting.
Any announcements?
MIKI TAKEUCHI, DIRECTOR OF THE SALON
Today is a holiday,
and we expect to be busy around 2:00 p.m.
So, please plan ahead in the morning
along with your assistant.
Also, we have a job offer.
There's a hair and make-up job
on October 24th.
It's the hair and make-up for Girls Award.
It's for a few of the models.
The members currently assigned are
Nishikaji, Otani, Kojima,
me, and Uchihara.
Once we work out the details,
I'd like to have another meeting.
MARUNOUCHI, TOKYO
-How are you?
TADAMICHI KAWANO, M.D.
YURIKO'S EX-BOYFRIEND
-Did you wait long?
-No, not at all.
-I went ahead and sat.
-Oh, that's all right.
I thought you'd bring me a Hepalyse.
It's seriously been awhile.
You've been busy, right?
What department are you in now?
Nephrology now.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
Are you pretty busy, too?
Mmm, exams are coming... in a week.
-In a week?
-What? Yes.
Are you ready for them?
-Look so good.
-Yeah.
-You like bagna càuda, right?
-You liked it, right?
-Yeah.
I remember it...
It's been awhile
since I've had such good food.
You usually don't eat much?
I rarely eat out.
At the hospital?
I've eaten most of the food
delivered to the hospital.
Of course.
-You surprised me.
-Where are you looking?
This way, please.
-Head massage and treatment, right?
-Yes, please.
"Yes, please"?
I'll take care of you.
-What? What?
-I get to see you work.
This is embarrassing.
-Does it hurt?
-No, it feels nice.
The massage is done.
Relaxed?
Relaxed. It felt really good.
It's so soft.
-Silky, right?
-Yeah, silky. It's amazing.
Super silky, right?
You know what?
If you make me dinner, we'll call it even.
Really?
What kind of food?
Think of something for me.
-Oh, there it is again.
-Yep.
-I don't even know what you like.
-Think of something for me.
Pasta?
You're gonna make pasta for me?
Yeah.
-When?
-Whenever you want.
-Today works for me.
-All right.
So today, um...
There's something I want to tell you...
which is why I asked you out.
We broke up in a positive way.
But really...
I haven't been able to forget.
I still love you.
I thought maybe we could start over.
Or I thought...
When you called me asking to meet,
I was honestly happy...
and I was looking forward to seeing you.
But seeing you in person today
and talking like this...
I felt like it wasn't really like you.
You told me
you couldn't forget about us...
but it didn't quite make me feel ecstatic.
Before exams, we always tried
to focus on our own studies.
At least while we were together.
I know you're looking for an answer,
but I'd rather you concentrate
on your studies as a med student now.
I can't give you an answer right now.
After I get through exams...
will I be able to get an answer?
I think I'd like to
give you an answer then.
I understand.
Oh, wow.
How was your head massage?
It's so soft now, and it felt really good.
-So you're all ready.
-Not even close.
I can't walk straight yet.
-You're practicing today too, right?
-Yeah.
-It's going to take a while, right?
-Call me when you want to practice.
-Okay.
I'll help you.
-Oh, you're cooking.
-I'm cooking.
Looks so good!
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
What's my score?
A hundred points.
All right, I got three stars.
It's almost the Girls Award thing.
Which brand are you working for?
It's still in discussion,
so I still don't know the details.
I see.
But afterward,
we should go out for dinner.
-Okay.
-Whenever our schedules work.
You're not busy afterward?
I think it'll calm down.
I want something tasty.
Then let's get something tasty.
So soft...
You're posing here and there, right?
Go ahead.
Minori!
Good!
-Looking at it, what do you think?
-Yeah, it's actually straight.
You don't do that thing anymore
where your left foot goes out to the side.
-I think the practice is paying off.
-I'm glad.
Of course, you were working so hard.
If I'd started working on it
a long time ago,
it wouldn't have been like this.
Have confidence.
Thank you.
Uchi and Minori are set now.
For sure.
The head massage...
What you said was classic Professor Tokui.
Please say it again.
It's an Indian foreplay.
The Kama-sutra.
-Head massages are an Indian foreplay.
-Thank you very much.
All that steam, with his hands...
Oh, stop that movement.
And plus, her face is here.
And so to come over like this,
to get close like this is fresh, isn't it?
-Here...
-Her face...
The face...
Stop! You're troubling Ayumu.
Ayumu, close your eyes
and cover your ears!
You're too good for this place.
But Yuriko's ex...
He's such a good guy!
Anyone who wears a sweater like that
is not a bad person.
The one with the white spots
around the top?
No bad person wears that.
Sawabe used to wear that.
-Oh yeah, a good guy then.
-Definitely a good guy.
-But that was a stylish scene.
-You're right.
She tells her ex
that she wants to get back together,
and he replies, "That's not like you."
Mr. Tokui, somehow when you say it,
it comes out sounding a little dirty.
Really? But I wasn't trying.
It's just natural to you.
Oh, so it's kneaded
into the dough already.
-Like spinach pasta.
-Oh, I see.
Do you remember
our nasty comments from last week?
-What did we say?
-"Oh, he saw her on TV."
"I'd hit that one more time.
Just one more time."
He probably saw her on TV and thought,
"Hey, she looks pretty good."
Yeah, he probably thought
maybe one more time.
Just one more time.
You said he was trying
to do her one more time!
He did say that.
That was Tokui!
That was me.
I deeply apologize!
We're so sorry.
When I'm hurt,
I'd like for you to treat my injury.
So I...
have an announcement.
What is it?
The league matches end on October 18th.
I told you before, right?
And when it's over...
-I'm thinking of moving out.
-For real?
-When you're done with baseball?
-Yeah.
I'm thinking of moving out.
Well, not really thinking.
I've already decided.
What made you decide?
After baseball is over...
I want to think about
what my next move will be.
And I considered doing that here.
But if I really want to move forward,
I think I need to put more pressure
on myself.
Even if it's not as a baseball player,
I'm sure there are lots of other paths.
I'm sure there are.
Both of you guys are independent.
You're both working, and seeing that...
Something...
I felt something.