-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
Last week, Yuriko left Terrace House...
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD
-She's going to focus on her exams.
-Yes.
She's going to concentrate.
Last week, we had great guest appearances.
-Minori's big sister.
-Kurumi.
She was able to give a big push
to a stalling relationship.
She did.
So you're afraid
his feelings aren't at that level?
KURUMI NAKADA, 23 YEARS OLD
Like, embracing you
because he can't hold back anymore?
-Yeah, that'd be...
-That's totally what you want!
Why don't you put yourself
in that mindset?
I am.
So seeing her sleeping face
doesn't make you want to kiss her?
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD
I can't bring myself to do it.
But if you do something like that,
it'll make everyone think,
"Wow, you like her that much."
I'll try my best.
That was the Kurumi Mix.
They threw in the Kurumi Mix.
It's been very effective thus far.
It did seem to make Minori want to
take some action.
And Yamachan's favorite new member...
Don't say that!
What if she's watching?
-What's going on here?
-Yeah, what's up with that ugly guy there?
Call me obnoxious, but don't call me ugly.
I'm Arisa Ohata.
-Arisa?
-Arisa Ohata.
-Where are you from?
-I'm from Kagoshima.
What do you do?
I'm now getting ready
to start my own hat brand.
Can I ask what's your type?
Someone who can survive
on a deserted island.
Not many people can give
an answer like that.
She's gotta be good.
Yamachan, you speak too soon.
-But she said she kinda liked Arman.
-Yeah.
Arman seemed easy to talk to.
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD
He seems like he'd be able to survive
on a deserted island.
He's definitely that type.
No, I hope it doesn't work out
for her at Terrace House.
What are you trying to accomplish?
I hope she fails.
Arman should get together with Mizuki!
Oh, I don't know.
Cheers.
-The new member's here.
-Yeah, finally.
She's cute. Very cute.
She is.
I didn't say it earlier,
but she's totally my type.
I think our eyes met when we both saw her.
I totally thought she'd be your type, too.
I guess it's down to which one of us
could survive on a deserted island.
-What about your job interview?
-The interview?
I heard back.
It was a no.
You really wanted it, too.
Yeah, but I'll give it another shot
at a different place.
-Can I come in?
-Oh, hey.
Joining us?
Clean it up, Arman.
-These aren't mine.
-Must be Uchi's.
-Man, that Uchi.
-Yeah, Uchi's so messy.
-A glass?
-I'll go grab one.
-What are you drinking?
-I didn't buy too much today.
-But aren't those from today?
-No, those aren't from today.
They were just there.
-You got me a glass.
-I'm sorry there isn't much left.
I should've come earlier.
We only have this and a small beer.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
A toast?
-Thanks for letting me join.
-Welcome.
Cheers. It's nice to meet you.
I didn't expect you to join us for drinks.
Did you have a boyfriend until recently?
I haven't had a boyfriend
for about two years.
You must be popular.
I've never had a guy I liked
like me back.
What?
-Do you do any sports?
-Sports?
-I'm not good at sports all.
-That's fine.
You never played any?
In junior high,
I was manager of the baseball team.
Ah, a manager.
Do you go to the gym?
-Not at all.
-You look like you're in shape.
Thank you.
I jog sometimes.
-Shall we drink?
-Is there any left?
Should we go out to drink?
-I guess it's late. You've got work.
-I'll go buy some real quick.
I'll be right back.
-Have you gotten used to things?
-I have.
Really?
-I'm envious.
-You'll get used to it, too.
You think so?
Can you go anywhere with one bag?
About two years ago, I went to Thailand
and the Philippines with just a backpack.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I can hunt.
Hunt?
Well, when I was in Hawaii,
I would spear fish.
You dive and shoot them with a spear.
Where I'm from, it's all mountains.
So there's nothing, just the countryside.
-I'd like to live there in the future.
-Oh, you want to go back.
Sometimes I miss being in nature.
Like, recently, I climbed Mt. Takao
with a friend from my hometown.
Is that close to Tokyo?
-Yeah, it takes an hour by train.
-For real?
-Do you want to go?
-Let's go somewhere like that.
-You want to go to Mt. Takao? Really?
-Yeah, I've got time.
-Next week maybe?
-Okay.
ARMAN BITARAF, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 28 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
DAIKAN-YAMA, TOKYO
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-Did someone from the price tag shop call?
-Yeah, he did.
-He said he would come at 6:00 p.m.
-6:00 p.m.? Okay.
So you should prepare
the paper and data for the tags.
I see.
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD
FROM KAGOSHIMA
PREPARING TO START OWN HAT BRAND
SINGLE FOR 2 YEARS
Hmm?
-What?
-Sleeping?
Your nails are chipping.
I can fix them.
I'm certified as a nail artist.
-Level four.
-What does that mean?
-How many levels are there?
-I don't know.
Okay, ready?
My pinky is fine.
-You got some here.
-Where?
You're shaking.
What did my sister say?
She said...
Well, never mind.
No, tell me.
It keeps me up at night.
She said I'm not conveying my feelings.
-That's what she said?
-Yes.
Did she give you examples of how to act?
I wonder.
-One-one?
-One-one.
-That was from over here.
-I didn't touch it.
I'm winning for the first time.
-Oh, wow, it's three-one.
-For real?
-From the start...
-You're in trouble, Arman.
I might win.
-I lost.
-My first win!
-I worked up a sweat.
-I'm gonna grab a drink.
Did you drink a lot last night?
Well, Yuki went to buy more drinks...
He bought more alcohol?
Yeah, he got more,
so we had highballs.
So, Mizuki...
is there someone you're into?
-I'm not sure yet, but...
-I see...
It's only been a week since Arman came,
but we went out together once.
Since then, I'm more conscious of him.
That's where I'm at.
You've changed since your sister came.
Have I? How?
You're trying to change.
-Change in what way?
-Hmm?
In what way?
Well, in many ways.
-I...
-You always make it vague.
What's wrong with that?
You're right.
I do always make it vague.
You don't say everything you're thinking.
I know, I need to fix that.
Will you make me curry?
-You want curry?
-I do.
Bon appétit.
Where are the meat and vegetables?
They kinda melted.
-Is everyone asleep?
-Hmm?
-I think they're still up.
I think they're doing something.
Do you have work tomorrow?
Yeah, I've got work.
It was really good.
-Thank you for making it.
-Was it enough?
You're going to sleep?
-He's so stupid!
-So stupid!
So stupid!
So oblivious!
That was the notice-me missile.
Yes, she threw the notice-me missile.
So, the new thing is
the notice-me missile?
What was that? Just oblivious?
-She wanted him to make a move, right?
-What would you have done, Tokui?
He did her nails,
and then there was the curry...
I think, while doing her nails,
I'd move in,
and then she'd be like, "What?"
And then I'd say, "Oh, nothing."
That'd be my first move.
I'd throw that in there.
And then?
I'd throw that in first,
when nothing would happen.
I'd make her think,
"Oh, he tried to make a move."
And have her go make curry.
Since I threw that nothing move
in there first,
-I'd do nothing while eating curry.
-Oh, I see.
And it'll make her think, "Wait, what?"
She'd think,
"Oh, so nothing's gonna happen."
And lean back into the sofa.
Then the notice-me missile would fly.
No, but I'd make a move
before the notice-me missile.
When?
So, right when her nails are done,
he should grab her arm
and pull her towards him.
What?
He should already start pulling
as he's finishing her nails.
"Oh, but you just did my nails..."
Like that right?
Yeah, and then some of the polish
would smudge on the hand.
And they'd come apart and say,
"Look what you did to my hands."
And then he should kiss her again!
Nice.
Even you got that, right?
That a kiss should've happened there?
Yeah, I think so.
If it were me, when serving the curry,
I'd want him to ask me
to feed him the curry.
What?
That's so cute!
"Minori, the meat
to go along with the curry."
What are you saying?
"I'm sorry. Kill me, please."
-"This piece is too big."
-Oh, quiet you.
What the heck are you guys talking about?
But seriously, what's up with him?
-Maybe he's actually surprisingly shy.
-Maybe.
Though Minori was trying really hard.
She tried to give him opportunities.
And he knows
she's been wanting more out of him.
If he didn't do it then,
when will he do it?
That's true.
If not now, then when?
We've been so caught up.
We've forgotten Arman's making moves.
That's right.
Did you see how sad Mizuki looked
when they were playing ping-pong?
When she was keeping score.
It was sad.
-Arisa now knows how Mizuki feels.
-She told her.
The question is, what will she do
now that she knows?
She's gonna throw Arman a light jab.
When Arman comes after her,
she's gonna say, "Oh, no.
Mizuki likes you, so I can't."
All the while, making him come after her.
It's Arman's fault if he follows.
She said no, so he shouldn't go.
You've changed, man.
What happened to your black wings?
Look, I'm wearing a fluffy knit sweater.
-It's gentle.
-Oh, the one reserved for the good guys.
Did Uchi like your curry last night?
-He said it was tasty, but that was it.
-That was it?
And today?
I'm making omu-rice today.
-For Uchi?
-I'm going to make it for him.
You should clearly say,
"Look, I made this just for you."
So that he gets it?
-Do you have work tomorrow?
-I do.
-What are you doing tomorrow?
-I'm going to run in the morning,
and in the evening, I'm going to Target.
The gym?
I want to join a gym, too.
You should come to Target.
Are you interested in kickboxing?
Kickboxing?
-Yeah.
-You want to?
Kickboxing? Not the gym?
Well, you should come check it out.
I want to lift my butt.
-Squats are best for that.
-That's so hard.
Yeah, they're a hassle to do.
Sounds like they're having fun.
-Sounds like they're having fun.
-Does it?
-What's going on?
-Yeah, sounds like fun.
-Please.
-Looks good.
Don't judge by its appearance.
Bon appétit!
They've got our names on them.
-Did you notice?
-I did.
There was a heart, too.
-I didn't.
-What?
-Delicious.
-Yummy!
It's hot.
What did you do yesterday?
I was talking with Uchi.
Have things changed since we last spoke?
Not really.
He's probably got some pride issues.
-Because he doesn't know how?
-Yeah.
I think it'd be okay for him
to be more lovey-dovey with you.
-I agree.
-Nothing.
Yeah, I did talk to him about that before.
What should I write on his omu-rice
to get his attention?
"I love you."
That might be too forward.
Easy to write but...
Maybe hearts?
It could be cute.
"Welcome home," or maybe not.
Dear Uchi,
Welcome back.
Please eat and enjoy.
"Coward"?
-What did you write?
-"Coward."
-That's perfect.
-I wonder what he'll think.
He'll think it's cute,
but I'm sure it'll hit a sore spot.
Like an arrow going through.
I wrote it, great,
but now I can't face him.
Ooh, I want this.
-That looks expensive.
-It is.
If only I could have one.
Come in.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Minori, come here, will you?
What is it?
Here? Is that okay?
-Come over here.
-What? Why?
-Never mind why.
-Why?
Just come this way.
I'm scared.
Over here.
-What?
-Here.
Close your eyes until I say to open them.
What? No, I'm scared.
-I'm scared.
-Just close your eyes.
-Lift your chin.
-Why? Why?
-Keep your eyes closed. Don't worry.
-I'm scared.
Never mind then.
I scared you.
The two of them disappeared.
You wrote "coward."
-I did.
-What did that mean?
Exactly what it said.
Since you called me a coward...
I felt like I had to prove you wrong.
But there are other ways to do that.
At this point, it doesn't matter.
I need to be emotionally prepared.
When will you be prepared?
I wasn't expecting to see you today.
I'm going back down then.
-Thanks for the omu-rice.
-Yeah.
Minori...
Are you all right?
-Are you crying?
-No, I'm not crying.
How'd it go?
-I was surprised.
-Of course you'd be.
Of course.
I wrote it, sort of egging him on...
so I guess...
of course he'd react.
He wasn't mad per se,
but he wasn't happy
about being called a coward.
So he wanted to show me otherwise.
But I totally wasn't expecting it.
Oh, he's so terrible at this!
So, that was his reaction.
-I hope he does better.
-Must have been hard for you to watch.
-He said it three times.
-Yeah, he kept saying, "Close your eyes."
He thought I wasn't ready for it.
-Was he upset?
-Yeah, I think he was a little down.
Maybe I should go talk to him.
I'm calm now.
What will you say to him?
He probably thinks I rejected him.
-So you're going to tell him otherwise?
-Yeah.
And if I leave things like this,
it'll be really awkward tomorrow.
What the heck is he doing?
Why is he dragging it out?
Despite the fact that he's good-looking
and stylish...
maybe he's a virgin?
-He is giving off that vibe.
-I'm strongly detecting it.
He's never had a relationship?
I didn't understand it.
Lifting her chin...
in front of everyone?
What would've happened after that?
He would've tried to kiss her after that.
She called him a coward,
so he went to prove her wrong.
Like, "See, I can kiss you."
That's so lame!
Even though there's still lots
that Uchi doesn't know,
he hasn't been able to ask.
For a long time now, probably.
People just assume
he's gone out with lots of girls.
That he's good at his job
and sensitive to others' needs,
-that is his weakness.
-I see.
But he's the one who first said
he'd date all three.
That's exactly why he came up with
such an awkward idea.
That's proof.
He didn't do that
because he was experienced with women.
It's because he didn't know any better.
He genuinely didn't know
how to fall in love.
So he wanted to figure it out
by trying it out with everyone.
His intentions were truly pure.
-Seriously?
-So unexpected.
You know, the coward part...
-that was something.
-It made my heart pound.
That was really cute.
That was a legendary omu-rice.
-Truly legendary.
-A legendary omu-rice.
"Coward."
-Wonderful.
-It really is.
So she's going to see him now?
I think so.
She's gonna go, then kiss!
Go, then kiss?
Yeah, go to get kissed.
Even if she isn't planning to.
To the far end of Terrace House we go,
then kiss?
If he misses this chance, then that's it.
We're rooting for you, Uchi.
He just has to go for it.
-Doesn't matter if he's bad at it.
-Oh, bittersweet youth.
"I know how to kiss!"
So cute!
Okay! The kiss!
You don't have to be an expert.
Come in.
What's up?
What's wrong?
-I thought I'd come talk to you.
-Talk?
I'm sorry about earlier.
Don't worry about it.
This is unusual.
-I've calmed down.
-Calmed down?
I was totally out of sorts earlier
and couldn't speak.
I see. I was so surprised.
I wrote that
with a specific intention in mind.
Because yesterday...
I didn't think you would react that way.
So I didn't know how to deal with it.
You didn't know how to react.
I thought I was prepared for it,
but it kind of happened in a way
I wasn't expecting.
Do you like me?
I like you.
Are you ready now?
I've been ready.
That's why I wrote "coward."
Close your eyes.
You seemed so experienced.
I'm not.
-What?
-I'm not.
I'm sorry I can't do it better.
Thank you.