-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week, Minori and Uchi...
-left the house.
-That's right.
It was a tearful goodbye.
It finally felt like
everyone was under one roof.
Some warmth was finally back
at Terrace House.
This was all thanks to the meat incident.
That's true.
Meat can do so many things.
It's not just delicious.
And if they left, that means...
-Misaki's arrival.
-That's right. Tamosan is here.
-I'm sorry, what was your name again?
-I'm Misaki Tamori.
-Misaki?
-Misaki.
My friends call me Tamochan or Tamosan.
Tamosan?
-Super cute?
-Yeah?
Your type?
-She's pretty high energy.
-Yeah.
I love that.
Dreams for the future?
We haven't asked that yet.
An amusement park.
-To build one?
-Yes.
-An amusement park of everyone's dreams.
-That's right!
-A pretty girl.
-Yes, very beautiful.
-Her dream is to build an amusement park.
-Yeah.
Didn't you know someone like that
as a kid?
"When I build it,
I'll do your store, too!"
It's a little strange to say
after you turn 20, though.
That's right.
-The new guy is coming today.
-Yes, that's right!
-He seems mature.
-Very mature.
I'm very interested to see
what he looks like.
What made you decide?
I'm graduating...
I figured it'd be a good change of pace.
-Seems like the smart type.
-Yes.
-That's what's nice.
-I want to see his face.
-I want to see his face. Let's watch.
-Shall we watch?
I'm really nervous for some reason.
Maybe because it's so sudden.
-Wow.
-What do you mean, "Wow"?
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Handa.
It's nice to meet you.
-Kanda?
-Kanda.
What was your name again?
-Handa.
-Oh, Handa.
-I'm Yuto Handa. It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-What do you do?
-How old are you?
I'm currently still in university...
-You're a student?
-I'm graduating in March.
I major in architecture
at Tokyo University of the Arts.
I'm studying architecture.
I'm 27, trying to become an architect.
-He's older!
-You seem happy.
-You're super happy.
If you study architecture,
do you also design?
-Yes.
-Design?
Mainly designing and drafting, too.
I've been taking outside projects
such as renovating and designing cafés.
I'll continue to do it
and work independently.
With tools.
-You do it all yourself?
-I do.
-Wow.
-Not the best results.
-Oh, then he can make my amusement park.
-Amusement park?
-It's her dream.
-She wants you to design it.
Design an amusement park?
Sounds difficult.
-The dream is big.
-The dream is huge.
Why did you come to Terrace House?
I'm graduating,
but I don't plan on looking for a job.
I plan to spend this year preparing
to study abroad.
Is there a specific school in mind?
A school you're hoping to get into?
I'm aiming for Harvard in Boston.
-That's my first choice.
-Harvard?
-Harvard Architecture? That's impressive.
-Wow.
Yes, if I can get in.
Otherwise, maybe Columbia.
-You must be really smart.
-Not at all.
What do you need to do to get in?
Know English?
English, a portfolio of my work,
and an interview.
What about studying?
I do have to study a little.
A little bit.
So you finished school,
but you want to go back?
Yes. Graduate school.
-Wow.
-For a master's degree.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-I do.
-You do?
-Yes.
-Where? I mean, not where...
-Where?
How long have you been together?
-A little over two years.
-Oh, a long time.
How old is she?
She's turning... 23, I think.
-She didn't oppose to your moving here?
-That's right.
She did a little bit,
but she sent me off in good spirits.
-Do you drink?
-What?
-Yes, I do.
That's good.
Would you like a drink now? No?
Sure. Is that okay?
-Have you had dinner yet?
-Only a little.
-There's curry.
-Curry?
Sure, I'd love some.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
I'm gonna get water.
What do you think of...
Oh, you've only seen the living room.
-Yes.
-Me, too.
The exterior surprised me, though.
It's huge!
Right, this is right up your alley.
Are you looking around?
I'm planning on taking
a closer look at the details later.
Details? What details?
-Oh, the finer points around the--
-Here you go.
Thank you.
That's a big serving.
Is it?
I'm used to serving Hikaru.
I thought maybe that's not enough.
I can totally eat.
-Can I go ahead?
-Of course.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Do you like to keep things clean?
-Nope.
-Not at all?
I'm super messy.
Super messy?
So besides Natsumi,
does anyone else keep clean?
She just came in,
so I don't know how bad she is.
-I think it's pretty bad.
-You seem like you'd be messy.
Maybe that was rude.
Of course I'll keep clean, though.
It's a co-op after all.
Yay! I'm glad.
Let's do it together.
How long have you been together
with your girlfriend?
This is the second time you've asked,
but two and a half years.
He's so mature.
The way he answered that.
Two and a half years, huh?
It's that complicated point
in a relationship.
-That's your opinion.
-You said that earlier, too.
That's true.
It can be complicated.
-Especially during spring time.
-Right?
What do you mean, "Right"?
What are your plans tomorrow?
My friend just got married.
He asked me to build a table for him,
so I need to work on that.
Do you have tools with you?
-I have a lot.
-Really?
Where do you keep it?
I keep it at the studio.
-You have a studio?
-Yes.
Where is it?
We're asking so many questions.
Um, near Ueno.
Near the school.
He was nice enough
to pick up the trash here.
I thought maybe I dropped it.
Isn't that hardened leftover noodles?
-Hardened noodles?
-When is that from?
-I don't know.
-That's true. It's a little hard.
It's hard?
-I like that about him.
-He made your heart flutter?
I'll show you the rooms.
Can I put my luggage away?
-Me, too.
-That's right.
I'll wash this later.
You're so sweet!
-Well, I'm the one who ate it.
-I'm impressed.
Oh, thank you.
-Is this it?
-Yes, that's it.
I'll lead the way.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
ARISA OHATA, 25 YEARS OLD,
HAT DESIGNER
HIKARU OTA, 18 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
-Is that a traditional-style tattoo?
-Yeah.
-It's really cool.
-Thanks.
It had been just completed.
Added the color.
What are you working on right now?
My priority right now is the café project.
-The...
-You're doing the interior?
-The exterior.
-The exterior?
They asked for a more stylish exterior,
so that anyone would recognize it
as a café.
That was the request.
It's about 80% done.
It's really small, so it's quick.
Well, it was supposed to be.
But more requests came up.
So I'm just finishing some details.
Things like re-painting.
I'll be happy to help.
-There's a lot I need help with.
-Of course.
-I can help paint at least.
-Yeah, that'll be great!
Is there something you want
to accomplish at Terrace House?
I didn't come here with any clear goals.
I consider it an adventure.
I don't know what'll happen.
I just thought
something new would come out of it.
I don't think there are too many people
in co-ed living situations.
I thought it could be fun.
Not just as friends, you know?
-So you'd be mad if it was messy here.
-No.
This much is okay?
Of course, of course!
But leaving cups out all dried up...
That's not me.
No, I think it's you.
It's your first day,
but I feel so comfortable with you.
Yeah?
Probably because you girls are so nice.
-Yeah!
-I think that's why.
-What about the guys?
-The guys...
They're nice, too.
-But a little scary?
-Not scary--
-I feel like Hikaru might explode someday.
-That's true.
I didn't think
a guy would also come today.
Me neither.
-But he has a girlfriend.
-Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
-That's right.
-I was so surprised.
-It was a surprise.
-Wasn't it?
He seems really nice.
-He seems mature.
-But dirty.
-Dirty?
-No, that's not what I meant.
He said he didn't like to clean.
But when he picked up that trash...
-I'm sure he's a cleaner.
-Really?
-He was just being modest?
-Yeah, he knows how to be modest.
Hansan...
I wonder...
He's got a girlfriend, you know?
But you never know.
They might break up.
They'll probably break up.
They're probably gonna break up?
Well, I don't know, but...
It doesn't matter if he has a girlfriend.
If I fall for him, that is.
-Seriously?
-It doesn't matter at all.
Oh, man.
Mr. Perfect is here.
What? Is that the chat room opinion?
The voice of the chat rooms.
I can't believe Mr. Perfect is here.
-A real good one arrived.
-Yeah.
He's the type of guy
that's really popular.
-Yes, very popular.
-What do you think, ladies?
-He's hot.
There you have it.
You can go to him for advice.
I want to go to him for advice!
Torichan!
-We've got a strong contender.
-You never know!
Don't be fooled by the way he talks.
He's not saying much.
He's just saying he's building a café.
It just sounds cool
because he's saying it all low-key.
Why are you talking so fast?
I have no idea what you just said.
It was just ugly.
It was ugly.
That speed was ugly.
It's nice that he's not aggressive.
Since it's likely
he won't make the first move,
-it makes you want to make the first move.
-What are you saying, Torichan?
-What are you saying?
-What was that?
He's got a girlfriend!
-He doesn't seem cold.
-Yes.
-That's right! And--
-Torichan!
Did you pee your pants?
You're too excited.
When he lightly said,
"This is the second time you asked."
-His light teasing.
-Yes, very light.
"This is the second time you asked,
but it's been two years."
I loved that.
If he had said it like
"This is the second time you asked!
The second time!"
-That would've been bad, right?
-That would just be chilling.
Even when he said
he wants to go to Harvard,
he didn't force all his plans on everyone.
He was asked, and he just answered,
"I'm thinking of Harvard."
-In a humble tone.
-That's right.
-That's what was different from Tap.
-Totally different.
YUKI ADACHI, TAP DANCER
Tap aggressively announced it.
Maybe he's got a really weird mole.
Actually, it'd be great if he had one.
-What if it looked like a face?
-"Oh, it's a mole. How nice!"
And then I'd feed the mole.
"Open wide!"
Wow.
Wait, this can't be happening.
I can't even bad mouth him.
He has no faults.
-No, he doesn't.
-Everything is just right.
But there have been many instances
in Terrace House
where there's sort of a bubble
on the first day.
Oh, the first day bubble?
-The bubble has burst in the past.
-I'll try not to have expectations.
Bubble, burst, please!
This might be the bubble that won't burst.
Well, bubbles always burst, you see.
-History has proven this.
-That's true.
Your upper lip is all sweaty.
Bubbles burst.
He's determined.
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
'07-'11 WASEDA UNIVERSITY,
SCHOOL OF EDUCATION
'12 ENTERS TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS,
DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE
-Good morning.
I went for a run.
-You did?
-Yeah.
-Oh, Hansan.
-Hansan.
-Good morning.
-Morning. You look a little pale.
-Are you okay?
-I always look like this.
Are you okay?
-Low blood pressure?
-Yeah.
-You're studying English?
-Yeah, a vocabulary book.
It's been a long time.
I've forgotten everything.
Feel free to ask any questions,
or I can read that to you.
Great.
Okay.
I went for a run.
How healthy of her.
-Good morning.
Excuse me.
Morning!
-Good morning.
-I'm back.
Welcome back.
Were you able to sleep?
-Totally.
-No way!
-What's your part-time job?
-My part-time job?
-I work at a convenience store.
-Really?
-Today?
-No, I'm off today.
You're going out?
Yeah, I was going
to pick up things I needed.
-That's a good idea.
-Wanna go?
I'm missing so many things I need.
-You're off today?
-I was going to do some work,
but I'm going to have drinks
with some friends in the evening.
-So shopping works, too.
-Oh!
Will you get some Gekiochi scrubbers?
-Oh, good idea.
-Nice!
Finally, someone who understands.
Yeah, the corners are a little dirty.
Yay!
You need to clean square off,
but not round at the corner of the floor.
If you guys have time,
I'd love to get some help.
-Doing what?
-I need to build some furniture.
-Totally!
-It sounds fun!
-Come to my studio.
-Sure. Where is it?
UENO, TOKYO
-Thank you for having me.
-Please, come in.
Thank you for having me.
It's a little messy.
-Thank you for having me.
-Oh, wow.
It's clean.
-Is it?
-Yeah.
It's not at its best.
Amazing.
-Feels like a studio.
-Right?
-Did you live here?
-Yeah.
It's stylish.
-It's so stylish!
-Yeah.
-It's so nice.
-Not at all.
-Thank you for having us.
-Of course.
You do your work here?
The messier projects I do over there.
I work mostly on my computer here.
-Wow.
-Or I draw out here.
Wouldn't this be great if you were a girl?
-What do you mean?
-Like, "Here's my studio."
-Yeah, it's cool.
-Right, it is cool.
-That's how he got the girl.
-Oh, is that your strategy?
Maybe that is how I got her.
-What do you want us to do today?
-Oh, right.
Today...
I'm making a table.
So I thought I'd have you paint.
-Sawing might be difficult.
-Yeah, forget about it.
So painting and sanding.
I'll lend you something to wear.
-So I'll have you change.
-Yay.
I hope we can be of help.
You can just cheer us on, Tamochan.
"Go, team, go!"
I could.
Got it.
Here it is.
It's a little cramped.
It's a little messy.
-Wow.
-Amazing.
-Here are the gloves.
-Okay.
For everyone.
-Thanks.
-I've never painted before.
-Oh, really?
-Me neither.
-Here I go!
-Please do.
When did you decide you wanted to do this?
-I've known since kindergarten.
-What inspired you?
I went to an unusual kindergarten
where we had to build a shack together.
So we all made a shack
to keep all the cleaning supplies.
A pretty big one.
-A real one?
-Yeah, we used saws.
-Oh, so that made you...
-Yes.
I realized how fun it was.
-That's amazing.
-So that never changed for you?
Well, I did give up on it once.
But I realized again
that this is what I want to do.
-So I re-applied to college.
-I see.
So you went to a normal college as well?
Yes, I graduated
and then went to the school of arts.
That's amazing.
Dust is gonna fly.
I'm scared!
Amazing!
The machine, yes.
-So cool!
-Yes, the machine is.
Amazing.
I can't picture the end product.
Yeah, I'm sure it's hard to picture.
I'll show you when it's finished.
-Yay.
-Finished?
-Where's Hansan?
-He said he'll be back around 11:30 p.m.
-He's out drinking with friends?
-Yeah.
-You can put that there.
-Here?
I'm sure the curry tastes even better.
Why? Why?
Because it's the second day.
You guys seem like
you're good friends already.
-We are.
-What?
-We get along really well.
-You do?
-Yeah.
-For now at least.
-For now?
-You never know, right?
-Yeah, you never know what'll happen.
Hansan's place was really great.
-Hansan's?
-His studio was really nice.
-Really. What was it like?
-Stylish.
Was it hard to make the table?
-It was easy.
-We just painted today.
You know how he was wearing that outfit?
I got a different impression from him.
-How?
-It made him look really cool.
Kind of badass.
-He was glowing.
-Yeah.
-Right?
-He was excited.
When you're doing what you love...
-Lucky.
-You glow.
He's known what he's wanted to do
since kindergarten.
What he's doing.
-Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
-It's good.
-Is it?
-The flavor is good.
-Yeah.
-Nice.
-Hats off to Nacchan.
-Impressive.
-Yeah.
-Do you have a grasp of each of us now?
Hansan is still a mystery though.
What did you think when he said
he had a girlfriend?
-I was surprised.
-Yeah.
To come to Terrace House
when you have a girlfriend...
Really? I'd want to live here
even if I had a girlfriend.
I wouldn't let you
if I were your girlfriend.
Stop me? But not every guy comes here
looking for a relationship.
True. Maybe not stop you,
but I wouldn't like it.
Some girls might say that.
But maybe his girlfriend's not like that.
I'm full.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thanks.
Thank you for the food.
Once again, we were taken care of...
by Nacchan again.
Thank you, Hikaru.
Thanks.
-Thanks.
-Thanks, Little Hikaru.
-I don't usually, so--
-What'd you call me?
-Thanks, Little Hikaru.
-"Little Hikaru"?
-Little Hikaru.
-Little Hikaru!
I'm just teasing.
Don't be mad.
-I'm not.
-Don't be mad.
It's as if I'm the angry guy.
You do get angry easily.
I'm not mad.
That's not mad.
You were mad yesterday.
You guys saying I was mad
when I wasn't is annoying.
See, you're mad.
-This is not mad.
-All washed?
Done.
Have you gotten used to things?
It's only been two days.
A little bit.
It's pretty easy to get comfortable.
I'm surprised that everyone is nicer
than I expected.
I don't think there's anyone bad here.
I wonder what'll happen.
I want to do something fun.
-Something fun?
-With everyone.
Yeah.
-You don't like going places?
-I do.
With everyone?
-Do you have a lot of free time?
-Yeah, I'm pretty free.
-Have you seen my motorcycle downstairs?
-I did.
I was wondering whose it was.
It's mine.
You can ride it.
I can't.
I don't have a license.
It's scary riding the back.
-It's not scary with me.
-I think I'd definitely be scared.
-I might speed up on purpose though.
-I think you would.
I'm just kidding.
I seriously want you to ride with me.
Just normally.
I'm scared though.
-Is it cleaner than usual in here?
-Yeah.
Earlier, when Nacchan and I went upstairs,
what did you guys talk about?
I was planning on asking her out.
Like, "Let's go somewhere."
I was planning to, but... I couldn't.
I couldn't find the right opening.
It was kind of difficult.
I did say,
"Let's go somewhere on my bike."
Or that's what I meant to say.
But I don't think she got it.
I think it's fine to just ask.
But she did say
she wanted to ride the bike.
-She did?
-Yeah.
She said that but you didn't ask then?
I asked if she wanted to ride with me.
You didn't say, "Let's go somewhere"?
Well...
maybe I just didn't say it right.
-Just ask her casually.
-Casually?
Yeah, casually.
You know, normally.
Like, "Let's go somewhere together"?
-On the bike?
-On the bike.
"You said you wanted to ride,
so let's go somewhere."
Nice. Sounds fun.
-Should I ask her now?
-Now or sometime soon.
-It's fresh now. She may forget later.
-She might forget.
It's like I'm Yuki.
I don't like it.
Well, everyone has their own timing.
I should do it today.
So he takes everyone to his studio...
He's so cool.
It was a good move.
-You seem happy.
-Very happy.
And his motivation, that was 100 points.
It was 100 points.
He built something when he was a kid,
and he couldn't forget how fun it was.
He went to college to study,
but he still wanted to try.
And then he's able to get
into Tokyo University of the Arts.
-Right?
From School of Education
at Waseda University.
-And he never mentions it.
-He doesn't.
"I gave up on it once.
I went back."
He's so cool!
So perfectly balanced.
-His pentagon diagram would be perfect.
-Beautiful.
When Tamosan said,
"So this is how you got your girl."
His reaction wasn't,
"No, I don't do that!"
But, "Maybe it was."
-So good.
-That was good.
-It was really good.
-He's in a bubble. He can do anything.
-Anything.
-Everything.
-Everything he does is good.
-True.
Apparently he's always pale.
I don't mind that at all!
I'm totally with you.
So this is the bubble!
-We've seen this happen a few times.
-We have.
We've seen it a few times,
but I knew the mask would come off.
-This time, it's the real deal.
-It may be the real deal.
In the past,
even if everyone fussed over someone,
I knew it wouldn't last.
-I had a sixth sense.
-Yeah.
Also, the bubble tends to burst
when relationships get involved.
Their quirks tend to come out,
and the bubble usually bursts.
-So we'll see if that'll happen here.
-That's right.
-But Nacchan's facial expression...
-She likes him.
-Right?
In the morning,
when Nacchan came back from jogging,
and Hansan came to the sofa...
And then she says, "I went for a jog,"
and sort of leaps from the sofa.
That behavior...
It was very girly.
-It was.
-She leapt.
She seemed excited.
Completely different from
when she was arguing at the sink before.
She said if she fell,
it wouldn't matter
if he had a girlfriend or not.
-So I'm sure she'll come on strong.
-I'm sure.
-I want to see how he evades those moves.
-Me too.
-He's gonna say something good.
-Yes, he will.
-I want to see it.
-He's going to deftly decline.
-I'm sure of it.
-I want to see!
Like, in a way that shows his sincerity.
Yeah.
With no false niceness from him.
Nothing fake.
Like, I'd want to be rejected this way.
You're totally seeing Hansan
from a female perspective.
Let's watch.
I want to see Handa.
-Welcome back.
-Hey.
Hey.
-They're smiling.
-What?
What movie did you guys watch?
-Nothing.
-Oh, really?
Hansan will be home soon.
Hansan said he'll be back at 11:30 p.m.
The two of them went to the studio today.
-I went, too.
-Arman went, too.
You were there, too?
-I thought it was just the two of you.
-I see.
Did they say I wasn't there?
You weren't mentioned, Arman,
-since you drove.
-So you went, too?
I need to use the bathroom.
-Do you want water, Arisa?
-I'll get it myself.
I'm tired of this drink.
There's Aoyama.
-What?
-Aoyama.
-What was it?
-Awamori?
Hansan's running late.
-What time is it?
-11:40 p.m.
What I was going to say...
What is it?
Do you seriously want
to go somewhere on the bike?
-Sure.
-You want to go?
-Where?
-You can pick.
-If you don't care where, I can pick.
-I don't care where.
You're okay on the back of a bike?
-The back?
-You're not riding on the back?
-We're taking the bike, right?
-Yeah.
-Are you driving?
-Wait, what?
-You riding behind me, right?
-Yeah.
Then I'll decide where.
When are you free?
-You're mostly free, right?
-Mostly free.
-What do you mean I'm mostly free?
-Because you are.
I am mostly free.
I'll ask you on a day I'm free.
I'm going to ask you when you're free.
Okay.
It can be anywhere.
Far or close.
Is there something you want to do?
I'll leave it to you.
You were thinking "What a hassle!"
just now, weren't you?
-I wasn't.
-You're lying.
-It's easier when it's up to me.
-Really?
I can do whatever I want, right?
That's right.
-Then I leave it to you.
-Okay.
Okay.
I'll be looking forward to it.