-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
So last week, Rikopin and Hayato
went out on a date to a meat festival.
-The weather was so nice.
-He's 11 years older than her,
but the difference in age didn't show.
She did say
dating someone 11 years older is scary.
I've only ever dated guys my own age.
I like experiencing things together.
Like going somewhere
for the first time together.
She'd like couples to experience
things for the first time together.
-How adorable.
-So cute.
Rikochan began to make some moves.
-Finally.
-She went for a job interview.
She ate a proper dinner
for the first time.
-Her comment caught me by surprise.
-Totally.
I didn't know we had this.
This is the first time I'm eating in here.
Whatever the case, it is peaceful.
-It is.
-For sure.
-But incidents are happening.
-Certainly.
-Hayato cried.
-Yes, he cried.
Yes, about how he gave up acting and why.
It really takes courage.
But I'd already made my decision.
Of course it's frustrating.
I don't think you have to give up.
I've already decided.
And finally, the immobile Arman...
-may be falling in step for love.
-That's right.
-This week is the date, right?
-Right.
-We'll see if issues arise as it unfolds.
-Right?
He'll be taking Momoka, who loves comedy,
to Earth's show.
-Earth!
-Man, it's been so long!
Earth! What are they up to now?
You mentioned
you wanted to see a comedy show.
Ippei said there's something next Sunday.
I'm looking forward to it.
-I'll find out what time it starts.
-Okay.
We're not going to the beach?
-We'll do the beach next time.
-Next time? Okay.
What was that?
It was like Momoka approached him.
Right.
I think she might already be into him.
The fact she stared at the stars in bed
means she was thinking of him.
That's right.
But she might also be totally nuts
about stars.
Like, totally fanatic about them.
-Her parents might not approve.
-Right?
You know?
A guy with tattoos...
"Oh, dear! A man with tattoos.
Momoka dear, this man has tattoos!"
Your impression sounds more
like an effeminate man.
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
-Welcome home.
-I'm back.
Oh, beer.
Lots of beer.
Do you want one?
-I can't.
-You can't?
-I've seen you drink.
-I can drink, but...
You have work tomorrow?
-It's my first day as a ballet teacher.
-That's right.
-It's your first time?
-Yeah.
What about you, Arman?
I'm carrying the mikoshi in Asakusa.
-Oh, the mikoshi!
-Oh, wow!
-Like this?
-Yeah.
I'll be doing that tomorrow
and the day after.
I'm not sure if I need to bring anything.
It's my first time carrying one.
-Wow.
-It suits you. You fit the role.
You totally fit the role.
-I've always been interested.
-Will you wear a hachimaki headband?
-Sounds interesting.
-If you're free this Sunday, come watch.
-I want to.
-I also want to watch.
CHUO-KU, CHIBA
DANCE STUDIO
I'm Momoka Mitsunaga.
By way of quick introduction,
I've been dancing since I was five.
I've also studied ballet abroad.
I'm hoping I can pass on to you
even a little bit of what I've learned.
-I'm looking forward to working with you.
-Thank you.
-Please do your best.
-Yes.
-Let's begin.
-Thank you.
To the back. Return.
To the side. Return.
To the front. Return.
Lift and bend your knees.
More this way.
Yes, now place your feet down,
and that's it.
That was perfect.
What we just did are the movements
of a pirouette.
This.
This shape is the foundation of the spin.
-Once you get it down, it'll be easier...
-Will we be able to spin?
Of course you'll be able to!
When should we go on our next date?
We're going on another date?
Has that been decided already?
No, not at all.
Do you want to?
Have you thought...
that maybe you don't want to?
You mean go on a date with you?
I do want to go out with you.
Why? You don't want to?
I'm younger,
so I feel like you think I'm just a kid.
Your age doesn't bother me.
How can I put it?
Age is just a number.
-It's just for reference.
-A reference?
I see.
Even if you were 29...
you'd still be you.
I suppose that's true.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere.
There it is.
Would you prefer the city or nature?
-Either.
-There it is again.
Jeez.
Have you ever been...
to Tsukiji Market?
-No.
-Then let's go to Tsukiji.
You can eat fish there.
-Nice.
-Is it?
-I guess it's decided then.
-Okay.
-It's funny.
-What's funny?
-Why?
That you're interested in an 18-year-old.
-I'm going to bed.
-Okay. Good night.
Good night.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
MOMOKA MITSUNAGA, 21 YEARS OLD,
BALLERINA
ASAKUSA, TOKYO
SANJA FESTIVAL
-Will they go through here?
-I don't know.
It's amazing.
-It's so nice in Asakusa.
-Is this your second time here?
My third. Or is it my fourth?
-It's increased.
-Yeah, I've been a lot.
-Is Arman coming?
-Will we find him?
-Can you see him, Riko?
-I can't see him.
Huh? Where?
-There he is!
-Arman!
There he is.
Are they saying something?
-Arman!
So cool!
You're so cool, Arman!
-Arman!
-Arman! You look like a different person.
-That was cool.
-He was so cool.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hansan.
Welcome. Welcome.
This is amazing.
-It's this thing.
-I've seen this before.
I made this at home.
-What, this?
-All of this.
-This too.
-You made this, too?
-Yeah, last night.
-Amazing.
-What were you doing today, Hansan?
-Well, I was here...
This restaurant belongs to
a former client of mine.
Tomorrow,
the parade will pass in front of it.
So they want to have a little storefront
for when that happens.
So I was helping them out a bit.
-So that's why.
-Yes.
-How was it?
-He wasn't the Arman we normally see.
-Was he serious?
-It was really...
He was in the very front, holding it.
-Nice.
-It was cool.
-Oh, Arman.
-Yo.
-You worked so hard.
-Arman, what's up?
What's up?
-Did you cut your hair?
-I did.
-It looks good.
-Thanks.
-It's refreshing.
-You were so cool.
-Oh, really? Thanks.
-Did you shave your beard a little too?
-Yeah.
-Oh, he did.
-You look better that way.
It's good.
-We started already.
-Oh, no worries.
-Was it fun?
-It was really fun.
-The vibe and the whole scene was great.
-It looked like fun.
It was so much fun.
I'm so happy now.
Arman, there's something
I was thinking about.
-Yesterday...
-Oh, yesterday!
-The vibe seemed pretty good.
-Yeah, it seemed good.
-What?
-Well, Hayato was in the living room--
-His head was like this beside you.
-Yeah, his head was like this.
-Like, lying down and...
-No, Hansan, it wasn't like that.
It seemed like you guys were
really getting along there.
Yeah, it seemed good.
-The air surrounding you two was...
-It seemed so natural.
It was like...
So open and...
It really was.
-Did he ask you to go out somewhere again?
-Yeah, he did.
-He did?
That's a big deal!
I don't know what the boys
have talked about.
I don't think Hayato has zero interest.
Of course he doesn't have zero interest.
-Right.
-It's obvious.
Although he tells me not to be concerned
about our age difference, I'm concerned.
Right, your age difference.
But the moment you like each other,
that won't matter anymore.
It's like I have to grow up a little.
I think that part will be
a little tiresome for me.
I think you won't be happy if you're bound
by the ideas you've come up with.
I think you would be happiest
if you break those binds
and just go with how you feel.
Yeah, I agree with that.
-You understand that.
-Riko understands that.
So what's up with the vibe
between Hayato and Riko?
-It's really nice.
-It's a good vibe.
That whole thing where she thinks
she's too childish or something...
-So cute.
-It's cute.
And then she'll try to really grow up
and be mature.
But then he'll come and say,
"Just going your pace,"
and pat her head.
-"Aw, come now."
-"Come now."
Like in the mangas.
But it seemed like they got along.
It seemed like they were closer today
than at their meat festival date.
Yeah, when they were pretty chummy
on the sofa.
Hayato is relaxed.
There are no signs of nervousness at all.
That's right.
Like, "We've been together for five years.
Come on, choose. Why not?
He said "there it is" so many times.
Like, what exactly was "it"?
Anyway Kentaro,
given what your life is like,
three-year-olds squeal at you, right?
Anyways?
I'm not that great
with people younger than me.
-That's good to know.
-It is.
-So you tend to go for older women?
-I guess so.
What would be the oldest
you would consider for a girlfriend?
Well...
Come on, just say fairly old.
It would be better if you say a bit older.
But listen, what if you say a bit older
but you still didn't qualify?
-Okay, so honestly now.
-Yeah, honestly.
My sister is 28 right now,
so maybe 25 or 26.
No, I think you can even go up to 32.
-I've never gone that far.
-Right?
That's so nice to know.
It's so nice.
I'm saying it's good to know,
but he's the same age as my son!
As long as you're not related.
I agree, but my son's watching!
I'm so stupid.
-Morning.
Thanks for getting it.
-Oh, hamburger ingredients?
-So teach me.
-Should I cut up some onion?
-Can you cut onion?
-I can cut onion.
-Really?
Upright.
You're fast.
If you cut the side, it's quick.
-Don't cut all the way through.
-Right.
Up to here. Be careful.
-Watch out.
-At this point, just chop.
Let's fry this up.
I'm glad you turned out to be decent.
What?
-You thought I was sketchy.
-I'm sorry I called you gross.
So you've said.
-Sorry.
-Like, "This gross guy's here."
Yeah, like, "He's gross."
You said gross because I'm gross, right?
-But turns out you're a normal person.
-What's with that?
-What's critical is how to cook, right?
-Yeah.
-That's all you want to know.
Press down the center.
It's harder for heat to reach there.
-So make the middle thinner.
-Make the middle thinner.
-There's the edge of the pan, right?
-Yeah.
The edge of the burger should be touching.
-How long do I cook it for?
-Cook the first side until it browns,
then flip it and keep it covered
for seven minutes.
-Less than ten minutes.
-Are you having fun at Terrace House?
-Co-living? It's fun.
-I'm glad.
-I'm having fun.
How long have you been here?
Three months?
-It's my third month.
-How is it?
It's fun.
-That's a long time.
-But someone sketchy arrived.
Who, me? I've already heard that.
-It's done.
-It looks good.
It's good.
-Is it okay?
-It's not hard.
Of course it's not hard!
Thank you.
Now I know how to cook a hamburger.
What's next?
Teach me some more.
Sure.
-He's sleeping.
-He is.
-Welcome home.
-I'm home.
Welcome home.
-"I love you."
Sorry, I don't really know
too much about ballerinas.
What is the highest achievement
of a ballerina?
There are only about five ballerinas
every year
that make it as professionals...
out of the entire country.
So I'm trying to be...
one of those five.
That's an amazing place to be.
How old are the ballerinas usually?
Between 18 and 22.
-Oh, that young?
-Yeah.
You usually know by the time you're 22.
Is there an exam to become a professional?
Yes, around March.
No matter how much you practice,
if you fail in March,
it all ends there.
I see.
If you make the slightest error,
they just tell you to go home.
-Really?
-So severe.
-Yeah, so--
-There's no room for mistakes.
You can practice a thousand times over,
but if you mess up just once there,
they say, "Thank you."
What kind of person are they looking for?
I mean, you're so busy.
If you have that something
that no one else does...
it would be better.
I think...
that guy over there is pretty nice.
In my opinion...
-For sure.
-...I think it's the best way to be.
I feel happy when I hang out with him.
For sure.
I don't consider him
as a potential mate, so...
She said it out loud.
He might be listening.
I would be happy
to introduce him to a friend.
I could do that with confidence.
Hey.
Arman, it's late.
You'll sleep better downstairs.
What time is it?
It's okay. Good night.
I'll let you sleep.
-Didn't he just ask what time it is?
-No way.
-And you said it's okay? Oh, okay.
-It's okay.
-What time is it?
-See?
See?
We said it's okay.
-See?
-Really?
I've gotten used to Arman's way
of speaking quickly.
The first time I was here,
he talked so fast...
I couldn't understand him.
You gotta stop him and ask,
"Can you say that again?"
Otherwise you can't have a conversation.
-You've got a date with him, right?
-Yes, on Sunday.
Don't just nod and let it go.
Okay, I'll stop him every time.
I'll ask him to repeat everything he says.
-Is it cold?
-No, it's not cold.
-You're not going in?
-What?
-No. It's cold!
How boring.
I'll get sunburnt. So cold!
-A tanned ballerina is nice.
-No way.
Is this okay?
It's super cold.
It's cold!
-Isn't it cold?
-It's refreshing.
-What?
-The air is warm.
Wow. The master.
I'll go in next time. Someday.
-Next time?
-Next time.
But I do want to go in.
-Don't go under so suddenly.
-Oh, sorry.
-Did you say something?
-No, I didn't,
but when I looked up you were gone.
-Stop doing it while I'm talking to you.
-Sorry.
-It looks so refreshing.
-It feels great.
Yeah.
-How about we leave soon?
-Sure.
Are you done?
You won't do another lap?
No, I'm good.
It feels nice but cold.
I'll go in next time.
-Comedy.
-I'm looking forward to it.
We gotta go.
SHINJUKU, TOKYO
I still haven't seen Ippei perform.
Don't you get anxious
when it's someone you know?
Not really. I'm excited.
-Really?
-Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
-Don't you worry--
-I've only seen him at the gym.
KOC COUNTERPLAN
STAND-UP COMEDY
MANTLE IPPEI, 31 YEARS OLD
COMEDIAN
MAG MANPEI, 31 YEARS OLD
Thank you, thank you!
I feel really good right now.
I came to Shinjuku station
on a bus from Saga.
To you,
the one person who listened to me...
I give my heartfelt thanks.
The next time we meet
will be at the Budokan!
Thanks for today!
I'm feeling good right now.
The next time we meet will be
at the Budokan!
Thank you!
This is the end!
I'm really done!
Thank you!
Seriously, does anyone know her?
Help me, please.
What?
I thought she was applauding...
but she's forming a hamburger patty!
I'm seriously scared!
Thank you.
-Arman!
-Nice job.
-Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
-I'm his partner, Manpei.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Thank you.
-It was seriously great.
-Really?
-Yes.
-What made you come?
-I really enjoy comedy.
I used to go to shows in Kyoto
when I lived there.
You're on a date?
Quick recovery.
-Quick? It's been awhile actually.
-Oh, has it?
-On to a new love?
-Well... a date anyway.
-Well, I'll see you.
-See you next time.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Thank you.
That was funny.
After having gone on a date with Arman,
do you feel differently about him?
Well...
It's not that I ever thought
he was scary...
but...
he was surprisingly pure and kind of cute.
No way.
I haven't been on a date in two years,
but usually I'd get nervous.
I mean, I was at first,
but less than I'd imagined.
He made me comfortable
and I was able to have fun.
I'm glad.
I was so nervous at first, right?
Yeah, in the beginning.
-But you were okay?
-Yeah, I was fine.
I'm glad.
Miraculously, there were two scenes
of hamburgers being made.
Yeah.
Who would've thought?
-The hamburgers connected everything.
-They did.
-Earth.
-Yes, Earth's show.
-It's been awhile.
-Yes, our alumni.
It felt nostalgic.
Reminds me of my days
at the comedy school.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
But if it were me and I knew Terrace House
would be coming to film...
I would've slipped some more jokes
into the conversation.
But you know that lady character?
The joke is that
she's there the entire time... right?
-The humor may have been a bit obscure.
-Yeah, a bit too obscure.
-Maybe like Vincent van Gogh.
-Oh, yes.
So they'll be appreciated after they die.
After watching it for ten minutes,
it's probably funny.
Babachan?
Ten minutes of that?
Babachan!
-They work hard.
-I'm glad to see they're working hard.
-Ippei lost some weight.
-He did.
Momoka...
She's totally into him.
-She is.
-She's having so much fun.
But she needs to concentrate
on her ballet career.
It's difficult to tell
how serious Arman is.
-He should've been a magician.
-Totally!
You can't read his emotions at all.
Or maybe a judge?
Like, "You're guilty, right?"
"Guilty."
You're so cold!
A lawyer might lose the case the moment
they find out Arman is the judge.
"It'll be a tough battle."
TAKESHIBA, TOKYO
EBISU MUSCATS
SECOND EP LAUNCH
Oh, you crack it.
-Did they give these out?
-No, I bought them.
I thought we'd only be three people,
so I only bought three.
-They're pretty bright.
-Wow.
I don't get one?
Here you go.
-This is yours.
-You're doing great.
LOOK THIS WAY MISAKI!
-So I don't get one.
-Looking good.
Everyone!
Are you ready to get loud?
Let's go, Ebisu...
Muscats!
She's really looking around.
Here we go!
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
Welcome back.
-Welcome back.
-Thanks, everyone.
-You worked hard.
-You did good.
-Did you see us?
-Yes, I saw you.
I was so surprised, it made me laugh.
Yeah, you were smiling
-I was so nervous today.
-Welcome home.
-I'm home.
-You were nervous?
-Today--
-Can I?
-Oh, sure.
-Everyone told me I was acting weird.
-No way!
-Did you have fun?
-It was so fun!
Riko looked like she was having fun.
-Thanks for coming.
-I was mesmerized.
Thanks.
-I want to see Momochan too.
-Ballet?
-I want to see.
-In June...
around the end...
-I decided to enter a competition.
-What kind of competition?
A ballet competition.
-A competition?
-Yeah.
So there are people dancing
the same thing?
You dance whatever you're good at
and then there's an evaluation.
-We have to watch.
-We have to check it out.
I need to go work downstairs.
-Okay.
-See ya.
I gotta do laundry.
Me too.
The quickest one wins.
So...
I've got the dryer set to very dry now,
so you'll have to wait.
I think I'll tidy up here.
-Only one's open.
-Really?
Rock, paper, scissors.
-I win!
-I win.
I won!
I'll go take care of this.
-Riko, it's just the two of us now.
-I'm off to sleep.
What? Don't go sleep.
So you want to go to Tsukiji?
Don't brush it off.
-Do you want to go?
-I do.
I want to go.
So? What about you?
-I want to go.
-So we'll go?
Yeah.
-We'll go next week.
-I forgot my phone.
-Next week?
-Yeah.
Are you busy next week?
-I might have school.
-Really?
I think.
-Good night.
Good night.
I know you want to go.