-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
SIX STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
LIVING TOGETHER
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Let's see, a lot happened last week...
-It did last week.
-It did.
You have feelings for each other,
but to be secretive about it
because of your career...
is the biggest problem.
Yeah.
I couldn't help but think about the fact
that my actions would be seen.
I felt now wasn't the right time
for us to be together.
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD
But I still like her, so things happened.
Conscious of their TV image,
they hid what they were really doing.
-But Hayato was running, right?
-Yes, that's right.
I was okay with going out with you.
But...
When you said we shouldn't go out
because of my career...
I thought maybe you were
just running away.
I need to focus on
my chef training.
It's just when I thought about
what I really need to do right now...
for me, you didn't come first.
You told me how much you like me.
But to say I'm not first for you...
To put a number on it...
I'm going now.
-I'm sorry.
-Yeah, bye.
So for Riko as long as he felt the same,
she did what she did because
she was okay with going out with him.
She shared her honest feelings,
but what she got was,
"We should focus on work."
He told her she wasn't his first priority.
Riko just said, "Bye."
-That "bye" carried weight.
-Yes, it did.
And at the end...
Arman, on their second date,
told Masako how he felt about her.
It's fun being with you.
Will you go out with me?
I like you too, probably.
I like you.
But you're going back to Hawaii.
That bothers me.
I have things
I need to take care of there.
If we went out for a month
and if I felt like I can't leave,
then I won't leave.
-You like me that much?
-That much.
-He has things to take care of in Hawaii?
-I wonder what it is?
Maybe he has to take care of sea turtles.
He probably has a sea turtle friend.
-A sea turtle?
-It comes when Arman calls.
That's so cute!
-I want him to go home soon, then.
-Right?
So they've fallen for each other?
She did put ointment on him.
Oh, yes, the ointment...
Truly a lucky break.
Wasn't it?
-This is how they came up with the saying.
-That's right.
Maybe he purposefully got run over.
For the great payoff.
-And everyone...
-Yes?
...including tonight,
there's only two weeks left.
-That's right.
-Next week is the final episode.
I thought it'd go on forever.
-Should we do it on our own then?
-Should we?
-Yeah...
-We can each bring a member.
We can all pitch in to rent a place.
We should do it.
It's been awhile since anyone's said
anything like that to me.
I see.
What worried me the most
was that you're going to Hawaii.
It was a barrier.
But what you said...
Your response was above and beyond,
it made me really happy.
You don't seem like you're serious...
but you actually think about everyone.
That's why I like you.
That's what I like about you.
It made me want to believe in you.
-So, you'll go out with me?
-Yes, that's what I mean.
Don't stare at me!
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-Cheers!
-Cheers.
I'm really happy.
No, no. I'm so embarrassed
I can't talk today.
-So that's it for today.
-What?
-You're cute.
-No.
-Welcome home.
-We're back.
Welcome back.
You're looking stylish today.
You're wearing a button-down.
-Welcome... I'm back, I meant.
-Welcome back.
-Was it fun?
-It was fun.
Where'd you go?
-On a boat.
-Nice.
It's subtle,
but you're touching each other.
His feet and thigh was brushing her.
-We talked...
-There's something on you.
We talked...
And now--
That was too forced!
Wait, what?
Do it again!
Wait. What happened, Arman?
-What?
-What happened?
Nothing, I just told her how I feel
and now we're going out.
Yeah!
-Nice!
-Congratulations!
You worked out that issue?
Oh, yeah.
We talked about that, too.
His answer went above and beyond
the issue.
That's why I agreed to going out.
It really made me see him as a man.
It made me like him even more.
Nice!
-I'm really happy for you, Arman.
-Yeah.
-At the very end.
-Right?
It's really near the end.
-It was a good day.
-Yeah.
It'll only get better.
Yeah.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
I've told you about Riko and me, right?
So since then Riko and I talked.
She said I'm using work as an escape.
She told me she was disappointed with me.
How do you really feel about Riko?
JUNTA ISHIKAWA
OWNER/CHEF
I like her.
I like her...
and I wish we could go back
to how we were.
Simply put.
What's important to you, right now?
In your mind.
Is it to think of her future
and take a step back?
Is that your way of caring for her?
Both for her and for yourself, of course.
Do you already have an answer
for what you think is best?
The members I've betrayed...
No, the members you've betrayed,
without all that, it's about what you
can really do for Riko.
What's important is what you want to do.
-A lot was going through my mind then.
-I understand.
About our work and everything.
Without all that...
Man and woman.
Person and person.
If I think of it that way...
then I've never changed.
I like her.
I want to be with her.
You do it because you like her.
As long as that feeling
isn't communicated,
Riko won't understand,
no matter what you do.
In the end,
it's about how you feel about the person.
Only that.
When you're able to convey that to her,
then she'll be able to give you an answer.
I got the job I auditioned for last week.
-Oh, wow!
-Seriously? Congrats!
-Congratulations.
-High-five!
I'm filming tomorrow.
Oh, I stuttered.
-It's like Misaki.
-You're talking like me!
-We're on a roll.
-Yeah, wow.
Misaki got a job, Martha got a job...
Starting tomorrow night...
Five, six, seven, eight...
I won't be back until the eighth.
-For what?
-Why?
For a job back in my hometown.
You're going to be gone for four days.
I'm pretty sad.
-Yeah.
-I'll work hard.
-Oh, he's back.
-Welcome back.
-Welcome back, you're late.
-I'm back.
-You're back late today.
-Yeah.
-Welcome back.
-I'm exhausted.
Welcome back.
Is your cold better, Riko?
It's better.
Your voice sounds funny.
Still?
Yeah, maybe.
Can we talk later?
Yeah.
Should we go?
No, we'll leave.
-I'm borrowing Riko.
-Sure.
-Is the guys' room okay?
-Yeah.
What are they going to talk about?
I wonder.
Well, we said all we could.
I do wonder though.
But going by that tone,
something may happen.
-You think?
-Yeah.
We talked before, right?
I really felt that way at the time.
I was thinking about our jobs.
And about your future.
I was thinking of too many things.
That's why I did the things I did.
Having said what I did...
I was going to leave the house.
That was my way of taking responsibility
after thinking about it at the time.
But after you told me you were
disappointed with me.
I'm sorry I made you feel sad.
When I think about just you and me...
I do like you.
That's the truth.
It wasn't like I was half-thinking it,
and came close to you.
And with all that's happened,
it might be hard to believe me.
I'm sure you're feeling confused.
But I...
want to be with you.
I like you.
I hope we can...
laugh together again.
That's how I feel.
Because you're the person I like...
I was hurt.
I want to believe you, but...
I can't.
Not right now.
I...
want to hang out with you again.
And if I can get your trust back,
I want to go out with you.
I don't...
need an answer right away.
So...
Next week...
Next week, on Monday,
in the evening, after work,
I'll wait for you at the restaurant.
You can think it over.
And if...
you think you can trust me again...
then I want you to come.
Okay.
I'll think it over.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
I'll go now.
He confessed to her again?
-Well, I guess.
-Well, yeah.
But he was going to step back,
because of her career.
Considering work,
they couldn't go out.
-That's why he said what he did.
-I see.
That's what it sounds like.
Whether he's being honest or not,
it's up to Riko to decide.
From a female point of view,
has Riko moved on already?
I think she's moved on.
What do you think?
I think it's still 50/50.
-50/50?
-She still has feelings for him.
If Riko...
can emerge from her shell
from this experience,
and then go out, that would be nice.
Because he won't change any time soon.
No, probably not.
It's up to Riko.
I don't approve.
But when girls emerge out of their shell,
then it might be too late.
-If that's the case, then it's too late.
-It's too late.
But still, two couples.
-Yeah.
-It's so nice!
It's so cute that he tried to kiss her,
but he was rejected. Too cute!
So cute.
So if it had gone well for Terashima,
there would've been three couples.
Happiness all around.
And ending with all couples.
-It could still happen.
-Well, that's true.
You think so?
Are we jumping to Monday now?
Already?
What else is left?
Well, there's couple lovey-dovey time.
I don't know...
if I want to see that.
Going to my hometown for work
for five days. Riko.
-It's almost time.
-Yeah.
One week left.
Right?
What are you going to do?
-Me?
-After this.
I'll go back to where I lived before.
-You're going back?
-Yeah.
But...
I'm always asked
if I'm going to live with you.
When the time is right.
After some time.
-Yeah, when the time's right.
-Yeah.
I feel like we'll get to know
each other better.
Until now, there was everyone else...
to consider while living here.
I'm sure you've been holding back.
And work, as well.
-We have to work hard.
-What are you going to do about work?
-Oh, my part-time?
-Yeah.
I'll work really hard.
I'll work hard and...
I'll work hard as an entertainer, too
I feel like I can work harder
than ever before.
You've gained something living here.
Even if the environment changes...
my feelings won't change.
So, don't worry.
-Don't change.
-Nothing will change.
You'll...
be seeing me still.
You'll be seeing me, too.
KAMAKURA, KANAGAWA
-Nice work!
-Cheers!
HISATO KOJIMA
OWNER
I have an announcement.
I'm going back to Hawaii next month.
Really?
Thank you...
for taking care of me.
Big thanks.
I have one more announcement.
Seriously?
I told you a new girl came, right?
About five days ago, we started going out.
-You have a girlfriend now?
-Yes, I have a girlfriend.
That's a first out of the members
that came to work with us.
They say it's our fault.
They say we hold them back.
It hasn't happened for the last 10.
You're going to Hawaii together?
No, I'd like for her to but...
she has work, so probably not.
So it's already
a long-distance relationship?
-Yeah, it'll be long distance.
-It's all over then.
Don't say that.
I see.
That's so great for you.
At the end, finally.
Yes.
It's sad for us
that Terrace House is ending.
-That means we won't get part-timers.
-That's right.
-It's sad.
-Yeah.
Arman was the hardest worker.
Yeah, he was a hard-worker.
-When you call his name, he'd run over.
-That's true.
-Thank you.
-I'm glad to have known you.
-Me, too.
Thank you.
I'll be here until September,
so I'll stop in before I leave.
That's right.
ANJO, AICHI
ANJO TANABATA FESTIVAL
YUKATA COLLECTION 2016
We have a special guest with us today.
Thank you for waiting everyone!
When I say go,
please yell out "Rikopin!"
Ready?
Go!
Rikopin!
-So cute!
-Hello.
-You're so cute! Hello!
-Rikopin!
-Come this way.
-Here.
I'm coming to you!
-Hello!
-Hello.
There's so many people here to see you.
Really? Thank you so much.
Rikopin, you were the winner
in the cutest high school girl
in Japan contest.
-Thank you.
-Oh, there's people waving to you.
And she's currently in Terrace House.
-Is it fun living there?
-Yes, it is.
She'll be hosting today.
-Please give her a hand!
-Thank you for having me!
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
I talked to Riko.
I told her I'd be waiting for her
here on Monday.
-Monday?
-Yes.
-Here?
-After work, you mean?
-Yes.
I was going to make a summery dessert.
-Is that what you're prepping now?
-Yes.
What's the reasoning behind
having her eat this?
I wanted her to see...
I wanted her to see my work.
And if she can't trust me anymore,
she won't come.
-So she may not show?
-Yes.
-Will you taste it for me?
-What?
Will you taste it?
-Oh, man.
-Good?
This is good.
She'll definitely enjoy this.
I enjoy it.
-Seriously, isn't it good?
-Yeah.
-It's definitely good.
-It's good!
Let's make it again and take a picture.
-Should we put it on the summer menu?
-Really?
We can call it the "Riko Special."
That's embarrassing.
Great job.
-It's okay?
-Yeah.
I'll go with this on Monday.
ANJO TANABATA FESTIVAL
-Thank you!
Good job.
MISAO NAGAI
RIKO'S MOTHER
-I'm so tired.
-You are?
-You look cute.
-No way.
You look cute.
-It was hot.
-Was it? Want a break?
-I'm so tired today!
-Good job today.
-The mornings have been early for you.
-Yeah.
Friday, Saturday, Sunday, Monday.
-Until tomorrow.
-Until tomorrow night.
I told you I'm going straight back
to Tokyo, right?
And after that...
After work...
he asked me to come
if I want to be with him.
Are you going?
Or are you not going?
At first...
he said I like you, but let's not go out.
The second time,
he said we both have things to focus on.
So it wasn't the right time to go out.
And then this third time,
he says let's go out.
He says something different every time.
It confuses me.
I still like him. But...
I'm very worried.
-You're still 18.
-Yeah.
I think you should date more.
You have to enjoy yourself.
You have to enjoy it.
-Yeah.
-Relationships, I mean.
You should really think about it
and decide for yourself.
Yeah.
Whether you go tomorrow or not.
I still have some time left.
I'll think it through.
Which do you think it'll be?
Who thinks she'll show?
I think so.
-She'll show either way.
-She'll go.
Of course she should cut him off.
That's what you wish for.
There's no reason for her to like him.
She's liked him from the start.
What your mother says is right.
Or for a daughter,
it's good advice to hear.
So he's going to serve dessert
and if he says what he needs to say...
-Yes.
-...there's still a possibility.
It's still possible.
The most entertaining move
would be to drop him, Riko.
It'll definitely be the most entertaining,
I know it!
Cut him off, Riko!
Arman was working the entire time.
-I'm glad we found that out.
-Isn't it?
-They said he was the hardest worker.
-They did say that.
Tetsu was useless.
TETSUYA SUGAYA
-Arman was a diligent guy.
-Yeah.
-We're sorry, Arman.
-Yeah, we're sorry.
-We thought he was a slacker.
-He was working hard. We're sorry.
What about that bit
with Misaki and Byrnes?
-From now on...
-Oh, yes!
There was some innuendo.
"Living together,
I'm sure you were holding back..."
She didn't look down like that.
-Why do you do that?
-See!
-You're in trouble again.
-It's the way you say it.
Why do you have to say it like that?
-Why do you look at Ken's penis?
-Seriously.
GAIENMAE, TOKYO
So if you don't mind setting up
for tomorrow's lunch.
-As usual?
-Yeah, the usual is fine.
-I prepped the salad already.
-Okay.
And the special dessert?
-The special dessert?
-Yeah.
I'll make it now.
Well, let's hope she comes.
Thank you for all your advice.
And for letting me use the restaurant.
That's not a problem at all.
Hope it goes well.
You're both young.
I'll head out now then.
-I'll finish up.
-Thank you.
Happy birthday, Martha!
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about this guy.
Don't worry about him.
You guys are so lovey-dovey!
-Happy birthday!
-Yay!
Thank you!
-Happy birthday.
Aren't they late?
I wonder what's happening?
Riko's probably on her way back
from Nagoya.
-Now?
-Today.
Did she tell him how she feels?
I don't know.
I don't even know if she'll go.
-Of course she'll go.
-She might come home alone.
I don't know.
Hayato was saying
he's making a fruit thing.
So it's one or the other.
Either they'll come back together,
or Riko will come back alone.
SHINAGAWA, TOKYO