-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
That's right.
So, last week--
-They were in the pool.
-Yes, they were.
Yes, there was a pool scene.
Minori has something good going on.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
Yeah.
She does.
She's got a nice body.
Just like her name, Minori has blossomed.
-She's bountiful all around.
-What?
-Dirty old man!
-We've got a dirty old man here.
And a dirty old man
who can't even speak properly.
-The lowest kind.
-The lowest!
Buh-buh-boobies!
Well, overall,
there's some movement going on,
especially from Mr. Uchihara.
You can see where
their hearts are pointing.
Yes, you can.
Unexpectedly, actually.
-Like, Yuriko was around here.
-Yeah.
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
But now she's going off like so.
She's come a long way.
Makoto and Mizuki...
-Yes.
-The barista.
-There's something there.
-They have things in common.
Yes, there is.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
A game?
Who did you lose to?
-Let's see. Ura-Gaku.
-Ura-Gaku? From Saitama?
We can talk forever about this.
-Yeah.
-So we'll do this again.
-She made that fish meal. The barista.
-Yes.
-Oh yeah!
That definitely scored high with the guys.
-Yes, high scores for that.
-For the women, too.
I want some.
Do you know the power
of cooking with foil?
I had that for lunch at school,
and it was delicious.
So cute!
You get that for lunch at school?
Did you think that the cooks
were trying to hit on you?
Then there's Tap.
Won the Japanese championship...
-three years in a row.
-Amazing.
YUKI ADACHI, 27 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
He has yet to distinguish himself
to the women.
Yes, they probably
don't know that yet, either.
Right. Once his charms become apparent,
the girls may take interest in him.
That may happen.
What's surprising is that all the women
voted for Makocchan.
-Uh-huh.
-That's right.
Well, there are only three of them.
Which one would it be?
-I guess Makocchan seems calm.
-Right.
-Out of the three of them?
-Yeah.
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Makocchan.
His general vibe is nice.
-Wait, so we're all into him?
-I am surprised.
-So things will move today!
-I want to see!
-Cheers!
-Oh, thank you.
-Long time no see.
Is here okay?
-Hmm?
-Is here okay?
Sure. Sure.
-And tomorrow?
-Tomorrow I have school.
You already have school?
I have labs.
Everyone here is in university.
-Yes.
-Uh-huh.
Well, then you graduate.
Yup.
What will you do after that?
By then...
-You'll be a doctor then.
-Yes, I will be busy as a resident.
Just that?
I think so.
Makoto?
Since I play baseball...
A baseball player?
Yeah, but it's hard to become one.
It would be nice if I could.
Not everyone can, even if they want to.
Well, you're in your fourth year?
Yes, my fourth.
When is the season over?
By the end of October.
Oh, it is?
I would like that to happen for you.
Any thoughts if you don't make it?
Not make it per se, but...
I don't like thinking about it.
-Well, just to have an idea.
-I guess so.
I do want to have a plan B.
It is still exciting
to have all your momentum
focused just on that one thing.
That's true.
So with that, I pass the baton.
The modeling industry may be even harder.
Damn, I'm not good at
conversations like this.
Really?
You've thought about it,
but can't say it out loud.
Yes, I suck at talking about it.
But if you were able to talk about it,
-they could encourage you.
-That's right.
They may be able to help you.
More people will help you.
If we are to live together,
and if we don't know
what each of us
is aspiring for,
it doesn't feel
like we actually live together.
It doesn't?
If we knew each other's ambitions,
and could encourage each other,
it would be meaningful.
Yes, it would.
And we can enjoy being together.
For sure.
Oh, sorry.
-Why are you using different ones?
-Shall I pour us something?
-Something else to drink?
-Yeah.
When do you want to go for a run?
Anytime.
Anytime?
But how many miles?
Going there and back,
15 to 20 minutes.
How about tomorrow? I can run tomorrow.
-Go run tomorrow?
-Yeah.
Okay. What time? At night?
At night, around 6:00 or 7:00...
-You'll be back?
-I'll be back.
So after we relax a bit
after dinner, we'll go?
-Like around 9:00 or 10:00.
-Really?
Get prepared mentally.
I will during school.
HASAKI BEACH
KAMISU, IBARAKI
One more time!
So?
How's it going?
For now, we're all into the baseball guy.
KAZUKI SHIDA, 20 YEARS OLD,
MIZUKI'S BROTHER
-What?
-Yeah.
I'm a little concerned.
About what?
I'm concerned.
If it was someone else, no.
But because it's you...
Why? No need to worry about me.
We can't help it.
-You can't do anything.
-No way.
We wonder
if you are keeping your room tidy
or if you are getting along.
I always get along with people.
While everyone else is having trouble.
-Really?
-Really.
Hey.
-Well?
-Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
Delicious.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
What did you make today? Okonomiyaki?
-Good timing.
-Yeah, just in time.
-Did you eat?
-No, but I bought some natto.
-There's some left.
-Oh? There's some?
-We can make another serving.
-Really?
Thank you for the meal.
Delicious.
It's 9:30 already.
Running?
Aren't you going for a run?
We'll go run.
It's 9:30.
So at 10:30.
How many miles?
I don't know. I'm letting her decide.
You're running together?
Just the two of them?
Two miles? That's quite a bit.
-Really?
-Maybe not.
Three miles?
Until I'm in pain.
Please.
We'll start just before 10:30.
Okay.
-Can you lend me a jersey?
-For sure. Top and bottom?
Yes.
Okay.
That was delicious. Thank you.
-I'll go get ready.
-Go get ready.
I'll clean up.
Thank you.
-Sure thing.
-Off you go.
I was thinking. Isn't there watermelon?
It might go bad soon.
-Yeah.
-Let's eat it.
SHIBA PARK, TOKYO
-You okay?
-I'm okay.
-Want to go? Slowly?
-Okay.
-This way?
-Ready to go?
Yes.
You might want to run more later.
No, I won't.
We're going to finish soon.
It doesn't seem so bad.
-It's totally fine.
-Sure is.
-Another round?
-Hmm?
-This might be my limit.
Me, too.
The wind is perfect now.
Sure is perfect.
The wind feels nice.
-We can run together.
-Hey?
Go running again.
-I might ask you to accompany me.
-Hmm?
I might ask you
to come running with me again.
Within reason.
But I am not bad, right?
Yeah, you are not that bad.
I will try my best.
We'll increase the distance slowly.
Will I get used to it if I keep running?
You will.
Your endurance will improve, too.
-Will I lose weight?
-I am not sure.
Build muscle?
-Somewhat?
-Evenly toned muscles.
I think my work is just straight ahead.
Straight that way?
-What kind of shop is that?
-Hmm?
A clothing store.
-Clothing?
-Yes, an apparel store.
A boutique.
-The rain is getting worse.
-Yeah.
-Shall we head home?
-Sure.
I'm thirsty, too.
-Want to go?
-Uh-oh.
-What? Is it bad?
-Is it okay?
-It's bad.
Sorry.
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD, MODEL
YUKI ADACHI, 27 YEARS OLD, TAP DANCER
MIZUKI SHIDA, 22 YEARS OLD, OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA UCHIHARA, 23 YEARS OLD,
HAIR STYLIST
YURIKO HAYATA, 23 YEARS OLD, MED STUDENT,
4TH YEAR AT TEIKYO UNIVERSITY
Hey.
-Oh.
-Hey.
-Is that mine?
-Yup. Thanks.
Sure.
I'll wash the jersey
before giving it back.
-Why are you smelling it?
-He is smelling so hard.
You are smelling so hard.
-It won't smell.
-It doesn't smell.
Makocchan,
your laundry doesn't smell either.
You look tired.
I will sleep well.
Why are you smiling at me?
Well, you two seem to have fun...
going for a run.
-You up early tomorrow?
-No.
Hit the pool again?
Blue?
-Huh?
-The blue swimsuit?
-Hmm?
-Have you brought many kinds?
No, I just have the blue one.
-Ah, the blue.
-Only the blue.
You remember it well.
When you guys came in,
he yelled, "Blue!"
I heard it.
-You probably heard it.
-Yes.
You have the kind of bum he likes.
The kind of bum I like?
Yay.
-Yay?
-How about a high-five?
High-five.
Yay.
-Okay then.
-It's okay.
-And you?
-Hmm?
-What's that?
-Are you going for Yuriko?
Well, Yuriko drinks too.
A-ha.
So we have a lot of opportunities to talk.
Maybe I'll ask her out for dinner.
-Oh?
-You should ask her out.
-Hmm.
-Whoa.
-Nice.
-That's a nice vibe there.
Is the barista going to be okay?
She seemed annoyed there.
Yeah, she seemed a little irritated.
The barista's swimsuit
was amazing though.
Yes, it was.
What was going on there?
She looked like Doronjo,
the anime character.
It was amazing.
She did.
-The vibe after the jog was really nice.
-Yes.
Like, "Oh, do I have a stain?"
"Oh, where?"
"Oh, it's bad."
-"Sorry."
-"Sorry!"
Like that, right?
Wasn't it nice in the rain?
Yeah, that was super nice.
Then Tap said she has the kind of bum
that Makocchan likes.
-Yes.
-He did say that.
-She said, "Yay."
-Right.
-That expression there--
-Yes.
...is like conveying,
"I'm interested in you,"
-directly to him.
-What?
So if she wasn't really into him,
she would be more like,
"Really? Yay!"
That's it.
That's what I wanted to say.
-Right?
-Yes.
So what does it mean?
So, "You have the kind of bum he likes."
"Yes. This makes me happy a bit.
Wait. I'm taking too long to respond.
They might realize
that the comment made me happy.
Yay!"
So that's what it means.
-It's easy to understand.
-I see.
So Minori took a step forward.
That's right.
Yes. I wonder
if the barista will be jealous.
What will the barista do?
I wonder what will happen.
She was irritated for sure.
Then I'm sure you will hear
a high-pitched voice from somewhere,
"What are you guys up to?"
That's Mr. Kobayashi, right?
"Please come here!"
You do a real good mimicking.
All of a sudden.
He disrespects both of them.
My bad. I went overboard.
My bad. Excuse me.
So anyways,
how was the, you know, jogging date?
Well, not a date.
-Okay, we went for a run.
-Yes.
-How was it?
-The night run?
-Night run?
-Night run.
It was nice. More so than usual.
-More than usual?
-More than usual.
-So did you have fun?
-Did you have fun?
-It was fun.
-Oh? Do we have something different?
Yes, I changed it.
Really? I'll get angry if there's alcohol.
-Don't worry.
-Why the doubt?
-Can Minori run?
-She can.
-My muscles ache.
-Really?
My hip joints hurt.
-Is Makocchan fast?
Well, not really, but...
You've got stamina, no?
Was that a normal pace?
It's a little slow.
You are competitive.
You know?
She did get cramps though.
But I kept running.
Right.
-I'm tired.
-Is that good night?
I also want to "see you tomorrow."
-I'm sleepy.
-Should we start the bath?
-Go for it.
-Have you gone?
No, I haven't.
Go sleep now.
So how was it?
-The night run?
-The night run.
It was nothing too special.
-And you?
-Me?
I'll ask about Minori's side
from her directly.
She's independent.
Oh, right.
-You're the same age, right?
-Yes.
-That's right.
-We're the same age.
That's right.
I'm getting sleepy.
Uh-oh. It's 1:00 in the morning.
Should we go to bed?
I think she'll be done soon.
We'll take turns with the bath.
I'm off to the bathroom.
HARAJYUKU, TOKYO
MAKOTO HASEGAWA, 21 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT MEIJI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
FROM SETAGAYA, TOKYO.
SINGLE FOR 18 MONTHS.
Done.
Has the season already started?
Baseball is in September.
Sometime mid or late-September.
AOYAMA, TOKYO
IMAGE
MINORI NAKADA'S MODELING AGENCY
Whenever you are ready.
Sorry for the wait.
-Nice.
-Sexy.
MINORI NAKADA, 21 YEARS OLD,
MODEL. FROM SANO, TOCHIGI.
SINGLE FOR 4 MONTHS.
Looks good.
Just put "Adachi-kun" wherever.
Like we're total strangers.
Manners for a stranger?
How do you spell "Adachi"?
The characters for
"a leg" and "stand up."
Adachi-kun.
-Oh, nice.
-Aw! Cute.
ADACHI-KUN
Are the characters correct?
-Aren't they?
-Wouldn't it be sad if it wasn't?
There may be other ways to spell it.
Oh, no.
-It's spelled wrong.
-What?
I think we spelled it wrong.
Sorry, I said it without confirming it.
"Yuki Adachi,
a tap dancer filled with soul."
What? That's amazing.
I wonder what kind of
an amazing person he is.
-It's a little...
-It's kind of dark humor.
I'm sure he'll be a good sport about it.
-Let me see.
-It's not cool.
-It's not bad.
-He's coming!
He's coming!
I'm home.
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
-Thank you!
-Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Put your bag down
and be the star of the moment.
-Sit over there.
-Please sit here.
This is great.
Huh?
-We got it wrong.
-It's wrong.
So sorry.
I'll put it on anyway.
Thank you!
Happy birthday!
-So?
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Ta-da!
Ah! It's so cute!
They're swim trunks.
Practice shorts.
-Practice shorts?
-Practice shorts.
Thank you!
Here we go.
Three, two,
one.
Yeah!
-I totally closed my eyes.
-Whose phone is it?
-It's mine.
-Makocchan's?
So, when did you start tap dancing?
Tap dancing?
Around seven years old.
-Wow.
-Around grade one or two.
Seven years old?
Then I went abroad to study.
Is New York the best place for tap dance?
I guess so.
I went to a vocational school there.
Oh.
For about two years,
and I performed there, too,
while I was studying.
We want to see you perform.
When can we see you perform?
The soonest would be
the 4th of September.
I can go!
It's summer break.
-Really?
-I can go.
We'll all go.
-At night?
-At night.
-I can go at night.
-Let's go.
-8:00 start.
-8:00?
How long will you tap dance?
-Forever.
-Forever?
-Tap for your whole life?
-Until you die?
-That's cool.
-Sure, I guess.
Well, instead of just talking about me,
I wonder how we can share
our visions for the future
and live together.
Like, what do we strive for?
I don't want to be just...
all casual, like, "Hey, whatever."
It's not like your ambitions, but...
-I think it would be good to know.
-Right.
I do have a clear vision,
like how we've talked about it before.
-Both my parents are hair stylists.
-Is that right?
I looked up to my parents,
which is probably why
I chose to become a hair stylist.
So as a hair stylist,
you'll develop your trade,
and then what?
You'll be independent?
Somehow, I want to go overseas.
Right.
You're a little different there.
-You're in medicine.
-Yes.
My father is also a cardiologist.
Is your father a doctor too?
-Yes, he is.
-So cool.
That's why I wanted to become a doctor.
How about you, Minori?
I haven't really decided yet.
I'm not even sure
if modelling really suits me.
I haven't really thought about
what I would do in the future.
They say to think of
where you want to be when you're 50.
Then trace the steps back.
I wrote that out when I was 17.
Yes.
Isn't it amazing to write it out?
And you did that?
When I get older,
I want to have my own shop.
How should I explain?
Like, how old?
Yeah, like from what age...
At what age would you consider someone
an older woman?
What kind of shop?
-Maybe a café.
-A hostess bar?
-Shut up.
-A bar matron!
Why a café?
Well, I like coffee.
Most of all, I like people.
So I want to create an environment
where people can gather.
I like traveling and accessories.
And I like people and coffee.
And interior design.
So what I want
is to gather all these things I like
so all the people I like
can easily get together.
It's not that clear.
I kind of spaced out.
Like, I wasn't getting anything
even though you've talked a lot.
Really?
It's confusing.
For most people.
-It's unclear.
-Like, where will it be located?
Let's say out loud what we're doing now,
and what we want to do.
Clearly.
Futsal and coffee.
And do what with it?
I want to make futsal big.
And I want to do something
with coffee in the future.
-As your career?
-Yes, and make the environment I like.
Mizuki, I think
you need to take things a bit further.
-You are being rather general.
-General?
-Well, I'm--
-What I thought I wanted was that...
I would work hard
and then get married in my 30s.
Well, it's different for a man
than it is for a woman.
But after I went to university
-and studied hard--
-Are you okay?
It would make me happier...
if everyone had some kind of ambition.
I thought...
I was doing things with certainty.
But I couldn't make you understand that.
Though I do seem to get lost in it.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Yuri?
Why? Why are you crying?
Mizuki was trying so hard to talk it out.
Yuki clearly figured out what it is
that you want to do.
Still...
It's heartbreaking to watch.
Well, we're lucky to be here.
Of course it's easier if
we knew each other's goal.
This will all be over in a few months.
I want to make sure that while we're here,
to build the bond that lasts beyond that.
I don't want to play house.
For sure.
That I have to tell you.
-Whoa.
-What?
Suddenly, it got all dark.
I think we found the heel of the season.
He is hopeless.
He made other people
talk about their dreams,
but meanwhile he's like,
-"I wasn't getting anything."
-That's it.
Can't you understand anything,
you jackass?
I know!
And after he points it out,
he's making faces, grinning and whatever.
That really gets me.
It's like, "Woops!
I think that stung a little."
No, no. His chin wasn't out like that.
His chin wasn't all crooked.
-Like this?
-No, not like that.
Well, he has danced stoically
since he was young.
So he is rather hard or strict
on others.
Not everyone can live stoically
from the age of seven, you idiot.
Exactly.
Forcing that kind of value
is what I hate the most.
-I don't even know my goal now.
-That's right.
We do just about anything.
If I met him, I would get in trouble.
Right.
"You still haven't decided?"
I am scared!
"You're going to die soon!"
I'll get in trouble.
I really don't want to meet him.
I guess we don't like him 'cause of that,
but what do you think?
I actually like that type of person.
What?
-There it is.
-Why?
It's horrible! Disapproving everything.
Well, I grew up with that kind
of environment.
I was relating to that as I watched.
So if you don't clearly have ambitions,
they won't materialize?
I think we stink of unworthiness
right now.
-It's not good.
The stink of unworthiness.
The kind that clogs up your nose.
-It doesn't come off.
-It won't come off.
Even if I shower.
-It's stuck.
-It's gone way up your nose.
I'm choking! Hack! Hack!
Okay, so,
it's possible she's crying
because she realized that.
So in a way,
the barista may have been touched by that.
I see.
Hmm. Could it be that?
So that's what you see
if you observe it with a pure heart.
Right.
-It's after this.
-After this.
Right? Depending on what Tap brings out.
She may think like,
"What that guy said was right,"
and something might change
how things are going.
Do you think she's grateful?
If I were her,
I would hate that guy forever.
I would never forgive him.
Wouldn't you say something back online?
No, I would think to also do my best
and strive for something.
What's with you, man?
Stop it.
-Don't speak to him like that.
-Stop it.
-Please don't fight.
-What're you saying?
-That was shocking.
-Yeah.
Yes, it was.
In so many ways.
-Though I do think he's right.
-I guess so.
If you don't have a vision,
-for both people, it's unpleasant.
-You can't support them either.
Don't you think
he shouldn't have gone that far?
But crying won't help.
-Crying won't--
-It really won't help.
Then the conversation is over.
Hmm.
So this is what it's like
on the second floor.
-Right. This is what it's like here.
-Have you been here before?
-No. It's my first time.
-I see.
-Have you?
-No.
While listening to the conversation
with Mizuki,
I was wondering what you thought.
Because there wasn't
something concrete, so...
I wanted to help her clarify
by sharing my vision and dream.
Even if I talked endlessly
to someone who is not as passionate...
something might resonate
within that person.
So I wanted Mizuki to talk about it
and then support her,
whatever it is.
Is it not okay if you're in
the process of figuring it out?
That's okay.
But what's important
is what you want to do right now.
Right. There's no right or wrong to it.
Well...
So it's just...
talking about it today
was fun.
-Thank you.
-I mean, I cried, but I had fun.
Since most of my friends
are also in medicine
and that's all we talk about...
so I thought I could ask something
totally different.
I would think that I should just shut up.
What's that?
I'm not thinking that.
I'm glad we talked.
Well, next time...
let's go have a drink.
Yeah, I want to talk again.
For sure.
There's one thing I want to ask.
Good night.
I want to ask how the night run went.
I want to know what happened.
I mean, Makocchan seemed happy.
-Really?
-Yeah, he had fun.
He was all smiling
despite being all sweaty.
But that's all he said, right?
Right, so...
I wanted to ask you.
I was just wondering
why he asked me to go.
On the contrary, is there somebody
you would rather be with?
-I guess Makocchan.
-Makocchan?
Why?
He's easy to talk to.
Like, how it's easy to talk with you,
but in a different way.
I think that's good.
I think that's great.
Give it your best.
-What's with you?
-What's with me?
Easy now.
Well...
-Are you satisfied now?
-Yes, I'm good.
Aren't you up early tomorrow?
Let's hit the sack.
-You're sleeping here?
-I think I'll sleep here.
Right.
-Don't catch a cold.
-I think I did.
-Have a good night's sleep.
-Good night.