-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
KENTARO FUJIMURA NOT PRESENT
DUE TO A FILM SHOOT.
So last week, Masako invites Hayato
out and they go to lunch.
Where he tells her the two of them
should not hang out alone anymore.
Maybe we shouldn't go out
alone together anymore.
Us, you mean? Sure.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
Masako's giving up.
-For Riko...
-He put an early stop to it.
She even tells Riko.
-And then there was Arman's accident.
-There was that.
I'm fine.
No bones are broken.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
I got four stitches.
I'm so relieved, though.
I'm sorry, Yuuki.
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD
-Sorry.
Even though Byrnes
cares so much about Arman,
he let's it slip that Masako
likes Terajima right in front of him.
You're crushing his heart now?
But because of the accident,
Masako tends to Arman's wounds.
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD
-That's right.
-There was hope at the end.
-You have to go to the hospital tomorrow?
-Yeah.
Get better quick so we could go somewhere.
Yeah.
So this week will be the yukata date.
-Will it be the yukata date?
-Yes, the yukata date.
Will Hayato make a move?
-He seems like he wouldn't though.
-That's true.
Will Riko be writing "coward"
on an omu-rice again?
VIDEO OF UCHIHARA AND OMU-RICE
-Brings back memories.
-Brings back memories!
The omu-rice from hell.
-That did happen.
-Yes, it did.
The omu-rice did not look tasty.
It really didn't.
-I don't think we said anything like that.
-Yeah!
-It wasn't from hell either.
-We applauded her for it.
-Yeah, it was cute.
Did we?
Yeah, your memories switched it
into something dark.
KITASENJU, TOKYO
Oh, you bought one?
-A yukata?
-Yeah, I did.
It's nice.
-Shall we get going?
-Let's get going.
-It's good. It looks good.
-Really?
-Nice.
-There's so many people. Look.
-Wonder where they'll shoot the fireworks.
Over there, probably.
-Over there?
-Probably.
Maybe it'll be from here.
-It's nice along the river.
-Yeah.
Cute.
-He's so cute!
-He's cute.
He's so cute!
-Is it okay here?
-Yeah.
-Should we go all the way down?
-Here's good.
Oh, man, the wind...
Hold this a second?
-Ready?
-Okay.
-Sit, sit.
It's soft.
So we're at a fireworks show.
We are.
I wanted to go.
-So you thought it'd be okay?
-Yeah.
-You've changed.
You're an adult now?
-Yeah. I've grown.
-Yeah, you have.
Now that we've come to a fireworks show...
have you thought about what
you want to happen with us?
Going forward.
I haven't thought about it.
But...
before this...
going to a fireworks show with a guy...
is something I wouldn't have done it.
-You've said that.
-Yeah.
That's good.
-Is it?
-It is.
-You don't need to overthink it.
-Yeah.
It's so pretty.
Nice.
Wow.
That was amazing.
-It was hard to see with the smoke.
-What?
-Yeah, it was.
Was that it?
Let's go.
-What's wrong?
-What?
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
MISAKI TAMORI, 24 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
HAYATO TERASHIMA, 29 YEARS OLD,
CHEF-IN-TRAINING
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
YUUKI BYRNES, 23 YEARS OLD,
HIP-HOP DANCER
MASAKO ENDO, 22 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING CHILDCARE WORKER
Welcome home.
You look so cute!
Speaking of.
-It looks great on you!
-Really?
It's so cute.
-It's nice!
-It does look mature.
It's nice. I'm glad.
Really?
It's been a month.
How was the date?
-That's right. It's been a month.
-Yeah, about a month.
Well...
it felt...
steady.
The same as usual?
Yeah, nothing really different happened.
He didn't hold your hand?
He didn't.
I wonder why? Maybe because
I've already said I wouldn't.
Maybe he's trying to go along with me.
So if Hayato held your hand,
would you have liked it? Or no?
I didn't want him to.
I want to save things like that.
Especially because we've been
going out on dates.
I felt like I wanted to save that.
-So you like him?
-So she wants to take things slow.
So you do have feelings for him?
I see, so you just want
to take things slow.
Yeah.
What did you guys do?
Nothing.
It was the same as usual.
What?
But it was your first date in a while.
Weren't you guys excited?
Not really.
Wait, not even a kiss?
It's too fast for that.
-But you held hands with her?
-No.
-No? I see.
-You didn't go for it?
She invited me.
So I asked her whether she's been thinking
about what'll happen with us.
Like what she wants to happen
with me.
She said she hadn't really thought
about it.
-That's when you take the lead.
-Yeah, you're supposed to take the lead.
-You can't...
-You can't ask Riko that.
I mean she said she wouldn't do
yukata dates with a non-boyfriend,
but she went with you.
-She's sending signals.
-Yeah.
I didn't really feel like making a move,
to be honest.
So you're just going to
keep things like this?
You're just going to keep things
the way they are?
I won't be the one making the move.
So you can't see yourself with her?
I can't help but see her as a sister.
No attraction to her as a woman?
I don't really feel that way about her.
Normally, you'd want sleep with her
or kiss her or something, right?
You feel that desire toward a woman.
I don't really feel that for her.
You should make that clear to her.
Right now, it just feels like
you're dragging it on.
I can't tell if Byrnes is stupid or smart.
What he said made sense.
Yes, he did make sense right there.
So...
Terashima doesn't see Rikopin as a woman.
-He's just not attracted to her.
-That's what it sounds like.
And Riko, too.
She doesn't want to hold hands.
She still doesn't want to.
-Then nothing's gonna happen.
-Yeah.
So neither of them
really like each other that much.
They're not really attracted
to each other.
What?
They just went to see fireworks
because it's summer.
What?
So we just watched
the daily life of roommates?
I feel like...
as if she is a virgin slut.
What should we do?
A virgin slut?
So Martha didn't need to give up.
Martha is probably just not his type.
Yeah, that's probably the case.
How can you reveal such a thing?
That's what it is, right?
-I--
-I'm so shocked.
I thought about saying that last week
but I held back.
Toward the beginning of the fireworks,
-Hayato asked about their future.
-Yeah.
-You ask because you're interested, right?
-Yeah, what was that about?
-I think he just asks out of habit.
-Why would you ask?
He can't help it.
He's someone who likes to confirm things.
He's too responsible.
"What are your plans going forward?"
Is this some kind of orientation?
Maybe both of them are just cautious...
-But the things he says--
-...about the way they feel.
His eyes were shining
when he saw Rikopin in her yukata.
His eyes just shine in general.
That's what it is!
At this rate, it'll take six years
for them to kiss.
-How many seasons will that take?
-Then yes, at this rate.
Riko didn't want to hold hands that day.
She just wants to do things right.
So it's not like she doesn't have
feelings for Terashima.
-Yes, she just wants to go slow.
-She wants to treasure it.
Withdrawing and then pressing forward.
It's supposed to be something
that happens more impulsively.
You said that so well!
-I like it.
-They should be more impulsive!
That's how it should be!
I want her to say, "I'm not a child!"
with tears in her eyes.
To make a scene, you mean?
"I'm not a child!"
That's what I want.
You're doing it on your own.
You wanted it so much,
you just did it yourself.
Please, let it happen!
-Let it happen!
-Tokui gets possessed sometimes.
-That would be nice to see.
-Yeah.
TAMACHI, TOKYO
SHIBAURA HORMONE
-Cheers!
Cheers.
How are things with you?
No complaints since getting together?
None at all.
So things are pretty perfect?
Things haven't changed much.
From before you got together?
Everyone asks if we're sleeping together.
-Yeah, I was thinking that.
-I totally wanted to ask that.
Because I'm sure you want to.
I...
Well, I'm not sure.
It's not that I don't like him,
I love him.
But I feel like it's not the right time.
Have you told Yuuki that?
-I have.
-What did he say?
He agreed.
He's being patient for your sake.
But that's not what it's all about, right?
Being together, I mean.
It's not just about sleeping together.
That's true.
What about your part-time job, Martha?
-Me?
-Has it been decided?
I've been hired at the apparel shop.
But I haven't been able to go.
What about work in the industry?
I keep getting cut.
-From the auditions?
-Yeah.
It's the same for me, too.
I know that's just how it is.
I'm feeling concerned about it.
-That you're getting cut?
-Yeah, I keep getting cut.
My only work is with
the Muscats right now.
I'm probably in the same boat.
If I'm home, it means I don't have work.
Yeah. I was thinking that, too.
-And we're all home pretty often.
-Yeah.
"He's working so hard, I should, too."
We don’t have anyone like that.
I think that's totally necessary.
I feel that way especially since
living at Terrace House.
There's less than a month left
for Terrace House.
You're right.
GINZA, TOKYO
I hardly ever come to Ginza.
-Me neither.
-What?
-You're laughing too much.
-It's bathing suit time.
-Yeah.
Which pool should we go to?
Summerland?
-Yomiuriland.
-Should we be stylish and drink cocktails?
SAN-AI MIZUKI RAKUEN
-I'm coming out.
-Okay.
-It looks really great!
-Don't come close.
Why?
-How is it?
-It's good.
It looks cute.
It looks really good on you.
Really?
I've never seen you show
so much skin.
Yeah. I'm only covered here and here.
Stop that.
I'm going to try the other one on.
-Yeah, I want to see it.
-The khaki one.
-This one's nice, too.
-Which one's better?
Which one's better do you think?
You're so cute. Now I'm nervous, too.
This makes me really nervous.
Which one do you like better?
Um...
Maybe this one.
-This one?
-Yeah.
Okay.
-Then I'm going to change.
-Okay.
Don't stare so much.
What did you think of our date?
At the fireworks?
It was fun, but...
It was just fun.
I was just wondering how you feel.
-How I feel?
-I've asked you before, but...
but if you're having fun, then...
I feel the same, too.
I think it's fine if we have fun.
-That's how you feel?
-Yeah.
It didn't feel like a lover's date.
You see me more as a sibling?
Yeah, I think so.
I want you to work on your career.
Yeah.
I do want to work hard on my career.
You have school, too.
I feel a little guilty.
I don't think you need to feel guilty.
I don't think you need
to worry about those things.
-You think about my work?
-Of course. I want you to do well.
I see.
Where did they go?
-You're going to go see?
-I'm going to go do laundry.
-Hey.
Are you going to use the laundry machine?
I don't know.
Laundry? No, I'm not.
What were you talking about?
I asked her what she thought of the date.
She said it was fun.
-That's all you said?
-So then...
I asked her what she wanted again.
She said as long as she has fun.
-Riko said that?
-Yeah.
So I said I had fun, too.
But that she feels like a sister to me.
If you can only see her as a sister,
then you can't see her as...
a girlfriend.
I didn't say that part.
Why?
I mean, she hasn't said
she feels that way about me.
Wouldn't it be presumptuous of me?
You have to say it.
Why do I have to say it so clearly,
when she hasn't said anything.
She had fun. I had fun.
I really think that...
Riko likes you.
We don't know that.
She hasn't said it.
I think Riko likes you.
You really can't see that?
That Riko likes you?
After all this?
You don't know, right?
Of course, you know.
How can you not know?
What? I just don't know.
She invited you on a yukata date.
A 19-year-old girl who said she wouldn't
invited you.
I know that.
That's why I went.
And then it's "that was fun"
and that's it?
That's what she's saying.
You say that it's because
it's what Riko says.
You're leaving it all up to her.
-That's not true.
-You need to step up and be a man.
Shut up.
It just looks like
you're playing around with her.
Whatever.
I feel...
really bad for Riko.
I think...
you should let her know early on.
I'll leave it to you.
-He's sulking.
-Yeah.
EBISU, TOKYO
HAMAJIRO
-Let's sit in the back.
-Okay.
-I'm hungry.
-Me too.
-It's so hot.
-What do you want to drink?
-A highball.
-Okay.
I'll have a draft beer.
Draft beer? Okay.
-Cheers.
Delicious.
I wanted to thank you.
About?
Don't laugh.
I laughed because you laughed.
It's funny. So what was it?
When I got in the accident,
you looked after me. Thank you.
I'm glad you're better.
-It's healed a lot.
-Yeah, in about a week.
-It healed in a week?
-Yeah.
-We're home together so much.
We're always at home together.
This heat feels like summer.
I invited you out today because
I wanted to get to know you better.
What do you know about me?
-By living together...
-We hang out together.
I'm starting to know your personality.
I didn't know you well at first,
but I've learned a lot recently.
It's fun hanging out with you.
I wonder why?
I feel comfortable with you.
That makes me happy.
How long have you been at Terrace House?
-Nine months, I think.
-Pretty long.
-I've been here awhile.
-Yeah.
Nine months.
That's almost a year.
You must be used to living
with everyone by now.
I am.
It's nice to meet people
but the goodbyes are hard.
Living here for almost a year,
I just came wanting to enjoy Japan.
And I'm really enjoying it.
But I should head home soon...
and start working.
You're going back to Hawaii?
-Well, I haven't decided when.
-So someday.
Someday.
It's been more fun recently.
Life at Terrace House.
-Recently?
-Yeah.
Why?
The train.
-Oh, excuse me.
-Oh? This is your second time.
-Good night.
-Stop that.
Misaki's bed.
It's dirty.
-What?
-The T-shirt.
What's wrong?
The way Hayato was acting yesterday.
I...
can barely stand it.
I'm the only one who saw it.
I've seen them acting lovey-dovey.
And I saw them kissing
in front of the elevator.
Knowing that,
I'm trying to tell Hayato what I think.
But Hayato is trying to hide it.
So...
-It's hard to see his true feelings.
-Yeah.
So what the two of them
are doing is just...
It's just so different.
It's all messed up.
I've noticed Riko missing before.
But when I ask the two of them
how they're feeling,
their answer is never what I expect.
Like, "Oh, I don't know."
And you want to say
of course you know.
And it makes you say things.
I wish I had said something
before things got confusing.
That's how I feel.
I knew what was going on earlier.
Well, it was last week.
Why are they so secretive about it?
Maybe because Riko is an idol.
Well...
-She's just starting.
-Yeah, she's just starting.
She has a lot of male fans...
who might not like her having a boyfriend.
I'm sure that's it.
So they're matching stories
behind the scenes...
and Hayato says he wants Riko to focus
on her studies and career.
That's what he's saying.
Shouldn't you tell him this in person?
I mean, he's kissing her even though
he's saying he doesn't want to.
Then he's not doing what he's saying.
Yeah, that's true.
If Riko seriously likes Hayato...
Then I feel bad for her.
Then Hayato is just playing Riko.
So I want him to be clear.
I'm not taking sides or anything.
Wait, do we need to see that again?
This is a huge problem!
-What?
-Wait, I'm kind of in a panic.
Yuuki witnessed Hayato and Riko kissing.
-What?
-Before the fireworks date.
-Yes.
Then what was all that
about holding hands?
What they're doing and saying
are totally different.
On the surface, he's acting
like he's not that interested.
Taking the stance that
he only sees her as a sister.
Byrnes just revealed
that it was all an act.
That's a huge bomb to drop.
This is a first for Terrace House.
I'm super shocked right now.
-It was shocking.
-It was a shock.
This is the first time...
None of us realized any of this.
It's embarrassing, we were played
by an 18 and 29-year-old.
That's true.
How can we get revenge?
How dare you damn kids play us?
This is really shocking.
You have to give it up to Terrace House
for telling it how it is.
This is entertainment, Terrace House!
-Amazing.
-They've done it.
But you know,
if the honest kids like Byrnes
were all doing something different
than what they're saying,
then what are we supposed to do?
Are we supposed to go along
with their act?
-That's right.
-Yes, that's true.
I was watching so intently.
We're really in a panic right now.
How can you act lovey-dovey
with the guy you like
without bringing your TV image down?
So you act lovey-dovey
when the camera's off.
And in front of the camera,
you act the best image of yourself.
That's what these two realized.
-That's what it is.
-Yes.
Then what was all that about going to
amusement parks only with a boyfriend?
So she was acting the part
of an innocent, shy girl on TV.
Shock.
It's the gap of what they're doing
and what they're trying to show on TV.
That gap is sneaky.
"So you don't mind if he held your hand?"
"No, I want to save that."
I was just remembering
how she said that so adamantly.
They don't have my support anymore.
I can't believe them anymore!
-This is crazy.
-It is crazy.
I can't believe them.
This is the biggest shocker
since Terrace House started.
-It's a major incident.
-Very major.
Wow, this is entertainment!
What's great is there's still video left.
And that thanks to this incident,
we've forgotten things
are going well for Arman.
-That's right! It looked good for Arman.
-We're sorry!
Except when the train
passed by the café.
He should've said, "Because I like you."
Yeah, the whole
"it's been more fun recently."
"Why?"
"Because you're here."
"What did you say?"
"Oh, nothing."
He had a chance for that kind of scene!
Instead he said, "There's a train."
-Very serious.
It was his chance
for an unforgettable scene!
Is it a good thing then?
That she's comfortable with him?
Should guys take that as a chance
if a girl says that to them?
It could go either way.
It could mean she doesn't see him
as a man.
I won't go so far as to say that,
but often it's like,
"We're not like that."
Masako is vulnerable right now,
but in any case...
-putting that aside.
-Rather...
-We should listen to what they say.
-That's true.
I'm sure Prosecutor Byrnes
will be questioning them.
-Prosecutor Byrnes?
-Yes, Prosecutor Byrnes.
-Prosecutor Byrnes.
-No, no...
It's not Kenji Moriwaki.
KENJI MORIWAKI
He'll get to the bottom of things.
-We have to hear their thoughts.
-I can't believe them.
Going to Kagoshima for a shoot.
-Martha
I'm kind of reaching my limit.
When he came back to our room
after the fireworks,
he said he can't see her as a woman.
That he can't hold hands with her
or kiss her.
-That's what he said.
-He did.
-He's totally doing all that.
-Yeah, all of it.
Yeah.
Knowing all this,
I can't really give advice
to Hayato anymore.
You mean how even though things
are progressing between them,
we have to pretend we don't know.
Yeah.
Making conversation
even though we know...
-It's not real.
-Yeah.
We should be clear about that.
It's just not fair.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
Hey, Hayato.
I'm back.
Let's have a drink.
Sure.
I'm exhausted.
-Should I go get her?
-You don't seem tired.
It's been a while.
-What?
-Us drinking together.
It hasn't been that long.
-No way.
-It was the day before last.
-Was it?
-Yeah.
Good morning.
-Morning? Were you sleeping?
-Morning.
-Welcome back.
-I was taking a nap.
We sort of...
needed to talk to the two of you.
Which two?
You and Riko.
I wanted to talk to you.
Recently...
Well we talk, right?
About your dates and everything.
And I give advice.
But to be honest, what you're doing...
and what's being said is too different.
There's a gap.
You meet after the rest of us are asleep.
When I ran out of the elevator
the other day,
I saw you guys kissing.
When did you guys start sleeping together?
I noticed you disappearing
about a month ago.
When I'd wake up around 4:00 a.m.
sometimes Riko would be there.
What's the real reason you're doing this?