-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
-Well, let's see...
-What happened?
It seemed like Hikaru and Misaki
were gonna be the cute couple,
but it seems like Hikaru's trying
to distance himself from her.
"Did I say I like her?"
-He did say that.
-And "I don't like co-ed baths."
-He made several cold comments.
-That's right.
Where are you going?
Have you decided yet?
Maybe the hot springs.
But I don't like co-ed baths.
-You don't?
-No.
But isn't it okay with someone you like?
Did I say I like her?
-What was that about?
-I don't know.
What's going on?
Did he have a change of heart?
-And that's how things ended.
-Yes, that's right.
We were left wondering
why Hikaru was acting like a brat.
-And...
-That's right!
-...the other drama.
-There was, wasn't there?
The beginning of the affair.
-We got to witness it.
-Yes.
-The how-to guide to cheating.
Please don't try this at home.
I can't go fishing with you
if it's just the two of us.
I had promised my girlfriend...
What's wrong?
Oh...
It's nothing.
Are you okay?
Something's bothering you.
Yeah, I am.
Let's get a drink.
-Right now?
-Yeah, let's go now.
Okay.
-That makes me so happy.
-Let's go.
From Hansan's girlfriend's
point of view...
It wouldn't be surprising
if she considered that cheating.
Just because he turned down fishing
doesn't mean it's all okay.
It's like he turned down fishing,
so he feels like he did what he needed to.
As for the rest,
well, whatever happens, happens.
He's popular with the ladies, so...
maybe he's a player.
-No.
-I'm making a statement.
I'm proposing the theory
that Handa is a player.
Nacchan was slightly attracted...
If I were to use a fishing analogy,
the hook is in her mouth.
Now it depends on
whether he's gonna reel her in.
That's right.
We might be able to see that moment.
And the hat left...
Yes, she took off her hat.
-She did take off her hat and leave.
-"Thank you."
-See you, Arisa.
-See you!
-See you later!
-Good luck.
-Bye!
And then we got to see
the bottom half of the new member's face.
She seems so young.
-The mom seemed young too.
-Right?
-Call me anytime.
-Yeah.
Come home if you don't like it.
-Bye. Be careful.
-Bye.
I'm just going to say this now.
I've already met this person.
What's with you?
Why are you looking at me
as if I've stalked her or something?
No, I met her on the job
at the Girls Award fashion show.
I was told to go to the press conference,
and I wondered who this person was.
That's when they told me
she's about to join Terrace House.
And I was like, "What? You're joining?"
You're going to be really surprised
when you see her personal profile.
Seriously?
It's like, "Wow, someone like that
is finally joining Terrace House?"
-What?
-Her job résumé or her profile.
What?
-Working tomorrow?
-No, not tomorrow.
-What about you, Hikaru?
-Construction work.
What are those pants called?
-Chocho Longs.
-They look really cool.
-They're not that cool.
-You looked really cool.
Right?
-I looked cool?
-You did.
-I looked that cool?
-Yes! Don't make me keep repeating it.
-You should wear them.
-Me? Wear them?
-Yeah, you wear stuff like that at home.
-You're terrible!
-What are your plans tomorrow, Nacchan?
-I'm going to Osaka.
-For four days?
-Yeah.
-That made me jump!
-That made my heart jump!
Let's go see.
You wanna come?
-Oh, man! Oh, man!
-I'm starting to get nervous.
-Hello?
-Hi, I'm moving in today.
-Okay.
-Please come in.
Her voice sounds cute.
-Oh, she's got short hair.
-It's short.
-Hi.
-Come in, come in.
She's cute!
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Good evening.
-Please sit.
-Excuse me.
I'm Riko Nagai.
-Riko Nagai?
-Yes.
-Rikochan?
-Nice to meet you.
-Please come sit.
-Yes.
-She's so cute. So young.
-She looks young.
Are you around 18?
-Yes, I'm 18.
-No way!
-Are you in your first year of college?
-I'm in my third year of high school.
-You're a high school student?
-Yes.
Have you graduated already?
It's an online school,
so I have another year.
I'll do the last year while working.
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
-While working?
-Yes.
What do you do?
Last week I won a beauty contest.
I don't know where that will lead to.
I'm not sure yet.
Was it a beauty contest
at your high school?
No, it was a national contest.
Do you know it?
-You won the grand prize?
-Yes.
Whoa, that's serious.
-Wow.
-That's amazing.
Where are you from?
I'm from Aichi.
-Oh, Nagoya!
-Yes.
What made you come to Terrace House?
I wanted to live in Tokyo.
So this is
your first time living in Tokyo?
-Yes.
-Wow!
I've been living with my mom,
just the two of us.
I've never lived with strangers
or any guys before,
so...
I'm a little worried.
-Do you have a boyfriend?
-Not for two years.
I'm not even really sure
I know what a relationship is right now.
She's 18!
I think you should do what you want.
Have you turned into old ladies now?
I mean, she's 18!
She doesn't even know what love is!
I'm sorry I put it that way.
I'm really...
It's so nice.
It seems like she hasn't met
too many foreigners or mixed people.
I should've hidden my tattoo.
She looked scared.
She never looked me in the eyes.
She probably was scared.
She was probably thinking, "Oh, no!"
I suddenly feel really old.
I don't mean you, Nacchan.
I haven't said anything.
-Are you okay with the Osaka accent?
-Of course.
Are you making fun of me?
What if I asked,
"Are you okay with the Hokkaido dialect?"
That's not what I meant!
You know, the Kansai dialect can be
a little blunt.
Are you okay?
I prefer it
when people are straight with me.
-I'm glad.
-Yes.
Is there something you want to do here?
I'd like to meet people I can trust here.
I thought that would be nice.
Since I don't know many people in Tokyo,
and everything is so new to me,
I'd like to build relationships
like that here.
Are you looking to find love, too?
That would be nice, too.
I do have an ideal type.
Someone funny and tall.
What about looks?
Of course I'd prefer someone good looking.
But for now, he just needs to be tall.
I feel like there aren't too many people
who are both tall and good-looking.
That's true.
Are you excited?
I am.
Before I came, I was really worried.
Now that I'm here, I'm excited.
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
HIKARU OTA, 19 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
What are you doing tomorrow?
I don't have plans tomorrow,
so I was going to buy things I need.
-Welcome back.
-Welcome back, Hansan.
-It's nice to meet you.
You don't seem surprised.
I'm Handa. It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Riko Nagai. Nice to meet you.
-Nagai?
-Yes, Nagai.
-Nice to meet you.
-She's in pageants.
-You are?
-Yes.
-Pageant competitor.
I won the grand prize
for high school girls.
Amazing. She seems like that type.
Out of the whole country!
That's amazing.
What are your plans for the future?
I'm not really sure what'll happen,
so I'm going to look for a part-time job
in the meantime.
Does your school have a branch here?
-No.
-You're going to commute?
-I'm going to commute.
-On the bullet train? Every time?
Well, I have to go about twice a month.
Oh, that's it?
Your mom's okay with this?
She is, but she's very worried.
Are you hungry at all?
-I am.
-You are?
Well, I actually brought home
some chashu pork.
I'll go heat some up.
-With sauce? Is there rice?
-There's no rice.
He's tired from work, too.
-He's impressive.
-I wonder if he has a lot.
He's so sweet.
-He's a nice guy.
-He is a nice guy.
If you need advice about relationships,
Hansan might be good to turn to.
I think he'd be good.
Or you're welcome
to come talk to me anytime.
-Was there any?
-All done?
Onions are so pungent.
I had trouble getting rid of the bite.
Oh, wow!
My apologies for serving chashu
so late at night.
Bon appétit!
-It's from your dad?
-My uncle runs a ramen shop in Nagano.
You were way off.
-He sometimes sends me things.
-Wow.
It comes frozen.
It's homemade.
It's so good!
We'll have to have a welcome party.
-We should go see the cherry blossoms.
-Nice!
-Let's go see cherry blossoms.
-Maybe cherry blossoms and a barbecue.
-It sounds fun.
-What day works best?
I'm actually leaving for Okinawa tomorrow.
-So you won't see me for a while.
-Until when?
I'm coming back on the second.
-The second?
-So, four days.
I'm coming back on the third.
-So sometime after the fourth?
-Yeah.
-Are you leaving early tomorrow?
-At what time are you leaving, Natsumi?
-I'm thinking of leaving by 7:00 a.m.
-I've got to leave by 8:00 a.m.
I'm free tomorrow.
Do you want to go shopping together?
-Yes, please.
-Let's go then.
-You're acting like a big sister.
-Yeah?
I am 23 after all.
-She's so cute!
-A high schooler.
She's still a kid and really cute.
The way she talks still sounds young.
-The number one high school girl in Japan.
-Right?
She's so flighty and only 18.
I wonder what kind of conversations
they'll have.
You know?
I'm sure she'll get used to it, but...
Even in terms of relationships,
to an 18-year-old, 27 is so much older.
-So much more adult.
-Definitely.
But there were girls in high school
who dated guys in their late twenties.
-The popular girls in class.
-Yes, those girls.
Teens though?
If it were me,
and maybe it's just my age,
she'd be too cute to go for.
Even if you wanted to.
I'd be all over Misaki,
but she's easy to go for.
It's hard to imagine
how they're going to interact.
She just arrived, said she was hungry,
and was served only chashu.
It's more like an appetizer.
And Hansan were like,
"Sorry to serve you this so late."
But those who thoughtlessly didn't serve
any food should be sorry.
In the history of Terrace House,
this group might be
the least skillful at cooking.
-You may be right.
-That's true.
-Nacchan's really the only one who can.
Both Hikaru and Arman can't,
Handa does chashu...
Misaki's a bit of an airhead
and Riko's 18.
Starvation might be a possibility.
-Rikopin's gonna start wasting away.
-Poor thing.
-Good morning.
-Were you able to sleep?
-Yeah.
I slept pretty well.
Thank you for washing the dishes.
-Oh, these are the ones I used.
-Oh, they're yours?
We're down to four today.
-Hansan's gone too.
-Two people are out.
I'm off to Okinawa -Han
I'll be in Osaka! -Natsumi
-Do you have any makeup on?
-No.
Your skin is so nice.
I'm jealous.
What do you need to get?
Some hangers and...
a box?
-Oh, to put stuff in?
-Yes, a box to store things.
House slippers?
Oh, yes. I want some.
DAIKAN-YAMA, TOKYO
-Is this your first time in Daikan-yama?
-It is.
It's so stylish.
That ice cream shop is delicious.
Or so I heard.
You heard? You haven't had it?
-Here we are.
-It's so cute.
It's hard to believe everything's 300 yen.
It's so cute!
2013 ENROLLED IN
KARIYA HIGASHI HIGH SCHOOL
2014 SWITCHED TO ONLINE COURSES
2016 WON NATIONAL BEAUTY PAGEANT
-This one's more shallow.
-Yeah, I'll use this for underwear.
SINGLE FOR THE LAST TWO YEARS
Here are some hangers!
-There are so many kinds.
-Yeah, it's so cute!
Is there anyone you like?
-There is.
-You're so lucky!
-Who do you think it is?
-One of the members?
Yeah.
-Who can it be? Hikaru?
-Yeah, I get so nervous around him.
Really? That's love.
What are you like when you're in love?
If it's one-sided...
I'm shy and hesitant.
That's normal.
-Is that how you are now?
-Yeah.
I'm probably not feminine enough.
-Really?
-Have you seen my pajamas?
They're sweats.
-Will you come with me to buy some?
-Let's go.
I need to start showing my feminine side.
Maybe in a subtle way.
If you show small glimpses
of femininity...
That's true.
I'm learning a lot.
SHIBUYA, TOKYO
Let's look at loungewear.
-Oh, something like this.
-That's pretty sexy.
-Would you wear something like this?
-No, never.
-It would look good.
-What do you think works for me?
Something mature...
and sexy.
Mature and sexy?
That's a cute set.
My sweats.
I like wearing them.
Have you gotten used to things?
I guess it's still early.
A little bit.
-Is Misaki easy to talk to?
-She is.
-Are those rabbits?
-They're rabbits.
Why'd you pick those?
'Cause they're cute?
I got them 'cause they're cute.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
What's with that outfit?
Isn't it nice?
What's going on?
What do you mean?
-What's going on?
-Nothing.
No, what's going on?
No, something's up.
You're usually dressed pretty lamely.
Am I?
Don't try to act slick
and cross your legs.
What's going on?
I mean, it's cute.
It looks good.
Seriously?
-You're just saying that.
-I'm telling the truth.
-For real?
-Yeah.
Why are you acting sexy?
It's not even sexy.
You're so mean!
I'm just kidding.
You look sexy.
But why? What's going on?
-It's really hot right?
-That's right, it's hot.
-Why are you laughing?
-Oh, man.
Why are you laughing?
-It's hot, isn't it?
-Yeah.
Did I ever say you weren't sexy?
Is that why you're dressed like that?
I can't look in that direction.
-Why not?
-Because I can't.
I can almost see your butt!
-Then don't look.
-You don't have to cross your legs.
Fine, like this then?
Why are you looking all over the place?
-You're going to sleep?
-I am.
-Good night.
How do you think it went?
Should I have taken my top off?
It was embarrassing.
I'm sure.
-It's hard to have it seem natural.
-Yeah.
That was the best I could do.
-Showing your shoulders?
-Yeah.
But he said it was cute.
But he was like, "What's going on?"
at first.
That's because
it was embarrassing for him too.
So he was just saying that,
even though he thinks it's cute.
Did he?
I couldn't pull it off at all.
It was so bad.
EBISU, TOKYO
So Misaki is just so-so?
She's still, well...
I like her, but...
Did yesterday's outfit change things?
That kind of thing isn't going
to change my mind or anything.
But some things are holding me back.
Like what? The way she acts?
She seems emotionally unstable.
Like how she cries easily?
-Or she seems insecure.
-In general you mean?
I don't know how she feels,
whether she likes me or not, but...
-But you're going out again, right?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I'll give it another shot.
See how it goes.
Does she try to show how she feels?
I don't know. Not really.
I don't know.
This is tasty.
Oh, Nacchan.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-Did you tan?
-No.
-Are you tired?
-Welcome back.
How were things?
Did anything happen?
I thought I'd work on my feminine side.
I thought I'd start with my pajamas
since I'm always in sweats.
So I went to buy some.
I'll show you later,
but it's pretty revealing.
And I showed Hikaru.
It was extremely awkward.
-So you did it already?
-Yes.
And did he make a move?
No.
Didn't you say you guys were going out?
Yeah, this month,
but I haven't come up with a place yet.
SANGENJAYA, TOKYO
-Hey.
-Hi.
AKANE SAKANOUE
MISAKI'S FRIEND, ACTRESS
-It's been awhile since I've seen you.
-Have you been watching Netflix?
I've seen up until episode 25.
What do you think from what you've seen?
What do you think of Hikaru?
-He's a little scary.
-Scary?
A little thuggish.
Like how he reacted
when I said he looks like a bad driver?
Yeah, he was scary!
-He was scary?
-Yeah, scary.
I suggested going to the hot springs,
but he said he didn't want to.
He said he didn't want to go in with me.
And when Nacchan said,
"But isn't it okay with a girl you like?"
He said he didn't like me.
-About you?
-Yeah, that's what he said.
Even when we're all together,
if I say something,
he'll say, "That makes no sense".
He'll say stuff like that.
He's really blunt.
His phrasing can be pretty harsh.
He's especially harsh with me.
Especially?
Like, "What? That's gross."
Or, "You can't be serious."
Doesn't that annoy you?
No, it doesn't.
Listening to you so far,
all I hear are bad things.
-About Hikaru?
-Yeah.
So what do you like about him?
-About Hikaru?
-Yeah.
It really makes me wonder.
What do I like about him?
I'm not sure.
But I don't think you need a reason.
-I just like him.
-You always say that.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-Doing well?
-Yeah.
-Are you?
-Yeah, I'm doing well.
Those are cute.
-The rabbits. Did you buy them?
-I did.
Are you used to things now?
-Yeah.
-That was quick.
That's good.
-Do I scare you?
-No.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
-I thought I scared you.
-No.
-You're okay?
-Yeah.
I'm not a bad person.
Are you getting along
with the other girls?
Yeah.
-With Misaki?
-Yeah.
-That's good.
-She's been really nice to me.
That's good.
-Do you like the ocean?
-I like the ocean.
Have you been to the ones near here?
Like Shonan?
-I've been to Enoshima.
-Oh, you have?
If you have time...
-we should go.
-I'd like to.
-There's a place I always go to.
-Is it far?
It's about an hour by car.
I work part-time in Kamakura.
I see.
-I wanna go.
-Let's go.
I haven't been lately.
-You need to go soon then.
-Yeah.
I need to refresh.
Tamosan's approach was interesting.
That was lingerie, wasn't it?
Not many people would wear lingerie
in the living room of a shared house.
-You normally wouldn't, right?
-It's a turn off, isn't it?
It's fine if it's for fun.
If she had just gotten out of the bath
and was on her way back to her room...
If he happened to see her...
Then it's like, "Wait, what?"
You shouldn't purposely show it.
She came downstairs just for that.
She came downstairs
and showed her shoulders.
That's Midori Satsuki's move.
MIDORI SATSUKI
If you're in control of your sexiness
like Ms. Satsuki...
Only she could pull off
something like that.
Now that Riko is here,
Misaki's acting like a big sister.
Somehow redeeming her?
I doubt it.
Emotionally, I think
Rikopin and Misaki are the same age.
Misaki might even be slightly younger.
Riko seems more responsible.
The conversation between her and Arman
was going nowhere.
It must be a recording or something.
"Have you been to the ocean?"
"Yes, I've been to the ocean."
-I think it'll be a disaster at the ocean.
-Everyone should go together.
It'll be tough with just the two of them.
It'll be like, "This is wave."
I'm looking forward to
Tamosan's sad attempts.
-I'm sure there will be a lot of failures.
-Poor Tamosan.
She's gonna try
to make eating vegetables sexy.
Like a zucchini.
You can't go there.
-A cucumber's okay. But a zucchini?
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-That's too far.
-I'm sorry.
NAKAMEGURO, TOKYO
The cherry blossoms are so pretty.
-Are there cherry blossoms in Hawaii?
-There aren't.
There aren't?
Then it's been a while
since you've seen them.
Yeah, it's been ten years.
-It's nice.
-Isn't it?
I'm glad I got to see them.
Are you used to things?
A little.
Who scares you the most?
No one's scary.
Welcome to Terrace House.
-Cheers!
-Wow.
-Yeah.
I'm changing the subject.
What do men find attractive in women?
What do we find attractive?
I wonder.
What about loungewear?
Loungewear?
-Loungewear?
-Loungewear.
Because that's something
only boyfriends usually get to see.
Terrace House is an unusual case.
You get to see girls in their loungewear.
-No?
-Me? No.
I've got one.
When girls wear only a white button-down.
Only that?
I totally get it, Arman.
But who does that?
That's nice, but...
Even if you did,
you probably wouldn't at Terrace House.
Because everyone else is here.
-But it's okay to do it, isn't it?
-Sure, you could.
If there's someone you want to show it to.
Someone you want to show it to?
You can't do it intentionally.
-You had to have always done it.
-Yeah.
It's better if it's natural.
Let's not talk about loungewear anymore.
-What's wrong?
-Was that at me?
Ask them over there.
What kind of loungewear
do you like, Hikaru?
-The sexy kind?
-Yeah.
I do.
Nacchan can be a little mean sometimes.
-How come?
-You say things you don't need to say.
I don't understand.
I'm scared.
What do you mean? Like what?
Don't worry about it.
That's gonna fester later.
You didn't have to bring up loungewear.
I wasn't talking about you.
I just wanted to hear about Hikaru.
Something's up.