-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers, men and women,
6 STRANGERS, MEN AND WOMEN,
SHARE A HOUSE
living together, and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
-Last week...
-Oh, yes. Last week...
I know we're dying to know what happened,
but, before that,
let's talk about the new member.
-Rikopin.
-Yes, Riko Nagai.
-She's adorable.
She was chosen as the cutest
high school girl in Japan.
Out of 640,000 girls.
-Are you in your first year of college?
-I'm in my third year of high school.
-You're a high school student?
-Yes.
Have you graduated already?
It's an online school,
so I have another year.
She's so pure.
Still inexperienced and untainted.
But she can be surprisingly
calm and mature.
Tamosan went to her for some advice,
though this ended up leading
to some problems.
She put on sexy loungewear,
did the shoulder move
and tried to attract Hikaru's attention.
-What's going on?
-Nothing.
No, something's up.
You're usually dressed pretty lamely.
Why are you acting sexy?
It's not even sexy.
You're so mean!
But why? What's going on?
Hikaru was like,
"What is this girl doing?"
And Tamosan picked up on that.
-And under those circumstances...
-Under those circumstances.
...they had the welcome party for Rikopin
with the cherry blossoms.
And that's when it happens.
-That was crazy.
-Yeah, it was crazy.
What do men find attractive in women?
What about loungewear?
Loungewear?
You can't do it intentionally.
-You had to have always done it.
-Yeah.
It's better if it's natural.
Nacchan can be a little mean sometimes.
I don't understand.
I'm scared.
-What do you mean?
-Don't worry about it.
That's gonna fester later.
You didn't have to bring up loungewear.
I wasn't talking about you.
I just wanted to hear about Hikaru.
Their expressions were right out
of a daytime soap opera.
A suspicious wife who opens the door
on an unsuspecting husband working away
from home, and...
It's ironic though that the expression
was from the perpetrator this time.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
-Isn't that scary?
-Yes.
"That's gonna fester later."
That's right.
She said it would create conflict.
But she's always creating conflict.
She probably doesn't realize
that her comments can be the trigger.
She's thinking she's doing it for her,
so for her to come back and say that,
she must be crazy.
It's like, "What's she thinking?"
Right?
So basically,
she thinks she's being helpful,
and when her actions are denied,
she snaps.
Let's see what happens.
-No, I'm scared. But I wanna see it.
-Yeah.
The two of them will be found bloodied
under the cherry blossoms.
Nice.
Good morning.
-You went for a run?
-Yes.
You're up early.
What's going on?
-Sorry about yesterday.
-It's okay.
I'm fine.
-Really?
-Yeah. But...
about the loungewear...
I was wondering why you brought it up?
I thought it'd be helpful information...
if we could find out what Hikaru likes.
Because Misaki would never ask.
I guess.
Because I was with her
when she bought it
and when she showed him,
to ask that in front of her...
I didn't think it was right.
I know how hard she was trying.
I know Misaki was put off by it.
It kind of put me off, too...
at the time.
I didn't like what happened.
I noticed her change in expression.
I...
I do wish that you had noticed,
but you didn't mean to hurt her, right?
You said it thinking it would help, right?
I think Misaki will understand
if you explain that to her.
Otherwise, Misaki might feel unsettled.
That's true.
If my words were taken that way
then I should explain it to her.
But...
I'm glad to hear
that you had good intentions.
-So you're okay with me?
-Yes.
I'm hoping Misaki will understand too.
I see.
What are you doing?
Well... So...
I said I was going
on a date with Hikaru, right?
So I was going to...
go ask him now.
Well, to give him a day.
I'm going to ask him out.
Oh, so that's why
you're fixing your makeup?
That's right.
-Nice.
-Wish me luck.
You're very feminine right now.
I'm trying.
I'm starting to sweat.
It's not the date yet, you're just asking.
That's true.
-Hikaru?
-Yeah?
What's up?
Excuse me...
-Should I leave?
-It's okay.
-You sure?
What? What' going on?
No, it's okay.
-Well, so...
-What is it?
-You know how we said...
-What?
...that we'd go out on a date?
-How about the 10th?
-The 10th?
I finally decided.
Nice.
I hope you look forward to it.
Well, then...
Where're you going?
I'm going back to the room.
I meant on the 10th?
What? I don't have to tell you now.
-I'm curious.
-Bye.
-You're not going to tell me where?
-No.
-Why?
-Don't worry about it. Bye.
-That was it?
-That was it.
Was that okay?
-It was, right?
-Yeah.
The 10th, huh?
ARMAN BITARAF, 25 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING FIREFIGHTER
NATSUMI SAITO, 26 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, ASPIRING ACTRESS
HIKARU OTA, 19 YEARS OLD,
MODEL, CONSTRUCTION WORKER
MISAKI TAMORI, 23 YEARS OLD,
ASPIRING ENTERTAINER, PART-TIMER
YUTO HANDA, 27 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR AT TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
RIKO NAGAI, 18 YEARS OLD,
4TH YEAR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
Hansan.
-Hi.
-Hi to you, too.
-This morning...
-Yeah?
Riko asked me
why I said what I did the other day.
-About the loungewear.
-Oh, the talk about the loungewear?
I had totally forgotten about it.
Well, I asked about it later.
Because I didn't know
why she was so upset.
I didn't know...
that she had bought loungewear.
In which case, it may have been better
if you didn't bring it up.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
It would've been fine
if it was before she bought it.
I'm not sure why it was wrong.
Is it really that big of a deal?
I think it was something
that was important to her.
It seems silly to me,
but she doesn't get upset that easily.
Misaki tends to make assumptions.
She does that sometimes.
She said I was being mean.
It's a little bothersome, to be honest.
I think it's important to say
what you're thinking to each other,
but if it's going to be so bothersome,
I don't care about
other people's relationships.
But this time...
I think you need to be more accepting.
The reason is because Misaki...
is truly in love.
And that person was present.
I think.
-Have you two talked?
-No.
It's only going to get worse.
Yea.
If you talk it out,
I'm sure it'll resolve quickly.
I have to hand it to you.
-I'm sorry to interrupt your work.
-It's okay.
-Do you have work tomorrow?
-No.
I'm seeing off an old teacher
from high school who's retiring.
That's so nice.
Is that it for tomorrow?
Then I'm coming back to Tokyo
and I'll do some work at my atelier.
Maybe I'll come visit you there.
-Tomorrow?
-Yeah.
Okay.
But I'm just gonna do my work.
-There's nothing I can help with?
-Oh, to help me with?
-I'm sure there's something.
-Okay.
I needed some advice, too.
I'm happy to lend an ear.
Who does she think she is?
Seriously?
-That was a little tough.
-Yeah.
The fact that she had forgotten all about
is the scariest thing of all.
Both Riko and Hansan
tell her the same thing.
-"I have to hand it to you."
-She did say that.
It's horrifying.
She doesn't know what she did wrong
and says
Misaki makes assumptions.
It's the same thing
that happened with Minori.
She thinks Misaki is the one that's wrong
and that she's the victim.
She's the one making assumptions...
-but she thinks it's the others.
-Amazing.
While Tamosan puts in so much effort,
fixing her makeup
just to go ask him out on a date.
Rikopin is keeping it cool
by saying she's only asking him out.
-It's not the date yet.
The 18-year-old is the most mature.
Nacchan is a little inept
at social interaction.
She'd make a tough wife.
Any small offense could upset her.
She'd get into fights
with the other neighborhood wives.
She'd tell you
what the other wife said to her.
But if you say,
"But I think you were in the wrong there."
She'd be like, "What?
I don't understand. What did I do wrong?"
She's going to create enemies all over.
-"That's going to fester."
-Famous words.
She's a good girl when she's not upset.
UENO, TOKYO
-Hansan!
-Yes.
Come in.
-Can I come in?
-Yes.
-It's a mess as usual, but...
-Excuse me.
-A delivery for you.
-What is that?
-A delivery.
-For me?
-Here you go.
-Thanks!
What do you think it is?
Well, it's written in French...
Don't worry about the packaging.
Thank you.
It might be a little cold now, but...
Oh, it's my favorite!
But if you've eaten already,
you can have it for dinner.
-I'll heat it up and have some later.
-Please do.
But I'll take fries now. Thanks.
What's this?
That's the job for you.
I was going to have you help with that.
They're dried flowers.
-We use them for architecture models.
-How cute!
It's scaled 200 to one.
If you can just cut off the flowers,
it's easy.
Oh, so they become trees for the models.
-They're trees, right?
-Yeah, with an X-Acto knife.
Like this.
If you don't mind working on that.
You can sit and work on that.
Bon appétit.
Oh, of course.
You mentioned needing advice yesterday.
I'm feeling uncertain
and it's all become a little bothersome.
Living at Terrace House has become tough.
I see.
Do you think I'm just insensitive?
At some basic level...
maybe you don't really realize
how values vary depending on the person.
I do think that at times.
-Values?
-Yeah.
Like what?
However you may feel,
the fact Misaki got angry
means you didn't consider her enough.
It depends on each person.
How you choose your words
depending on the person...
is something you're supposed to consider.
You said you were going
to support Misaki's romance.
That could mean...
that there may be times you need to lie,
or hold back for their sake.
I think it means you might have to take on
the dirty job at times.
What?
It's so much trouble.
But this is the time
you should put in the effort.
I think it's a good chance
to reflect on yourself.
Yeah...
Hello?
What're you doing?
Really? You're working?
You're at a café?
Wanna grab dinner together tonight?
NISHI-AZABU, TOKYO
I thought over a lot of things.
I talked to Hansan about it.
And... I'm sorry.
Why did you say what you did?
That's what I was wondering.
If you had done it
in consideration of me...
I wish you had asked him
when I wasn't there.
It wasn't very considerate of you.
That was my thought.
I think I did say things
without considering your feelings.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going on the date on the 10th.
-Maybe you knew already.
-No, I didn't.
I'm going to tell him how I feel.
You've decided?
I've decided.
How are things lately?
With Hansan?
I went to his atelier,
hoping for some advice.
I made hamburgers.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
You went to have hamburgers
with him, right?
And he said they were his favorite.
But you don't like him?
No, it's not like that right now.
Do you think you could like him?
I'm not sure.
-Of course you could.
-I didn't think so at first.
But maybe I do now.
Definitely.
But don't stir up anything.
I mean, I know I did, but...
-You're the one that stirred things up.
-You're right.
-That's how it was.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hilarious.
Hold on.
Are you stupid?
You're the one who stirred thing up.
Don't stir things up.
It'd be good for her to recognize
her own misconceptions.
For her own future.
Just like how Hansan said,
maybe this was a good opportunity
for her to really consider other people.
Within a span of a few months,
there's been two big fights.
That's a good amount.
Which means the fault lies with her.
-That might be true.
-It was the same with Minori.
People tend to talk it out
because they're at Terrace House,
but if this happened
between friends in ordinary life,
people tend to just go
their separate ways.
So maybe she's never had the opportunity
to realize things.
So coming here, she was able to realize
she needs to talk things out.
I hope she learns from this experience.
I wonder,
but I don't think she really has.
I feel like she's thinking, "Look at me!
I'm compromising, isn't it amazing?"
Maybe.
Like, "I'm apologizing for you."
She likes Handa...
and that may have a big role
in her apology.
-A huge role.
-Yes.
What would've happened
if Handa hadn't been there?
She might have left.
-It's whether she really understands.
-That's right.
I don't know. It'll be bad
if things aren't settled this week.
My feelings will be untamed.
-You mean your job after this.
-Yes. After this...
I'll be making a lot of noise on YouTube.
Sounds crazy.
It's gonna be bad today.
I can usually hold back on YouTube,
but I don't think I'll be able to.
Where are you going today?
-Today?
-Yeah.
We're going to Yokohama...
and...
going to a slightly fancy restaurant.
And then...
we'll go see the city lights.
I'm going to tell him how I feel there.
-Pretty.
-Okay.
-I'm ready.
-Good luck.
Misaki's totally excited.
-She went shopping yesterday.
-Seriously? For what?
I don't know.
Probably an outfit for today.
She went with Nacchan.
I was gonna go dressed like this.
I'm just wearing a hoodie.
-Good morning.
You look pretty.
-What?
-You look pretty.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Do you mind driving the car today?
Sure.
See you, Arman.
Later.
See you.
-Have fun.
-Bye.
The Rainbow Bridge.
Yeah, this one.
-It's probably pretty at night.
-Yeah.
Yokohama's known for views
of the city lights.
City lights...
Is that what we're doing?
-I haven't said that we are.
-I see.
I didn't say that.
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
-Is this your first time?
-No.
You've been here before?
Just once.
You have once?
What about you?
-Is this your first time?
-Yeah.
It is beautiful.
It is.
I like the atmosphere.
-You like Italian food, right?
-Yeah.
But I go to places like Saizeriya.
I get it.
I get nervous in places like this, too.
Let's toast.
-Cheers.
-Yokohama's beautiful, isn't it?
-Yeah, I've never been before.
I thought we could go see
the city lights after this.
I told you.
-So we're gonna go see the lights?
-Yes.
You don't want to?
Okay.
Why do you laugh?
-How is it?
-Tasty?
It's been awhile
since I've had such good meat.
You can have mine.
Cut me some?
-This much?
-Yeah.
That was delicious.
I can do another course.
Another whole course.
Wow.
It's pretty.
-The sound of the waves is nice.
-Yeah.
It's calming.
Look, they're kissing.
Guess it's that kind of place.
It's like we're a couple.
-Who?
-Us.
We're not a couple.
I wanted to talk to you.
What is it?
You probably...
already noticed.
I like you.
In the beginning,
I really just liked your face.
But...
after spending time with you,
it's become more than that.
I started seeing
all the good things about you.
Your bad parts, too...
but I still feel I like you.
So, if you feel the same way...
I'd like to go out with you.
That's how I feel.