-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers picked to live in a house
and have their lives taped.
All that has been prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
-Let's see. A lot happened last time.
-What happened?
The night before Naomi left for Japan...
There was a great line.
-That's right! By the pool.
-Yes, by the pool.
What do you mean by "positive"?
In terms of both my work and my love life.
I actually already made a move.
Really?
That's why Yusuke's not here.
I told him I wanted to talk to you alone
before I left.
From Naomi's perspective,
she and Yuya were becoming closer.
His behavior made her think so.
He was wearing her earring.
And that night, he made parfaits with her.
-He lent her his jacket.
-He did.
-But for now, he's brushing it aside.
-Yeah.
-Yuya and Avian...
-That's right.
-He wants Avian, right?
-Yes.
He said he did.
-Are you interested in anyone?
-Right now?
You are?
The time right before something starts
is the best.
-If something's starting.
-It's exciting.
-That "hmm" was the top of its class.
-A top-class hmm?
It's decided then?
-Yes, a top-class hmm.
-It was very progressive.
-And Lauren and Eric...
-This is the problem!
But they're not...
-We don't know what will come of it.
-They just went shopping.
But later, Eric and Lauren...
-Eric asks Lauren to help with his wall.
-Yes.
He's coming on strong.
-And Yusuke sees that and sort of...
-Yes.
He walks away.
-He held back a little.
-Yeah.
We were going to just paint it at first...
So that's where I want your help.
Of course!
He should've invited Yusuke
to take a look, too.
-Right!
-That wasn't cool.
I mean, he knows Yusuke
is interested in Lauren.
-He knows that.
-Right.
Maybe working with Lauren
has nothing to do with Yusuke.
Maybe he's simply thinking,
"Lauren's a little fox."
You're an idiot.
[impersonating Eric]
"Lauren's such a little fox."
-That sounds like him!
-Exactly like him.
Remember we talked about
me asking Lauren out?
I haven't gotten, like...
my head in the right place.
I recently found out
how amazing Yusuke really is.
-How's that?
-I keep mentioning him...
but Eiichiro Oda sent me
his thoughts again.
He sends me a message
every time Terrace House airs.
He said, "Yama-chan, are you sure it's
okay to make fun of Yusuke?"
And he sent me a video of Yusuke.
I forwarded it to all of you.
-Yes, you did.
-Eiichiro Oda messaged me...
"He's so amazing.
How can you make fun
of his virginity, Yama-chan?"
-He is really amazing.
-Is he that good?
He's amazing.
It made me want to send him a tweet.
-To Yusuke?
-You?
I decided not to, though.
I'm a professional after all.
Of course not!
How could you even consider it!?
Stop trying to suck up to 18-year olds.
I said I decided not to!
I stopped myself.
Watch out, Ken-chan.
Your popularity's taking off
like a rocket right now,
so Yama-chan might
try to hop on for the ride.
If you make one more good movie,
I'll really start kissing your butt.
If it goes that far, it's almost cool.
That's true, that's true.
Did anything happen while I was away?
Just my date with Avian.
That's all that happened around here.
Can I ask about it?
You should ask Avian first.
That would definitely be better.
-Here, eat this, Yusuke.
-You're right.
-Bon appétit.
-What do you want to do tomorrow, Naomi?
-I want to go shopping.
-Shopping?
-For stuff for the house.
-Groceries?
-That and...
-Have fun.
Huh? You're coming, too.
Come on, let's go together.
-It'll be too heavy to carry.
-I might have to go to school.
Did you get up on time all week?
-Were you late at all?
-Hm?
Were you late?
You really want to know?
This week? Yeah, I was late.
How many times?
Twice.
No one woke you up?
Eric told me your alarm kept going off.
For, like, 30 minutes.
-What did you do in Japan?
-I shopped.
I bought some cute pajamas.
-Oh, yeah?
-Nice ones.
I'll show you sometime.
Do you usually wear pajamas?
No.
-You don't?
-Not usually.
Why'd you buy some if you
don't usually wear them?
-Because it's cute, right?
-Yeah.
-Would you want a girl to wear pajamas?
-Would I?
It's okay for me to wear them,
but I wouldn't want my partner to.
-You know?
-That's weird.
Well, maybe it's weird
for me to say this...
but pajamas just seem so stiff.
Don't they? No? What am I saying?
Wearing pajamas makes someone seem
more open, doesn't it?
The most open is being naked.
-That's a given.
-Don't say that with a straight face.
Do you sleep naked, Lauren?
There are three of us, so, no.
-I sleep like this.
-You should just sleep naked.
Lauren is never naked in the room.
Yeah, only in the shower.
-Only in the bath.
-Yeah.
-But Naomi's naked all the time.
-Yeah, I am.
I walk around the bedroom naked.
You do?
-Not much I can say about that.
-Yeah, right?
-You do, huh?
-Maybe that was too much information.
How was your date with Yuya?
The date, yeah...
It was, like...
It was different than usual.
You know, when we all go surfing together?
I felt nervous this time.
-Nervous?
-Really nervous.
Because it was a date this time?
Yeah...
-What do you think of Yuya?
-I really had fun that day.
-Really?
-The date was fun.
Terrace House just started airing,
so I watched the first episode.
-You saw it?
-Yeah, I told you. Did you?
-Not yet.
-Oh, really?
I haven't seen it,
so I don't know what's going on.
On the first night...
the guys were talking in their room
about who they were interested in.
And Yuya said he gets along with you best.
That he was interested in you.
-He said that!?
-He did. On the first day.
That's really embarrassing.
-Embarrassing?
-Yeah.
-I suppose so.
-He doesn't act that way at all at home.
Even though we're living together,
he doesn't really talk to me.
Yeah.
-He's always on his phone.
-Or listening to music.
Yeah, or watching Netflix.
-What about Eric?
-I think he's a good person.
The first couple of weeks,
I didn't get along great with him.
But now I really like his personality.
What if he asks you out on a date?
Would you go?
Well...
I might get all anxious like that.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
MODEL, ASPIRING ARTIST
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
Nice.
I finally get to see it.
-Where I work has been a mystery, right?
-Yeah.
So, have you come up with any good ideas?
It might be hard to see
with a design like this.
-You mean the letters?
-Yes, it might be hard to see the letters.
But I want to draw it...
so that the letters pop.
And the colors?
It'll be something like this,
but with different colors.
-The colors--
-Nice.
-Nice?
These four.
If you finish that...
I'll bring it home after it dries.
Okay, then I'll paint it at home.
We're all so quiet.
Sorry.
Why?
We're starting to build on Tuesday.
-You're starting already?
-Yeah.
-Those are the colors?
-The Punch Bowl?
-Are you adding more colors?
-No, this is about it.
-Show me the bottom.
-I'm gonna get ready for school tomorrow.
Okay.
Good luck, Eric.
-Thank you!
-Like this?
I'm making everything.
I'm going downstairs.
Okay.
To do work?
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
I'm gonna head downstairs
for a chat with...someone.
With who?
Who knows?
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Who knows?
-I'm going downstairs, too.
-Okay.
-Good luck.
-Thanks, thanks.
Mysterious Avian.
-Right?
-Mysterious?
Why do you think so?
Because I can't guess anything.
-Really?
-About what you're like in a relationship.
Are you the type to
pamper or be pampered?
I like to be pampered, like any girl.
How? Like getting more attention?
What about you?
You like to be pampered alot, right?
-Yeah, I'm that type.
-That's what I thought.
You're the type that can't be alone.
-Yeah, not really.
-Right?
-Seems that way.
-I need someone to talk to.
That's why you're always talking to Naomi.
She's always willing
to accommodate me.
-Accommodate you?
-I mean she responds to what I say.
Lauren doesn't respond to you?
Yeah, you and Lauren always ignore me.
I don't ignore you.
You never talk to me.
Yes I do!
Recently, I think we were talking
on the sofa,
but you ran off to the rec room.
-Got any plans tomorrow?
-No.
That's perfect.
Want to go somewhere?
Maybe a café?
-We can get something to eat.
-Sure. Let's go.
We can go whenever.
I'll wake you when I get up.
Don't stare like that.
-Stop. Seriously.
-Why are you embarrassed?
I'm not embarrassed.
-Want to split this? It would be perfect.
-Sure.
We can split this
and get two cups of coffee.
Sure.
Do you get asked out by guys often?
It seems like it.
They do.
They do, but...
Do you go out a lot?
No.
You turn them down?
I don't want to be misleading.
And you?
Would you go if you were asked out?
If I was asked, then I would go.
It's not something I try to be, but...
I've been told by a lot of people
that I can be really misleading.
People always tell me that.
I can see that.
No way, really? Do I do that?
Well...
-With Naomi, yeah.
-No way!
Seriously?
For example, when Naomi says she's cold...
you'll lend her your jacket.
-That sort of thing.
-That's what you mean?
-That's not my intention at all.
-People don't usually just lend jackets.
You do it someone's cold, right?
I do it all the time.
You do? To just friends?
I don't do that.
-Why not? They're cold.
-I don't think I would.
-Really?
-Well, it's because you're nice.
I'm not conscious of that
when I'm doing it or anything.
I think there's a limit
to how nice you should be.
There's a love triangle,
and Yuya's in the middle.
Even while she's telling Yuya
he shouldn't do something...
Avian's feelings toward
the sweetness of this younger guy is...
It's like it might overtake her.
They were flirting a little bit, right?
-When they were cutting shirts together.
-Yeah.
But on the other side of the wall,
Naomi's like...
-And the way the phone lit her face...
-Yes.
-It was lit up.
-Kind of blue.
She was really focused on her phone.
-Maybe she was googling poisons.
-Could be.
-"Poison. Untraceable."
-Exactly.
-"Easy to grow."
-Stop it!
She's not like that!
And what was with that
ridiculous pajama theory Yusuke had?
"Pajamas seem stiff."
-It was so cute!
-After Lauren mentioned being naked,
-Yusuke became quiet and did this.
-Stop that.
Tokui said the table was about to rise.
-A little bit, right above Yusuke's lap.
-Like in the comics.
Like a Japanese porno comic.
But Naomi also says she bought pajamas.
And that she'll show them off sometime.
And Yuya asks all insensitively,
"Why'd you buy them?"
"Do you usually wear them?"
"No."
-"Then why'd you buy them?"
-He did say it like that.
Yusuke jumps in to say,
"It's because they're cute, right?"
That was nice of him.
-It was sweet.
-It was so sweet.
-Yuya's so insensitive.
-He is.
He's seriously insensitive.
You always know one person like that.
An older woman like Avian
might find that cute.
That kids are like this.
That's fine if she thinks it's cute.
But if she sees him as a kid,
-then she won't see him as a man.
-That's true.
There was a younger guy that really
liked Seina, remember?
With hair like a shih tzu.
What was his name?
-Daiki!
-Daiki.
He has to love Avian at that level.
Otherwise, she won't think it's cute.
Avian is calmer than Seina.
She's saner.
It'd be interesting if Seina showed up.
-What would happen if she did?
-That would be really interesting.
-She'd be so high-energy in Hawaii.
-Right?
Maybe we can have a separate shoot
with Seina in Hawaii.
-I want to see that.
-There'd be so many great lines!
Nice work!
You were so cool.
Really? Thank you.
I was so worried.
You were first!
-I was like, "Oh, it's Lauren!"
-Yeah.
It was a last-minute change.
I was third,
but then all of a sudden
They were just like,
"Put on this bathing suit. Go!"
-So you weren't meant to go first?
-Yeah, I was supposed to be third.
But thank you so much for coming.
-It was fun.
-Yeah, it was amazing.
Are you heading home now?
-I have work.
-I'll probably head home.
-Then I'll see you in the evening.
-Let's talk then.
-Good job.
Thank you so much.
I'm going to take a bath and go to sleep.
-Right, you've got tomorrow.
-Good job.
Good luck. I'll come tomorrow.
Good night.
-Good work.
-Good night.
What's that?
-Someone's knocking.
-Someone's here.
Who is it?
There it is again!
-Hello.
-Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
Aloha! Mahola!
That means "thank you."
-I'm Daiki. Nice to meet you.
-I'm Eric. Nice to meet you.
-I'm Seina. Nice to meet you!
-I'm Yuya.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Wow, amazing!
-Good evening.
It's nice to meet you.
Let's drink.
-You're in Hawaii?
-Yes, I'm visiting Hawaii.
SEINA SHIMABUKURO, MODEL
I arrived yesterday.
I've been in Maui for about two months.
She came yesterday.
DAIKI ITOH, WINDSURFER
We met up and came to Oahu.
-Where should I sit?
-Anywhere.
-Really? I want to sit there.
-It's free.
Please, go ahead.
-I want to sit here.
-Let me get a glass.
This has the best camera angle.
-Is that so?
-Seina, did you used to be on...
-Were you on the show?
-Yeah, I was one of the first members.
-I'm pretty much a legend.
-I knew I heard your name before.
I'm a pretty big legend.
-Wow.
-I recognized your name.
Let's toast.
-Cheers.
-Thanks for having us!
This is great. I'm so happy!
I never thought they'd set
Terrace House in Hawaii.
Insane, isn't it?
-Wasn't there another surfer?
-There was.
What was his name?
-Masato Yukawa.
-Oh, Masato.
I was mixing you two up.
-That's not me.
-Right.
I'm the long-haired one.
-The one with the long hair.
-Yes, yes.
And there was a party
where you got drunk and...
-kissed in the rec room.
-That was her.
Yeah, that was me and another guy.
-Oh, I see.
-Yeah.
But we're here now
because all of that happened.
Yeah.
-What do you do, Daiki?
-I windsurf and...
I've been traveling overseas
for the World Cup.
Going to different places,
like Spain, now Maui.
I stay in Maui every year
for about three months.
Amazing.
But she gets mad.
-Why?
-She wants me to come home.
-I do go home.
-It's a long distance relationship.
But it's been a pretty long time now.
Around two and a half years?
-That is long.
-Yeah, and we met on Terrace House.
So there's hope for you.
Yeah, there is.
-Yeah, just go for it.
-There's hope.
So is there anything going on,
romantically?
-Romantically?
-Not really. Here and there...
Are you in love?
-I'm...
-Are you?
-Not at all.
Well...
-Why are you being vague?
-You are, for sure.
I'm focused on work right now.
You're focused on work?
You're already 27, right?
-Am I getting old?
-Yeah, you better hurry.
What was it like
when you first started going out?
He's six years younger than me,
but he kept asking me out on dates.
Yeah, it's just harder
for girls to ask the guys out.
So if you're interested in someone,
you should just ask them out on a date.
-You're right.
-Yeah.
Everyone hanging out together is different
from two people hanging out alone.
Yeah, it really is.
-Have you had a girlfriend before?
-Never.
-You've never dated anyone?
-Not even once.
-Seriously?
-So you've never been with a girl before?
-Well, yeah.
-Excuse me.
-You've never kissed a girl?
-Never.
That's amazing.
You have so much to look forward to.
Looks like Avian never came back home.
-She's late.
-I can't reach her.
-What?
-She's super late.
-If she's coming, we'd like to meet her.
-Yeah.
-But it is late.
-She's not coming?
-We should get going.
-Maybe she's out seeing another guy.
No way!
No, she's working.
Oh, is she?
I'm just joking.
Even if she is, it doesn't matter.
"It doesn't matter"? Oh, wow!
He's making you look bad.
Pretty bad, no?
"It really doesn't matter."
Wow, I didn't think I'd hear that
from an 18-year-old.
If you just show what makes you appealing,
they'll come to you on their own.
-Well, yeah, that's true.
-Right?
You're right, it doesn't matter.
-It doesn't matter.
-It totally doesn't.
It doesn't matter
if she's out dating or whatever else.
-That's right.
-Yeah.
Well, that was fun and I got to say
what I wanted. Time to go home!
-You're leaving already?
-Yup.
It was fun. I'm glad you came.
-Thank you.
-I'm glad we got to meet.
-See you! Hug me, hug me!
-Thank you.
-Hug me, see you later!
Thanks for coming.
Thank you! Hug me!
-Thank you.
-You can do it!
-Come again.
-We will!
Thanks for having us! It was a lot of fun!
Thank you! Sorry to bother you!
-Good night! See you!
-Good night.
-See you.
-Thank you!
Man, she's a vibrant one.
-Amazing.
-She's got a lot of energy.
[impersonating Seina]
"See you! See you!"
-It was crazy.
-It was nice.
-That was surprising.
-That was fun.
It's hot.
-Too hot.
-Right?
Can I turn on the air conditioner?
Are you just getting ready
for your test today?
Yeah, all I have to do today is study.
-Nice. Good luck.
-Thank you.
But the test seems like
it'll be pretty easy this time.
-Really?
-Yeah. Last time it was about names.
But this time it's about
what I like on the menu.
I haven't tried anything yet,
so I'm just imagining it as I go.
-You have to ask about allergies, too.
-Yeah, stuff like that.
-Like, what's in it.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Is it okay if I talk to Lauren alone?
I was just thinking of leaving.
I'll show myself out, then!
-Let me get up.
-Take your time!
Ah, don't worry about that.
You don't have to be so formal.
Are you already done
with that modeling job?
Yup, it's all over.
Are you free at all next week, then?
Next week...
Yeah, I'm pretty free.
Are you free on the 18th or the 20th?
The 18th...
Okay.
Let me take a look.
I think it's a Friday and a Sunday.
Either day is fine.
Yeah, I'm free.
-Wanna go somewhere?
-Which day?
Um... whichever.
Either day works?
Want to go see a movie together?
Is there anything you want to see?
Hmmm, what's playing now?
You said before you like animated movies.
Is there something like that out?
I'm sure there is. There must be.
-Really?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
Something must be playing.
Any time is okay with me.
-Any time?
-Whenever works for you.
I'll check my schedule
and get back to you later.
Okay, thanks.
Don't thank me!
I'm sure it'll be fun.
I'm going to get ready for the gym.
-Have fun.
-Thank you.
Alright.
Hey.
-What are you doing?
-Playing a game. Killing time.
You asked her?
Yeah.
How'd it go?
It went.
It went?
You mean you're gonna go out together?
Yeah.
That's great. What did you say?
-What did you say?
-Well... I...
I asked her if she was free
on the 18th or the 20th.
And if she'd want to see a movie
if she's free.
-I was so nervous.
-And?
She said she'll check her schedule,
but she's probably free.
-Like, "Sure."
-Nice.
A movie date, huh?
-It's a date, right?
-I'm sure she doesn't think it is.
-But for me...
-It's a date?
Yeah, it is.
A movie alone with a girl...
Your first time?
-Of course.
-Oh, yeah.
That's great.
-Makes your heart race, doesn't it?
-Yeah.
Wow, this is insane.
-You're happy?
-I'm happy.
He's so cute!
This is going to affect his music.
Is that okay?
-He's so cute!
-I'm happy for him.
Nice!
-It was so surprising!
-We predicted it.
-We must be prophets.
-Yes!
I yelled so loud, I'm embarrassed.
You really did.
Wait!
Isn't that Seina and Daiki?
-No way!
-It's Seina!
She has descended! Seina has descended!
-I was thirsting for Seina.
-Seriously.
There was the famous "hug me."
"Bye! Thank you! Thank you! Bye!"
"I'll come again!"
It was past midnight. How terrible!
-But it was great.
-Thanks to Seina...
Is it? Is it really thanks to Seina?
-Yeah.
-She pushed him to do it.
-There needed to be that kind of...
-Power.
Thanks for setting things
in motion, Seina.
-As expected. She makes things happen.
-She does.
-She can make things happen.
-She really can.
But I think I'm full now,
so I don't need her again for a while.
-But she made him ask her out!
-He did.
The way he said
she probably doesn't think it’s a date...
That was nice.
-He made an effort.
-He did it.
He was nervous and talking quicker.
He drank so much water. It was so cute!
And offering two dates as options...
He definitely thought hard about that.
And he asked what movie she wants to see.
Like, "What's playing now?"
But I'm sure he has it all researched.
And he said, "You said you're interested
in so-and-so, right?"
I'm sure he researched that genre.
-That was so surprising.
-It was amazing.
-For everyone watching...
-This was really a treat.
Yusuke asked you to a movie?
Yeah, and I said I'd go.
-You did?
-But at the time,
and this might be a cultural difference,
but if a guy friend asks you to a movie,
it's normal to go as friends.
-To go as friends?
-Yeah.
That's normal here.
It's not a date unless you say it is.
But thinking about it now...
I'm sure he thinks it's a date.
-Yusuke?
-Yeah, Yusuke.
-You haven't talked about that?
-No, not yet.
He didn't say it was a date,
but he was really nervous.
I can just picture it.
Like, "Lauren..."
I don't know what Yusuke's thinking.
-If he thinks it's a date...
-He likes you.
I don't know. I...
-He does.
-I don't know that at all.
Yusuke probably...
Well, he talked a little bit about it
to me before.
He said he wants to get to know you.
Because he doesn't really know you
since he hasn't really gotten
to talk to you.
He told me that.
I was just wondering,
what should I do?
And I didn't say anything.
But right now, I feel...
I'm sure you know,
but I don't feel that way towards Yusuke.
You don't know what to do?
-I think it's fine to go.
-Me, too.
I should give him a chance.
I should go and have fun.
If something changes, then it changes.
And if it doesn't, then nothing changes.
If you go and you have fun...
then you're okay with that?
If nothing romantic happens,
then that's fine with me.
You don't want that, right?
-Yeah, not right now.
-You don't, right?
Right now, I don't feel that way.
I think that's okay.
You should try going.
I will.
And later...
if you don't have feelings for him,
you can just tell him.
Yeah, it's just the timing.
I think if you're clear about it,
Yusuke would understand.
Yeah, Yusuke would definitely understand.