-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Saito will be hosting with us today again.
Hi, I'm Saito.
I watched Your Name once,
but Terrace House twice.
-The movie version?
-Yes.
-Wow!
-That's amazing.
Should we review what happened?
Naomi and Yusuke,
who were very entertaining,
have now left.
-I think I need to step in now.
-You don't.
It's none of your business.
Eric also announced that he's leaving.
Explain it right!
-He'll catch a cold. Hurry! Get his hat!
-Hurry!
Do that once more
and I'll get the flu!
Now that we've collaborated
and the pop-up is opening...
I've finished what I set out to do.
So after this...
I'm leaving.
All we've seen of his project are
graphics of a shack spinning.
So he'll leave once it's completed.
Yuya and Avian are getting
closer and closer.
They like each other.
They went on a date.
There was a cool scene.
-Active people--
-I like girls I can work out with.
I see.
Wait, hold on...
He said, "It's you."
-That was so cool!
-The two of them laughing...
It's nice when you can
laugh together like that.
-It is nice.
-It means you get along.
The comedy trio Robert would say,
"They're so easy to work with!"
She's easy to work with.
The type you'd want to hang out with.
-But the reason she's easy to talk to...
-Stop that.
"She's the least pretty of the three."
That shocking, shocking assessment.
She's probably the least pretty
of the three.
But after getting to know her...
she's really pretty to me.
Just as the two of them become closer,
Terrace House does something like this.
A new female member joins.
-Are you from Hawaii?
-No, I'm from Japan.
Japan?
-But you live in Hawaii?
-It's been about three years.
What kind of guy is your type?
Well, I surf.
Do you?
I've only been doing it for two years.
-You must be really good.
-Not at all.
I'd like someone I can go surfing with.
-Let's go together.
-Yeah, let's go. I'm glad.
The way Yuya was looking at Haneishi...
it seemed like he was interested.
She's the type guys like,
the type they're attracted to.
-The way she dresses is cute.
-Tomochika would say...
that she's got an erotic mouth.
-Plump.
-Yes, plump.
The two of them have surfing in common.
Saito noticed in that scene
that Avian's eyes went to Yuya for a sec.
-That's right.
-At Yuya.
It's like Cristiano Ronaldo
before a pass.
-Was it really like that?
-Was it?
If so, that's a big deal.
-She's definitely going to pass.
-Definitely.
And there's also a new male member.
-Today!
-We'll get to see him today.
I'll be going to Hawaii to fall in love.
He looks attractive.
What if his eyes are far apart?
You're terrible!
-You're terrible.
-Enough to be a turn off.
Of course they won't be.
What's wrong if they are?
No, if they're really far apart.
-That's not even human.
-Just barely.
So that point where he's not
human if they're any farther apart?
Do you--
-I'll go.
-Eric!
Eric?
-What?
-No way!
Seriously?
-A third new member?
-Not three.
-Eric is still here.
-He is.
-Hello.
-Come in.
Excuse me.
-Are you okay?
-Thank you, I'm all right.
Wow.
-Should I put my bags here?
-Sure, anywhere.
-Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Taishi Tamaki.
-Taishi Tamaki?
-Yes.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm Yuya.
-Yuya? Nice to meet you.
-I'm Anna.
-Anna? Nice to meet you.
-I'm Lauren.
-Lauren? Nice to meet you.
-I'm Avian.
-Avian? It's nice to meet you.
-I brought some gifts.
-Seriously?
-I came from Los Angeles.
-I see.
-You came from Los Angeles?
-Yes.
-You're from Los Angeles?
-I'm not from LA.
I work as an actor in Hollywood.
-How long have you lived there?
-A year and a half, almost two.
So I still don't speak English very well.
-There's a lot of stuff.
-Thank you!
-I figured I should have six.
-Thank you.
-Wow!
-And...
Dark almond.
Some were half off.
-See's Candies is so good.
-I love it.
-How old are you?
-I'm 29.
And you?
-I'm 18.
-You're 18? 18 years old?
I'm 18.
Well, it's nice to meet you.
How about...
-I'm 26.
-26?
-I'm 18.
-18?
-I'm 22.
-Okay, 22.
-Seriously? You don't look it.
-There's one more who's 27.
27? Phew! That's good.
-There's a 27-year-old.
-I'm glad.
What do you plan on doing in Hawaii?
I plan on falling in love in Hawaii.
-You're determined.
-You've got determination.
I left all my jobs in Hollywood for this.
What kind of person are you looking for?
Generally, I like really feminine girls.
But I don't know.
I plan to just go for it.
And hopefully not fail... I think.
I'm so nervous, it's bad.
-I think everyone's nervous.
-Really?
You're right.
-Why are your hands so...
-I was thinking that, too.
-How embarrassing.
-Lauren draws.
I love to draw. I was drawing earlier.
Are you an artist?
-She's really good.
-I see. Wow.
-I'd like to go to LA in the future.
-Seriously?
-So we're in the same boat.
-Yes.
How long did you live in Japan?
I was born in LA
and lived there until I was six.
Then I went back to Okinawa.
-Oh, Okinawa.
-Yes, that's why my features are defined.
Yeah, I see it.
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
-Yes, a little.
-I see.
So I grew up in Okinawa,
I went to college in Tokyo,
graduated and became an actor.
Then I moved to Los Angeles.
That's kind of how it went.
-You were born and raised in Japan?
-Yes.
My dad is American and my mom is Japanese.
Do you speak Japanese with your dad?
We spoke English when I was younger.
I heard I spoke it when I was six, too.
-But I've forgotten everything.
-I don't remember it.
-I see.
-We'll teach you.
Please do, teacher.
Teach... Teach me Japanese.
I can't talk right now.
What?
You're so nervous.
-Please teach me Japanese.
-Of course.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
Wow, it's so cute.
I'm looking forward to my time here.
-Us, too.
-It's nice having you.
Are you looking for love?
I'd love to find it...
but I haven't found anyone.
You guys haven't been
in relationships in a while?
No.
-What do you think?
-Of the guys.
Of the guys.
-But I haven't met one of them.
-Yes.
Not counting that one.
From the one's in the house at the moment.
What do you think of the other two?
They both made good impressions.
I guess...
-I'll have to see.
-You'll see.
I'm really looking forward
to living in this beautiful house.
Hawaii is small, but it's hard
to meet people, don't you think?
-I've never dated anyone in Hawaii before.
-Really?
I've also never had a relationship
in Hawaii.
I haven't dated in Terrace House.
A date...? Yusuke...
It was kind of a date.
Date...
Don't stop there, Lauren.
Wait a second...
It wasn't quite a date?
There's a fine line?
There was
a little miscommunication, I think.
Do you have other plans in Hawaii
other than finding love?
Well, I was thinking of working.
There seems to be
an agency in Hawaii, too,
so I was thinking of joining that.
I need more information.
What do you do normally?
-I go to school.
-School?
-What kind of school?
-A language school.
-Can I go, too?
-Yes.
-Really?
-Maybe I'll go.
-Oh, do you want to?
-Yeah.
-You can come.
What is it like?
It's from the morning until the evening.
-Well, we study English until 3:30.
-Pretty hardcore.
-Vocabulary, grammar, listening...
-I see.
Then I won't have time to work.
-Maybe not.
-I see.
Can I take just a few classes?
You can do just the morning classes
if you want to free up the afternoons.
I see.
Can I ask you a personal question?
What's the relationship situation like?
-In the house?
-Yes.
Well, I have feelings for Avian.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
You're making moves?
-I've asked her out on dates.
-Seriously?
I see.
Anyone you like on first impression?
-First impression?
-Or were you too nervous?
Yeah, I was just trying to keep up.
I was nervous.
I did think everyone was cute.
Do you go to acting school?
I did from time to time.
And I was supposed to start
in January again,
but I had to cancel.
It's interesting though.
In Japan, you just get into it.
You do some theater and learn as you go.
But in America, there's method acting.
There are techniques to learn
on how to play a role.
That's what I wanted to learn.
For example, how you use emotions,
how to draw those emotions from yourself.
-Wow.
-To become that character you mean?
Yes, it's interesting.
-And auditions?
-Many auditions.
There could be a thousand people
auditioning for a role.
-That many?
-Initially.
Then you audition once you get chosen.
Do you get nervous?
-Nervous?
-You seem experienced.
No, I'm not at all.
The supermoon is amazing.
-Oh, yeah, today's the last day.
-Let's go see it later.
-The supermoon.
-Here. I'll take that.
Thanks.
-Bon appétit.
What's everyone doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
-We're boxing together at 5:00.
-That's right.
Boxing?
-It's a complete coincidence.
-We're members of the same gym.
Do you have plans for tomorrow?
I was going to look for work.
What kind of work?
Somewhere where there aren't
too many Japanese people.
I need to expose myself to English,
or else I'll forget.
-How's your English?
-We could...
How's your English?
English test.
Scary!
-You can totally speak English.
-Not at all.
It's so nice!
-Nice.
-Can you see the supermoon?
-It was big yesterday.
-It was biggest when I came home.
It's the last night tonight.
-It's beautiful.
-Nice. I wanna go in the pool!
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
Are you the famous Papa Eric?
Oh, a new member!
-You couldn't see?
-I didn't see at all.
It's nice to meet you.
You both came at the same time?
-I'm Eric. Nice to meet you.
-I'm Anna.
-I'm Taishi.
-I'm Eric.
-What was it again?
-Taishi.
Haichi? Taichi?
-I'm Anna.
Actually, I'll be leaving soon.
-Really?
-Has that been decided already?
Yes.
-Around the 18th or 19th.
-The 18th or 19th?
-So you won't be here for Christmas.
-No.
-So I'll only be here a little.
-Then we'll have to have some beer.
That makes me happy.
Having someone to drink with.
-Taishi!
-Yes, Taishi.
He's very noble looking.
He has strong eyebrows.
-It's nice. He's lively.
-He's looking more and more attractive.
Saito noticed something.
Lauren seems very excited.
-That's true.
-For Lauren, it's a Terrace House first.
Yes, she's never acted like that for me.
-For you?
-It's very frustrating.
Is it because he's older?
He's older and seems like a good guy.
He's well-spoken.
Lauren initiated conversation
during dinner.
Yes, so he can practice speaking English.
I think it's good.
So it's about appearances after all.
But if Saito's head was fluffier,
he'd be like Taishi.
-Is he the same type?
-We are similar.
-You do have a manly face.
-Yes.
But you've got this.
-He's going to get the flu.
-I'll need a week off.
-It's the flu, after all.
-That's tough.
I wanted to be with Lauren.
All you had to do was open the door.
I really wanted to open that door.
If only I could go.
I'm a little busy right now.
That's true.
-Good morning.
-You're leaving already?
-Yes, I'm going.
-The coffee might be a little weak.
-Thanks.
Is it weak?
-When will you be done? 4:00?
-Yeah.
-Is it strong enough?
-Yeah, it's good.
-Thanks for this. I'll look into it.
-Sure.
I'm sorry I can't show you around.
Don't worry about it.
Whenever you have the time.
-Do you like sweets?
-I love sweets.
-Like pancakes?
-I love pancakes.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-There are so many places in Hawaii.
-That's true.
-See you.
-Bye.
If there's anywhere you want to go to...
So, you're free until 5:00 today?
Yeah, until 5:00.
-You're free?
-Yeah.
I have lots of time.
Do you mind accompanying me?
I'm still new to Hawaii.
Let's go for a drive,
maybe along the beach.
I know it's cliché,
but can we go to Waikiki?
Sure.
-Then let's go to Waikiki and have lunch.
-Sure.
This is perfect! It's insane!
-This feels good.
-Right?
This is insane!
-Let's go.
-Insane!
So you've never had a boyfriend out here?
-No.
-I see.
What's your type?
-I like manly guys.
-I see.
I tend to do everything on my own.
-So you want someone who takes the lead.
-Yeah, I think that would be nice.
-That's Diamond Head, by the way.
-Oh, this is it?
I had no idea.
-It's huge.
-Then I'm glad I mentioned it.
-It's so nice. This drive is so fun!
-Yeah, nature is nice.
The sand is white.
It feels nice, doesn't it?
This is nice. It's the ocean!
It's so pretty.
The way the waves sparkle is nice.
-Did it turn out okay?
-It looks good!
It's not backlit. It looks good.
-I'll send it later.
-Yeah, please do.
-This is amazing.
-Looks good.
-Bon appétit.
Looks so good!
The long-awaited loco moco.
It's so good.
Have you found a job yet?
I haven't thought about it.
I've been having too much fun.
-You said by the end of this week.
-Yeah.
-It shouldn't be too hard.
-I'm sure.
Did you work for long
at the Japanese restaurant in LA?
About half a year.
I told them I'm going to go fall in love.
That's determination, coming to Hawaii.
Have you experienced a love of a lifetime?
Never.
What are you like in a relationship?
I don't know,
but I think I get pretty into it.
You focus on it?
Do you usually initiate?
It can go either way,
but it's never gone well
with girls who asked me out.
-So, it's better if you initiate?
-Yeah.
I've never been the one to initiate.
I'd like to be in a relationship
that I initiate.
Good.
Challenge is good.
We went to eat loco moco.
-Where'd you go?
-You went to eat?
We did.
-Aloha Table, I think.
-Yeah.
-The demi-glace sauce was so good.
-It was, wasn't it?
-Where? In Waikiki?
-Yeah, Aloha Table in Waikiki.
I was enjoying Hawaii.
-Let's play basketball tomorrow.
-Let's surf.
-Basketball.
-Surf.
-Let's play basketball.
-Let's surf.
Why?
Basketball. It's decided. After school.
-Taishi, you practice kendo?
-No, not kendo.
What is it?
-Tate-do.
-Tate-do?
-Iaido.
-What's different?
Tate-do uses a wooden sword,
while iaido uses a practice sword.
Oh, I see.
-Can we see it now?
-Now?
You brought it, right?
I want to see!
-I want to see.
-Well, okay.
Oh, wow!
You're a professional.
-No, I'm not a pro.
-Try something.
What you normally do.
Like what you practice all the time.
-Is it for movies?
-Yes, for movies.
There's a style where you swing straight.
But mine, you swing diagonally.
The way he holds it is amazing.
Seems painful if it hits you.
You usually wear armor.
-You wear armor?
-It hits the armor.
So you go diagonally.
-Be careful up top.
-Don't worry.
-Wow.
-Amazing.
Here's my iaido sword.
Oh, so you practice with that first?
-I saw it yesterday.
-Wow!
-That's scary.
-That's amazing!
-I've never seen one!
-Is it real?
No, I wouldn't be able
to bring a real one.
A practice sword.
Amazing.
-You're going to continue in Hawaii?
-Yeah, I brought it to practice.
-Wow.
-Katori Shinto-ryu.
What made you want to do this?
If you're Japanese,
those types of roles are common.
So I wanted to be proficient.
Good morning.
My shirt had a hole in it.
-It sucks when you get a hole.
-Yeah.
What are you doing today?
Today? Um...
I'm going with Avian to Costco at 6:30,
if you're free.
-Costco?
-Yeah.
So no plans until then?
No plans.
-Have you thought about lunch?
-I haven't.
-Then let's go somewhere.
-Shall we? Okay.
-I've got a ton of time.
-A ton?
Tons and tons.
Anywhere you want to go?
-You're vegetarian, right?
-Yes.
Let's go somewhere like that.
Are there a lot of places in Hawaii?
-There's a place I like.
-Oh, yeah?
-You want to go?
-Let's go there.
Did you really join Terrace House
to find love?
Yeah.
In an acting class,
they tell you to open yourself up more.
So if I fall in love
and become deeply connected to someone,
then it might make me more appealing
as an actor as well.
I'm turning 30 next year.
We're 11 years apart!
-Isn't that crazy?
-Eleven?
-Eleven years.
-Well...
Here it is.
-I'm hungry.
-Me, too.
You have two siblings?
Yes, I'm the youngest.
-Do you have siblings?
-I have three.
-Three?
-Yeah.
I have an older brother,
and a younger brother and sister.
You're the youngest,
so you're probably a crybaby.
When I'm really stressed, I cry.
Do you cry a lot?
-I cry easily.
-Really?
-I cry watching movies.
-Me, too.
What kind of movies do you like?
I really like sad Japanese movies.
-Really?
-I love them.
I also like Japanese movies.
Nice. Let's watch a movie.
I'll rent one.
-Bon appétit.
-Your goal is similar to Yuya's.
-Yeah.
You should help Yuya.
Teach him what you know.
I'll totally help him.
I'm still a newbie, too.
-It's been two and a half months?
-Yeah.
You haven't fallen for anyone?
-No, I haven't.
-You haven't?
Was the timing not right?
It wasn't the timing.
Everyone just became a good friend.
I'm full. It's surprisingly filling.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, take your time.
You have a beautiful face.
I mean...
That's not fair!
Do you guys talk about relationships?
With other guys? We do.
I used to talk to Eric.
About what?
Like...
if there are places
you wouldn't know about.
Places I don't know?
I do live here.
Wanna stretch?
-I have a leg cramp.
-Are you okay?
I'll help you.
Face up. Face up. Yeah.
Ow!
Just give me one leg then.
-Does this hurt?
-It doesn't hurt.
I feel like Cinderella.
Okay. Does it still hurt?
No.
Do you have plans for Christmas?
No plans yet. Just one party.
Really?
Want to go somewhere?
A Christmas date.
On the 24th or the 25th?
-Do you have school?
-If it isn't a weekend, I'll have school.
But you'll be off for Christmas, right?
Let's go out on a date.
A Christmas date.
Where?
Where do you want to go?
I thought we could decide together.
I don't know. I can't think of anything.
I'll come up with some options.
What would be good?
I want to have Christmas dinner.
You're thinking so hard about it.
But I can't think of a good place.
You're leaving everything to me.
Well...
Let's do some research.
Let's research.
Close.
-This is bad.
-That was rough.
Oh, no!
-This is rough, right?
-Oh, no!
-Attention please.
-Yes, teacher.
While you were all talking...
Avian said something important.
I don't know if she pulled her muscle,
but you all saw the stretching scene.
She said, "I feel like Cinderella."
Then she went with the flow
and said in English,
"I'm your Cinderella."
He made a perplexed face
and then put her foot down.
He obviously looked troubled.
Obviously, Yuya is having
a change of heart.
-Right when we were all fooling around?
-Yes.
She asked him out on a Christmas date.
-But he wasn't into it.
-He wasn't answering.
I'm sure you've all experienced it.
When you're not into it, you don't talk.
It was exactly that.
-I sort of know how Yuya feels.
-What do you mean?
When you like an older woman,
it's good while you're the one chasing.
To have her suddenly become that into you
the way Avian is with Yuya,
you would be taken aback a bit.
That's why during dinner,
when she was like,
"Let's play basketball,"
-he seemed like he wasn't into it.
-Yes, that's right.
That's scary!
The chances are low
that Anna has anything to do with it,
but there's a little of that.
Love that began as a chase
needs to continue as a chase.
I see.
So she should act like she isn't into him.
Women always fall into that trap.
I'm telling you, it's stupid.
And you can't sleep with them.
Look who's talking.
-He'll get worse.
-Tuberculin.
Tuberculin?
I haven't heard that in a while.
-An old-school shot.
-Yes.
The one that hurts.
-Well, we still don't know.
-We don't know.
This is all in our imagination.
And during all this...
Tamaki and Lauren are looking good.
He's good. He just throws it in
and tells her she's beautiful.
Yes, he stares at her awhile.
As she's eating, she looks up and is like,
"Oh, I'm sorry. I'll be quick."
"Oh, no, it's not that.
I was thinking about
how beautiful you are."
-Like that.
-He's leaving it open.
And the way Lauren is embarrassed...
He's very smart, isn't he?
-He is.
-And it's not in a lewd way.
He keeps it light and easy.
His boss from the sushi place
did compliment him before he came.
He said he's seen many people,
but Taishi was serious and good.
He's serious and he's got
the likeableness of Okinawans.
-The friendliness.
-Yes, the friendliness.
It's refreshing.
When is the pop-up store opening?
-When will the store be done?
-It's been forever!
-Cheers.
It's good.
-Did you look for a job today?
-No.
I had lunch with Lauren.
You did? Did you have fun?
I did, but I was tired today.
You were practicing kendo in the morning.
It's not kendo.
-You were practicing?
-No, just part of my daily routine.
-In the morning?
-Yeah, it feels good in the morning.
-I'm so full.
-What about Yuya?
He's sleeping downstairs.
Did he go surfing today?
-I wonder.
-He said he was going.
-Where did Avian go?
-I don't know. Back to her room?
-I'm going to go.
-Okay.
-Yes?
-Can I come in?
Come in.
I was wondering what you're up to.
-I was just checking an email.
-Really?
-It's spacious.
-Isn't it?
This is Anna's.
-I'm here and Lauren's there.
-I see.
So this is the girl's room.
-Yes.
-It's so clean.
-Sit down. Here's a cushion.
-Okay.
Wherever you want.
I was wondering what you're doing.
I was just going through my emails.
-Thanks for cooking and the beer.
-Oh, no problem.
I seriously wanted a drink.
I went to Costco with Lauren, so...
I'll pay you later.
-You're working tomorrow, too?
-Yes, tomorrow, too.
Starting at 10:00 in the morning.
-Can I come visit?
-Sure.
-Come.
-Is there a good time?
-Noon.
-Noon?
-Is that okay?
-It's good.
We could get lunch,
and you can show me around Waikiki.
Okay, what do you want to eat?
I had loco moco and vegan food already.
Maybe pancakes?
You probably don't want that for lunch.
-That's okay.
-Are you sure?
Is there a place? I'll look it up.
-Can I leave it to you?
-Sure.
-I'm looking forward to it.
Tomorrow then. Pancakes.
It doesn't have to be pancakes.
-It can even just be tea.
-Okay.
-See you later then.
-Bye.