-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
There is no script at all.
The time has finally come.
After what happened last episode...
-What happened?
-Last time...
-Yusuke said he's thinking of leaving.
-That's right.
Wasn't that what happened?
-He only told Naomi.
-Right.
-Yes.
-That's right.
-Yes, it was a double shock.
-The other members don't know yet.
-Only Naomi knows right now.
-That's right.
Wait a second!
Who are you?
Excuse me. I'm Saito.
-I didn't recognize you!
-Saito!
-I've got this on today.
-That hides 90% of you.
TSUKASA SAITO
TRENDY ANGEL
90%? Only one tenth.
-Why are you here today?
-I really love Terrace House.
So I used my popularity,
told people how much I love it,
and then I was invited.
-Yay!
-I'm honored. I'm honestly very nervous.
Recently, I worked with Takeshi Kitano
and Ken Shimura,
but this is even more nerve-wracking.
You're making them feel bad.
I feel like I can't disturb this scene.
It's like getting my picture taken
at Disneyland.
It's at that level.
Have you been a fan since the beginning?
Yes, I have.
Do you have any favorite people or scenes?
Well, to be honest...
I've been asked in interviews
whether I've ever cried before.
The scene when Hansan is about to leave...
That's the most I've cried in my life.
-You're kidding!
-Your entire life?
-You too, right?
-Me too!
These two cried, too.
-You're right!
-Yes, it's true.
I wondered why the rest of you
weren't crying.
It was touching, right?
That was the most moved you felt
in your entire life?
-No way.
-It's the truth.
I downloaded that scene and have it saved.
-It's on your phone?
-So I can watch it any time.
-No way!
-You understand the greatness of Hansan.
For us, it's like, why did he come?
-It was so great, wasn't it?
-It was.
How about this season?
I love Lauren.
Really? You like Lauren?
I thought I wouldn't
since she seems so perfect,
but she's been showing
some vulnerability lately.
Her true self, you mean.
Yes. Well, that's a bad choice of words.
-Watch out for him. Careful.
-Yes.
Because of that,
she's slipped into my zone.
-She was on a pedestal...
-That's exactly right.
-...but became human.
-I feel like I might have a chance.
-She's been stressed out lately.
-That's right.
Sparks flew last time.
-Because Lauren...
-Oh, Thanksgiving.
I know you want to spend time
with your family.
We can have our dinner earlier.
I might get in trouble, but okay.
That can't be helped.
Then don't tell us you'll be in trouble.
Many people felt that she should've
just changed her schedule to begin with.
That's not true at all.
And then for her to say she's stressed.
Is that our fault?
And Naomi's farewell trip...
-They went snorkeling.
-That was nice.
Avian's bottom was very attractive.
-She does have a nice bottom.
-She does.
And between Yuya and Avian...
things have been going well.
Are your feet ticklish?
Stop that! Seriously.
I'm sleepy.
-On the sofa outside.
-That's right.
-They should've kissed.
-Yes.
-But he didn't make a move.
-He didn't.
And Yusuke will also be leaving
Terrace House...
-Only Naomi knows.
-He only told Naomi.
You're leaving
Terrace House tomorrow, right?
I'm thinking of leaving soon, too.
-Shall we watch, Saito?
-It's gonna start.
Thank you. Finally!
Naomi, I have to go.
Okay, I'll see you out.
The last time.
-Good luck.
-Yeah.
-Sorry I can't see you off.
-That's all right.
-Here.
-Good luck in Japan.
See you.
You're going to be late, Yusuke.
Go. Don't worry about me.
Don't worry about me. You'll be late.
Okay.
Have a good day.
Good luck.
-Thank you.
Keep in touch.
Good luck. Have a good day.
-I'm off.
-Bye.
I'm off.
Good luck.
-Good luck!
-Thanks.
-See you.
-I'm off!
-Have a good one.
-See you!
-Bye!
NEW SONG
INTRO
-It's better when it's bigger.
-Really?
-The pop-up opens on the 10th?
-The 10th.
-Can I come?
-Come! Of course.
Okay, I'll come.
Having someone to collaborate with
on Terrace House...
I was hoping for that.
-You're glad?
-I'm really glad.
I'm glad, but...
It's so quiet now.
No one's home when I get back.
Not to further put a damper or anything...
but now that we've collaborated
and the pop-up is opening...
I've finished what I set out to do.
So after this...
I'm leaving.
I think there'll be more opportunities...
once I open the pop-up.
-And you'll have your café?
-Yes.
-You're going to open one in Tokyo, too?
I'm sure we'll work together again
in the future.
Yeah.
I was hoping to meet someone
who would inspire me.
So I'm really glad I met you.
I'm glad I met you, too.
You're probably
the easiest member to talk to.
-Really?
-Yeah.
That makes me happy.
It's been really fun.
It really has been...
this experience.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
IZAKAYA TAKONOKI
-You're really leaving?
-Yeah.
I don't want you to. Really?
It's good timing.
I want to open the main café, too.
I want to focus on that more.
-Let's eat!
-Let's eat, let's eat.
When I'm with you, it's like I'm 18 again.
It's both good and bad.
Yeah.
I have the most fun hanging out with you.
We're probably similar.
Yeah.
You know how...
I said I was interested in Lauren?
The age difference is significant...
and we work together.
So I don't want things to get complicated.
And Yusuke went out on a date with her.
I think it was better...
that he went out with her rather than me.
What are you going to do
if the new girl is really cute?
Well, I really like Avian right now...
so I don't think it would matter.
Nice.
She's probably the least pretty
of the three.
But after talking with her
and getting to know her...
she's really pretty to me.
She's like an older sister,
but she can still put herself in my shoes.
And sometimes she'll teach me things.
-She affects me in different ways.
-That's good.
I'm glad we did this.
It's been a while.
-Let's still meet up even after you leave.
-Yeah, let's.
LOUKIE WONG
AVIAN'S MOTHER
HENRY CHAN
MERCHANDISING DIRECTOR
Hey.
How are you?
We said we'd come see the sunset,
but it's totally dark.
It's totally night time now.
This is nice, too.
There are even Christmas decorations.
-Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
You look different today.
Is that a compliment? Thanks.
-Is that a compliment?
-No, it's not.
This is really good.
You seem happy.
The food is good,
and I'm having dinner with you.
-Yeah.
-How was the talk?
-Good?
-It was.
-We talked about starting a bikini line.
-You did?
What did your mom say?
Was she surprised?
She agreed with me.
Would the brand...
be part of 88 Tees?
No, it'll be my own thing.
-I'll come up with a name.
-I see.
People always ask if I'm taking over.
When they do, it makes me feel...
-You don't like it?
-No.
I feel the pressure.
So I can't picture it now, but...
-But?
-When the time is right.
You're working at your mom's store...
but you have your way
of doing things, too.
So you should work on developing that.
Even if the bikini line fails...
I think you'd succeed with anything.
Of course,
succeeding with the bikini line is best.
Yeah.
-I'll be rooting for you.
-Thanks.
You're an active guy.
We're alike in that way.
We are.
It's partially why I was attracted to you.
Really? Because I'm active?
-Active people--
-I like girls I can work out with.
I see.
Wait, hold on...
Have you dated someone active before?
There has never been anyone
I could work out with.
I see.
I've never gone surfing
with a girl before.
Go ahead, eat.
I'll peel this.
Is it good?
-Good?
-Yeah.
-Are you full?
-We ate a lot.
How much?
I have...
Seriously.
Seriously, seriously, seriously.
Thank you.
Naomi left just like that.
Please pick up on what happened.
I'm sure they all talked at the table,
and they gave her a card.
Think about it as you watch.
Don't accept everything
at face value.
But it took her two and a half minutes
to leave.
How long have you been in television?
You can fall in love in two minutes.
-Who's talking big?
-Me, Saito.
And we got to hear Saito sing.
-Yes, during the opening.
-Yes.
How can you not sing along?
-I'm hearing it behind me and in my ears.
-It's stereo sound.
I wonder if Yusuke will write songs
about his experiences at Terrace House.
Something like,
"I cried salty tears over catfish."
Do you think he'll use the catfish?
The catfish I was supposed
To share with you
That's so lame!
It was a little too big
To have on my own
Nice!
Is it a folk song?
-It's a folk song.
-Like in the style of Kosetsu Minami.
-Oh, and Eric!
-Right?
He's the older brother figure.
The timing is right for him, isn't it?
Yuya made a pretty shocking comment
during their talk.
Hey.
I was stunned.
What did he say exactly?
I wasn't listening.
"She's not the prettiest of the three."
Does he really need to say that?
He's not a bad kid,
but his choice of words
-is too careless.
-Yes.
-It's hurtful.
-His words are too naked.
-Too blunt.
-Yes, too blunt.
He was just trying to say
she's fun and has a great personality,
and used those words with that purpose,
at least in his mind.
It's like "Not A, but B,"
like in textbooks.
-That's right.
-It's the real life version.
The switch after that was good.
He said he likes girls who work out.
-Then he said, "It's you," in English.
-That was good.
I think I'll use it next time.
-You will?
-Yeah, it was nice.
It's embarrassing to say, "I love you."
It's like how Soseki Natsume wrote,
"The moon is beautiful."
-How he translated "I love you."
-Yes, it was like that.
-Where?
-Seriously.
He hid his shyness
by switching to English.
What is this baldy talking about?
-What? I'm not bald today, Yamachan.
-Let's see, let's see.
-The moon is beautiful.
-Is it?
The moon is beautiful.
So your head is saying "I love you."
Yes, excuse me.
-There's the flip.
-Excuse me.
Well, there's a reason why I called
everyone here today.
-I wrote a song.
-Oh, really?
So I wanted you to hear it.
-Yeah.
-Wow.
Looking up
There stood a house of emerald stone
I took a step forward
Opened the door
And there were unfamiliar faces
Imagining my new life with the faces
I stared at the views outside
I had no faith in myself
I put on bravado
I've always gotten along with everyone
But after rethinking
And repeating and repeating
I've become my true self
I've become honest
And experienced more
Lived through the same moments with you
I want to thank you
I want to tell you that
My story
Still continues
It's about Terrace House, right?
-The lyrics?
-Yes.
What I wanted to say...
is that I'm thinking of leaving.
-Seriously?
-What?
-You're leaving?
-Yeah.
No way!
After I open the pop-up store...
I'm leaving, too.
-When it's done.
-Wait, wait. What?
When did you decide, Yusuke?
When Naomi said she was leaving.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-So early?
-When you two talked?
Me, too.
I felt like the timing was right
for me to take the next step.
Let's work hard.
When are you leaving tomorrow, Yusuke?
-10:00? 11:00?
-Probably around 10:00.
-Maybe 11:00.
-Okay.
I'm going to miss you.
You, too.
Is there only another week or so?
About nine days.
Thank you for cooking, Lauren and Eric.
-Bon appétit.
-Your parents are picking you up?
-Yeah.
I already know Eric's,
but what is everyone else's goal?
I've already mentioned it,
but I have a gallery show on January 2nd.
Really?
-I'm going.
-It's been decided?
Yes! Did I not tell you?
I didn't know.
-I told everyone it'll be at ARS Café.
-Around here?
-In Japan?
-Near Diamond Head.
-I see.
-On Monsarrat Avenue.
-So it'll be just your art?
-Just mine.
-That's amazing, isn't it?
-Wow.
Isn't a solo show uncommon?
Maybe, but it's only for two days.
I'd love to have my own concert, too.
Let me know if you're going to have one.
I would go.
Based on the way you were
before Terrace House
and the way you are now,
do you feel different?
I feel like the hesitation
is totally gone.
-Toward other people?
-Yeah.
I can say what's on my mind.
What would you say to your old self?
Talk.
-Talk?
-Yeah.
Stop hesitating.
-Good morning.
-Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Who made this?
-Yuya!
-Seriously?
-Yuya's scrambled eggs.
-It's really good.
-Seriously?
-We made this.
Seriously?
It makes me really happy.
-Let's hang out again.
-Yeah.
Keep in touch.
Thanks.
Well...
I'll get going then.
Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for the food.
Bye.
Bye! See you!
How are you, Avian?
With Yuya?
There's a big age difference.
-Yeah.
-How many years? Nine?
-Eight.
-Do you feel the difference?
It really bothered me in the beginning.
But it's fun to hang out.
I've stopped thinking about it.
Does Yuya talk about me?
Yeah, he does.
Like what? Am I allowed to ask?
Sure.
He talks about his feelings for you.
How does he feel about me?
I can't go into detail.
Why not?
-Why not?
-You can ask Yuya directly.
Directly?
-That's pretty tough.
-Why?
It'll cause trouble
if I miscommunicate anything.
I'm scared.
-About what?
-Asking him how he feels.
I'm not sure.
And there's going to be a new girl coming,
so I'm really scared.
That he might be into the new girl?
Yuya has...
pretty strong feelings for you.
Definitely.
I'm going to live at the Terrace House.
Wait, wait.
-Yeah.
-Really?
I thought I should tell you
since we live together.
I told you I applied, right?
You mentioned it.
-What made you decide to go?
-What made me?
-I've gotten used to the life in Hawaii.
-That's true.
To everything.
-It'll be something totally new.
-That's true.
Right? I hope I meet someone!
What kind of person
are you looking to meet?
I've been really into surfing lately.
So someone I could surf with would be nice
since I always go alone.
Muscular and tanned.
Mr. Shige, I've got something to tell you.
I know I'm quitting rather abruptly,
but I've been accepted
to the show Terrace House.
It's my dream to succeed
as an actor in Hollywood.
I'm currently getting a steady stream
of jobs in LA,
so to have to leave LA right now
is a risky move for me.
But for me to continue as an actor,
I think I need to experience
being deeply in love.
I want to have this experience
while I'm in my twenties.
It's been 30 years since I came to the US.
Working in this business,
I've met many waiters
who are trying to make it as actors.
From them, you're one of the most serious.
You should do what you can now.
I'm sure the next step will follow.
You should work hard.
If you should fail, feel free to call me.
-Thank you.
-I'm happy to lend an ear.
I'll be going to Hawaii to fall in love
for the last year of my twenties.
-Thank you!
-Thank you for your work.
-Did you hear what he said?
-He's 29.
"I'm going to Hawaii to fall in love."
-I can't wait!
-It's time for you too, Yamasato.
The love of a lifetime?
Go experience
the love of a lifetime in LA.
Only Ayabe's there.
Yusuke's announcement went as expected.
I want to see the lyrics.
-It was a little quick.
-It was fast.
It was a great song.
-He was like Scatman John at the start.
-Yeah, his tempo was.
He wasn't like that at all!
Eric didn't tell Avian...
-Of course not!
-Who would?
It was the perfect opportunity
for Eric to gain some points.
-In your view.
-Yes, in my view.
Like, "He said you were the least pretty."
It's not "Yay."
Seina would've definitely told her.
That's true.
Seina may have said it.
Yeah, certainly.
Like, "I'm saying this for your sake."
She would've said something.
Avian seems to have really fallen for him.
-She really likes him.
-It just happened.
At first she was like a big sister,
almost rooting for Naomi's feelings.
The age difference bothered her and
she said she couldn't keep up with him.
-But it happened.
-It did.
I don't understand women.
-Even you don't understand women?
-I don't.
No matter how many times I fall in love...
I agree.
I always discover something new.
And you?
I haven't reached your level,
so I can't say.
I live on air.
-You're a wizard?
-I am.
More so than Tokui?
When you're at Saito's level...
Yes, very much so.
Come back to reality.
He caught a cold!
-That makes you sick?
-So quickly?
I can see why he's popular
with the ladies.
-He's very popular!
-Really? Really?
-I was thinking what the difference is.
-From me?
-Why you aren't popular.
-Me?
You choose to go...
to the unpopular side.
-I see.
-That's his professionalism.
I see.
-You should take it easy.
-Be quiet!
He gets sick so quickly.
I'm gonna make you sick, damn it!
You're gonna make him sick?
Avian is realizing
how much she likes Yuya.
But when she thinks
about the fact that he's 18,
she must be like, "What am I doing?"
But they haven't told each other
how they feel.
Just as they're about to get together,
a new girl who seems to be Yuya's type
appears at just the right time.
She loves to surf...
She's got wavy hair like a surfer.
I think he'll go for her
if she's exactly his type.
But you never know.
What about the guy from LA?
Didn't he say this is the last year
of his twenties?
That makes him 29.
An older guy.
-He wants success in Hollywood.
-Like Yuya, he's trying to be an actor.
-She might go for him.
-She may like him better.
Or maybe Lauren will become interested.
-His face...
-I wonder what kind of person he is.
Either they'll show his face at the end,
or he'll come in,
but they'll only show him up to here.
It's going to be the latter.
As usual.
It's Saito's first experience.
-My first.
-That's exciting.
I'd like to enjoy the moment, yes.
We have a doorbell?
Open it.
We'll wait.
This is kind of embarrassing.
-Hello.
-Come in.
-Yes, thank you.
-I'm Yuya.
-I'm Anna. Nice to meet you.
-Should I take off my shoes?
-Leave your bags here.
-Hello.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Anna.
Nice to meet you. I'm Lauren.
-Lauren?
-Yes.
Nice to meet you. I'm Avian.
Avian? Nice to meet you.
What should I do? Can I sit here?
-Sure, anywhere is fine.
-Please, sit wherever you'd like.
-Whichever chair you like.
-Thanks.
Welcome to Terrace House.
-Are you from Hawaii?
-No, I'm from Japan.
Japan?
-But you live in Hawaii?
-It's been about three years.
Three years?
How old are you?
-I'm 22.
-22?
What do you do?
I work here, but I came as a student.
I work now.
Where?
At the sandbar. Do you know it?
-I know the sandbar!
-Yes.
-It's where you go in the ocean...
-Yes, in a boat,
and the sand comes up.
-It's beautiful.
-Yes, very beautiful.
I also work at a restaurant
in Ala Moana Center.
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
It's in the basement floor of Ala Moana.
I see.
What kind of guy is your type?
Well, I surf.
Do you?
I've only been doing it for two years.
-You must be really good.
-Not at all.
So I'd like someone I can surf with
because I always go alone.
-Then you've got friends.
-Really?
-We go often.
Where do you usually surf?
-I usually go to Diamond Head.
-Diamond Head?
That's where Eric usually goes.
We go, too.
Oh, there's one more member.
His name is Eric. He's 27.
-He should be home in the evening.
-Really?
I'd like someone I can go surfing with.
-Let's go together.
-Yeah, let's go! I'm glad.
I always go by myself.
You already seem
like you're a local Hawaiian.
-Yeah, somehow.
-You look very local.
People always say my
Japanese is good.
I didn't expect to stay in Hawaii
for so long.
I thought I'd stay
for no more than two years.
But I love it here...
so I can't leave.
Do you--
-I'll go.
-Eric!
Eric?
-What?
-No way!
Seriously?