-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Let's see. Last week...
Taishi has been vocal
about his interest in Anna.
Yes, he has.
Well, I felt more with Anna.
I think she is the most similar
to the type of girls I have dated.
And Anna tells Taishi
she wants to talk to him.
-In front of everyone.
-Yes, so they can talk alone.
Thanks for bringing this.
Will you take it back?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
-I've got the coffee.
-Are you okay? Need a hug?
-Hugs are important.
-Thank you.
-The hug seemed even more like--
-That's right.
...if something's going to happen,
just let it.
The hug was like an attack.
Yes, now that we know where he stands.
But I noticed that
when Taishi and Anna were talking,
there was a shot of an iconic
facial expression we've all seen before.
There may be some meaning behind it.
-And Eric finally completed his pop-up.
-Eric left.
-And...
We have a new member.
-He came.
-Yes, Guy, who all the ladies like.
-Yes, they say he's cute.
-He is cute.
A pro surfer from Shonan.
Guy Sato, 20 years old.
How long have you surfed?
It's been 15 years already.
-Fifteen years?
-I've surfed since I was five.
Do you plan to surf here?
Yes, I plan to attack the big wave.
-The pipeline?
-How cool!
-My sponsor's house is right in front.
-Oh, Volcom!
-Volcom house!
-Oh, Volcom.
When did you start competing?
When I was about seven or eight.
His relaxed demeanor is cute
because he is a pro.
-Having that foundation is important.
-It is.
You're more persuasive
when you have a solid foundation.
And... Oh, that's right...
-Yuya and Avian.
-That was painful.
What? It was nice.
We found out that Yuya was cold to Avian
because he was embarrassed about
his true feelings for her.
He really likes her.
But I was embarrassed.
I was cold to her out of embarrassment.
I know what you mean.
But it's already Christmas.
I'm hoping to tell her how I feel now.
-But he gets embarrassed easily.
-Yuya?
His words can be harsh,
but he's just hiding his embarrassment.
He's sweet.
But what will you do
if Yuya asks you to go steady tomorrow?
-He won't.
-Why?
He won't.
For some reason,
Avian doesn't think he'll say anything.
Because she knows Yuya so well,
she thinks he'll be too embarrassed
to say anything on Christmas.
-She knows him well.
-She really understands him.
-Only Avian would understand.
-Right?
That he was just embarrassed.
Naomi must be watching Netflix
saying, "What?
What? With that attitude?
That's ridiculous! I've left already!"
-We'll see the date and maybe Guy surfing.
-I want to see that!
The skills of a pro.
But Guy...
With Taishi saying he's interested in Anna
and Yuya and Avian getting together...
"Lauren, let's eat rice balls."
I don't know if he'll be able to ask her.
You're treating him
like he's Winnie-the-Pooh!
-"I want some honey."
-"I want to eat some honey."
He's starting to look like him!
-We'll get to see Christmas Guy.
-Yes, Christmas Guy.
-I want to see that!
-Me, too!
I want to see all the versions of Guy!
-Guy!
-Tai!
TAI VANDYKE
HOUSE MANAGER
GUY SATO, 20 YEARS OLD
PRO SURFER
BEGAN SURFING AT AGE 5
PASSED PRO EXAM AT AGE 15
'12 GRADUATED JUNIOR HIGH
'15 GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL
RANKED 15TH AT 2016 JAPAN PRO SURF TOUR
LAST RELATIONSHIP: ONE MONTH AGO
Keys?
I guess we don't have to lock it.
-What about the keys?
-They're in the car.
-Thank you.
-Go ahead.
Off we go!
-Let's go.
-Etiquette is important.
-Now I'm ready to kiss someone.
-You are.
-I can kiss someone now.
Wow. They have places like this in Hawaii?
-I feel like I'm in Disneyland.
-It's totally different.
I think I'm gonna fall.
-You're nervous, aren't you?
-I'm going to fall. I don't want to fall.
It's okay if you fall.
-Would it be embarrassing?
-It would.
-It would be embarrassing.
This is embarrassing.
Why?
I don't know.
You are shy!
Your face is so red!
-Your face is red.
-Is it red?
-You're nervous, aren't you?
-I am.
Nice. That's cute.
No!
Why?
This is so embarrassing.
It's fine.
Come sit here.
I'll sit there.
Thank you.
Thanks for inviting me today.
It's not often I get to spend Christmas
on a date with someone I like.
It's really nice.
-I was really worried.
-Why?
I was worried you liked someone else.
You don't have to worry about that.
My feelings won't change.
I couldn't have known that.
Anna may have arrived,
but I like you. That hasn't changed.
It still hasn't changed.
-I was worried, though.
-It was the same for me.
-Really?
-I was really worried.
I like you.
This is embarrassing.
Want some bread?
-Want some more bread?
-I'll have some more.
I like you.
I can't handle someone saying that
to my face.
But me, too. Thank you.
That makes me happy.
-Why are you embarrassed?
-It's embarrassing.
The fact that I like you won't change.
I've liked you from the start.
That hasn't changed.
And it won't change.
Okay.
Why are you telling me this?
I realized I haven't told you.
Yeah.
It makes me really happy
that you're telling me how you feel.
There were times when I was like...
"Why is he acting like this?"
-But I wasn't sure if I should ask.
-I was just embarrassed.
That's what I thought.
It wasn't how I really felt.
Thank you for telling me.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
GUY SATO, 20 YEARS OLD
PRO SURFER
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
I'm so full.
Should we take the rest home?
I'll toast the pizza tomorrow
for breakfast.
-Do you mind if I use the restroom?
-Go ahead.
Not yet.
-They haven't brought it.
-I struggled to find the restroom.
Really?
You know how we said
we'd exchange Christmas presents?
I brought your present today.
Seriously?
Open it. Here.
Thank you.
It's not.
-It's not?
-Open it.
What is it?
A jacket?
You know Kanye, right?
Kanye? Seriously?
-Yeah.
-It's Kanye's?
-It's from Kanye's concert.
-No way!
Thank you.
Oh, wait.
Wait, is it not in there?
It's there? Good.
And shoes, for you.
I can get a pair with this?
Yeah, of course. It's a gift certificate.
Wow, I'll go buy some.
-You didn't forget, did you?
-What?
Did you forget my present?
-You didn't get me a gift, did you?
-I only got the Secret Santa gift.
I knew it!
You're horrible!
-You forgot?
-It's not that I forgot.
Right?
Do you remember?
-You don't remember?
-When did we talk about it?
We said we'd exchange gifts.
No, we didn't.
-You don't remember?
-We didn't.
-When did we talk about it?
-When we went surfing.
You don't remember.
It's fine, but...
-You look so disappointed.
-Thanks for dinner.
You're so disappointed.
Why did it have to end like this?
It's okay. Let's go.
This way.
-Which is it? Did he really forget?
-He's done it now!
-I don't think so.
-It seems like...
Maybe he'll give it to her later,
when they're looking at the city lights.
He totally forgot.
-I don't think so.
-I think he really forgot.
There's still the car ride home.
-No, I think he forgot.
-Right, Torichan?
-You think so?
-Seriously?
The Secret Santa he mentioned
is a gift exchange with everyone.
-Oh! So that's what...
-What?
She said, "That's all you remembered?"
He only remembered
the gift exchange with everyone.
Yes, he only bought the gift for that.
So the gift exchange
between the two of them...
-He didn't get her a gift.
-He forgot about that.
-I think he has a gift for her.
-He definitely doesn't.
I want to bet on him having one.
I want to believe that.
-He definitely has one.
-Oh, this is...
What a great show!
This is what I'm talking about!
What's the point of watching someone
win all the time?
This is what I'm talking about!
Before that, they just kept saying
how they felt about each other.
-They kept saying it.
-They kept repeating it.
There wasn't just one confession.
It was never-ending.
They were like a broken record.
It wasn't like the big wham
from Taiko: Drum Master,
but the non-stop repetitive drumming.
-Like the yellow bar.
-Yeah, when you keep drumming.
Like when you keep repeating combos.
It's funny, isn't it?
When you like someone so much...
and you didn't get a present
when you were expecting one...
I guess you would be upset.
Of course you would be upset!
"I like you."
She said it twice. She really likes him.
But she still got upset.
-This is really bad.
-I think he got her a gift.
Kentaro still thinks
Yuya has something prepared.
He went to the bathroom for a while
and said he got lost.
He has to have something up his sleeve.
-No way! Right, Torichan?
-Let's watch.
He was just embarrassed about
taking a dump.
-That's why he left?
-Stop it!
-Should we make a toast?
-Yeah.
-It's good.
-The apple cider is good.
-The pumpkin soup is so good. It's sweet.
-It's delicious.
-It's so good.
-It's tasty, isn't it?
What did everyone do on Christmas Eve?
I slept. I had a cold.
Totally asleep.
You went on a date in the morning.
-You did?
-With who?
With Guy.
I'm just kidding.
-The two of us.
-You said it.
It was fun.
-We were carefree.
-A carefree date?
We'll finally all surf together tomorrow.
Finally.
Our schedules never worked.
-The waves were good today.
-They were pretty rough.
-They were, but...
-The shower didn't work today.
-Yeah. What was that about?
-The faucet was stuck. Right?
-I didn't shower.
-Me neither. It was covered in bees.
Did honey come out?
Of course not.
Why would honey come out the shower?
-Because there were bees.
-There were bees.
Because there were bees,
there's honey in the shower?
-You're from a different planet, Guy.
-Seriously!
-He's a mystery.
-I like Guy's planet.
-Guy's planet is great.
-Isn't it?
Did you all prepare gifts?
-We put them there.
-Did everyone?
-I put mine.
-Me, too.
It looks so good! It's so cute!
I'll wash the dishes.
-We can all do it.
-Really? Please do.
Wait, you guys.
That's fine with me.
Don't you want to jump in and volunteer?
-No one did.
-You can do it.
-Taishi, you don't want some?
-I'll have a bite.
-Have more. Here's the Santa.
-Thank you.
Bon appétit.
-Please eat it.
-I can't bring myself to eat that.
Let's do the Secret Santa.
How do we do it?
-We'll all look for our names.
-One person at a time.
-One person at a time?
-Guy, you can go find yours first.
-I found it!
-Two?
-There are two?
-There are two.
-You have so many, Guy.
-Maybe there are more.
-More?
-There could be. Look!
The same wrapping paper must be...
Wait, you had three Secret Santas?
-What is it?
-What could it be?
- A bathing suit?
-A Hawaiian shirt maybe.
-There's something else here.
-Wow, so many.
-What's that?
-Sunscreen?
-Oh, it's sunscreen.
-Oh, wow.
-I'm so happy.
-It's the kind you put on your face.
-I totally wanted this.
-It's nice. So cool.
-This is great for surfing.
-Thank you. Who's it from?
We can't say yet.
-Next up.
-Anna.
Perfume?
-What's that?
-Wait.
Oh, wait. This is definitely...
-And a bookmark.
-Someone knows I like to read.
-So it's not from Guy.
-It's not Guy.
This isn't oil, right? It smells so good.
Oh, I know, I know.
You put this in and it smells good.
Thank you!
What's this? I'm so happy!
-What is it?
-A soccer ball! I'm so happy!
-I'm so happy!
-We can all play soccer.
I'm so happy with my soccer ball.
Insane.
-We can play soccer.
-I'm so happy. I really wanted one.
He totally had his reaction planned.
-I didn't!
-You're an actor!
-The single tear.
-Wow.
I'm so happy.
-We can play soccer.
-Yeah, let's play. I'm so happy.
-That's nice wrapping.
-Wow. It's pretty.
The pattern's like a zebra.
It's perfume!
It's Chanel. It's Chanel!
-It's next level.
-Who's it from?
-Wow.
-That's a grand slam.
-And it's the one I use.
-I see.
-It's what you use?
-Are you almost out?
-I have to take a picture of Lauren.
-What's this?
-What is it?
-This is so cute!
It's a cute pencil.
Oh, it's cute!
-It's so cute!
-Nice!
-Her modelling switch came on.
-Her face is on.
Nice.
-It's cute.
-You can use it when you draw.
-Right? That's true.
-Oh, wow! Insane.
-What?
Sunscreen, hair wax, snacks...
Wow, so handpicked.
-Amazing.
-Wow, very original.
-There's lots of stuff in there.
-And the wrapping...
-Let's start with Guy.
-Who do you think it's from?
-Avian.
-You're right.
-Who is it?
-Taishi?
You got it.
-Thank you.
-You got it on one try.
We talked about books,
-so I figured it was him.
-Yeah, she didn't have a bookmark.
Lauren?
I told Lauren I play soccer.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
-Wow, a soccer ball.
-I'm so happy.
-I'm glad.
-Yes.
-Yuya.
-Yeah, it's from me.
This is from Guy.
That was quick. Really quick.
-Does it have lenses?
-No.
Thank you.
-From Avian. Right?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-Should we take out the trash?
-Yeah, let's clean.
Let's clean up!
Avian, can we go downstairs?
Okay.
Where's the soap?
You're going to drink, right?
I can, but...
-You'll be fine.
-Maybe just one more glass.
-Let's drink. It's Christmas.
-Yeah.
You might have thought
I forgot about our promise yesterday,
but I never forgot about it.
I thought I'd give you your gift
with your Secret Santa present.
That was my plan, but the Secret Santa
was for the six of us.
I realized that the gift has more meaning
if I give it to you when we're alone.
So... wait here a minute.
It's wrapped weird, but...
Open it.
I'm giving it to you today because
I thought it'd be nicer to have two gifts.
I had you as my Secret Santa, too, so...
-Can I open this?
-Yeah.
It's so cute!
You know I like earrings.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
I'll put them on.
Maybe not right now.
I'm so happy.
That's supposed to mean "family."
-This means "family"?
-Yeah.
You're wearing one, too.
Yeah, I bought one for myself.
Really? They match?
Really?
This is the first time
I've had matching jewelry.
-Do you not like that kind of thing?
-I do.
-You do?
I'll wear it.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I should've given it to you yesterday,
but I ended up giving it to you today.
Thank you.
What?
I'm pleased you're so happy about it.
-Yeah.
-I'm happy. It's my first time...
It's my first time
wearing matching bracelets.
You can wear it on your ankle, too.
I got a looser size.
-I prefer the wrist.
-You'd rather wear it on your wrist?
-Can you make it tighter?
-Okay.
-Is this good?
-Yeah.
I'm so happy.
You know how much I like earrings.
-And bracelets.
-I know you like this kind of stuff.
Thank you for the perfume, too.
I'll trim it for you later.
-I'll get scissors.
-Okay.
Thank you. It's cute.
Thank you.
-That's a cute board.
-Right?
-Yeah, here.
-Is it called Fish-something?
It's so short.
-What? My height?
-Your board's so short.
-Thanks for waiting.
-Thank you.
-Bon appétit.
That looks good. Are you mixing it?
-Want some?
-Yeah.
Too bad!
-Bon appétit.
-I'll share. I'll share.
Did you notice their wrists?
-I asked her about it earlier.
-What?
I just noticed you had matching bracelets.
-I gave it to her yesterday.
-It's super cute.
-Does that mean the two of you...
-Are in a relationship?
-We're not in a relationship.
-You're not?
-Why not? Why are you not?
-What about it?
I'm being blunt.
-I want to take things slow.
-Why?
-You're really pushing.
Because we've only recently
gotten to know each other better.
Why leave things undefined?
Why do we have to be in a relationship
just because we like each other?
Don't you want to be?
What does it really mean
to be in a relationship?
-If I may ask?
-He's getting all worked up.
-What's a relationship?
-Are you getting mad?
I'm not mad.
I'm not mad. I'm just wondering
what defines a relationship.
-What does it mean for you?
-I don't like undefined relationships.
If you like each other
and you're together,
but you don't clarify your relationship,
then for me, it's like, "What is this?"
I just want to spend time
with the person I like.
That's nice.
I agree.
We're on the same page about that.
Really? I'm glad.
Lauren, are you using my pencil?
-What?
-Are you using my pencil?
Not yet. It's too nice to use.
When are you doing an exhibit in Japan?
-An exhibit in Japan?
-Oh, not Japan. Hawaii.
In one week.
-In Hawaii?
-In one week in Hawaii.
-That's why you're working furiously.
-Yeah.
Maybe I'll go to your exhibit
to be inspired.
-It's in one week?
-Yeah.
-What's your dream?
-My dream?
Maybe that question's too broad.
What's your first step?
For my first step,
I'd like to have an exhibit in Tokyo.
So your exhibit in Hawaii
will be your first step?
Yeah.
Hawaii is step one
and Tokyo would be step two.
When you start drawing,
what do you think about?
I find happy thoughts are a little boring.
-If you were to draw them?
-Yes.
I see.
I draw a lot when I'm sad.
But I'm drawing now
because of the exhibit.
I'm not sad right now.
Surfing is similar.
Your feelings are expressed on the waves.
For me, your drawings are fascinating.
It's totally fascinating.
-What kind of guy do you like?
-What kind do I like?
I feel like you're not interested in guys
right now.
-Maybe.
-Yeah.
Thanks for the food.
What kind of girls do you like?
Me? Someone spacey.
-Spacey?
-Spacey.
-Someone silly.
-Someone silly!
-Yuya's asleep?
-He is.
-Really?
-I'm awake.
You totally have a cold.
I'm a sick person.
-You should drink this.
-What is it?
It's ginger tea.
-Thanks, but I already had some.
-But this is organic ginger.
-You should drink a little.
-It's okay.
Okay, thanks.
-Thanks.
-From Lauren.
Oh, from Lauren? Thank you.
Surfing was fun, even if I couldn't stand.
Anna was pushing the board for me.
-Did it make you happy?
-It did.
That's good. You look really happy.
It makes me happy, too.
-Why?
-Because you said surfing was fun.
-Yeah, it was.
-And it made you smile.
Of course it makes me happy.
But I wanted to have
a deeper conversation with her.
-It's too early. Yeah.
-Is it?
-Am I rushing things?
-It's too fast.
-Is it too early?
-It's only been a week.
-Am I rushing things?
-You're rushing things.
-It's premature.
-Is it?
-You are premature.
-I need to be more patient.
-Good luck with that.
-I know what I need to do.
-I'm sure Anna knows.
-You think?
That you're coming on to her.
I wonder.
I'm sure she's thinking about it.
Should I ask her out on a date?
Is it too early?
-You can ask for a date anytime.
-You think?
But don't rush things.
Yeah, I tend to become blind
to everything else.
He did end up giving her
a personal gift, but...
why didn't he give it to her on the 24th?
I think Professor Triendl
here had the right answer.
That's what it is. I think so, too.
Please tell them.
Maybe he forgot and bought it that day.
On the 25th.
He forgot, but he acted like he didn't.
It's like when you haven't done
your homework and say you left it at home.
And they like each other, but...
-Yeah, what's that about?
-They're not dating.
"Why do we have to be in a relationship
because we like each other?"
That's something Ozawa would say.
Ozawa... Only Ozawa would understand.
It's true, though.
"Relationship" sounds so formal.
-Don't you think?
-I agree.
-It's true. What is a relationship?
-What is a relationship?
-It's true.
-It's a verbal promise.
What's the difference?
He likes her. She likes him.
And even if Anna or someone else
comes along, he won't like them.
It's only Avian for him.
How is that different from a relationship?
It's not.
Maybe stronger rules?
Like you can't see someone else.
So it's better
to not be in a relationship.
If possible. For as long as you can.
It's fine if you're both fine.
But, for example, at some point,
the girl may...
If they sleep together
before they're dating
and they continue that relationship,
she might want to clarify
that they're in a relationship.
Like, "What do you want?"
We will come back to that issue.
We got a glimpse of Guy's world
at the beginning of the show.
-"What if honey comes out?"
-So cute! It's so cute!
He was truly Winnie-the-Pooh
in that moment.
We were all saying, "Oh, it's Pooh!"
After that,
he was eating something yellowish.
A big mound of rice with something yellow.
That wasn't curry. It was honey.
That was honey.
It would be nice
if he was there during a fight.
So cute.
He could stop a fight.
You can't get upset at anyone
if someone like Guy is around.
"I broke a dish."
"That's okay! It can't be helped!"
That's a little dangerous.
"I broke a dish."
When asked what kind of girl he likes,
he says, "Someone silly."
He'd be in trouble if he went out
with someone as silly as he is.
He seems like he really would.
There are couples like that.
Silly couples.
-Like they're from another planet.
-Yes.
I wonder if things will continue
without any major problems,
except for the non-relationship issue.
Since Avian and Shibusawa
are lovey-dovey,
Anna and Tamaki may be influenced by it.
But while Anna and Taishi are friendly,
there are shots of Lauren's
unhappy expression again this week.
What does it mean?
And Guy is just really...
-He's a really calming presence.
-Guy is just good.
Maybe when someone gets hurt,
he'll gently...
Maybe he'll comfort them.
"Do you want some honey?"
What if they say, "No, I don't!
That's not what I need right now"?
"Honey is the best for wounds.
Hold on. Oh, no. I ate it all."
It's been fun lately.
Terrace House has been changing.
-There are new members.
-Three of them.
Are you talking to them?
Guy is very... very interesting.
Surprisingly.
What about Taishi?
What? What's with that smile?
Well, I...
-You went to lunch once, right?
-Yes, we went once.
And you were Taishi's Secret Santa.
-Yeah, I had Taishi.
-He was so happy about the ball.
I really thought about what he'd like,
and I thought he'd like a soccer ball.
How do I say this?
After I went to dinner with Taishi...
Not dinner, I mean lunch.
I thought he was really... nice.
Really?
I... I can't... I'm embarrassed.
I haven't told anyone.
I'm too embarrassed and too scared.
Taishi's really sweet.
He's also very caring.
When we went to lunch,
he'd open the car door for me
and that sort of...
-He was a gentleman.
-I really liked that.
I like that kind of behavior.
But...
I heard that Taishi is already interested
in someone else.
-You heard?
-I did. From Yuya.
I talked to him earlier.
-We were talking earlier.
-You were?
Just a little.
He asked me what I thought about the guys.
I didn't say anything. I was so scared.
I just said, "Yeah, they seem nice."
You should go on a date with Taishi.
-No, I...
-You don't have to go on a date,
but I think it'd be good
to spend more time with him.
I do want to get to know him better.
The two of us haven't really talked.
What should I do?
Right now, I'm just thinking
I'll try to talk to him more.
That's what I'm thinking.