-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Tonight, Ken will be absent
due to a film shoot.
Saito is very passionate
about Terrace House.
-I get really into it.
-Yes, he does.
Being here really brings it out.
Oh, shut up.
Wow, it's blue inside. How stylish!
-Torichan...
-It's so stylish.
Did you not watch our bit?
-Last week...
-Yes.
-Let's see... Oh, Lauren and Taishi...
-Lauren and Taishi...
Lauren unexpectedly...
-She was cut down.
-Yes.
That's right.
-I'll put the piece up in LA.
-Thank you! That makes me happy.
I'll show off saying,
"My friend drew this."
-Nice.
-I'm glad.
-There wasn't a chance for her to talk.
-No, Taishi didn't let her...
-Taishi referred to her as a friend.
-He did.
-That was a little...
-He put up a wall.
And Lauren went to Japan.
Then Anna and Yuya went to lunch.
There's going to be a conflict.
What are your plans with her?
I haven't really thought about it.
I'll feel better when things are clear.
Why does it matter to you so much?
-It feels kind of unsettled otherwise.
-It doesn't.
On my end.
Anna is sticking her nose
in Avian and Yuya's business.
She's questioning their relationship.
Anna went on a horseback riding date
with Taishi.
-I'm starting to remember.
-Yes, Taishi...
-Taishi likes Anna.
-He loves her.
The date seemed really fun.
She even made a bento lunch.
He gave her an apron
to make the meal and everything.
-But...
-It seemed like things were going well.
I don't really feel that way about Taishi.
He's not your type?
I don't think he's my type.
Anna said she doesn't see him that way
and that he's not her type.
You've got to be kidding me.
Who the hell does she think she is?
-Well...
-It can't be helped.
It can't?
No. People don't fall in love that easily.
That's why when it happens, it's splendid.
You're so right, Saito.
We have no right to judge her.
-And then Lauren...
-Yes, she went to Japan.
-She reunited with Naomi.
-That's right.
I thought about asking him,
but Taishi is interested in Anna.
-I see.
-So, I think...
-I'm okay.
-You're okay?
-I'm okay. I...
-You won't regret it?
I think I'll be able to discover
my new self here in Tokyo.
In a whole new environment.
I think it's time to move on
to the next chapter in my life.
She said she'll be starting a new life
in Tokyo.
So she'll move to Japan.
She'll go back to tell everyone,
and then go to Japan.
I can't imagine
what will happen this week.
Right? Let's watch.
Things tend to happen
when people decide to leave.
OMOTESANDO, TOKYO
When will you be back?
Around the 21st.
You're here for work this time?
For work this time and to stay a week
to see what it'll be like...
So you'll be back in Tokyo again?
Next time, I'll be moving here.
So you won't go back and forth?
I want Japan as my base.
I see. So it's flipped now,
and this will be your home base.
I really want to start a new life.
ELLE GIRL ONLINE SHOOT
Looks good.
-You got really sunburned, Guy.
-That's what Yuya said.
I thought that right away.
-He's red.
-Yeah, Guy got dark.
-I want to see Guy surf.
-Yeah.
-Me, too.
-When?
-The waves will be huge tomorrow.
-No way!
-We have to go.
-Let's go.
-I've got school.
-You do, right?
-Too bad, Yuya.
-Yeah, too bad.
-You're all going?
-I'm so excited. Seriously.
-It's 10:30 already.
-Yeah.
I'll be going then.
-Going to sleep?
-I'm going downstairs.
Me, too. Let's go together.
What are you going to do downstairs?
-Work...
-Don't ask that.
-See you.
-Work hard.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I have hula in the morning.
Like... like that?
-Was that offensive?
-Yeah, a little bit.
-We should make hamburgers.
-Sounds nice.
We can make a bento lunch for Guy.
-To eat when Guy's surfing? Nice.
-Yes, we can go watch him.
I'll be cooking, too, not just Anna.
Gross.
What does that mean?
FUNABASHI, CHIBA
This coffee table...
and this shelf unit.
-For today?
-I want to buy those today.
-Yes.
Got it. Let's see...
I'll give you a list of your choices,
and once you're set, we can finalize
-and work out delivery.
-Yes, thank you.
The apron looks great on you.
-Does it?
-It does.
I love it. Thank you.
-I always wear it.
-I have great taste.
So, you're in charge of chopping.
-Like this?
-Yeah, as long as it's minced.
Wow.
No compliments, please.
I'll cut my finger.
I've done that before a lot.
You're much better than me.
Just chopping.
Amazing.
I used to do the prep all the time.
You're seriously very good at that.
It's just chopping.
I used to chop five kilograms every day.
-Really?
-It was part of prep work.
Sounds tough.
Nice.
You're the type of girl who can cook.
-Am I?
-Yeah, you cook pretty well.
No way!
-You've gained points, seriously.
-Really?
So, Avian...
-was saying she wanted to make cheesecake.
-Really?
-For Yuya's birthday.
-Nice.
-It's almost ready.
-Hey, hope I'm not interrupting.
-Go ahead.
-What'd you do today?
I did some job hunting
and then went to the gym...
and was on the computer.
-You've gotten bigger.
-Have I?
-Right?
-Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah!
-A little macho.
-I'm working on it.
-You've gotten so much bigger!
-I'm working hard.
Yes, you have been.
-Let's eat.
-Looks good.
-Bon appétit.
Someone's home.
What great timing.
-Guy?
-Guy!
-Welcome back.
-Guess he can have some.
-Want a hamburger?
-Oh, a new board.
Do you want a hamburger?
Hey.
One more time.
-Bon appétit.
It looks so good.
-Is it good?
-It's so good.
It's cooked through.
-This'll be in your lunch tomorrow.
-Wild.
That's right.
-I'm getting really focused.
-You are?
-I am.
-No way.
-Why?
-I'm scared.
-Scared?
You do seem different than usual.
You're not laughing as much today.
Wow, that's impressive.
It's life or death if you wipe out, right?
-Wow.
-It's crazy when you think about it.
People would normally be too scared.
If you wipe out on this,
you'd get hurt, right?
Let me see.
-Will it be like this tomorrow?
-Yeah, like that.
That's insane.
-He's really on it.
-Looks like Waikiki.
No, it's Waimea.
-That's Waimea?
-It gets like this in Waimea?
-You can tell?
-How can you tell?
-The waves are different.
-You can tell from the wave?
Impressive.
Like the color's different?
-The wave is different.
-The wave?
You're a different person
when you talk about surfing.
-You're not the usual goofy Guy.
-Seriously.
You're not goofing around at all.
-It's amazing.
-He has his game face on now.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
GUY SATO, 20 YEARS OLD
PRO SURFER
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
We're eating shrimp.
How are the waves?
-They're slowly getting there.
-Are they?
Are you nervous?
No, since they're still growing,
they may or may not get bigger
in the evening.
-So you don't know yet.
-But it'll get there.
Over there is the famous Banzai Pipeline.
Right. This area is for advanced surfers.
That's the pipeline.
-That's where it is.
-That looks insane. That's insane!
Wow, that's insane.
Isn't that insane?
-It's just getting started.
-It is?
-It's just starting.
-Really?
They're riding it!
-It looks so fun. I wish I could go.
-I'm going to go in.
-Are you leaving this?
-I want to go watch up front.
You guys are loud.
-We're too loud.
-We're being rowdy.
-He's riding it!
-He is!
-Amazing. Guy's on the wave.
-Wow!
That's insane. He's so cool.
-He's so cool.
-That's just insane.
There he is, Guy!
-Is that him?
-That's Guy.
He's so cool.
He's too cool.
-Go!
-He's going.
Insane!
-Wow.
-He's amazing.
That looks so fun!
Wow, there are so many people here.
Amazing.
-The waves are getting bigger.
-Wow.
It's huge!
-Is that Guy?
-That's Guy. That's Guy!
-It is.
-No way!
Wow!
He's amazing.
-The wave's huge! It's huge!
-Wow!
-This one's huge.
-Insane!
Isn't it insane?
It's big, it's really huge.
Amazing.
This is what everyone was waiting for.
-It's so different from before.
-Totally different.
-It's amazing.
-It is.
Guy was great today.
Did you take a video?
-Well...
-You didn't?
He was a little too far.
-You couldn't see?
-I wanted to see.
It's amazing for him to be able to
ride a wave that big.
What time is he coming home?
We didn't get to ask.
We left before him.
-You didn't wait for him to come out?
-No.
We decided to leave when the sun set.
I think he was still there.
Where's Guy?
-He's not home yet.
-I wonder if he's on the way?
Probably.
-Hey, Yuya.
-Hey.
I wonder when he's coming back.
It's the tournament tomorrow, right?
I'm sure. I don't know, but...
-What?
-Are you okay, Guy? What happened?
-Guy...
-What happened?
-What?
-This is a surprise.
-You all right?
-What happened?
-I ate it.
-Seriously?
Are you okay?
Seriously?
-I ate it.
-You're serious.
Are you okay?
-When?
-Seriously, Guy?
-Are you okay?
-Was it your board?
Are you okay?
-When did you guys leave?
-You should sit.
Right around when the sun set.
So after you left, there was a big wave.
Are you okay?
The wave came at me
and hit me in the neck.
Then my face slammed into the reef.
And... I'm not really sure...
I got really scared for a moment.
It was really scary.
Did you go to the hospital?
-I went and got a CT scan.
-Really?
You were allowed to go home?
Yeah, they said I could go home.
-Seriously?
-Are you okay?
It all happened so quickly.
The moment I went under, I hit the ground.
I got disoriented when I was underwater.
It felt like I was
on the verge of blacking out.
-Seriously?
-My teeth hurt like crazy.
-It looks rough.
Your face is really swollen.
-Your face hurts?
-It does. The wave went into my neck.
I heard the sound of my neck twisting.
-You got whiplash.
-Then I hit the ground.
I don't even know why my back hurts.
I know why my neck hurts.
I felt it twist the moment the wave hit.
-Is this the first time you...
-Yeah, my first time.
Really?
It's scary. I was scared. I came out...
and I cried.
-I was so scared.
-You could have died.
My body was shaking.
If I had lost consciousness...
It was dark, so...
I probably would have died.
That thought made me really scared.
What did the doctor say?
That you should rest?
He said to see how things go,
and if I have any problems,
I should contact him.
You might be in more pain later.
I was just scared.
After it happened, all I felt was fear.
I'll open that.
-Can you take a sip?
-I don't know.
-I wonder if we have a straw.
-We have a straw.
I remember seeing a straw.
Thanks.
It looks painful.
It hurts.
-Avian.
-What?
-Guy got hurt.
You can't just say "Yo."
Are you okay, Guy?
Of course not.
-How did I look though?
-You looked really cool.
Each wave is so powerful there.
And there's always a risk, but...
Surfing with all the pros,
I think I waited an hour
for the first wave,
and I was able to ride one.
That's how it is there.
So it takes time and focus
for just one wave.
I need to charge my phone.
-I'll do it.
-I have a tournament tomorrow.
-You can't surf in your condition.
-You shouldn't.
-I need to cancel.
-I can grab it from downstairs.
Should I grab the laptop?
I'll grab the laptop and charger.
-Guy, here.
-Avian.
-Here's ice.
-You should keep it cool.
Thanks. Where should I put it?
Here.
Just a little...
Can you send a cancellation email?
She types so fast.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys, for coming today.
I was genuinely really happy
that you guys came out,
that you wanted to know what it's like.
I'm happy you understand.
It was amazing.
I've been wanting to go for awhile.
I finally got to see you surf.
-We didn't expect this to happen.
-Right?
I guess things like that happen.
It's scary.
When the waves are that big,
you can seriously hurt yourself.
The way he described it was scary.
The way he heard it
when the wave hit his neck.
He said it twisted his neck.
So it came down on top of him.
-It's crazy.
-It's scary.
He said he could've died.
I'm glad he's okay.
He wasn't exaggerating.
I'm sure he really felt that way.
He said that his teeth hurt, too.
He hit the ground as well, so...
I'm sure he hit his teeth.
Where is the reef?
The reef is where the coral is clustered.
Yes, there.
Wow, he hit that?
That hard area.
-It hurts just to walk on that.
-That's right.
-That's true.
He looked really cool though,
when he was riding the wave.
He was. But while he was on the verge
of death, Lauren was shopping at IKEA.
The way you said that. That wasn't nice.
"I want this shelf." That's what she said.
Lauren is preparing to do her own thing.
Everyone mentioned this,
but when Guy was riding those waves,
the way Anna was reacting...
Is that just a, "Wow, he's so cool"?
Just like us while we watched.
Like, "Wow, amazing!"
Can women fall for someone
in those moments?
-Totally.
-Yes, of course.
I mean, Anna doesn't like anyone yet.
But for Taishi,
he's like,
"Let's make hamburgers together.
The apron looks good on you."
He's got that vibe.
He's ready to go out with her any time.
But it's a one-way street.
It's hard for a man to tell.
I'd think she was into me.
Me, too. If she acted like that,
I'd think I could go for it.
But what about when you
see how cool Guy is?
-Like how Taishi sees Guy?
-Yes, you mentioned that.
They're not rivals or anything,
but when your guy friend is showing off
how cool he is,
it's fine
because you're into different things.
But it gets to you.
So the best thing a guy can do
is to be even more supportive
and show how you're okay with it.
It's a defense mechanism.
So that's why he kept saying
how cool Guy was?
-It's a defense mechanism?
-He was yelling the loudest.
Wasn't it because
the waves were amazing?
Yes, but if you say it the loudest,
louder than the women,
-you protect yourself.
-These two understand.
-They really get it.
-They've got experience.
-It's not on purpose.
-I see.
If it were me, I'd say,
"Let's go home."
You're showing your petty side.
It's so romantic.
This is amazing.
-I've never been here.
-This is Sky.
It's beautiful.
Thanks for bringing me here today.
You seem different today.
What? What?
I've never worn a dress
in front of you before.
You should wear dresses more often.
More often? Like every day?
-Not every day.
-You'd get bored of it.
-I guess it's nice because it's rare.
-That's right.
It's so good.
It is? I'm glad.
I'm glad you like it.
I'll remember this.
I'll always remember this.
The day isn't over yet.
I have a gift for you.
Now?
-All of a sudden? Thanks.
-A gift for you.
Open it.
It says "happy birthday" on it.
What do you think it is? Can you tell?
Sunglasses?
All your sunglasses are broken.
You don't own any good ones.
-Try them on.
-I'm so happy.
Try them.
They'll be even better in the sun.
They look great on you.
-They do?
-Yes, they do.
-They're totally your style.
I'm glad. You didn't have a white pair.
When Yuya gets back.
-When Yuya enters the room?
-Yeah.
-When he comes in.
-Okay.
It's so cute.
We're back.
How disappointing.
-Welcome back!
-The poppers weren't that good.
Wow, this is so cute.
-Wow, nice.
-It's really cute.
-Thank you.
-Happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
Thanks.
-Happy 19th birthday!
-Thanks.
-Bon appétit.
Is it good?
-Is it good? Can I have some?
-It's so good.
-You're a good baker.
-It's really good.
I think it came out good myself.
-Why is your strawberry so big?
I took the one on top. Do you want it?
I can't take that from you!
You know you want it.
-You can have it.
-I'm not going to take it.
That's so cute.
-The swelling has gone down.
-Yeah, it's gotten better.
I'm all better.
That was really quick.
I'm actually going back to Japan
for a checkup.
-It's decided?
-I have tickets for the 22nd.
-The day after tomorrow?
-It's decided?
-Really?
-When are you coming back?
In a week.
They're going to check my teeth
and do a checkup.
-That's a good idea.
-You should go get checked out.
Just from other surfers'
past experiences...
Just in case.
Avian, do you want
to say something to Yuya?
-Avian...
-I love stuff like this.
To us.
I totally thought
he was going to kiss her!
I thought he was going to kiss her.
We were waiting for it.
Yuya, are you sure?
Do you want to try again?
Again?
Well, I...
-She's luring me in.
-She's totally asking for it.
-Oh, Yuya.
-Be a man!
-Really?
-She tempted me.
Nice. I'm getting warm.
-Me, too.
-It's so hot! It's hot!
I'm the one who's hot.
-Maybe we should leave.
-True.
It's okay.
-It's your birthday.
-Your birthday night...
-The two of you should...
-Really?
So...
I was wondering what we should do.
What we should do?
About our relationship.
I wanted to talk about it a little.
It's difficult to decide.
Because...
when I go back to Japan...
We're together all the time,
but suddenly,
we won't see each other at all.
We won't hear each other's voices.
I'm worried whether or not...
we can make it work.
-Long distance?
-Yeah.
My previous long-distance relationship
didn't work out.
I want us to be in a relationship.
Right now?
Yeah. I want to be with you.
You'd be okay
with a long-distance relationship?
It didn't work out for me before.
I've never seen long-distance work before.
I don't know.
I can't see how it would work.
I'll give you some time to think about it.
Hey. I'm home.
Welcome back!
She's got a lot of stuff.
-Oh, wow.
-Insane.
How did you bring that home?
-Thank you, thank you.
-I got it.
Isn't it raining? Oh, this is light.
-Are you okay?
-It's lighter now.
It looks cold outside.
-I'm sorry. I caught a cold.
-You did?
-I caught a cold.
-Where should I...
It's been a while.
-Is Guy surfing?
-He's sleeping.
He can't surf right now. He got hurt.
-It was bad.
-Really?
He got hurt on the pipeline.
-His face?
-He hit his face.
Is Anna at work?
-She's at work.
-I see.
-She's working late today.
-Really?
Oh, I went horseback riding with Anna.
-How was it?
-It was so fun.
-It was?
-Look at the pictures.
-The scenery is beautiful. Nice.
-It was beautiful.
Horses.
-Doesn't it look fun?
-It does.
That's all.
-Nice.
-It was fun.
I'm glad.
-How was the date?
-It was good.
-Any outcome?
-Outcome?
Outcome? I'm not sure.
I've been wondering.
I had fun and want to hang out
with her more.
But I'm not sure.
We did talk about getting drinks.
-Drinking might help.
-Yeah.
-You'd be more relaxed.
-I want to talk to her more.
Yeah...
The 19-year-old Yuya.
There's no difference between 18 and 19.
-It's the last year of your teens.
-It's almost your turn, Lauren.
In three weeks.
-What's going to happen?
-I wonder.
That was quite dramatic.
Avian said she wants to be with Yuya.
She couldn't do it anymore.
She said she wants to be with him.
-She said it twice.
-She did.
He doesn't seem to know what to do.
I think maybe Yuya isn't that into her.
To kiss her in that first moment
would've been a statement.
-That they're together?
-Yes.
I feel like that reflected
his lack of confidence.
-There's a bit of that.
-A little.
-Avian was definitely expecting it.
-Yes.
If he kissed her then,
he'd have to sign a marriage license.
-That far?
-But he's not ready.
-It would've been official.
-Would it?
The whole long-distance thing
sounded like an excuse.
Right.
It wasn't like he was really traumatized,
and he doesn't want to hurt her, was it?
It was just, "Well, it didn't
work out in the past, so..."
Yes, how are we supposed
to respond to that?
That's true.
After what he said,
their relationship can't go anywhere.
But for Avian...
he should take off that hat...
That really flashy one with sparkles.
It did take away from the moment.
When you give men time to think...
don't they really take their time?
Like, how long are you going to take?
She's mad.
-That's probably true.
-Definitely.
-Especially someone like Yuya.
-It seems like he's going to run.
-It does.
There was a time we all thought
he didn't have feelings for her at all.
He was just embarrassed then,
but is it different this time?
-That's true. That happened before.
-It did.
He could have been truly traumatized
from a past experience.
-He's always confusing us.
-That's right.
-I wonder which it is.
-Avian won't wait that long, though.
I'm sure she'll ask him again next week.
"So, what are you going to do?"
And he'll say, "I can't do it. I'm sorry."
-Then it would just end.
-Yes, it would.
I want to hear, "Then why did you kiss me?
-Then why did you kiss me?"
-"Why?"
-We want to hear that.
-Yeah.
I'd definitely take the sunglasses back.
That's true.
All of her gifts have been expensive.
It's not cost-effective.
-You're leaving for Japan today?
-Yeah, today.
For how long?
About a week.
When is your checkup?
The checkup is the day after,
and the dentist the day after that.
Um...
-What?
-Taishi and Anna aren't here right now.
That can't be helped, but...
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm going to leave Terrace House.
If I move to Tokyo,
I'll have new experiences.
I feel like I'll be able to discover
a new me.
So I'm going to move to Tokyo.
So you were really preparing to move
while you were in Japan.
After going over there...
I feel really motivated.
When are you leaving?
I haven't decided on a date yet,
but probably this week.
-This week?
-This week.
You said we'd go hiking.
-We can go on a walk in Tokyo.
-A hike in Tokyo?
A walk in Tokyo.
Yeah.
I experienced a lot here.
I got to know everyone,
and I was able to open an exhibit.
I didn't get to experience romance.
Avian and everyone...
So much happened.
It makes me sad.
It was three months, right?
Four months.
It was amazing.
I won't ever forget this house.