-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Saito is here tonight once again.
-Oh, it's Saito?
-Yes, I'm Saito. Yes.
I supply my own wardrobe for the show.
I carefully plan out my outfits
before I come on Terrace House,
so the ratio of the cost of my clothes
to my income is going up.
Are you going to wear those Ray-bans
during the show?
I was just trying to decide.
I was going to get your opinion
and then maybe take them off.
You look like a pro bass fisherman.
Last week...
-Guy, our favorite...
-Guy...
-The real life Winnie-the-Pooh.
-He's so adorable!
-He is a pro surfer.
-He looked really cool.
-We loved the contrast.
-We love how relaxed he is.
-And Yuya and Avian are doing well.
-That's right.
They had their Christmas date.
They said how they liked each other
pretty frequently during dinner.
The fact that I like you won't change.
I've liked you from the start.
That hasn't changed.
And it won't change.
I like you, Yuya.
However, Yuya forgot her gift.
I got excited when they started to fight.
-Is this good?
-Yeah.
I'm so happy.
You know how much I like earrings.
-And bracelets.
-I know you like this kind of stuff.
That issue was resolved though.
The issue is
whether they're officially dating or not.
-That's right!
-That happened.
They have don't agree
on what being in a relationship means.
-We're not in a relationship.
-You're not?
-Why not? Why are you not?
-What about it?
What's it mean
to be in a relationship?
-If I may ask?
-He's getting all worked up.
I'm wondering how
you define a relationship.
-What does it mean for you?
-I don't like undefined relationships.
-Have you had similar experiences?
-I've had a few.
-You're popular with the ladies, right?
-I can't say that I'm not.
So in your case,
when things start to go well,
what do you say when she asks,
"Are we exclusive?"
I'll keep it vague at first,
but it always ends up being exclusive.
So you go along with it.
So, in the past--
Hold on, please be quiet.
Hey, I've been doing this for 22 years.
What do you mean, "Be quiet"?
I'm sorry. Please excuse her, Tokui.
I was just wondering how many girlfriends
you've had in the past?
Ten, but I've been in love with more.
Does that mean
you were rejected by the rest?
-There's that.
-That's right.
That too, but you know,
there were "adult" relationships, too.
-You mean the one-night kind?
-Well, not necessarily...
But some relationships
have only one focus.
-Wow.
-Amazing.
Were there a lot?
It might turn you off if I answer that.
It must be a lot then.
I can't really say in front of Kentaro.
There was a good number though.
There was a program a long time ago.
Women who've had
relationships with Saito came on.
Yes, with a comedian,
from Tombo Entertainment.
-The women said he was very skilled.
-Oh, you mean...
Yes, I've been told I'm skilled.
-You're good then.
-At doing the deed?
It seems I'm skilled, yes.
I'm very service-oriented.
Look, look.
-She's looking it up.
-You don't know.
Maybe she's looking up
Tombo Entertainment.
-She's not looking it up.
-No, no.
-You're very popular.
-Yes, I think women appreciate that.
-Oh, it fell.
-Yes, it did.
-Thank you.
-Backwards?
Are you a professional gamer now?
You suddenly look like
a guy who flies a drone.
-I'm sure Anna knows.
-You think?
That you're coming on to her.
-I wonder.
-Do you have a next move?
Should I ask her on a date?
Is it too early?
And then Lauren and Taishi...
-Yes, her feelings.
-Taishi's impressive.
After I went to dinner with Taishi...
Not dinner, I mean lunch.
I thought he was really... nice.
And you were Taishi's Secret Santa.
I really thought about what he'd like,
and I thought he'd like a soccer ball.
I heard that Taishi is already interested
in someone else.
You should go on a date with Taishi.
I do want to get to know him better.
I'm happy someone
finally caught Lauren's eye.
-I'm sad though.
-Why?
-I really liked Lauren.
-Oh, you liked Lauren.
She has the look of love though.
I have conflicted feelings.
-You can watch love-struck Lauren.
-You're right.
If it doesn't work out
you can go save her.
That's true. One ticket to Hawaii please.
You're selling yourself so cheap.
-It's so pretty!
-It is.
Everyone seems so happy.
Excuse me. Hi!
-Wow.
-Amazing!
-Thanks for coming.
-Wow!
-Thank you.
-Amazing!
-Lauren!
-Thank you!
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-This is amazing.
This is amazing.
-Oh, thank you.
-Congratulations.
Thank you Guy. Thank you.
-Wow.
-This is amazing.
-Thanks.
-You have so many.
-Amazing.
-Yeah.
She drew this with the pencil I gave her.
The bottom right.
-Really?
-Yes, all with Guy's pencil.
-Does this piece have a title?
-This one?
Oh, no, that's just random.
The exhibit is called 18, right?
Yeah, the exhibit title is 18.
You came up with all this on your own?
-It's amazing.
-Thank you.
What does it feel like to share...
your art with so many people?
It's like having strangers read my diary.
Oh, it's like a diary.
-So it's really embarrassing.
-That's embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing. I'm so nervous.
Last time I was like this.
Nice.
I think anyone who sees this
would think it's amazing.
-Really?
-Yes.
I thought there would be a specific theme,
but the works are all different.
I don't have a set style.
-I just draw what I like.
-Nice.
Thank you.
Amazing.
I like that one.
-Does it have a title?
-I do have a title for it.
-Oh, you're writing it now?
-Yes, I'll put it up later.
Are you nervous?
-You're so nervous!
-I'm okay.
Nice.
-You're selling those over there?
-Yes.
This one...
or this one.
Thank you so much.
-Let's take a picture.
-Okay.
With you in it.
One more.
Thank you.
Thanks for buying that Taishi.
-Are you going to sign it? Oh, you did?
-It's already signed there.
-You must be relieved.
-It's finally done.
-How do you feel?
-How do I feel?
-I want to work hard on the next one.
-The next exhibit?
-Yes, the next exhibit.
-Is the next one set already?
I'm motivated to work hard
on my next art project.
-You are?
-I am.
Nice.
-Did you make a lot of sales?
-Not too many originals.
-You couldn't sell the originals?
-I sold two.
-Oh, you sold two?
-You mean the ones in the back?
-Yeah.
-You sold two? That's amazing!
-Really?
-That's amazing.
Do you have a plan for your next one?
I have a meeting with a gallery in Tokyo.
Oh, wow.
A show in Tokyo?
-I don't know yet, but I hope so.
-Oh, you might.
Oh, I have a day off next Monday.
-Really?
-For what?
In English, it's "Coming of Age Day."
Oh, the one in Japan?
On January 6th,
I'm going home for Coming of Age Day.
-You are?
-This year?
The 6th is soon.
-Yeah, on the 6th.
-Wait.
-How long are you going for?
-Four days.
What are everyone's goals for 2017?
-Did you think about it?
-Oh, right.
-I haven't thought about it.
-I haven't yet.
I want to have an exhibit in Tokyo,
and I want to work on my modeling.
And one more thing.
If I find someone I like...
I want a boyfriend.
Finally.
Nice.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
GUY SATO, 20 YEARS OLD
PRO SURFER
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
None of the boys are here.
-Can I ask you a personal question?
-What?
What is it?
-What we talked about--
-Did you enjoy your date with Taishi?
The one you went on earlier.
-Earlier--
-Did you two go out after that?
Oh, you haven't.
I had fun.
-I was just wondering.
-Was that a personal question?
I guess it wasn't that personal.
We did go to lunch together the first day.
But it was right after we both moved in.
I didn't really know anything.
But Lauren and Taishi went out
the next day.
-To lunch you mean?
-Yeah.
Did you have fun, Lauren?
-It was pretty fun.
-Pretty fun?
Did you feel anything?
What do you mean?
You know...
Did you feel like you connected?
Like you're a good match?
-I have fun with him. I can be myself.
-Good night.
-You're going to bed?
-I'm going to take a bath.
-Good night.
If he asked you out again, would you go?
I probably would.
That's vague.
I'd totally go, of course.
Just like I would with you or Guy.
-The four of us did go surfing.
-Right.
We should go when you have time.
-We should go get lunch.
-Sure.
-I have a lot of questions for you.
-Seriously?
-I'll save them.
-What do you want to ask?
What do you want?
What are you doing with Avian?
Yeah.
Since we live together,
I can't help but wonder.
I can talk about that.
-I've actually been thinking about that.
-Oh, yeah?
-The exhibit was cute.
-It was.
-Amazing.
-Wasn't there a lot of dark art?
What was the puffy thing?
There was a round penis
chasing a salaryman.
It wasn't a penis.
My daughter is watching this.
A round cat then.
-Why are you calling it that?
-It's not a round cat.
Taishi's behavior at the exhibit
was impressive.
At the beginning, with Lauren and Taishi,
while Taishi's looking at the art,
her eyes go from Taishi to the art.
-That was nice wasn't it?
-It was cute.
She really turned into
your stereotypical love-struck girl.
She is 18, after all.
She declared later
that she wants a boyfriend.
In front of everyone.
-She never said that before.
-Not at all.
The guys who left the house
must not have been her type.
That's not important.
It can't be helped.
It's sad, but looks matter.
It's not just about looks!
With Taishi, it's not about looks.
-It's not?
-We're all worked up.
-It's not the looks.
-Yes, you have a sad sense of values.
Right, Saito?
It's how experienced Taishi seems.
He's a natural gentleman.
-Every move he makes seems to affect her.
-Yeah, it does.
-The way he touched her...
-It was very subtle.
The way he touched her...
At that point,
Taishi already knows it'll have an effect.
Well, he knows, but...
I don't think it's like that.
-It's like, "It's okay, Torichan."
-It's just like that.
But for Lauren, it has a big effect.
I don't think
he's playing games with her or anything.
You don't think so?
He's doing it nonchalantly,
but I think he knows
her body is responding.
Hey, that description might be
a little much.
If she's already in love with him...
-Just from this one touch, see?
-Tokui!
-See, just from this.
Children and teenagers
watch this show, too.
-She's love-struck.
-Her heart skips a beat.
She's sensitized to his touch
because she likes him.
Everything he says and does--
So a guy can tell if a girl is into him
when he's with her?
I think Taishi would know.
To be honest, you know and you enjoy it.
-What? Is this Saito's experience?
-Is this your experience?
-You're on Taishi's side?
-It's like, "Oh, this girl likes me."
You see yourself as a popular guy.
To be honest, I've had that experience.
I'm sorry.
So you knew then that your actions
affected the girl?
Yes, and then I'd think,
"It's just as I thought."
Wait, is this back when you had hair?
Yes, but I experienced more
after I lost my hair.
-Wow.
-It comes from confidence.
And on top of that,
you have skills, right?
So, you're perfect then. Amazing.
-Amazing.
-It's not about looks.
-Lauren was really floundering.
-She was. It was cute.
She was flailing.
She was at her limit.
"Oh, no. He's going to know!
-Or maybe he knows already!"
-It's like a manga.
-She felt like everyone knew already.
-She's so cute.
-Bon appétit.
I'm leaving for Tokyo on the 12th
for about a week.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But I have work on the 19th, so...
That job you got is only for one day?
-Yes, one day.
-What kind of job is it?
Well, it's for a perfume
for their catalog,
their website, social networks, and ads.
Three shoots for that.
Really? A perfume?
Yes, but it's a new brand,
so it's not famous at all.
That's amazing.
Yeah, I'm happy. It's my first big job.
-So I was going to rent an apartment.
-In Japan?
Yes, I was going to start looking.
I was thinking
I'd like to move to Tokyo this year.
Is that already decided?
I'm not sure how it'll turn out,
so during that week,
I'll go to the meetings with the gallery
in Tokyo and decide after that.
-Your future?
-Yeah, my future.
If I feel like life there is not for me,
then I'll go to college.
What are you going to do though?
If you're gone for a week...
-I wonder what'll happen.
-What'll happen with Taishi?
It's a whole week, Lauren.
Yeah, a week...
Yeah, I have no idea what to do.
-Do you talk to him?
-I was hoping he'd ask me out.
But he hasn't at all.
So maybe I'll ask him.
How do you want it to be?
Do you want it to be a casual date?
I think casual would be better.
I think it's fine
to ask him out in front of everyone.
Like, "Hey, do you wanna go out?"
I'm sure Taishi is interested in Anna.
He is.
So if I ask, he'll be like,
"Wow, Lauren doesn't get it."
I don't think that's true.
I wonder how Anna feels.
Anna doesn't talk about it.
I don't know what to do.
But you don't really show...
your emotions to others.
-Yeah, I don't. I'm too scared.
-So, from a guy's point of view,
they might think you're not interested.
I've never...
asked a guy on a date before.
I've always been asked.
I think it'd be good
for you to take more initiative.
I'm going to ask him to play soccer.
We've been talking about it.
-You gave him the ball.
-Yeah.
When we are alone in the evening...
I'll ask him.
I'm full.
Thanks for the food.
I ate a lot.
-Oh, is that a video of you?
-Yeah.
I want to see.
Wow! Amazing!
That's impressive.
-That looks hard.
-Surfing?
The waves in Japan are small.
-What's this? Is it yours?
-It's Taishi's.
I liked it. It's like a checklist.
-What's this word?
-"Clearly."
"Clearly, in detail..."
-Can you read it?
-"Write it out."
"Set..."
-"A time limit."
-"For your goals."
-Are you teaching her?
-"If needed, more...
-"Detail."
-"...detail may be added."
-How are you learning kanji?
-Through LINE.
-LINE?
-When I chat with my friend,
I have to read kanji on LINE.
-You learn it just from LINE?
-Kind of.
-That's amazing.
-It's amazing.
What is this?
It's what I use as a guide
when I set goals.
It's a passage from a book.
-Why did you type it out?
-What?
-Why?
-I look at this when I write out goals.
-For my own goals.
-What kind of goals?
For example,
I have a goal to be in a Hollywood film.
So I'll set a time limit for myself
and I write a plan.
-Are you going surfing tomorrow?
-No, I have soccer.
Oh, right, soccer. I forgot.
What time?
-Soccer? 1:00 p.m.
-In the afternoon.
-Can you come?
-I want to play!
What time are you leaving tomorrow?
I'll go surf in the morning
and come back then.
Do you play in that field? I want to play.
But aren't you going to Japan tomorrow?
That's right. I can't go surfing.
I'm envious.
-The Coming of Age celebration sounds fun.
-I'll send a video.
Did it touch my nose?
You can have it.
-You don't want it?
-I'm okay.
That's an indirect kiss.
You made me pause.
-It did touch you, right?
-I don't mind.
She doesn't mind, so it's okay.
You have her permission.
That woke me up.
-Are you sleepy, Lauren?
-I am.
-I have to go to the store.
-You mentioned that.
-At this hour?
-Yeah.
Go, boss lady!
-I'm gonna go.
-See you.
-I'm going to change.
-Be careful.
-Good luck.
-Bye!
I think I'll go to sleep early today.
I'm going to retire.
Really?
-Anyone want water?
-Did Avian leave already?
I think she's changing. I'm not sure.
-Good night.
Are you relieved
now that the exhibit's over?
Yes.
How are things with you?
The surfing is going well.
But I want to keep up my motivation
in the long-term.
Everyone's working hard.
Taishi, too, with his...
-his plan for his goals.
-Oh, yeah, that.
That's really good.
Taishi is cool.
We spend a lot of time together.
-He's just really cool.
-Really?
He's funny.
Do you go to the beach?
Not really. I can't go too often.
-What about the mountains.
-Mountains?
-Sometimes, for hiking.
-Well, I'm always at the beach anyway.
-Do you want to go hiking?
-I love hiking.
-Do I want to? Oh, okay.
-If you want.
Okay, sure.
Yes! We get to go.
-I'm going to go to sleep.
-You are?
I'm tired today.
Then let's meet in the mountains.
Good night.
What time are you leaving?
-Soon.
-You are?
Then I'll go with you.
-Where would you live in Japan?
-In Tokyo.
The high is 12 degrees
and the low is two degrees.
-It's cold.
-Um, I don't know Celsius.
-I'm American.
Do you have warm clothes?
-I do. I do.
-You do?
I'll buy some more, too. New stuff.
Ready to go?
-Yeah.
-I'm going, too.
-I'll go after I eat this.
-Oh, you're still eating.
-I'm running late, so I'll say bye now.
-Okay.
Ow.
-See you.
Have fun in Japan!
-Keep in touch. Send us pictures.
-See you!
-Have fun!
-Yeah.
I'll be in Japan for four days
for the Coming of Age celebration. -Guy
We went surfing the other day.
Taishi, Yuya, me and Anna.
And we went to eat after.
And during the meal...
Anna really questioned us.
Like, "Why aren't you guys exclusive?
Why don't you define your relationship?"
She really questioned us.
She put pressure on Yuya.
He answered all the questions.
I wonder why she cares so much.
Anna's lived here for a while now.
She's lived in Hawaii for a while now.
Why does it matter if we're
in a relationship or not?
Why does it matter to her so much?
Maybe because it's you and Yuya.
But why do we have to be questioned?
Well, Yuya's not mad, but...
You know, he's...
It's something
I eventually want to talk about with him.
What's he doing after Terrace House?
Going to Tokyo and then LA?
I don't know. He hasn't said anything.
Could you have
a long-distance relationship?
If there's a set time limit,
like a few months,
and we have a goal
of coming back together,
then I can do it.
But if there's no plan, then I can't.
If it's going to be a relationship,
it has to be serious.
I don't want it to just end after a month.
-But you're enjoying it now.
-I am.
I'm glad.
It seems like you guys are doing well.
I'm happy about that,
because I've seen it from the start.
That's right, since September.
It took some time,
but Yuya's really trying.
-We live together, so that's...
-Yeah, you live together,
so it's different from normal.
Sorry, but you look like a panda!
-Maybe, I can't see.
-Panda!
-It's so hot.
-That was a long bath.
It felt really good.
Really?
Want to come over here?
That's me.
Should I set it for 8:00?
-Can you get up with my alarm?
-Tomorrow...
-Do you hear the alarm?
-Yeah.
-You do?
I'm hot!
You're hot? I'll take the covers.
It's okay.
It's so nice.
It's so nice!
It's the best time.
You're right, Tokui.
It's so...
The head...
He burrowed his nose in her hair.
-I don't know about "burrow."
-You do that when you really like someone.
People do that
when they really like someone.
Snuggling under a blanket on the sofa...
I want to snuggle, too!
I want to snuggle!
-I want to snuggle.
-It's nice.
-And as you snuggle...
-Yes, things are bound to happen.
Amazing. They're not even exclusive.
The two of them?
You keep commenting
like you're someone from the Meiji era.
-What?
-He's being a prude
about them acting lovey-dovey
before being in a relationship.
So for you, it's wrong to act like that
before you're in a relationship?
Otherwise, it's too convenient.
So if you have the exchange of...
"Let's go steady." "Yes, let's,"
then you can do anything?
But you can lie about that.
They're just words.
That's right. You don't understand.
-You see here...
-You re-positioned yourself.
You're like a high school teacher.
Like a math teacher.
What's important
is that they care for each other.
-That's what's important.
-Is this prep school?
And Guy asked Lauren out.
-What was that about?
-It's hard to say.
-He seemed interested in her.
-Maybe...
He communicated by silently
bringing a piece of fruit to her mouth.
That's like a zookeeper and a chimpanzee.
Like counting... One, two, three.
A smart chimpanzee...
And he can surf.
-Guy is so cute.
-He is.
He asked Lauren out and got a yes.
He said, "Yay, we get to go."
It means he was happy.
I know love can make you blind, but...
while he was saying "yay,"
she gave a big sigh.
She's young.
-It can't be helped.
-She's in love.
It might just be she was relieved.
At that moment?
He's a chimpanzee, so he didn't notice.
-He didn't?
-He didn't.
No, Guy was just like,
"Yay, we get to go hiking."
A walk with the zookeeper?
"Let's meet in the mountains."
"I'll be happy if there's honey."
"I'm going to eat it."
You imitate Guy
like he's missing six teeth.
We're just overflowing with love for him.
And we got a scene
with the two in the bath.
-That's right.
-It was cute. The girls' bath time.
It was scary.
Avian was bothered by Anna
questioning her relationship.
-Like, "Why does it matter to her?"
-Yeah.
It's amazing. Whenever anyone takes
an aggressive stance to her,
the way Avian reacts.
Isn't it really scary?
She's strong. She's very straightforward.
-Like she'll destroy anything that moves.
-It's scary.
But girls don't like
questions like that, right?
-That's right.
-We sure don't.
Like, "What right does she have
to say that?"
Also, maybe a part of Avian wants that,
but having someone else point it out
is frustrating.
-Bull's-eye.
-Yes.
"I understand Yuya's stance
and I was fine with it."
Yes, yes.
"What right does Anna have
to point that out?
Now that she's said it,
it's making me upset.
-And now I'm a little upset with Yuya."
-Ah, I see.
She was letting off steam.
I wonder what kind of talk
Yuya and Avian will have?
Will that situation become crazier?
It might just end there.
-Hey, Tokui!
-Tokui!
I haven't finished it.
-What's happening now?
-Right now? Um...
Riko and Terashima?
-This guy.
-Oh, that's right.
They just went on a yukata date.
-Did you watch all of it?
-Not all of it, but the interesting parts.
What do you think of holding hands
before dating someone exclusively?
I think anything is fine.
Do you like it when guys come onto you?
That's usually how it's been for me.
I'm not good at taking initiative.
Really? Yeah, it does seem
like they'd come to you.
A lot of them.
-I remember this scene. It's good.
-It's good?
-It's good from this point on.
-No way.
-I can't watch.
-It's scary.
I might have dreams about it.
Maybe a nightmare.
I'll save the rest for later.
How have you been lately?
Lately...
Lately, I've been preparing for Japan.
-You're busy?
-I finished the exhibit,
and now I'm preparing for Japan.
-How are things for you?
-Right now...
-Right now... well...
-What?
I'm thinking of asking Anna out on a date.
She's been all over Hawaii, though.
I feel like no matter where I take her,
she'll know more than me.
Well...
Anna seems like she'd like active things.
-Yeah.
-Something outdoorsy.
Right now I'm thinking of taking her...
horseback riding.
I think that would be good.
But...
-I'm nervous about asking her.
-Yeah, I'm sure you are.
Have you ever asked anyone out before?
Me? No.
-No?
-No.
You should.
It makes you nervous.
-Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
But...
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
You said your goal this year
was to find a boyfriend.
If I find someone I like.
Oh, you like guys with talent?
-He doesn't have to be talented.
-What kind of talent?
-Anything specific?
No. Someone calm...
and cool.
-Someone calm and cool.
-Calm and cool, huh?
I think you set the bar high
for who you consider to be cool.
Not at all.
-Someone older then.
-Yes, I'd prefer older.
Everyone's out late today. I wonder why.
Yeah, they're out late.
Want to go somewhere?
Go somewhere? Now?
-Sure.
-Okay.
-Where?
-The park?
-Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
-Okay.
-We can take a walk.
Let's take a walk then.
Do you mind if I go change?
-I'll go change, too.
-You will?
-It's cold.
-That's true.
It's been chilly lately.