-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe
how they interact with each other.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Tonight, we start a new season in Hawaii.
Terrace House: Aloha State!
-Hawaii was fun, wasn't it?
-So much fun.
We went, too.
It was the most fun I had on a work trip.
It was really fun.
I can say it with confidence
that I had fun.
-Hawaii.
-It was nice, wasn't it?
-It was.
-But on our last day, Yamachan...
-That's right.
He got lost at Ala Moana Center.
-It was, like, give us a break.
-Seriously.
That was the only hiccup.
Yu told me that I was definitely
the least eligible bachelor.
You're the number one bachelor right now.
-Yes, he's number one right now.
-Tokui is so sweet.
Every day...
he'd find out what's the best burger place
for us to go to.
-Yes, thank you.
-It's easy with the Internet.
-Yes, the difference was astounding.
-Torichan!
In Hawaii, I realized
how different men can be from one another.
-I got in trouble at customs.
-That's right.
And one time, I got lost...
-You got plastered.
-Yes, very.
You couldn't check in.
You opened your luggage in the lobby.
You opened all your luggage in the lobby
thinking it was your room.
-Did you check in?
-I did.
-What are you talking about?
-What?
-I did it for you.
-I'm sorry.
Yu and I went to the front desk together.
We said,
"That guy hasn't checked in yet."
-It was so late.
-They said,
"You're checking in at 3:00 a.m.?
Are you serious?"
It was so fun.
I was happy to be with everyone.
It really was fun.
Terrace House is currently available
in 190 countries, by the way.
Since it's been gaining popularity,
we have our first season abroad.
Twenty-four episodes have been ordered.
-I hope it continues further.
-Yes.
But how could Hawaii's clear sky
provoke any drama?
-It seems unlikely.
-Yeah, very unlikely.
It'll let them be more candid.
And resolve their issues rationally.
It might go quickly.
-Hawaii! I'm looking forward to it.
-Let's watch.
Am I the first one here?
Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Yuya Shibusawa.
I'm 18 years old.
-I'm Lauren Tsai.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm 18.
-You're 18?
-Yes, the same.
-The same?
-Yes.
-Nice.
The same, huh?
-Lauren?
-Yes, Lauren.
-Tsai.
-Tsai?
-Yes.
-Are you from here?
-I was born in Massachusetts.
I moved to Hawaii when I was seven
and I've been here for about 11 years.
You're pretty pale though.
-Everyone...
-You don't tan?
Everyone always tells me that.
-That you're pale?
-Yeah, I am. I stay in a lot.
-You don't go outside much?
-I don't really like the sun.
-Were you born here?
-I was born and raised in Japan.
-Where in Japan?
-In the Yokosuka area. Do you know it?
-I don't, sorry.
-You don't?
My dad is American.
-Oh, okay. So you're a half?
-Yes, a half.
Yeah.
I just graduated from high school.
I want to go to acting school.
-Ah, to be an actor.
-Yes.
So I'm trying to learn English,
but I know it'll take time.
-I see.
-Yeah.
I can learn here.
You teach me English,
I teach you Japanese.
-Oh, okay, please do.
-Please teach me, too.
Wow, there's a pool.
-It even says "Terrace House" on it.
-There's a pool?
Oh, wow!
I want to go in the pool.
-It's amazing.
-It is.
It's like a hotel.
Definitely.
Even for a hotel, it's pretty luxurious.
-Hi.
-Hi, it's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm Avian.
-It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Lauren Tsai.
-Lauren?
-Yes, Lauren.
-I'm Shibusawa.
-Shibusawa? I'm Avian.
-Are you half Japanese?
-No, I was born here.
-Oh, you were born here.
-Yes, born and raised here.
I've been here for both
middle school and high school.
I was on the Big Island before.
I lived in Japan for about six years
while I was in elementary school.
What do you do?
Right now, I work at 88 Tees,
a T-shirt company in Waikiki.
-I know it!
-It's my mom's shop, but I help out.
I work as a shop employee...
Well, I do other things there, too.
Like things on the web and stuff.
-How old are you?
-I'm 25--I mean, 26.
I just had my birthday.
Have you seen everything already?
-No, not yet.
-You haven't yet?
-Just the pool.
-Oh, you saw the pool?
-Want to go see it?
-Yeah, let's go.
Oh, this is the kitchen.
-Wow.
-Beautiful. I love white.
-It's all white.
-It's fully equipped.
Feels comfortable to live in.
This is nice. Looks relaxing.
You're right, the pool...
It's beautiful.
Hi.
-Hello.
Hi, I'm Eric.
-Nice to meet you.
I'll sit here.
Is that all right?
-Nice to meet you.
Where are you from? Hawaii?
I'm from Nishinomiya
in the Hyogo prefecture in Kansai.
Can you speak English as well?
-I can, but my Japanese is better.
-Oh, nice.
What do you do?
-For work?
-Yes.
I build furniture...
A craftsman, I guess.
That kind of work.
I'm also starting a café with a friend.
-Out here?
-Yes, out here.
Which café is it?
We've decided on a location,
-but we've only just started.
-You've just started?
Yes, on the interior and everything.
I'm a model and illustrator.
I'm not a professional yet,
but it's my dream.
One day I'd like to work with a company
that makes animated films or video games.
-When I'm done with modeling.
-Nice.
-I enjoy modeling, too.
-I see.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
We're expanding.
Slowly.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Naomi Lorraine Frank.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
-What's your background, by the way?
-I'm half American and half Japanese.
Are you from Japan?
No, I was born in America,
but I've lived in Japan since I was seven.
So I'm totally Japanese.
-So you came from Japan?
-Yes, I came from Japan.
-I landed today and immediately came here.
-Today?
Yes, I was just at the airport.
-Wow.
-And pretty much came right here.
Are you entirely Japanese
or half Japanese?
I'm half Chinese and half European.
I'm not Japanese, but part Asian.
You speak Japanese really well.
When I was 15, I studied abroad in Japan,
in Hiroshima.
I was in Hiroshima for six weeks.
It made me want to move to Japan,
so I studied Japanese.
So you pretty much learned on your own.
I'd watch shows like Terrace House
and read the subtitles.
It helps a lot.
It really helps.
-That's the best way to learn languages.
-Yes.
I lived with my Japanese mom,
so I only spoke Japanese.
So I stopped using English,
and now it's a little...
Someone's here.
-Oh, wow.
-A musician?
It's heavy.
-Hello.
I'm Yusuke Aizawa.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm Eric.
-Excuse me.
-Are you a musician?
-Yes, I'm into music.
You've got a ukulele.
That's a ukulele, right?
Yes, a ukulele and a guitar.
Are you from Hawaii?
I currently live in Hawaii,
but I'm originally from Tokyo.
-When did you relocate to Hawaii?
-About three years ago.
-That's long.
-What did you do in Japan?
I was playing music in Japan as well.
Apart from that, I was just a student.
I'm currently still a student.
-Over here?
-Yes.
-I turned 18 the day before yesterday.
-What?
-Oh, we're the same. We're 18.
-I'm 18.
-Oh, really?
-You're so young!
I apologize.
I'm 27.
-You're 27 and she's 26.
-I'm 26.
I'm 23.
So that means you're graduating
in September?
-Next May.
-Oh, May, that's right.
And after you graduate,
you're going to pursue a music career?
I'd like to continue with music.
I'd like to become a top-level artist.
So do you perform in Hawaii?
I'll go wherever I'm asked to.
Any plans right now?
Right now, I'll be going
to an award ceremony
for Hawaiian Music Awards Japan.
It's sudden, but I'll be gone
for a few days starting on the 29th.
How sad, so soon?
I released an album last year.
That album made it to the finals.
There was an online vote
that only recently closed.
I was waiting for the results.
The ceremony's actually in Ginza.
Wow, that sounds serious.
-Wow, that's amazing.
-It's amazing.
This group seems like fun.
Everybody does something different.
This is definitely gonna be fun.
-Shall we?
-Let's go see.
This is really amazing.
-You could jump in from here.
-It's beautiful.
-See, you could jump from here.
-That's crazy.
There are places to sit, too.
-I always surf around there.
-Behind that area?
Yeah. You can surf over there, too.
If you sat there and played your ukulele,
it'd be perfect.
-We can light candles...
-You could play here, too.
-It's so cool.
-Wow.
We're so lucky
that we can see this view every day.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
TERRACE HOUSE
ALOHA STATE
-I want to see everything!
-It's like teatime!
-Insane!
-Oh, my God!
What's this? This is insane!
Wow, so stylish.
-Isn't it?
-It's insane.
Wow, the pool!
There's a hammock!
I totally want to nap here.
-There?
-Yeah, here!
-It's cushioned and everything.
-Wow!
-Amazing.
-This is perfect!
Insane!
Wow.
-Is it cold?
-It's warm.
This is really amazing.
I've never lived in a house with a pool.
Super fancy.
-Our room.
-Crazy!
-It's so cute!
-Wow!
-What's this?
This is like a dream, like a kid's dream.
Wait, which bed does everyone want?
-Wow, it feels so nice.
-It does!
The view is super nice!
Which bed do we each want?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, no, you're first.
What should I do?
I'll take the top then!
-You're okay with the top?
-Yeah, this one.
-I want the bottom.
-Okay, I'm the opposite. Okay!
-Wow, the bathroom's crazy, too!
-A walk-in closet!
Wow!
-You can see the ocean!
-Oh, yeah!
-It's really like a hotel.
-Amazing!
And there's even a spa bath!
-It could fit the three of us.
-Could it?
-Let's try.
-We can totally fit!
-It's a little tight.
-It's okay, I'm small.
Insane!
-Amazing.
-It's amazing.
-It's connected to the pool.
-Wow.
I'm good sleeping anywhere,
so you guys decide.
I don't mind any of them.
-Really? Then I'll take this one.
-I'll take this.
You guys both immediately chose.
I'll take this one.
-You okay with it?
-I'm good.
You could practice guitar here.
-If it doesn't bother you guys.
-Not at all.
Sometimes I play
until the noise bothers people.
I'll think of it as a lullaby and sleep.
If you're able to sleep to it,
I'll be happy.
The girls out here...
how are they compared to girls in Japan?
They're more assertive. It's nice.
-Is it?
-That's true.
Better than me being pushy
and getting turned down.
I want them to come strongly
so I can respond strongly.
-I get it.
-I feel like that works better.
But I've been single for a while.
Me too, for about three years.
-Three years?
-Yeah.
-Are you with anyone?
-Not for 18 years.
For 18 years, I've never been with anyone.
-That's critical.
-Yeah.
-It's your chance for first love here.
-It's bad. I really need...
to start being proactive.
-The playroom.
-The playroom, wow.
-A place to hangout...
-Wow!
-Looks comfortable.
-This is seriously amazing.
It's so stylish.
This is great.
-Knock, knock.
-Yes?
-Excuse us.
We were wondering
what the guys' room was like.
-The guys...
-Wait? Is this it?
-This is it?
-This is the playroom.
Oh, okay.
I thought this was the guys' room.
I see.
It'll be a little tight
if this was our room.
It's so different then.
-How's the room?
-It's pretty amazing.
-Seriously?
-It's perfect.
It's insane. We chose our beds.
The guys' room is pretty nice, too.
-I want to see it.
-Let's go see it later.
What does everyone want to do after?
-I want to go the supermarket.
-Me, too.
-I want to make food.
-Should we go to the market then?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
I need to buy shampoo and food...
Maybe some beer?
We're 18 over here.
-I'll participate!
-I'll drink juice.
I'll be watching you.
Please do.
They're all there.
It's a nice house
and everybody's been revealed.
The spaciousness of that hammock...
I feel like things might happen there.
Maybe they'll want to see the stars
together there.
I want to see two of them on the hammock.
The place has five bedrooms
and is 4,000 square feet.
-That's huge!
-It's so huge!
And there are three and a half baths.
If Aizawa got on the hammock
with someone, it might cause a problem.
Eighteen years old
and never had a girlfriend.
He seems very mature.
He's very classy.
-Yes, he is.
-He's very classy.
He's like an apprentice
at the fancy restaurant Kyubey.
-That's true.
-An apprentice saying, "Yes, sir."
When the tune of his ukulele changes,
we'll know something happened.
When you say his ukulele,
you really mean his ukulele, right?
Yes.
Yes, I mean his ukulele.
I didn't mean it
like "my 'baseball bat'."
-No, I didn't mean it like that.
-The worst euphemism.
I just meant if the sound quality changes
when he plays.
-I see.
-Then something may have changed him.
If Aizawa can get Lauren,
that'll be a dream.
That's true.
-I think that's possible.
-No way!
-It does seem to be possible...
-Right?
-The car keys...
-We each have our own.
Do they have our names?
Oh, I got mine on the first try.
-Avian.
-Thank you.
-Where does it say?
-Wow, we each get our own.
-This one's mine.
-It's so cute!
-Shopping time!
-I'm so hungry!
I'm hungry.
We can all pick stuff out
and eat it together.
Are we cooking today or not?
-If we cook, it'll take time.
-Yeah.
They have ready-made food here,
so we can just pick up stuff today.
-It feels so American.
-Let's go with that.
That's good.
-Is that enough?
-Let me know if you get tired.
Good work.
-Anything else?
-Well...
-Let's go.
-Is that too much?
Let's go, let's go.
-Let's go, let's go.
-The steaks are so big.
-Let's eat.
-Shall we eat?
-Time to eat!
-Let's toast.
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
-Thanks for the great day.
-Thank you.
What's everyone doing tomorrow?
-I have work.
-I have work, too.
-From seven to five.
-I've got school.
-Everyone's surprisingly busy.
-Yeah, I'm a student.
Am I the only one who's free?
-You're free, too?
-I'm free.
Should the three of us do something then?
-Yeah, let's do something.
-Yeah.
What do you guys do on your day off?
I usually go to Ala Moana or Waikiki.
Shopping?
But my favorite thing to do
is lounge at home.
I understand.
I totally understand.
Between Japanese and American men,
which is easier to get along with?
Which do you like better?
It really depends on the person.
I don't think nationality matters.
Do you prefer someone
who grew up in Japan or in America?
It depends on the person.
-Everyone's different.
-That's true.
I don't think it matters.
Have you gone out
with an American before? No?
I lived in Japan,
so I've only dated Japanese men.
You must have been popular in Japan.
Well...
there was a time like that.
I see.
Everyone is experienced.
What?
-It's amazing.
-Yes, you mentioned that.
I've never been with anyone before.
-You've never had a girlfriend?
-No.
But you've liked a girl before?
I have,
but it didn't work out the way I wanted.
Do you want a girlfriend?
-Yes, if it's possible
-If it's possible?
-Yes.
-Someone nice?
Be more confident, man.
-Do you have a type?
-My type?
Someone cheerful.
I used to be really shy.
I was uncomfortable
talking to people I didn't know.
So I'm more attracted to women
who can take the lead a little.
How about everyone else?
Someone who works out, has a nice body...
is manly...
-and sweet...
-That's a lot.
The list keeps getting longer.
And someone clean.
I like people who are creative.
And I prefer someone calm and more mature.
Someone I can respect.
That's it.
I like someone who has goals
and can take the lead.
I see.
-I have a grasp on everyone now.
-You do?
This is a little dangerous.
What time does school start tomorrow?
-8:00 a.m.
-8:00 a.m.?
What time do you usually leave the house?
Usually before seven.
You leave before seven?
-Hey!
-She brought something.
-Dessert?
-Dessert.
There are apples, too.
Thank you.
There's more coming.
Here it comes, late night dessert.
Let's eat.
You want to sit here?
You can't reach, right?
Let's eat.
-Your pajamas are so cute.
-Thank you.
Can you play something for us?
-Right now?
-Will you play something?
Play something.
-Something relaxing.
-Yeah.
-Right now? If it's okay...
-Please.
-...give me a few moments please.
-Sure.
-We'll be waiting.
-He's getting into it.
He's getting into his zone.
Here he comes.
-This song is called Dearly.
-Dearly?
It's an original.
-Nice!
-Amazing!
-Wow!
-Amazing.
-That was really cool.
-Wow.
-Really amazing.
-Really cool.
I got goose bumps!
He was way better than I expected.
-It was amazing!
-Wasn't it?
Yusuke, will you play the ukulele, too?
Seriously? Suddenly?
-But he'll do it for us.
-We're getting a show tonight.
-He'll be popular with the ladies.
-Right?
-Definitely.
-In one shot.
-He doesn't show off.
-Yeah.
He doesn't say how good he is.
-But that's what's nice.
-He doesn't say unless we ask.
-Like he doesn't need to say he's good.
-Yeah, totally.
-That's what's so cool.
-It is cool.
That he can play at that level when asked.
Excuse me.
My instrument has shrunk.
Amazing!
-Excuse me.
-Wow, amazing.
I can listen forever.
It was super amazing.
He glides in and glides out.
-He's quick.
-That's what's good about him.
I wish Yusuke would then
go sneak into the girls' room.
On the first night?
I don't want Yusuke to be like that!
-"You heard my ukulele, right?"
-No!
"You heard my ukulele, right?"
"Do you prefer that ukulele or this one?"
-"Hold the neck."
-You're so stupid.
-Look at him.
-I can't believe it.
It's unbelievable.
-I'm sorry Torichan.
-I can't believe it.
The trust you've built in Hawaii...
-it just crumbled.
-I can't believe it.
All the points I earned in Hawaii...
The girls keep saying,
"He has to be popular with the ladies."
Is that the same as saying he's hot?
It is. It's attractive
if you can play an instrument.
Is that how it is?
If you're a flirt who plays an instrument,
you might be harder to trust.
But if you're pure like Yusuke...
To say, "No, I've never had a girlfriend,"
and then to suddenly
play the guitar like that...
As Avian and Naomi were listening,
they were saying
he's definitely popular with the ladies,
but Lauren was quiet
and enjoying the music.
-Definitely.
-You think so?
Yeah, in the beginning when everyone
was having fun asking him to play,
only Lauren had a different air about her.
No way!
While she was listening, she was like...
She did do that.
She's already taken him in.
-She was like that.
-She was.
She was speaking through expressions.
So will a miracle happen?
-It's possible.
Even that's...
His pajamas were cute.
-I wonder why he has those.
-Right? They were so cute.
-I wanted to see more of it.
-The glasses were cute, too.
Maybe his master gave it to him.
His master at Kyubey?
"It's what I used to wear
when I was young."
Pajamas?
That's why he wore them?
That's so cute!
But you guys just made all that up!
First of all, he's not from Kyubey.
Are you going in the pool tomorrow?
I want to.
What do you think of the girls?
My type?
Which one seems interesting?
Which is interesting? Well...
I'm not sure.
I don't have an answer.
Then which girl's personality
fits best with yours right now?
Avian. I feel like I'd get along with her.
She was smiling the whole time.
You're right.
But definitely... she seems likeable.
Nice.
What about you?
Well, Lauren...
I've never met someone like...
like her before.
So I'd like to get to know her.
What about you, Yusuke?
-It's only the beginning.
-Only the beginning.
You should use your guitar.
-Use my guitar?
-Your sidekick.
-Super Yusuke.
-Not at all.
-His guitar skills were amazing.
-It was amazing. He's a genius.
-It was really amazing.
-Seriously.
-I could listen forever.
-He made my eyes sparkle.
He was amazing.
He really feels the music.
-But he... How should I put it?
-Humble?
He puts himself down. He doesn't...
He doesn't act like he knows he's good.
I really like that personality.
And he disappears quickly
after he's done.
Yeah, like, "Okay, I'm done."
He's committed to it.
Very serious.
What are your first impressions?
-They're good. Everyone's good.
-Everyone's nice.
Shall we go to sleep?
-Good night, everyone.
-Good night.
-I'm going to sleep.
-Okay.
TERRACE HOUSE
ALOHA STATE