-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Last week...
-It was so sad.
-It was Yusuke and Lauren's movie date.
Do you want to get dinner?
-No?
-I have dinner with my grandma on Fridays.
-I see.
-We eat together.
Then don't worry about it.
-I'm sorry today doesn't work.
-Don't worry about it.
Thanks.
She had dinner plans with her grandma.
Yusuke ate all alone
at the restaurant he reserved.
That was seriously bittersweet.
It's a historic moment in Terrace House.
-It was a memorable scene.
-It was.
And to top it off, he ate catfish.
I'm sure he learned a lot from that.
And he clearly said
he'll give up on her
and immerse himself in his music.
I'm going to give it up.
I should focus more on what I need to do.
I'm sorry, but I'm beginning to believe
that Lauren might not be very nice.
-In your opinion.
-Yes.
I'm the opinionated neighbor.
-And Naomi...
-Yes, Naomi.
She told Avian how she really feels
before announcing that she's leaving.
My last boyfriend of six years
had the exact same name.
-Yuya?
-Yeah.
I was drunk on the feeling
of calling him that.
Her excuse is appalling.
Yuya has the same name as her ex.
That's a new one.
She may have just said that...
For Avian's sake.
Since Naomi's leaving,
do you think we'll see the new person
right after she leaves?
I hope Seina comes during the transition.
Isn't that too strong for a transition?
Yeah, the transition may take over.
I'm leaving.
What?
You're kidding.
Really?
Seriously?
My original reason for coming here
was to remember how to speak English.
But...
being here, conversing...
I remembered more than I expected.
So, for me...
I've already achieved my main purpose.
I've completed my goal.
If I stay here, then my purpose would be
just living in Hawaii
and working part-time.
That's all it would be.
I felt like that wasn't right.
So, even though it's early,
this is the best choice for me.
I'm sorry, I'm going to cry.
Don't cry. I don't want to cry either.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't expecting this.
We've become friends.
If you hadn't been here,
I wouldn't have been able to do anything.
Don't say that.
I probably couldn't have gotten my job.
I couldn't even call them.
I didn't even have a cell phone.
You've taken care of me this whole time,
but can you do me one more favor?
I want to go out
with everyone on Sunday.
It could be the mountains or the beach.
-Yeah.
-For the last time...
Let's do what you want to do.
I was wondering
if you can make sure everyone is free.
Let's spend lots of time together
while you're still here.
Let's enjoy Hawaii together while we can.
Let's have a fun lunch.
I'm sorry.
The food got cold.
Good evening.
What's wrong?
How are things going?
How was your date with Lauren?
You looked really sad.
I was wondering if you're okay.
If she had to force herself to come...
I wish she had just told me
that she didn't feel like going.
I've already told Yuya and Eric
that I'm giving up.
-That's how you feel?
-Yeah.
In all likelihood,
she's not interested in me at all.
She may have gone as a friend.
But she didn't tell you that?
Lauren didn't say anything?
I think she realized it was a date.
I see.
But apparently she asked Yuya and Eric...
if they had pushed me into doing it.
She asked me about that.
So I told her they didn't.
-It was your decision.
-Yes, I told her that.
That's probably why she came.
But Lauren did say
that she enjoyed the movie
and that she wanted
to get to know you better.
-Did she?
-Yeah.
But listening to you,
it doesn't sound like that at all.
So I'm a little shocked.
How are things with Yuya?
What?
-You.
-How are things?
Hanging out with him is fun.
Nice.
I'm starting to see
that he's really good
at reading people's expressions.
Yuya's an amazing guy.
-That's weird coming from me.
-Yeah, he surprised me.
When I'm tired...
-He's observant.
-...or when I'm thinking about work.
He cheered me up the other day.
It made me happy.
Yuya's nice, right?
Surprisingly.
-Surprisingly?
-Surprisingly.
Surprisingly? That's terrible.
People tend to see him in different ways.
Yeah.
But I think the people who know him
have a different opinion.
That's true. Yeah.
Well, enjoy your time with Yuya.
Talking like this makes me think
you've really matured.
-Right now?
-Yeah.
You've totally different
than you were in the beginning.
Not yet. I still want to become...
-Seriously, though.
-...stronger.
I'll always cheer you on.
Thanks.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
There's something I wanted to ask.
Does the Thanksgiving dinner...
have to be on the 24th?
The 24th would be
my first holiday here...
that I could spend with everyone.
-So it'd be nice, if it were on the 24th.
-I see, I see.
But you made plans with your parents,
so you can't make the 24th, right?
You knew we'd be doing
Thanksgiving dinner,
but you didn't know
it would be on the 24th, right?
-You didn't know, so...
-Yeah, I wasn't thinking.
So the next time you schedule something...
I'd appreciate it
if you didn't keep changing on us.
I'll talk it over with my sisters.
I know you're double-booked...
and I know you want to spend time
with your family.
We can have our dinner earlier,
and you can go after.
I might get in trouble, but okay.
That can't be helped.
And before...
Why would you get in trouble?
Like, why am I prioritizing Terrace House?
You just have to explain to them, right?
It's not prioritizing.
Naomi's never spent the holidays here.
But you can do both, right?
Yeah, and if I get in trouble then...
Yeah, but...
Then don't tell us you'll be in trouble.
Otherwise, we'll feel bad about it.
You don't have to spend
the whole day with us.
And you don't have to cancel your plans.
You look like you're about to cry.
I know you love your family.
So you don't have to force yourself.
I just want to spend a little time
with you that day.
I'm sorry.
I don't even know why I'm crying.
I'd probably feel the same way
if we were in Japan.
I'm sorry for crying.
It's totally okay.
Why?
Nothing's happened, but I'm just...
stressed.
Talk to us.
If you tell us you'll get in trouble...
I want you to think about
how that makes us feel, too.
I didn't mean to say it like that.
Like, "Oh, I'll get it in trouble."
I'm going to disappear for a bit.
I'm sorry I couldn't say anything.
I'm sorry I let you do everything.
You should speak up, too,
and say you want it on the 24th.
Should I tell Lauren?
What do you mean?
She doesn't know
why I want it on the 24th,
so I think it's causing her stress.
Have you calmed down a bit?
With regard to what happened,
there's something I want to tell you.
I'm...
After Thanksgiving...
I'm leaving here.
Seriously?
Oh, no! I'm going to cry again!
Yeah, so, that's why...
Thanksgiving is the only American holiday
I'll be spending with everyone.
-That's why.
-It'll be my first and last one.
I had told Avian.
So Avian was upset...
because she knew my situation.
Naomi!
Can I hug you?
That was a little...
-It was heavy!
-It was hard to breathe.
-It was a little suffocating.
-A little.
Terrace House has been suffocating lately.
Something tiny turns into a huge deal.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Sparks fly.
You all tend to see Lauren
through rose-colored glasses.
I think you guys are insane.
When her mascara was running,
you said, "How beautiful."
Everything she does is perfect.
-Artistic, you mean?
-No, a little...
erotic.
Erotic.
I can't help but feel that way.
I don't think it's just miswording.
She simply tends to fight dirty, right?
She tends to mention things
she knows will make others angry.
Like, "I'll change my plans,
but if as a result...
I get in trouble, I'll take care of it."
If you're going to take care of it,
don't mention it.
That's true.
So what Avian was saying is right.
But Avian, too,
from a Japanese point of view...
If this was Japan,
you'd think to yourself,
"Why would you mention that?"
But when Avian is upset,
she comes out and says it.
I'd hate for someone to tell me
they're stressed out.
Well...
She did mention from the start
that living with others wasn't really...
She uses her family as an excuse
whenever she doesn't want to do something.
That's true.
What was surprising was that
they didn't mention
they wanted to get together on the 24th
because Naomi is leaving.
-Yeah, that was a little...
-They should've.
Avian knew,
and that's why she was especially upset.
She came on strong.
Since Avian was left in charge
of everyone's schedule,
she became the organizer.
It could be that they were going to
keep it secret until then.
So upon hearing that Naomi's leaving,
is Lauren willing to talk to her family?
I wonder.
I can't help but think
she could've done that from the start.
Hey.
-How are you?
-You don't need the charger?
I'm at 100%.
And it would never reach.
No more T-shirts to cut?
-Not right now.
-I want to do that.
-You do?
-I want to.
I'll bring back more.
How was your day?
I was at the shop.
-The whole time?
-Yeah.
Yeah, my shift is going to change.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-What time?
-Yeah, it's been decided.
I'll be at the store at 10:00 a.m.,
and I'll finish around 4:00 p.m.
If you're home earlier, we can talk more.
That's true.
Because we only talk before we go to bed.
What did you do?
-Today?
-Yeah.
I went to school, then I came home.
What about that thing with Eric?
Oh, Eric's thing?
I finished early
and there was nothing for me to do.
-Oh, you finished early?
-Yeah. I came home.
What do you do at Eric's?
I help out. I sand.
-You do that the whole time?
-Yeah.
You're always with Eric.
-It's fine, but...
-I'm helping out.
That's fine, but...
Since you want to get into acting,
you should go to an acting school
or something here.
Then you can make friends.
It seems like it would be
a good environment to be in.
-That kind of group.
-That's true.
What are you drawing?
-A turkey.
-Oh!
Nice.
Everyone bought so much.
Oh, by turkey, you mean the bird.
-You're really good.
-Not at all.
-I've been meaning to ask...
-Yes?
How was it?
Did you have fun?
-The movie?
-Yeah, the movie.
Yeah, it was fun.
It was. And the movie was great.
That's all I wanted to know.
Did you have fun?
Yeah, the movie was fun. Totally.
Well, you seem busy.
I'm going to get some rest.
-Everyone went to sleep so early.
-Yeah.
-I wonder why.
-It's so quiet.
Your feet are cold!
-I get cold easily.
-Super cold.
Are your feet ticklish?
Stop that! Seriously.
I'm sleepy.
I think I can sleep here.
-This is the perfect spot, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-Can I sleep here?
-You're going to catch a cold if you do.
Should I get a blanket for now?
-Sure.
-You want one?
-No, don't worry.
-Okay.
Thank you.
ELLIOTT GRAHAM, 23 YEARS OLD
CREATIVE DIRECTOR
-How are you?
-I'm good.
How is the design for the sign going?
For the design...
If we use acrylic paint,
the colors will be a little different.
It'll be different.
-So I'll use a computer.
-Nice.
For the background...
Maybe blue?
-Should we make it blue?
-Blue might not work.
The pop-up store...
When will it be ready?
The beginning of next month.
We plan on opening then.
-We'll make it, right?
-Yeah.
How was your date?
I knew you'd ask.
Yeah, it was fun.
He said he wished he could've talked more.
-I could tell.
-Yeah?
You were focused on the movie?
That wasn't the reason?
You just didn't want to?
That's rough.
If it had been a Thursday,
would you have gone to dinner?
Yeah, probably.
-You would've?
-Probably.
So it wasn't just an excuse.
No, it wasn't an excuse.
My grandma really made me dinner.
-Bon appétit.
Cheers.
I can reach.
-It's good.
-Apple cider.
-Tastes natural.
It's the first time
I'm having crab on Thanksgiving.
-Yeah?
-It's nice. Very Hawaiian.
-Is it?
-Yeah, Thanksgiving here
is different from the mainland.
It's a little...
-That's true, it is.
-Yeah.
It's been a while
since we all ate together.
That's true.
This is happiness.
-Seriously.
-It's great!
There's something I wanted to tell you.
I'm...
leaving Terrace House.
Seriously?
No way.
Have you decided which day?
If you're free this Sunday...
I wanted to go to the beach with everyone.
Electric Beach?
Eric mentioned it before.
-You said it was nice.
-For snorkeling.
I've been talking about snorkeling
with Avian and Lauren.
-I see.
-We bought new bathing suits.
The last hurrah.
-I'll leave Sunday open.
-Please.
I'm always free.
We all know that.
-Leave it open.
-Definitely.
The weather is great.
I'm glad it's sunny.
I thought it might rain.
It's nice today.
-We'll probably see dolphins.
-It's so sunny.
Dolphins.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-This is where you snorkel?
It looks like it.
-Rub and rinse?
-Right. Rub it all over.
Never.
-Like this?
-Nice.
-You've never snorkeled, right?
-This is my first time ever.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-This is my first time snorkeling.
-Nice.
-Should I go rinse it?
-No, it's okay.
-That's it?
-Yeah, just leave it.
The other way.
-Did you have fun?
-It was amazing.
-I'm glad.
-Seriously.
It was great.
I didn't think it would be this fun.
-It was amazing, wasn't it?
-It really was!
There were so many fish.
It was great!
It was so pretty!
-The turtle's so cute!
-When do you see something like that?
-Right?
-It's so nice.
Avian's bottom.
-Avian's bottom was nice.
-She has a very nice bottom.
-From the hips down.
-She's shapely!
The curves only women have.
It's splendid.
And things are starting to heat up
between Yuya and Avian.
-All that flirting.
-Touching her feet.
On that couch. That's a nice one.
-"Are your feet ticklish?"
-Right?
Very cute.
That was asking for a kiss.
-Why didn't they?
-They aren't official yet.
Do you kiss
only after you start going out?
-Don't you?
-"Okay, we're together!
Now let's kiss."
-What kind of kiss is that?
-Lame!
-Totally lame.
-"What's happening? What are we?"
-"What's going on?"
-Then, "Oh, we kissed."
-Now that's exciting.
"Oh, we kissed!"
"Wait, we did kiss."
-Right?
-Right.
You're the only ones getting excited here.
And the awkwardness
between Yusuke and Lauren.
It was awkward.
Did you really have to draw
that picture, Lauren?
She felt a little uncomfortable
talking to him,
so drawing was her escape.
And her conversation
with Eric and his friend...
I really didn't like that.
-That's usually how it goes.
-Yes, it is.
-That's how it is.
-I see.
Shit-head.
Shit-head?
I haven't heard that term in a while.
Lauren, if you're watching this,
don't ever watch Yama Channel.
-That's right.
-It looks like there's no escape.
I'm going all out
on these last two episodes.
-Should we toast?
-To the last night.
What are you all going to do?
-Same as usual?
-Same as usual.
Continue working
so I can open my main café.
-Yeah.
-I'll work hard.
Same for me.
-School?
-Yeah.
How about you, Lauren?
I want to have a gallery exhibit.
It's in discussion.
-And you, Avian?
-Me?
I want to start my own brand.
Maybe bikinis.
I'm thinking about it.
And you, Yusuke?
-Eggplant?
-Want a bell pepper?
-The meat is so good!
-Me?
I wanted to talk to you.
Do you mind?
-Right now? Sure.
-Yeah.
-What's wrong?
-What's up?
-See you in a bit.
-Yeah.
-I'll save you some.
-Yeah, save me a little.
What...
-What's going on?
-I have no idea.
He looked serious.
What's up?
You're leaving
Terrace House tomorrow, right?
I probably won't be here then, so...
I thought I'd just tell you now.
I'm thinking of leaving soon, too.
I haven't really talked to you
about the date with Lauren.
It didn't really go the way I pictured.
But she came,
and it was a good experience.
From now on...
I won't have to keep asking
Eric and Yuya...
for advice.
I can have the confidence on my own...
to talk to people.
I think I'll be able to do
the things I want.
I think you'll be okay.
You've been actively talking
to everyone lately.
You're totally different from before.
Thanks for telling me first.
For me...
the current members
are the Terrace House members.
I'm really glad to have met everyone.
That's how I feel.
This is tough.