-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
I'm certain you've noticed
that Torichan is not here today.
She had a prior engagement?
She's absent today
because she's booked for an important job.
Is it at Numazu Theater?
Or at Makuhari Aeon Theater?
Are you suggesting Torichan is
a new comedian from Yoshimoto?
I'll review what happened last week
in Torichan's absence.
Pure Yusuke encountered
a problem last week.
That damn Yuya...
He mocked Yusuke's virginity.
You should try
going out with someone, Yusuke.
What about your ex?
Oh, right, you've never had one.
-You knew that already!
-You knew that already.
They are the same age, after all.
So it's either friendly banter,
or he sees him in a lower caste.
Caste?
They used the pool for the first time,
and we saw Lauren in her bikini.
-Any scene could be used for a commercial.
-Yes, she's beautiful.
They asked Yusuke to join
so they could have background music.
It's like I'm working here.
Maybe it's because he was wearing
a Hawaiian shirt,
but it felt like he was working for them.
-That's true.
-But he'll be in Japan for three days
for the Hawaiian Music Awards Japan.
And Naomi and Eric,
the only members who drink,
drank together by the pool.
But Lauren and Eric
also have similar interests.
-They shared artwork.
-Their designs.
Yes, and the café design.
And Lauren and Yuya went for a night run.
It's so pretty.
Do you like one of the guys right now?
If I took this part of Yusuke,
and took this part of Yuya,
and this part of Eric...
-If you combined them, it'd be perfect?
-Yeah, it'd be nice.
Lauren states that she wants someone
who has the best parts of all three guys.
Nice dive!
-I'm going to dive in, too.
-It was really nice.
It was beautiful.
The water didn't splash.
Okay, I'm filming.
-Nice.
-No good!
-So you decided to join.
-Let me sit here. I'm lonely.
Is that watch waterproof?
-It's waterproof.
-Really?
Can you swim?
Yeah... but I can't do the breaststroke.
-Can you surf?
-I've never surfed before.
You probably can if you tried.
You guys can teach me.
Want to go on Sunday?
-Sunday? Okay!
-Yeah.
What?
And then...
What would the response be?
-Here, I'll be the...
-Okay.
Yes, please.
In that case...
-Can I make the call?
-Yes.
I was so nervous. Thank you!
Don't worry about it.
Next is...
Eggs 'N Things.
-In Ala Moana?
-Yeah.
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA
'16 GRADUATED MIURA GAKUEN HIGH SCHOOL
'16 STUDIED IN LOS ANGELES
LAST RELATIONSHIP: 6 MONTHS AGO
-That's amazing.
-Not at all.
You're drawing more and more.
-It's really amazing.
-Really?
I mean, it's not easy to have
so much character in your art.
Did you tell everyone about your job?
It's through Avian's connections.
So it's already kind of set,
but I'm going to have an interview.
-As a formality.
-Yeah.
That's great.
-At a restaurant?
-A restaurant.
-Go get 'em!
-I will, thanks.
I'm getting sleepy.
-Isn't it early?
-It's early.
Yusuke's coming home any minute.
We have an early morning tomorrow.
-I can't wait!
-We're going surfing.
-Where are you going?
-Waikiki.
Oh, Waikiki.
She's a beginner,
so it'll be easier for her.
Thank you.
Avian can teach you.
You're not going to teach me?
-He doesn't want to do it!
-Teach me.
-Maybe he's not--
-He's back.
-I'm home.
-Yusuke.
-Welcome back.
-I'm back.
-Long time no see.
-How are you guys?
-Really great.
I'm glad.
How was it?
-Well, I have this.
-What's that?
-Oh, you won something!
-Yes.
Amazing.
I won this special award.
Wow!
Let me see. Wow, amazing!
-I didn't win first place, but...
-Runner-up?
It was the special award
for making it to the finals.
Amazing!
-I won't touch it, but can I see it?
-Oh, go ahead.
What did you guys do while I was away?
While you were away?
We had a lot of fun.
-I knew you'd say that.
-Don't say that!
Lorraine and Yuya decided to go out.
We didn't!
-Yeah.
-I thought you were serious for a second.
They've been hanging out a lot together.
Neither one of them works,
so they're always together.
-We get along.
-Yeah.
She's easy to talk to.
Were there a lot of people present
when you performed?
More than I expected.
-Were you nervous?
-I wasn't.
-You weren't nervous?
-Did you make any mistakes?
None.
That was a great response.
-Your proud expression...
-That was good.
But everything else isn't good.
Not at all.
How insecure can you be?
Have some confidence.
I'm hoping to gain more confidence
in other areas.
-That's good.
-You will.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
-It looks easy to ride.
-It is.
-Where did you buy this?
-It was a gift.
It's a really nice board.
-The board's heavy! I'm gonna die.
-Nice.
You can use this one, too.
You put your foot forward.
-Like this?
-Yeah.
And then do this. Like this.
Make sure to bend your knees.
-Okay.
-I'll try.
Bon appétit!
-Brings me back to life.
-It's good, isn't it?
Totally brings me back to life.
Japanese cuisine is the best.
How did you like surfing?
-You want to do it again?
-My first surf.
-Should we go tomorrow?
-I was impressed by everyone.
What? That's too quick.
-Tomorrow morning.
-You want to go tomorrow?
-At 5:00 in the morning.
-I'll go.
It was your first time.
You're not up for tomorrow, right?
-Right?
-I'll take a break.
But surfing will make you healthy.
It's good for your body.
It's a nice lifestyle,
surfing with everyone in the morning
and then going to work.
-That's nice.
-And then go to school or whatnot.
It's nice to spend the weekend surfing
with everyone else.
Let's go hiking next time.
-I'm exhausted.
-Me, too.
5:00 a.m. tomorrow...
I'll make myself get up.
-You're going again?
-I am.
You should surf too, Yusuke.
I would if I had time.
Oh, you do want to?
Yeah, without these,
even though I'd be blind.
And Yusuke's a virgin.
That's true.
That came out of nowhere.
-I'm sure everyone knows already.
-You said it so suddenly.
I don't think that's unusual at 18.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
-You've still got time.
-I still have time?
Hopefully, at least once in my lifetime.
Only once in a lifetime?
-At least once.
-Wait, hold on.
-Welcome back.
-It's Lauren.
-What did you do?
It was my sister's birthday,
so we went out for dinner.
-Was it fun?
-It was, and it was tasty.
-I'm going to sleep by 10:00 tonight.
-Me, too.
I have school tomorrow, too.
I have to get up early.
Same. I have work tomorrow.
-Where?
-Banán.
-Do you know Banán?
-It's a new place, right?
Yes, that's right.
-Banana soft-serve--
-Instagram...
Yeah, it's all over Instagram.
-We don't have plans, right?
-Yep, no plans.
-As usual.
-Yep, as usual.
-I'm going to go do some work.
-Okay.
-I'm going to draw.
-You're going to draw?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
See ya.
I'm going to get things ready for school.
We're the ones left behind again.
-The two of us, as usual.
-As usual.
-But we actually get along best.
-Yeah.
-We're always talking.
We talk and hang out the most.
Yeah, we get along.
-You're easy to talk to.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
What should we do tomorrow?
What should we do?
Oh, we need groceries.
We're out of meat.
-We have to go shopping.
-Yeah, we finished it today.
Yeah, we need to go shopping sometime.
Then shouldn't we go tomorrow?
It takes forever when we all go.
I guess the two of us can do it.
We can just get what we'll definitely use.
Everyone will eat whatever we make anyway.
Let's just go grocery shopping somewhere.
-Should we?
-Yeah.
They went surfing...
But...
-It was a little...
-A little awkward.
Yeah, when the four of them were eating,
they were saying,
"Let's do it again tomorrow,"
and asked Naomi what she thought.
And her response was telling.
She said, "I was impressed by everyone."
-She did.
-She didn't say she had fun.
She said they seemed to have fun.
He's stupid and kept eating the rice ball.
That's harsh.
But Eric didn't notice
that Naomi was a little down either.
Eric is really just an old man.
His useless comment
that he's going to sleep at 10:00...
-A useless announcement.
-It's like, "So?"
It's something your dad would say.
"Daddy's going to sleep at 10:00 tonight."
-Who cares?
-And the whole family ignores him.
-Yeah, it's like, "Who cares?"
-"Go ahead."
Oh, we can't forget, Yusuke's back.
-He won the special award.
-Amazing.
The way Lauren gazes at Yusuke,
and the things she says to him...
It makes you wonder if the respect
will turn into love someday.
Lauren's eyes are so beautiful that...
Even when she's looking at you normally,
it makes you think
there's meaning behind her gaze.
And Yusuke has no experience with women.
He's a pure boy.
And whenever he's sitting on the floor,
-Lauren's hips are at eye level.
-That's right.
In a pair of shorts.
I wouldn't be able to stand it.
To have someone that beautiful in shorts
walk in front of a virgin...
That's a huge ordeal.
Even if it's only to lose his virginity...
I wonder if Lauren will help.
That would make for the best season!
Lauren can sit
with the ukulele beside her...
and say,
"Which do you want to play tonight?"
You're impossible. Just impossible.
I'm running late.
-For work?
-Yeah.
You don't have to eat.
I'll wrap it up for you.
-No, I want some.
-You'll have some?
Oh, then here's one that's ready.
-Can I eat it?
-Yeah.
-Do you really have time to eat?
-No, but I'm hungry.
-I'm digging in.
-Go ahead.
Thanks! You saved me.
Were the waves good?
It was really windy today.
-It was like a storm.
-Oh, so it was dangerous?
-No, it was fun.
-Was it?
I caught a few waves.
-All right.
-Okay.
-Thanks for the food.
-Sure.
Thanks for eating it
even though you have to rush.
-It was delicious.
-Thanks.
-Work hard.
-Bye!
-I'm off.
So for three more...
Looks good.
-I feel good.
-Avian's not up yet.
-Bon appétit.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm going back to sleep after this.
-You're going to sleep?
-Yeah.
So if we just go shopping today,
we're going to have a lot of free time.
We'll be bored.
Wanna go to the beach?
Sure, let's go.
There's a beach with a beautiful view.
It's about an hour from here.
-Let's go.
If we go to the beach, then go shopping,
then come back, it'll be perfect.
We can make dinner
when everyone comes home.
Are we going to swim?
What? No.
-We're just going to see it?
-Yeah.
Okay, I want to go.
Thanks for the food.
-I'm going to sleep for a bit.
-Sure.
Can you wake me up around 12:30
if I'm not already up?
12:30?
-Sleep well.
-Thanks again for the food!
See you later.
Are you nervous?
-You're nervous?
-Yeah.
You need to understand girls.
-Because this is a date?
-Of course I am.
And I dressed for a date today.
-I noticed that.
-Right?
Yeah, you're dressed for a date.
-Insane. It's already so beautiful.
-Right?
-I wonder which beach it is. It's so nice.
-It's so beautiful.
I wanna go in.
I should've brought my swimsuit.
-Did you bring yours?
-No.
-You didn't?
So pretty.
Hold on...
-It's better than I imagined.
-It's so beautiful.
-It's insane!
It's cold.
It's nice here, isn't it?
It was worth the drive.
-It's super nice.
-It's beautiful. The water is so blue.
-It's insane.
-The waves this morning were brown.
It's insane how beautiful it is.
-You should talk to Yusuke more.
-Why?
Since Yusuke went to Japan...
he feels like he missed out.
I think he's anxious about it.
-About what?
-That he's sort of missed out.
I think it bothers him.
-So will you talk with him more?
-Okay.
One of the reasons you wanted
to stay at Terrace House
was to learn English, right?
-Are there any other reasons?
-No.
-Nothing? That's it?
-Yeah.
All I want is to study English
and become an actor.
-Why do you ask?
-No reason.
-I just wanted to ask.
-What was yours?
Mine? Pretty similar I guess.
-I want to practice English.
-Refresh your English.
It'll be quick once you start working.
-When do you start? The fifth?
-You think?
My interview is on the fifth,
and I'll find out then when I'll start.
-All right, should we head out?
-You want to go?
-I've had enough.
-Bored of it?
For a while now.
-Okay then.
-You sound unsatisfied.
-Let's stay until you're satisfied.
-We came all the way here.
Should we go?
-Should we?
-Okay.
I want to nap here.
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-With a blanket laid out.
Remember how I said
I like picnics for first dates?
-That's right.
-I love it.
But this isn't a date.
-What is it, then?
-We're hanging out.
Just killing time.
Did you want it to be a date?
I don't know.
I just didn't know what this was.
-That's a really nice place.
-It was so beautiful.
Did anything happen?
-Nothing.
-Nothing?
No deep conversations?
-No deep talks.
-So Yuya is... done?
Done? What do you mean?
-I mean...
-Yeah, what do you mean?
So nothing is ever going to happen?
I don't think so.
-No?
-The setting was nice.
-Romantic?
-Yeah.
How was your day?
You had work, right?
Yeah, it was my first day at my new job.
It was fun.
Was it busy?
-Peel the skin.
-That's what I did.
Probably about 2,000 of them.
-The whole time.
-That many?
It was so much fun. I loved it.
I can think while I do it.
-Does that make sense?
-You were imagining things as you did it,
because you're only peeling.
You should draw a banana next.
-I will.
-Yeah, you should.
When you went...
surfing with Eric, Yuya and Avian,
how was that?
-Oh, you didn't hear?
-I don't think so.
-Really?
-That's right.
I was a mess.
-But Avian stuck with me the whole time.
-Really?
Eric and Yuya went off somewhere.
I thought Eric was going to teach you.
He showed me how to get onto a board
on the beach.
I thought he'd teach me in the water,
but he was already far away.
-Isn't that a little... bad?
-Yeah.
The guys were selfish.
They went off on their own
and left Naomi with me.
-Yeah.
-They should've waited for you.
-It's not too much to ask.
-Right?
The boys were so selfish.
I'm sorry, but I'm just going to say it.
It's unacceptable.
-They weren't gentlemen.
-I didn't want to mention this.
The night before you went surfing...
Eric said, "It would be better
if Naomi weren't coming."
-Really?
-Yeah. He asked me to help him.
-Why?
-He asked I do something else with you.
Like he didn't want her to come?
He said it wouldn't be fun.
I see.
That's really terrible of him.
Like, he didn't want to look after her?
I think he didn't want to teach you.
Like he...
Wanted to enjoy it himself.
We all went to have fun.
I wish he didn't say things like that.
That's right.
Maybe that's why he doesn't have one.
Thanks for telling me.
I'm glad you did.
I didn't want to, but...
I was so mad.
I thought it's better to tell you.
-Thank you.
-It's better you know.
I see him differently
now that I know he sees me as a burden.
-There it is.
-It's all over!
-The first crisis.
-The first problem.
That was really mean of Eric. The worst.
It's not what the oldest person
should say or do.
Those aren't the actions of a 27-year-old.
No wonder
he's not popular with the ladies.
They said that, too.
You know it's over when they say,
"That's why you don't have a girlfriend."
Yuya, too.
-He's not being shy, right?
-No, that's not it at all.
Who says he's bored when he's with a girl?
"What? I'm killing time."
-That's right.
-Who says that?
Even if it's not a date,
there's no need to say that.
Yeah, he could've just said
it's a nice way to spend time.
Like, "I wanted to bring you here
because it's pretty."
Yeah, like, "I'm glad we got to see it."
Yusuke might become popular.
There could be a foursome.
Foursome?
That would be a first!
The four of them could peel a banana.
Peel Yusuke's banana?
Okay, it's bad when Torichan's not here.
It's bad.
-I realize how important Torichan is.
-Seriously.
-I'm sorry.
-When Lauren was peeling bananas,
Kentaro and I were wondering
why they're peeling bananas.
We were about to say something,
but Yu was like, "Stop that!"
Because her co-worker asked,
"What are we going to do
with all these bananas?"
I thought, "Are you serious?"
-That's not normal.
-I mean, what would you do with bananas?
They're soft and mushy.
Your description is perverse, too!
You can freeze them.
Torichan!
-Torichan!
-Come back!
-Is this for your job interview?
-Yeah.
You have to do it online, I guess.
Are you doing okay?
Not at all.
-Oh, I thought you'd say you're fine.
-No.
I didn't know you had to do this.
I can't even enjoy this Coke.
-You have to work.
-Yeah, I'm in trouble.
-You can't log in?
-Hold on...
-I'm sure I made one earlier.
-It's so long.
Yeah.
Oh, I have to change keyboards.
I'm going to sleep.
I won't be able to get up at 5:00
if I don't go now.
Yeah, I'll go to sleep in an hour.
-Good night.
-Everyone who works there has an account?
-I think...