-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
There is no script at all.
-Terrace House: Aloha State has begun.
-Yes!
-The house is amazing, isn't it?
-Yes, it is.
It has a pool and everything.
-It's very large.
-A very large house.
And the six new members...
Things are happening slowly.
We're finding out
what kind of people they are.
First, we have Lauren Tsai.
-She's 18.
-She's beautiful.
She wants to be an illustrator
and currently models.
Am I the first one here?
She likes talented men.
She's an aspiring artist,
so maybe we'll get to see her art work.
I want to see them.
We'd love to see her work.
Second, we have Yuya Shibusawa,
age 18.
I wanted to go to acting school.
-Ah, to be an actor.
-Yes.
I'm trying to learn English.
You teach me English,
I teach you Japanese.
-Oh, okay, please do.
-Please teach me, too.
He's attractive.
He's from Yokosuka.
He may make naval curry someday.
"Here's Yokosuka's special naval curry."
He'll make it for everyone.
I'm sure he'll add some seafood to it.
I don't think naval curry
has seafood in it.
It doesn't?
The American troops served curry
on Fridays so they knew it was Friday.
-Oh, is that it?
-Yes, it was a system.
-You know everything.
-Yes, I do know a bit about some things.
And third, Avian Ku, age 26.
I was born here.
-Oh, you were born here.
-Yes, born and raised here.
Right now, I work with 88 Tees,
a T-shirt company in Waikiki.
-I know it!
-It's my mom's shop, but I help out.
I feel like I have a friend
who looks like her.
One of my high school classmates
looks like her.
Yes! She looks like an old classmate
you'd meet again at a wedding.
-Right?
-What are you talking about?
The daughter of the owner
of a famous T-shirt shop in Hawaii.
And there's Eric, age 27.
I build furniture...
A craftsman, I guess.
I'm also starting a café with a friend.
He's taken on the role of the leader.
Yes, like a big brother.
And Naomi... Naomi Lorraine Frank.
I was born in America,
but I've lived in Japan since I was seven.
So I'm totally Japanese.
She's pretty assertive,
Naomi Lorraine Frank.
She's the modern Tokyo girl.
Finally, there's Yusuke Aizawa, age 18.
-Last week's star.
-A musician who plays ukulele.
For 18 years, I've never dated anyone.
-It's your chance for first love here.
-It's bad. I really need...
to start being proactive.
It was amazing.
He stole their hearts in one performance.
He's actually a pretty impressive guy.
He released an album
while he was in high school.
He's a promising new musician,
and he's also never had a girlfriend.
He has no experience with girls
and is shy.
How will that play out?
Will we get another performance this week?
-I want one every week.
-Like "This Week's Yusuke"?
Yeah, "This Week's Yusuke."
"This Week's Yusuke"?
"This Week's Yusuke."
-In his pajamas?
-That'd be so cute!
-In a different colored one.
-So cute!
-So he likes that style.
-Yes, that style is comforting to him.
Is this...
Is this it?
Okay.
Off to school! -Yusuke
-Good morning.
-What are you drinking?
-Right now?
I'll have some milk.
When should we leave today?
When should we leave?
-We're going out for lunch, right?
-Yeah.
Should we leave around eleven?
But maybe Yu's not up yet.
-Good morning.
-I have to leave in a bit.
-Oh, okay.
-What's everyone doing today?
-Today? Um...
-The free people...
-The free people.
We're going out for lunch
and then to Costco.
-Okay, have fun then.
-Yes.
-Good luck at work.
-Yeah.
-I'll head out then.
-Bye.
-Be careful! See you later.
-Thanks.
I'll go put on makeup.
I'll do stuff here then.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
BORN IN MASSACHUSETTS
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
HAS BEEN DRAWING SINCE CHILDHOOD
MOVED TO HAWAII AT THE AGE OF SEVEN
LAST RELATIONSHIP: SIX MONTHS AGO
-Good morning.
-Oh, good morning.
Is that your drawing?
-Yeah.
-You're so good.
I was drawing
while Naomi's putting on makeup.
Were you able to sleep?
-Yeah, you?
-Yeah, I was.
That's good.
How long did it take you to do that?
-This one?
-Yeah.
This was my morning sketch.
-Morning sketch?
-And it took...
-It took between 30 minutes to an hour.
-Seriously?
-Wow!
-Not at all.
-It's amazing.
But thank you.
-You finished your makeup?
-I did.
-Good morning.
Should we get going soon?
We'll be making pasta! -Naomi
We'll be at Costco. -Lauren
I'll go change.
What?
The blinker...
-I want to go shopping.
-Yeah, me too.
-I want to shop, too.
-We can go to Waikiki in the evening.
-Yeah, I'd love to go there at night.
-It'll be great.
The three of us will likely be free often,
so let's go places.
I'll be free every day until October 10th.
-The 10th?
-That's when I start school.
Oh, you start school. I see.
-Such a pretty view. I'm so happy.
-It's beautiful.
It's very Hawaii.
It feels so good,
but I can't hear you two at all!
-You can't hear?
-Nothing at all!
-Can you hear me?
-What?
-I can hear you!
This is where Waikiki starts.
Wow, nice.
-We're here!
-We're here, we're here.
-We're in Waikiki!
-Yes.
-Wow.
-Wow, it's a city.
-There's a lot of people.
-We're in the city.
-We are.
-Wow.
Wow, wow, wow!
-And this is Waikiki beach.
-Wow!
So this is it?
-Amazing!
-We're here!
-It's Waikiki!
-There's a lot of people though.
-There are.
-This is where tourists go.
Amazing. I want to go to the beach!
Amazing.
It's Waikiki.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
-Is that Japanese anime?
-This area is really...
-That.
-That?
-The one that looks like Naruto.
-It's anime.
-It's Naruto, right?
-It's Japanese anime.
-Anime is popular.
-It is?
Everything sounds good.
-Anything you recommend?
-I recommend...
the acai bowl, or granola, or oatmeal.
They have breakfast foods.
But they also have burgers, sandwiches
and salads, too.
-Let's eat.
Did you live with your parents
in Japan, Yuya?
Yeah.
What are your parents like?
They're divorced, but...
Yours are divorced, too.
So we all have divorced parents.
I'm the only person in my family
who doesn't speak English.
My older brother speaks English,
but not very well.
So I want to learn English.
What about yours, Lauren?
My mom is planning to remarry.
-Oh, how wonderful.
-Yeah, it happened recently.
-I'm really happy.
-About the new partner?
Yes. So my mom moved to Virginia.
So my grandma, older sister and I
are the only ones left in Hawaii.
-I see.
-And I have two older sisters.
So all your past boyfriends
have been American?
I was 14 when I was
with my first boyfriend.
He was Korean.
But it was fine
because he was fluent in English.
And I didn't really
have a serious boyfriend after that.
-It was just...
-Dating around?
I did go on dates,
but I didn't have a real boyfriend.
-There was a Japanese guy, too.
-Oh, really?
I saw someone while I was in Japan.
But he was...
Are you looking for a girlfriend?
-I am.
-You are?
I want a real girlfriend.
I was seeing someone for six years.
He was someone who took the lead.
He was a really good person.
I haven't been able to get over him.
I need to move on,
and I thought if I lived with guys...
I think this lifestyle will change you.
I'm trying to change.
Do you worry about work-related things?
I worry about succeeding in the art world.
I worry about making it professionally.
I was just thinking, she's totally...
Um...
-How do I put it?
-What?
You're scaring me.
-You can say it.
-Well...
She's someone who likes to be alone.
Does that make sense?
-Really?
-Yes, like drawing at home alone.
-You're okay being alone?
-I'm totally fine being alone.
-I don't get lonely.
-She's always thinking about something.
-Really? Do I look like I worry?
-So if you just...
You can tell us
if you're worried about something.
That's true.
I never tell guys what I'm worrying about.
-Yeah.
-You should definitely talk about it.
-I've been thinking that lately.
-Right?
Not everyone is the same, but...
I'd prefer it if a girl told me
she was worried.
-Okay, I'll make sure to talk to everyone.
-Yes.
I'll talk to everyone.
But sometimes it's better
to only talk to the girls.
-Yeah.
-That's true.
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
'11 GRADUATED FROM FASHION INSTITUTE
OF DESIGN & MERCHANDISING
'15 GRADUATED FROM SHANGHAI UNIVERSITY
DEPT. OF FINANCE
CURRENTLY EMPLOYED AT 88TEES
LAST RELATIONSHIP: 7 MONTHS AGO
LOUKIE WONG
AVIAN'S MOM
What's everybody drinking?
-Water for me.
-Water?
Water for me.
Should I go ask Eric and everyone?
-He'll want beer.
-Will you call everyone?
Me, too. I want to drink with him today.
-Where do you want to sit, Eric?
-Wow.
-It's a feast today.
-There are six cups.
-I'll take the middle.
-The middle?
Go ahead.
-Is Avian at work?
-Yeah, Avian's at work.
She said she's working until 7:30.
-Shall we eat?
-Let's eat.
-What's this? Basil?
-That's pesto.
-Pesto?
-Pesto, Alfredo, tomato.
-This one?
-Yeah, I want that one.
Made with love.
-By Lauren.
-Yeah.
-It's homemade.
-Yes, homemade.
Is it good?
-It's good.
-Crazy?
-Really?
-Seriously. It's really good.
There's cheese, too.
-It's delicious.
-Let's dig in.
How was work today, Eric?
I was hammering nails all day.
-That's impressive.
-Yeah, seriously.
-For about nine hours straight.
-Nine hours?
When will the café be ready?
Maybe next year, to be honest.
-Next year?
-What kind of café will it be?
What kind of style do you want it to have?
-Hip.
-Hip?
A little Californian...
-Hip in that sense.
-How stylish.
-Sort of surfer-like.
-Sounds nice.
-Do you have a name for it?
-The name?
-Punch Bowl.
-Punch Bowl?
-Nice. It sounds hip.
-Very hip.
I'd like to make coffee there.
-You can? Seriously?
-Yeah, I can make latte art.
-You used to do it?
-I used to totally do it.
-Oh, really?
-So I've been wanting to do it.
What did the three of you do today?
-We totally connected today.
-Yeah, we did.
-Seriously?
-While we weren't there?
Do you have work tomorrow?
-I have work tomorrow.
-You have school?
I have school,
and then I'm off to the airport.
-That's right, the airport.
-That's right. It's goodbye.
Don't be so casual about it.
You could be a little sadder.
-How old are the other contestants?
-Everyone's a pro.
They're all adults.
-You're a pro.
-No, not at all.
It was really amazing.
I want to hear it again today.
-I want to hear it.
-Today, too?
-I got to listen earlier.
-What? That's so unfair!
-We should all see him off.
-Yeah.
No, that's not necessary.
I'll disappear on my own.
Don't say it like you're disappearing.
-Accept our offer.
-We'll see you off.
I feel bad. Thank you.
"I feel bad."
His Kyubey politeness.
They all went shopping, right?
And when they said they got close,
Yusuke seemed a little down.
Like he wanted to go, too.
Everyone else is getting closer
without him.
It reveals his inexperience with women.
-Does it?
-It makes him insecure.
-It's because he had school.
-Yeah.
Don't project yourself onto him.
That's true.
I was seeing myself in Yusuke.
I'm a little embarrassed now.
It's like I'm saying
that I rely on my talent, too.
He's talking to himself.
-He's talking a lot.
-We weren't reading that much into it.
You're not that similar.
My apologies.
We got to see
many sweet aspects of Lauren.
-We did.
-Very cute.
How can I put it?
The way she says, "What do you mean?"
This must have been
her first time cooking.
Her worried expression
while everyone ate...
That was extremely cute.
It was really cute.
That kind of expression by someone...
from a different cultural background
is really sweet.
-It's so nice.
-Hawaii's so nice.
-So the conclusion is, Hawaii is nice.
-That's the conclusion.
I can watch this forever.
-Water and beer, cheers.
-Cheers.
-Are you looking forward to college?
-College?
I don't have plans to go right now.
I'd like to head to Los Angeles after.
Why don't you go to
the music school, Berklee?
I did consider going there.
But it's expensive,
and it's also very far away.
What about you?
Are you planning on staying in Hawaii?
For now,
I'm planning on staying in Hawaii.
-For the café.
-Yes, for the café, too.
And while I'm living here...
Oh, here he comes.
-Nice work.
-I haven't worked.
-You took a shower already?
-I did.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
I was planning on asking if there was
something you wanted to accomplish
while you're at Terrace House.
Learning to...
approach people.
But you're doing fine.
And to say the things I want to say.
-You mean to be more open?
-Yes, to be more open.
-And try to find inspiration to compose.
-Nice.
So you want to write a song
while you're here.
Are there things
you two want to accomplish?
While we're here...
First of all...
I'd like to learn to speak English.
Like a native speaker.
And to find a girlfriend.
Those are my goals.
You want a girlfriend, too, right?
-I do.
-You do, right?
-Of course you do.
-If there's a nice girl, then of course.
-Yeah.
Are you the proactive type?
Or do you wait?
If I like her, then I go strong.
What was your ex like? What was she like?
She was originally a friend's girlfriend.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She said she had a change of heart
after she started coming to me for advice.
-She did?
-Yeah.
So we said we weren't together at first,
but we did things couples do
like go out on dates.
Is it that easy to have a change of heart?
I was surprised. She said her feelings
changed after about a week.
-One week? That's quick.
-One week?
You should try
going out with someone, Yusuke.
What about your ex?
Oh, right, you've never had one.
-You knew that already!
-You knew that already.
A man has to be proactive.
Yeah.
Nothing's gonna happen
unless you take action.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
-These are so cute.
-I really like these balls.
I love them, too.
Where should I put these?
It's fine here.
Another round.
Do you drink regularly?
-Or not really?
-Not really.
-I see.
-Cheers.
Only for special occasions then?
Well...
I don't really enjoy getting drunk,
so I only drink when I'm socializing.
-I don't normally drink alone.
-I see.
-This is really relaxing.
-Yes.
It's great.
The view here is great, isn't it?
Yeah, it's super pretty over there.
-I love the mornings best.
-The mornings are nice, too.
It's easy to drink here.
It's so refreshing, it's hard to stop.
Maybe I'll go get the Chemex tomorrow.
-What's that?
-From the office.
It's the coffee maker
shaped like an hourglass.
Now I'm curious.
-Let's use it at home.
-Yes, we should.
I don't really drink alone,
but I'll drink if there are people around.
There's only me or Avian.
Avian doesn't drink, right?
-So I'm your only drinking buddy.
-Yeah.
I'll keep you company.
Really? I'm gonna take you up on that.
I might ask often.
-Like, "Let's drink."
-Sure.
I'm not a fan of Japanese drinks,
but if its beer or wine...
Then let's go buy a nice wine next time.
-Am I the only one swimming?
-Wait. We're getting ready.
We're coming in.
Girls need time to prepare.
Ah, it's so cold!
-Let's play a game.
-Sure! Which?
If you flip over, you lose.
No way! I'll definitely lose.
Here she comes.
-Terrace House...
-Yeah, it's amazing.
This pool feels so nice.
Yusuke.
-You want Yusuke?
-Yeah, let's call him.
Ask him to play guitar.
-Okay. Sure.
-Tell him we want him.
-You hear him play, right?
-Every day.
-That's so unfair!
-I heard him yesterday, too.
The girls don't get to hear him.
It's warm.
Play, play.
Being this up close is so awesome.
Something like that.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-It's like I'm working here.
-What do you mean?
-I enjoyed it very much.
-Did you?
Going to Japan for three days!
-Yusuke
What about up there?
How about the skinny one?
Can I look at this?
It's really good.
-It's just a hobby for now.
-Really? This?
-You haven't gone to art school?
-No, I haven't.
I've loved drawing ever since I was two.
You should do it more.
Thank you. I plan to study it in school.
I plan to go to one in New York.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
How do you come up with the idea?
-I like it, so I'm always drawing.
-Randomly?
Randomly.
If I feel like it, I'll draw.
And I always feel like it,
so I'm always drawing.
You'll definitely keep improving.
I'm going running for a bit.
-Okay.
-Real running this time.
That's so cool!
-Editing is cool.
-It's so cool.
-It's like in the movies.
-Something's just different.
Even though they were just talking
about walking or running.
The content is crap...
-but they look good on-screen.
-They do.
Yuya was a little tough on Aizawa.
He finally ragged on him.
-He finally did it.
-It was light teasing.
Like classmate banter.
"What about your ex?
Oh, right, you've never had one."
That's really annoying.
Yusuke was taking it well.
Like, "You knew that already!"
He knew what he was doing.
It's annoying when he's condescending.
An empty-headed person
who only ever relied on his looks...
Don't underestimate the virgin,
you man whore.
"Don't underestimate the virgin,
you man whore."
What a fine phrase.
Isn't everyone sort of...
With regards to his guitar and ukulele,
aren't they kind of using him?
Well, yeah.
Like they're asking him to play
just for the atmosphere.
Like, "Hey, boy, play for us."
He is kind of like their younger brother.
He's like a younger brother,
and they want to hear it.
It'd be interesting if Yusuke exploded.
"I don't want to anymore!"
And he uses his guitar to beat them.
He cracked a joke about it himself.
"It's like I'm working here."
-He looks so cool when he's playing.
-So cool.
-He looks completely different.
-His expression.
Only Eric and Naomi can drink.
And that vibe. They're both...
The whole "I'll be the barista
at your café" thing...
It's a good foundation
for something to happen.
And if only the two of them drink,
they'll probably talk about
a lot of things when they're buzzed.
-Things might happen.
-They'll get closer.
Eric and Lauren, too...
they have a common interest in art.
Lauren feels like the star of the show.
-That's true.
-Things seem to be spinning around Lauren.
Wow, it's so stylish.
-Really?
-Yeah, it's stylish.
You don't think it's too rigid?
-No.
-This is the window.
This is the shelf.
The sign will be here.
I think that's good.
You can see everything.
-I'll try it.
-Okay.
Coming?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
We're going for a run.
-Good luck.
-Good luck?
Good luck.
-Running?
-Running.
-Have fun!
-See you!
Should we go right?
-I'm tired.
-You're tired? So am I.
It's so pretty.
-Is here okay?
-Yeah.
Good job.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
-You mentioned that.
-Yeah, one question.
You seem nervous. What is it?
I think it'll be hard for you to answer.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-Bye.
-Why?
Have you talked about
which of the guys you like best?
On first impression?
-Who do I like the best?
-Yeah.
Is there someone you like
out of the guys right now?
That's tough. Everyone has good features.
Today, I thought...
"If I took this part of Yusuke,
and took this part of Yuya,
and this part of Eric..."
-If you combined them, it'd be perfect?
-Yeah, it'd be nice.
I'm starting to see
everyone's personality.
-You're starting to see?
-I think so, but...
I'm not sure yet.
It's nice to talk one-on-one.
-Since we haven't before.
-No, we haven't.
Should we head home? I'm tired.
-Should we?
-Yeah, let's.
-I'm going to sleep well.
-Should we run?