-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
-Welcome back.
-Thanks for having me.
Saito understands
the male mentality very well.
-And can share his experiences.
-I'm just grateful.
I never expected to fit in so well here...
-In this show.
-Yes, he does fit in.
We think that Saito's favorite, Lauren,
-will take some action this week.
-She will.
She'll make a move.
There's been a lot leading up to it.
Lauren's heart was pounding all last week.
Are you nervous?
-You're so nervous!
-I'm okay.
As an excuse to ask him out,
she was holding the soccer ball
she had given him.
She tried, but she couldn't ask him
if he wanted to play soccer with her.
-She was the picture of lovesick.
-She was cute.
She threw aside the soccer ball.
-That was a good scene.
-Yes, it was.
She hoped to tell him how she felt
over a game of soccer,
so she kept the ball near her stomach.
-She was warming it up.
-Yes, warming it up,
hoping that romance might bloom.
But she threw it aside
when it wasn't possible.
And Guy asked Lauren out,
though we don't know if he's serious yet.
It was sudden.
He asked her out of the blue.
-Do you want to go hiking?
-I love hiking.
-Do I want to? Sure.
-If you want.
-Okay.
-Yes! We get to go.
-It's not clear yet how he feels.
-No, it's not clear.
Anna invited Yuya to lunch.
There's no deeper meaning to that.
-She just has questions.
-That's right.
Even though it doesn't mean anything,
if Avian finds out
and reads more into it...
-A misunderstanding.
-I hope there's a misunderstanding
and they clash.
-Let's be honest. Avian doesn't like Anna.
-That's right.
The way she talked...
-It's complicated.
-Things soured.
And Lauren, from her actions last week...
Though it's certain
he doesn't feel the same way,
she still asked him to go out.
This means she must have decided
to take action this week.
That's right.
-How are things for you?
-Right now...
-Right now... Well...
-What?
I'm thinking of asking Anna out on a date.
Everyone's out late today. I wonder why.
Want to go somewhere?
-Go somewhere?
-Sure.
-Where?
-The park?
-Yeah.
Taishi's plan to ask Anna out
put pressure on Lauren until finally,
-it lit a fire under her.
-Oh, I see.
And so she asks, "Want to go somewhere?"
Otherwise, even that
would've been hard for her.
-That may be true.
-So they'll go to the park.
She'll ask, "Do you know what you'll
talk about on your date?
-Do you want to practice with me?"
-There it is!
"Tell her how you feel."
Then she'll make him say, "I like you,"
and she'll say, "Me, too."
She can mix her true feelings
into the acting.
-She's not that skilled.
-So dramatic!
So dramatic!
If Seina was here she'd do it!
That may be too much
of a challenge for Lauren.
This feels like something
Tomoko Yamaguchi would do.
-Nice.
-In my head, it's like...
"Why don't you give it a try?
-That's not going to impress Anna."
-Yes.
"Get it right.
Try it again."
That's no longer Lauren,
but Tomoko Yamaguchi.
-This park is called Waialae-Iki.
-Waialae-Iki.
Thanks again for the soccer ball.
-I was so happy.
-I'm glad.
I was gonna get one myself.
This is unusual for you...
for you to say you want to go somewhere.
-Yeah, I've been so busy lately.
-Yeah.
What's that? Oh, a cookie.
-I've been so busy lately.
-That's right.
The exhibit was really good.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
-Nice.
-I will work hard.
-Yeah.
-I'll do my best.
-You want to do an exhibit in Japan, too.
-I do.
I want to open myself more to everyone.
-So I'll work harder.
-Nice.
I want to reveal more of myself.
The more I get to know you,
the more I understand your art.
Once I know what's behind the art,
then I form an attachment to it.
That's why I wanted the painting.
Because I know it's your art,
I wanted to buy it.
-Thank you.
-It was really good,
but I also know the background,
and that you worked really hard on it.
Seeing that makes the art...
makes it more special
than other art sold out there.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-That's how I felt.
-I'll put the piece up in LA.
-Thank you! That makes me happy.
-Send me pictures.
-I will.
I'll show off saying,
"My friend drew this."
-Nice.
-I'm glad.
Swings.
-You want to go on the swings?
-Yeah.
Swings, huh?
It's been a while
since I've been on one.
-Really?
-Yeah, a very long time.
Have fun.
This brings back memories.
Yes, it does.
It's a little scary.
Nice.
Did you ever go to Japan
when you were younger?
-No.
-Not at all?
-I went once with my family.
-Oh, with your family.
But it was only for three days.
-And you liked it there?
-I did.
Wait, wait. I can't see! It's too dark.
You can see.
-Whoa! I can't see.
-See?
Are you okay? Cold?
I'm okay. It's cold, but I'm okay.
-I'm always cold.
-You are?
-Should we head back?
-Should we?
Let's talk more often. It was fun today.
Thank you for asking me out.
-Shall we go?
-Okay, let's go.
You're too good. It scares me.
-What? Why?
-It's scary.
-You're good.
-I'm not.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
GUY SATO, 20 YEARS OLD
PRO SURFER
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
-I'm back!
-Welcome back.
Is it just you, Taishi?
-It's just me.
-Everyone's been so busy lately.
-Everyone comes home late.
-Right?
-How's the job hunt?
-Have you heard of Arancino?
You've mentioned it.
-I really hope I get it. I want to work.
-You haven't had an interview yet?
-No.
-You said you had one before?
-Somewhere you applied...
-I've applied to a lot of places, but no.
-No calls?
-There have been no calls.
-Arancino's nice.
-I've also asked Avian for help.
If she knows of good places...
When are you off next?
-I'm usually off.
-No way.
Let's go on a date.
-A date?
-A date.
Sure. Let's go.
I've been wanting to go horseback riding.
-Let's go.
-I want to go horseback riding.
Where can we go in Hawaii?
On the map...
-Turtle Bay or Kualoa Ranch?
-That one!
-Kualoa Ranch?
-I think that's what I was looking at.
Nice.
-What do you want to do for lunch?
-That day?
-You pick.
-Well, I...
I want... What's it called?
It's in a square box...
and it's really good
when two people eat it.
What?
-I have no idea what you mean.
-I want a bento lunch.
-A homemade bento lunch.
-Wait, wait...
A bento lunch? Nice.
-I don't care what's inside.
-Okay, got it.
-I can eat anything.
-I've never made a bento lunch before.
Good. It'll be your first.
-I'll give you details later.
-Good night. Let me know.
It'll probably be next week.
-Next week.
-Yeah, that'll be good.
-Do you need time?
-I need time to prepare.
Sure, you can cook wearing an apron.
I do want an apron, actually.
-I'll buy you an apron then.
-Really?
-I'll go buy one.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-What kind do you like?
-Whatever you prefer.
My preference might be too extreme.
Well, that makes things
more exciting actually.
-I'll think about the apron.
-Thank you.
-Good luck.
-Yeah.
-Good night.
-Yuya.
-Hey.
There?
-Did you just finish class?
-Yeah, around 12:30 pm.
-Bon appétit.
-Take some cilantro if you want.
I wanted to ask you
what was going on with Avian,
what your plans with her are.
I haven't really thought about it.
-I'm curious since we live together.
-I understand.
I'll feel better when things are clear.
Are Avian and I
creating an unapproachable vibe?
Yeah, sometimes. Especially at night.
Well, at night,
it's totally fine if you come in.
But it's turned into a space
for just you two.
I suppose.
Sometimes when I go downstairs
and see you two, I'll go back up.
It'd make things easier,
if your relationship was clear.
Why does it matter to you so much?
-It feels kind of unsettled otherwise.
-It doesn't.
-On my end.
-Well, maybe for you.
So with the way things are now,
if there was another guy with Avian,
-then you can't say anything.
-That's right.
But if she was your girlfriend,
then she'd consciously not do that.
I suppose, but even without
the title of "girlfriend,"
if you really care for each other,
you wouldn't do that.
Have you talked to Avian
about the future?
I have talked to her about it.
-What'd she say?
-It'd be a long-distance relationship.
Because you'll leave Hawaii, you mean?
So you don't plan on changing your plans
according to your relationship?
No, I wouldn't change my plans.
You're right about that.
That won't work.
What should I bring?
What do I need? Or don't need?
-You're leaving tomorrow?
-Yes.
-What time's the flight?
-7:30 a.m.
Morning?
-Yeah.
-Really?
-For one week?
-Until the 21st.
-How fun.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Right? How nice.
-I wonder how it'll be.
Have fun.
Thank you. I don't need this.
-Welcome back.
-Hey, Taishi.
How are things? Anything happen?
-The usual.
-The same old?
-I'll put this here.
-Thanks.
-Your hair color.
-You noticed?
-It's a little different.
-I dyed it.
-You did? What about the mohawk?
-I decided not to.
-I got scared.
-Why?
Let me see your hair.
It's super green.
-The way it's dyed...
-I didn't bleach it first.
-Oh, I see.
-I did it as is.
So the parts that were blond turned green.
-How was the Coming of Age celebration?
-It was fun.
-How are you?
-Well, I asked Anna out on a date.
In the last four days?
-What'd she say? Yes?
-She said yes.
We're going horseback riding.
You're eating it like that?
It's hot.
It's Anna.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-Welcome back, Guy.
-I'm back.
Wait, did you dye your hair?
-I did.
-She found out.
Welcome back.
It looks good. Insane. Is it green?
I dyed it green.
-Why green?
-I don't know.
I had a dream about green hair.
-A dream? Wow.
-Yeah.
So I thought it was a good idea.
-I got you an apron.
-Really?
Hold on. I'll get it.
Now you can practice cooking.
Yeah, I was planning to today,
but wow, that was fast!
-I went to buy it.
-Wow.
-Did you get to see your friends?
-Yeah, it's been a while.
How is everyone?
Oh, you're going on a date with Taishi.
-Who'd you hear it from? Taishi?
-Taishi.
He told you?
That was fast.
-That's perfect for Anna.
-No way!
Is it a flower pattern?
-It might be a little small.
-It's so cute!
-No, that's just the style.
-Will it fit?
It's tiny.
-I'll adjust the neck.
I'm going to practice today,
so you can't be home.
I won't be home. Try it on.
Nice!
-It's perfect.
-It's not too small at all.
-I'm glad.
-It's so cute!
-It's cute, right?
-Thank you.
No problem.
I'm looking forward to the bento lunch.
Is she gonna ride a horse
with the apron on?
Of course not! No.
Lauren couldn't take the next step
at the park with Taishi.
She couldn't.
-It was a tough situation.
-Yeah.
If only there had been
any moments of silence,
then Lauren could have mentally prepared,
and been like, "Okay, so..."
But not with Taishi constantly talking.
He said, "I'll show off saying,
'My friend drew this.'"
He used the word "friend."
I'm sure in Lauren's mind,
the word "friend" stood out in bold.
He asked if she was cold, and she said
she was but she was okay.
-She was trying.
-She was trying to communicate something.
She's cold but willing to stay.
That means something.
He may have been a little defensive.
When a guy is the first to say,
"Should we get going?"
Yes, it's very telling.
He has completely different attitudes
towards the person he likes
versus his friends.
-Completely different.
-Right?
Taishi is needier with Anna.
He shows his emotions more.
He smiles so happily with her,
like when he was asking for a bento lunch.
"You know, the square thing...
I want you to make me a bento lunch."
That's a technique.
Like High School Lullaby.
And Anna and Yuya's lunch,
why was it so tense?
Yeah, why was she attacking him?
Ken couldn't hold back his thoughts.
Tell them how you feel.
I can't stand Anna.
-Yeah, Ken.
-She's scary.
-Not for you, eh?
It's the way she asks.
-You didn't like how she phrased them?
-Yeah.
Sometimes you encounter people
who are really self-righteous.
Like when I'm at a party, enjoying myself,
I don't want to hear your life philosophy.
There are people like that.
Like, "I really wasn't
seeking depth today."
It happens sometimes.
"I had a really hard time
when I was younger,
but I never blamed others for it."
-Exactly!
-It's like, "I really don't care!"
And while Lauren was packing,
she seemed closed off to Anna.
"Japan seems fun." "Thank you very much."
-It wasn't like that.
-It wasn't.
As deadpan as Ken Watabe.
"Thank you very much.
-I'd be happy to."
-No.
Guy came back.
-And the reason he dyed his hair...
-He had a dream.
"I saw it in a dream."
He's starting to lose me a little.
-Guy?
-A little.
-I liked when he was Winnie-the-Pooh.
-Really? I'm still into him.
When he said, "I dyed my hair green
because of a dream."
-You were surprised?
-I agree with you Torichan.
I think he's bordering on insane.
Taishi gave Anna an apron.
It would have been funny
if it had been a strange apron,
-but it was very cute.
-He has a good eye.
I wished it had King Kamehameha I on it.
I agree.
-Lauren's gone for how long?
-One week.
One week, at this point,
will make things tough for Lauren.
Things will happen with
Taishi and Anna.
She's making him a bento lunch.
If Anna shows no interest in Taishi,
-it's possible it will all fall apart.
-That's possible.
She might not be into him.
But she's making him a bento.
Just making a bento lunch is fun.
-I'd make one for you.
-Seriously?
Making a bento lunch for a boy,
that's an event to be excited about.
-You really want to make it great.
-I see.
-Right?
-Yes.
If a girl told me she'll make me
a bento lunch, I'd think she liked me.
How naive.
-I'd fry tons of chicken.
-Right?
-Your fried chicken would be delicious.
-Yes, it would.
-It's probably juicy.
-And you would prep for it.
Yeah, I marinate it the night before.
Marinated over night?
I'd definitely think she liked me.
No, it's all for
the good fried chicken.
-Women are so hard to read!
-Are they?
-They are.
-I see.
"I am going to Japan.
See you soon!"
"Let me know if you want anything.
-Lauren"
I'm back.
Welcome back!
-You just got home?
-I just got home.
From North Shore?
-Are you making something?
-Yeah, a bento lunch.
For Taishi?
I don't have enough time. It's bad.
Looks good. Fried chicken?
You're only starting now?
-Yeah. I hope I finish in time.
-Can I try it?
For sure. I'm making a lot.
You can have some.
-Are you using the apron from Taishi?
-Yeah.
It's cute, right?
I thought we had more spices here.
-I'm in trouble.
-I'm hungry.
-I'm hungry, too.
-I haven't eaten.
-You surfed all day?
-Yeah, it was insane.
I surfed morning, day and night
and just got home.
That's crazy.
You haven't explored Hawaii at all?
Explored? No, not really.
It's good!
I haven't had fried chicken
in a while.
Yeah, it's good.
I'm glad.
-He'll be happy.
-Really? It's good?
-I want to go to LA.
-You seriously should.
-I want to go to acting school.
-We should go to one here.
-I wanna go.
-Let's go.
-I hadn't looked into it at all.
-You're 18 right?
I wish I had started working toward acting
when I was 18.
I'm already 29, so I feel very pressured.
My final goal is really vague.
I want to go to Hollywood and be an actor.
I want to be in an action movie.
That's all I've got for now.
I haven't done any research.
-I haven't taken any steps yet.
-I see.
That might be why
it's hard to push myself right now.
I write everything in my journal.
-Yeah, you do.
-My goals and such.
I'll show you. Let me grab it.
I haven't really written much yet.
These are my goals for 2017.
One is, I want to be in a Hollywood film.
So I thought about what I need to do
in order to make that happen.
I figured this is important.
So what do I need to do
to speak English like a native-speaker?
In order to do that,
I need to go to school.
Another method is to live
with American friends.
Big goals--
-Can I see it?
-Sure.
So you write one big goal,
and break down what you need to do
to reach your goal.
You won't be able to do everything,
but if you write it all down,
what you need to do becomes clear.
-It makes you do it?
-Yes.
If you want to focus on
learning English right now,
then you should decide
what level you want to reach and by when.
I don't have any of that.
You're probably just going to school.
Instead, you should decide what level
you want to reach at school.
Lauren had her exhibit, right?
I was really impressed.
Guy, too, he says he's just a surfer,
but there are many surfers
who can't become pro.
I'm sure it takes Guy a lot of work.
Guy doesn't show it,
but he goes to the beach every day.
-Today, too, he went early in the morning.
-He did.
He's probably thinking
of how he can ride certain waves.
That's what he focuses on
and what makes him get up early.
It's important to push yourself.
In order to achieve something,
you have to make sacrifices.
-Yeah.
When I first moved to LA,
I researched Japanese actors in LA.
I heard about a guy named Eijiro Ozaki.
He gives presentations and has a book out.
I hadn't heard of him, so I read his book.
I have it now. You can borrow it.
-You brought a lot.
-I'll get it.
He's been in The Last Samurai
and Letters from Iwo Jima.
-I've heard of him.
-You have?
This is how I've been studying.
Oh, I got his autograph.
-You met him?
-I did.
Aren't those words great?
"You make your own miracles."
Let's make our miracles, Yuya!
Wow.
I talked too much. I'm thirsty now.
-I'll go get water.
-I'm thirsty, too, actually.
Let's work hard.
OMOTESANDO, TOKYO
ERI TAKANE
CURATOR
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow. It's Santa Claus.
But it's a female Santa Claus.
Amazing.
-Yes, it's fantasy.
-I like fantasy.
I like the ones that have fantasy.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Amazing. Do you draw every day?
-I draw every day.
I'm not in art school,
but I draw every day for fun.
I have until May to decide.
If we show them here,
we could potentially show them
on this floor.
-Thank you so much.
-Not at all.
-Good morning.
-What's all that?
-Just some stuff.
-Stuff I've prepared.
-Like picnic stuff?
-Not really.
-Wow.
Are you ready?
It doesn't seem like it.
-I'm ready.
-You're ready?
-The bento lunch, too? All set?
-Yup, I'll go get it.
-Oh, wow. Nice.
-One is just drinks.
-Which one is it in?
-This one.
-What do you want to drink?
-Anything is fine.
-I got jasmine tea.
-Thanks.
-Got everything?
-Let's see.
Yes, I've got chopsticks and drinks.
-Let's go.
Have you girls been talking lately?
-Not really.
-No?
Really?
The guys talk so much
it's almost gotten boring.
-You three get along well.
-Yeah.
-Are you girls all right?
-We don't talk.
-Do you have any concerns?
-No, not really.
-Though I think Avian does.
-Really?
-Toward me.
What makes you say that?
It just crossed my mind one time
that Avian might be annoyed with me.
-I don't remember when, though.
-I see.
-There it is! Kualoa Ranch.
-Amazing.
-Jurassic Park was filmed here.
-Really?
-You didn't know?
-I didn't.
-Jurassic Park, Godzilla...
-Insane.
-Hunger Games, Lost...
-Insane!
It is.
-The horses are waiting.
-I'm excited.
Is it here? Oh, there's information.
-Over there. Inside, maybe?
-Oh, inside.
Wow!
How is it?
This feels great.
-The views are insane.
Are you okay?
It feels so good.
-It's an amazing view.
-It's so beautiful.
Let's go.
Insane. It's really pretty.
-This is a good spot for a picture.
-Right?
I want to take a picture of you.
-It's okay.
-I should've brought one.
Over there...
That's a great shot.
I'm going to take one, too.
You're kind of in it.
-Am I in it?
-Kind of.
Jurassic Park.
I agonized over this.
-Nice.
-Here.
-Oh, one for each of us?
-Yeah.
Nice. Oh, wow! It looks good.
-Really?
-It's cute.
-I worked pretty hard.
-You really did.
-Bon appétit.
-It looks so good.
-I hope it's good!
-I hope it's good.
-Where should I start?
The fried chicken.
It's good.
-Really? It's good?
-Super good.
You can cook.
It's so good.
-I'm glad.
-It's delicious.
-So this was a success?
-A big success.
-Really?
-It's really good.
I'm glad.
-I'm so glad!
-You're a good cook.
-Stop raising your expectations.
-It's really good, though.
-The pictures came out well.
-You took a lot.
-Nice.
-It's nice.
-Amazing.
-It looks fun.
-They came out super good.
-Yeah.
I didn't think
the pictures would come out so well.
-Send them to me.
-I'll send them later.
-It was fun, wasn't it?
-It really was.
-It was so good.
-This was a good choice.
-I had so much fun.
-I'm glad.
-It was so beautiful.
-Seriously?
It was so good.
Horse-riding was so good.
It was insane. I had so much fun.
-How was the bento lunch?
-It was so good!
-You saw it, right?
-I did. I ate some.
You did? You weren't supposed to eat it!
Why'd you eat it? That was mine!
-I had some fried chicken.
-That's the main part.
Oh, you! Guy!
The fried chicken was good, right?
-I was first to know you'd like it.
-You knew it first?
Was Anna nervous when she was
cooking yesterday?
-I was amazed she wore the apron.
-She did?
-Did you take a picture?
-A picture?
-Why didn't you take a picture?
-You should've told me earlier.
-You should pick up on that.
-Oh, right. Sorry.
-Do you have pictures?
-You want to see?
-They're so good.
-No, that's okay.
What?
-You can just show me.
-Yeah, I'm not going to show Guy.
Guy's not allowed to see.
It was like this.
-Oh, there's a path for the horses.
-Yeah.
-The entrance to Jurassic World.
-The entrance?
-You can go there?
-Yeah.
-Were there any tyrannosauruses?
-No.
-What about triceratops?
It was really pretty.
How was Anna? What do you think of her?
I'm feeling... pretty into her, I think.
-In what way?
-Have things changed?
Do you like talking to her?
Or do you think she's pretty?
She's just cute in all ways.
She hits my strike zone pretty hard.
But she seemed like she had fun today.
So I feel like things
are going pretty well.
-You said "interested" before.
-Yeah.
-Now you "like" her.
-That was quick.
-Is it?
But that's you, Taishi.
-You're here to fall in love.
-That's right.
If I'm here to fall in love,
I need to go full steam.
How did it go with Taishi?
We went out today
because he wanted to go on a date.
That's why we went.
But I don't know.
I don't know how Taishi feels.
How do you feel?
I'm not sure how I feel about Taishi.
But it was really fun hanging out.
Does it feel like
it's leading to anything?
Maybe not right now.
I don't really feel that way about Taishi.
He's not your type?
I don't think he's my type.
So what type of guy do you like?
I always say someone manly
when I'm asked, but...
Well, you do like sports and the outdoors.
So someone who can take the lead
on stuff like that.
-Someone I can do that with.
-But Taishi can do that.
Yeah, but I don't know how Taishi feels.
I'm sure Taishi is interested.
-Well, I don't know, but...
-He did say "date."
So I'm sure he's interested, but...
Well, it's fine as long as it's fun.
Considering how hard she was
on the others,
-she's rather...
-As long as it's fun?
Oh, no. I said too much.
-It's okay, Torichan.
-It's fine.
She attacked others,
and yet she didn't really give answers.
Of course we're all thinking that.
She made him a bento lunch,
but she's not into him.
To top it off, she said he's not her type.
-After all that!
-It's scary.
Or am I the only one who thinks so?
After how she's acted?
I don't know. It stinks.
-It stinks?
Do we have any Febreze?
She wanted to enjoy the horses
and the bento lunch.
That's what it was.
But if you keep having fun,
do things escalate?
It's possible.
If they keep having fun,
things may happen.
But they can keep doing that,
and it could still end
with her thinking he isn't her type.
The way the guys were talking afterward,
it was like a school trip where
they talk about their crush.
-It was like that.
-Right?
"What? You ate it? Why?"
-So Taishi's really into her.
-Yes.
He's almost ready to confess his feelings.
The scene with Anna and Avian,
-did it make you nervous?
-Yes.
-Like someone might step over the line?
I felt like no one blinked.
Neither of them.
Maybe they thought if they did,
they'd be killed.
If Anna had said she was interested
in Taishi, as well...
If Anna was more clear
about her feelings for Taishi,
then Avian may be more understanding,
and the matter would've been settled.
Now that it's clear Anna isn't
into Taishi,
there's a sense that they may
become enemies.
-That's right.
-A hint of it.
Anna and Avian's fight
sounds scary.
-Anna's headstrong too, right?
-Definitely headstrong.
There'd be sparks.
Like, "What's it to you?"
"What?"
She's definitely the type to say, "What?"
She's got the "What?" face.
-I want to see Anna say, "What?"
-I think it would be scary.
They might just go back and forth
saying "What?"
-Like, "What?"
-"What?"
No!
I kind of want to see that.
AOYAMA, TOKYO
TAMANA SHOKUDO
-It's been a while.
-It has.
-How are you?
-It's been so long! I'm good.
-Your hair is long.
-Is yours shorter?
-No.
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK,
PAST MEMBER
It's the same.
-It's been so long.
-I'm glad I get to see you.
-How are things for you?
-Recently...
I had an exhibit.
-In Hawaii.
-That's right.
We have three new members
and there's a different vibe in the house.
Is there any romance?
I was interested in Taishi.
-I was.
-"Was"?
Was? Am? I'm not sure.
-Are you still?
-I'm not sure.
-I see.
-Well...
I think he's really sweet
and a romantic person.
And I'd go on a date if he asked me out,
but he hasn't.
Nothing's happened.
I thought about asking him,
but Taishi is interested in Anna.
-I see.
-So, I think...
-I'm okay.
-You're okay?
I'm okay. I...
You won't regret it?
I don't think so.
Taishi won't fall for me.
-Why not?
-There isn't that vibe.
He's really interested in Anna.
And I'm 18. I want to be with someone
who really likes me.
I'll prepare for Tokyo and a new life.
Right now, I'm trying to start a new life.
I think it's time to move on
to the next chapter in my life.
You've decided then?
I've been thinking about
when I'd leave from the start,
but after coming here...
I made up my mind.
-So you've decided.
-I haven't told anyone yet,
but I think I'll be able to discover
a new self here in Tokyo.
You'll be in a totally new environment.
I don't know what'll happen,
but I want to do this.