-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers picked to live in a house
and have their lives taped.
All that has been prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
There is no script at all.
Last time, there was the surfing issue...
Lauren and Avian had a talk with Eric.
But the issue was solved Western-style,
very nice and short.
-They talked it out.
-Yes.
Coming to Hawaii from Japan...
So if I can't get along
with the people here...
then...
I'm not going to have any friends.
Incidentally...
Eiichiro Oda, the creator of One Piece
and a fan of Terrace House,
texted me after the first episode.
"Yamachan, I'm worried about Eric.
He's the kind of guy that
says stuff that starts trouble."
Wow!
Man, he's on top of things.
I wrote back, "I'm speechless.
You are ridiculously observant."
But anyways,
the most important part about the talk
was how Lauren refused to hug.
Her saying she's not "touchy-feely"
comes back into play later on.
-Yeah, it will. That was a good one.
-It was really, really good.
I was just about to come to you.
Is that for me?
-Good job.
-Thank you.
And this vibe between Yusuke and Lauren...
-He's wants a date.
-Yes, he wanted to ask her out.
He tried, but then she suggests
they all go out together.
What days are you off?
Friday and Saturday this week.
That's perfect.
Let's all go to the North Shore.
-Everyone together is fine one time.
-Taking it step by step.
He finally says he's interested in her.
I really like the way
her imagination works.
Ahhh...
Dumb and Dumber just nod along.
And Yuya said
he's going to make Avian fall for him.
-He sure did, didn't he?
-Yes, he did.
Avian and I have been talking
a lot lately.
-For real?
-Yeah, she's gonna be mine.
-I wonder how he's going to make his move.
-Me too.
So the North Shore date is a group date.
-And it's this week.
-Everyone all together.
-Good morning.
Naomi, can I get your headphones?
I lost mine.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Are earbuds okay?
-Yes.
You having breakfast or just coffee?
Just coffee.
-Why did you wake up so early?
-You only slept for like two hours.
I couldn't sleep.
It's like the night before a field trip.
-You were too excited?
-Yeah, way too excited.
-I got up early.
-Just like a kid.
Shall we, then?
-Let's do it.
-Let's go!
I guess I'm good with
just my phone and wallet.
-Did everyone pack their goggles?
-Yeah.
Uh-oh...
What's up?
-Are we all gonna fit?
-No way.
-I'll hop in the back.
-Me too!
-Let's sit together.
-Okay.
Can you hand me a towel?
I love Shepherds.
Like, German Shepherds.
Don't be like that.
-I wanna live in a place like this.
-That would be nice.
-With lots of dogs and cats.
-Nice.
This is totally the countryside.
-This doesn't feel like Hawaii.
-You're right.
-This is totally Hawaii!
-Extreme Hawaii!
-This is as Hawaii as it gets.
-Really?
-Really.
-This is the real Hawaii.
Yeah, the real Hawaii.
Not the resort Hawaii.
What did you get?
Are you excited?
You don't really like the beach, right?
-Not really.
-Me either.
-Are you going to swim?
-I'm not sure.
-Thanks.
-I'm wearing waterproof makeup today.
-That exists?
-Yeah.
-I don't think you even need makeup.
-Well, thank you very much.
Well, aren't you the sweet one, Yusuke.
I used to come here every week.
-Why?
-Just for fun.
-To go diving.
-By yourself?
-With friends.
-Let's come next week.
You wanna?
-Where'd you jump in from?
-Those rocks over there.
-There?
-Yeah.
-We can't go out there.
-Oh yes we can.
-There are red flags up.
-They always been there?
-I don't see any signs.
-We still can't go in.
-Why not?
-Because there are red flags!
I wonder how the waves are.
-They look rough.
-This is awesome!
It's so blue.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
MODEL, ASPIRING ARTIST
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
UKULELE MUSICIAN
-Bon appétit!
Mmmm!
Wow, that's good!
This is dangerous.
No kissing after eating this.
The garlic's too strong.
It's all good. No one will mind.
Is this a famous spot in Hawaii?
Yeah, pretty famous.
Everyone knows Giovanni's is the place
for garlic shrimp.
Wow!
Yusuke, you brought your ukulele
but you didn't play.
-You forgot.
-You totally forgot.
Yeah, I did.
On the beach?
-Yeah, I had it with me.
-You did?
-I'm gonna wash my hands.
-[with mouth full] Me too.
-That hit the spot.
-Yeah, it did.
How's your day going?
-Today?
-Yeah.
-I wonder if I got a tan.
-A tan?
Or am I still a little pale?
-You were passed out for a while.
-Yeah, I took a little power nap.
Do you want dessert?
-You're still hungry?
-What's on the menu?
-I'll go get it. My treat.
-We can all share.
Whoa.
What was that for?
-Can I have some?
-That was nice.
-Is it good?
-What are you getting?
So this is what it tastes like.
-It's not very sweet.
-It's very coconutty.
It tastes natural.
-What happened with your job, Lauren?
-My job?
I can't believe you got fired.
And it was only four days.
I can't believe it, either.
Wait, can you explain what happened again?
What was the reason?
Four hours after work, I got a call.
Just one call.
And they said,
"Please don't come in tomorrow."
-Are you serious?
-Like, just don't come in.
-Out of nowhere?
-There's a bunch of new employees,
so they're probably just
looking for the hardest workers.
And you were never late or made a mistake?
-I was still training.
-That's not cool.
So even if I did make a mistake,
well, I was still in training.
That's what training's for.
Of course I don't know everything.
-But Lorraine's got news. This Monday...
-Yup.
-She starts.
-First day on the job!
-Really?
-Didn't I tell you?
No, I didn't know.
-I'm starting at Tommy Bahama on Monday.
-Seriously?
-Finally escaping boredom?
-Yeah, finally!
-Let's go see her in action.
-Yeah, let's all go.
Come after I get used to it.
You were alone with Lauren at one point.
Behind us.
-Yeah.
-The four of us were down in the sand.
I noticed you guys were behind us.
I thought you were making your move,
then and there.
-But you joined us pretty quick.
-Sorry to disappoint.
She fell asleep for a bit.
-She did?
-Yeah, she took a nap and...
I couldn't find the right timing.
I know I shouldn't worry about that.
-But you do?
-Yeah, I can't help it.
She seemed really exhausted.
I thought it might be a bad idea
to try talking to her.
Like, maybe the timing just wasn't right.
That part's hard for me,
since I don't have a lot of experience.
You never know what'll happen
if you don't take a shot.
Yeah, that's true.
But if I come on too strong,
she might think I'm annoying.
-Is that a thing?
-If that happens, you fix it.
You fix it.
So I should fix it after the fact?
It doesn't always work this way, but...
when it comes to love...
If you don't get to know someone,
you'll never be able to get close.
-Not to that person.
-For sure.
That's true.
I guess I kinda blew it.
I think you overthink things all the time.
I don't think I have the confidence yet.
-You mean to talk?
-Yeah, talking, and like...
Being able to respond to people.
Responding to whatever they might say.
I just don't have that mentality yet.
Yeah, if you talk to someone and they
don't like what you say, it can hurt.
What about you?
Me? With Avian?
What's your plan?
I just have to go for it and see.
But it's gonna hurt if she turns me down.
The joy you feel when you try
and it goes well is amazing.
-Yeah?
-You feel so happy.
Sounds nice.
Get your confidence, get the girl.
That the plan?
Yeah, definitely.
Good.
Okay.
In my own way.
Damn it.
-What a beautiful place.
-It sure is.
-North Shore.
Everyone on the road together.
-To be young again!
-To be in that truck bed!
-That's the best seat!
-Aw, it's the dream!
-That's illegal in Japan, right?
-Yeah, I'm pretty sure it is.
I'd settle for a popped trunk.
I'd love to ride around Hawaii
sitting in a popped trunk.
Yusuke was so shy around Lauren.
But it was nice when he told her
she doesn't need makeup.
Yeah, she thanked him
and said he was sweet.
That whole vibe came out
because of the type of guy Yusuke is.
If Hugh Hefner or some womanizer
told a girl she's cute without makeup,
-it wouldn't be the same.
-Not at all.
It's his purity.
-You know he's not scheming.
-Right.
"She looks like an angel
standing in front of that register."
That's the thought
behind the makeup line.
Acting out the virgin?
His version of a virgin.
Some other facts came to light over lunch.
Lauren was fired from her job.
When she said she got fired
over the phone after four days on the job,
Yusuke was like,
"Are you serious?"
-He got upset.
-Yes, he showed...
-Some emotion.
-Yeah, he did.
-That was good.
-Yes, it was.
He's not gonna go file a complaint
or anything, is he?
Stage a sit-in outside her work.
Ukulele in hand.
Like some drifter.
What the hell'd you do
To my Laaauren?
They'd be like, "Beat it, punk.
Get outta here!"
"I ain't movin'."
How about Yuya's
relationship advice to Yusuke?
-It was good though, right?
-Yes, it went well.
He's a good kid when Eric's not around.
So Eric's a bad influence on him.
-Ahhh.
-That might be it.
Sounds like Yuya's
got his sights set on Avian.
He said he's going to go for it.
After Yuya left the room...
Yusuke mumbled to himself,
"In my own way."
And then just headed off to bed.
There's people who actually do that, huh?
He was talking to himself, huh?
He says important stuff out loud.
Maybe that talk hit home.
-He threw himself into bed.
-Yeah.
That'll make you do that.
-But that wooden bed didn't even creak.
-Not a peep.
-That's solid craftsmanship.
-That's what you care about?
ELLIOTT GRAHAM, 23 YEARS OLD
CREATIVE DIRECTOR
-Mr. Ono.
-That's me.
TSUYOSHI ONO
VICE PRESIDENT, UNIBAZAR
-Hey.
I brought the pop-up plans.
'08 GRADUATED MARIST INTERNATIONAL
'14 MOVED TO HAWAII
'16 JOINED WINDWOOD FINE FINISH
LAST RELATIONSHIP: 3 YEARS AGO
It's finally almost finished.
-You mean the plan?
-Yes.
Nice, nice.
The wall here...
starts here.
It would come out from here.
-About here?
-Yeah, about here.
Oh, wow.
-It would look like this from the front.
-That looks really good.
You've got the outside sketch, too?
The outside...
-This is the view from the outside.
-Punch Bowl Café.
-Punch Bowl Café?
-Yes, that's the name.
-It sounds good.
-That's it for now.
We want to match the vibe of the store.
That's the plan.
-Wanna sit down?
-Yeah, thanks.
Are you okay?
I feel like I haven't seen you
for a while.
-Lauren?
-Yeah.
I saw you yesterday, but not today.
Yeah, not at all today.
Did something happen?
Nothing happened, but from now on...
since we're living together...
Well, it's been about a month now?
Yeah, almost a month.
So since we live together,
maybe we should have some rules.
Okay.
For example,
we all share the toilet, bath, and shower.
So, if the toilet paper runs out...
then someone should
grab a new one and replace it.
We weren't doing that, but it'd be nice
if we could from here on out.
Yeah.
And it would be nice
if everyone could keep their area clean.
We all share the space, so...
Okay.
And like, the towels, for example...
Sometimes there's a bunch of used towels
that aren't hung back up.
They're all wet
and lying all over the place.
And you think that's me?
-No, not at all. I don't know who it is.
-No, no.
But since we all live here,
we should decide...
We should set some rules.
Yeah.
There is just one thing
I wanted to ask you to do, Lauren.
Okay.
Around the closet...
there's some used dishes sitting there.
And they've been there for a while.
-Could you clean those up?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll do that. I was thinking that, too.
-I shouldn't have to do that.
-You're right, my bad.
That's all. Sorry to ask.
Yeah.
Let's all just make sure we
clean up after ourselves.
That's a pretty simple rule.
Yeah.
-What are you doing?
-My English homework.
Um...
Ethan Aizawa...
-You go by Ethan?
-Yeah, it's my real name.
What about your homework, Yuya?
I'm too lazy.
-You have class tomorrow, right?
-I do.
But it's fine.
There was only
one homework assignment today.
Just for my last class.
Good evening.
-Hey.
-Hi everyone.
So, what's up?
We wanted to talk about cleaning.
-Are we making chores?
-Yup!
Ugh, do we really have to?
I knew you'd say that.
-We might have different perspectives.
-True, true, true.
-So this might be the easiest way.
-You're right.
-Since it'll be written.
-Yeah, for everyone.
-It'll be the easiest way.
-Okay.
-I think.
-Yeah.
-Please just give it a shot.
-Of course.
If we're gonna do it, I'll do my part.
I'll vacuum this week.
VACUUM: ERIC, YUYA, NAOMI
MOP: LAUREN, AVIAN, YUSUKE
-You cool with that, Yuya?
-Yeah, totally.
What were you girls talking about?
Cleaning.
-Cleaning?
-Yeah.
Did things get awkward
from talking about cleaning?
Just a little.
Did it get so bad you didn't
even want to see her?
-It's cool if you don't wanna tell me.
-It's not that...
Then...
Let's go talk somewhere else.
Alright. Alright.
I'm gonna go hear all the dirt.
Before we all sat down...
just us girls
were talking about cleaning.
-In your room?
-Yeah, in the girls' room.
And it's something Avian and I
have been talking about for a while.
So it's obvious to us we aren't the ones
who are making a mess.
I'd ask Avian if a mess was hers,
and she'd say no.
And she'd ask if a mess was mine,
and I'd say no. It happened all the time.
So when we just talked to Lauren about it,
we didn't point any fingers at her.
We said we should all make some rules.
And then Lauren just told me that...
she felt like we were saying she
was in the wrong and we were accusing her.
But I thought if we said we know
she's the one making the mess...
it would make her upset.
Well, I can understand how Lauren feels.
First of all...
it means she knows you and Avian
were talking about her.
That could make her sad.
I mean, one of you could
just tell Lauren,
"Hey, you never put things back.
Could you start trying to?"
At first, we did think
that one of us should just tell her.
But in that case, if I'm not there,
and Avian asks Lauren if she did it
and she says, "No, it wasn't me,"
we couldn't prove that we know it was.
But if Avian asked her and I was there,
Lauren can't just say, "It wasn't me."
But then it's two against one.
-Yeah.
-In the end.
Isn't that unfair?
You're ganging up on Lauren
with your opinions.
If Lauren lies,
then that's just who she is.
But I doubt she's the type of person
who'd lie about something like that.
Even if she lies about it...
you and Avian both know
it isn't either of you.
So Avian could say,
"Naomi says it wasn't her."
She could just say that.
What would happen
if you just told her?
Well, Lauren's pretty outspoken.
I was afraid she'd say,
"Whatever, you're a jerk."
That's ridiculous.
-That's so ridiculous.
-I know, but...
You have to just speak up.
Otherwise, it might be taken
the wrong way.
Thank you. You give such good advice.
-I...
-Well, this whole thing is ridiculous.
I know, but I thought
you'd be rougher on me about it.
Like, tell you you're wrong?
Or like, "Why can't you just say it?"
But thank you
for wording things so gently.
I feel a lot better.
I was feeling stressed about it.
CHRISTINE TSAI, 23 YEARS OLD
LAUREN'S OLDER SISTER
-Let me get that out of the way.
-Sorry.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
Just, we had the talk
about cleaning yesterday, right?
-The three of us?
-Yeah.
I wanted to apologize about that.
I wanted to say something, too...
about the bathroom and the rules.
The talk made it seem
like it was all my fault.
But, for example,
we can see who's hair is left.
We all have different hair.
No one's been perfect...
so it would've been nice
if it was put more nicely.
If there's an issue, you can just tell me.
Like with the dishes.
I know that's my fault,
so I'm happy you told me.
I'm glad. That's all I wanted to say.
Me too.
If you were living in a house
with six people...
wouldn't you want to pick up
after yourself?
Wouldn't you just pick stuff up and say,
"Hey, whose is this?
That's what a mom would say.
Like, "Hey, isn't this yours, Granny?"
Sorry!
-Can't they make the exchange fun?
-Yes, on the spot.
I didn't think Yuya's stock would rise,
but he is showing some signs
of increasing value today.
-Yes.
-He's doing well.
Lauren's not scary, but...
maybe Naomi is trying
to be careful around her.
But really, Naomi planned
to gang up on her.
Instead of telling Lauren herself,
Naomi used Avian to corner her.
Yes, it's kind of nice.
We're seeing signs of unpleasantness.
I don't know.
I was wondering what I was gonna do
since Yuya was off my enemies list
and Eric was the only one left,
but it looks like I've got a replacement!
I don't know if she falls onto that list.
She's just really girly.
Avian seems like the type to suggest
everyone talk about it.
-I think she was accommodating Naomi.
-I see, she did it for her.
I see, she used
Avian's understanding nature.
Hey...
You put it so meanly.
What do you mean, "used"?
There's power in words.
Excuse me. It's up to you
to take it however you will.
-Work?
-I haven't touched it today. It's bad.
I'd be in a better spot
if I did some this afternoon.
-If you weren't watching Terrace House?
-Yeah.
Definitely if I wasn't watching
Terrace House.
I watched a lot today.
When Byrnes told Misaki how he felt
in Yokohama...
-I watched it all today.
-Really?
I haven't seen that yet.
-Sorry! Spoilers!
-Don't worry about it.
I still don't know what she says.
She says...
Don't tell me!
I can't wait to watch it.
I was gonna try to come up
with some concepts today.
I had my sketchbook out.
I had everything ready.
But I just blanked for like an hour.
-Hey, what's up?
-Hey.
You just couldn't decide
what to work on the whole time?
Your designs?
Yeah, I wanted to start today,
but nothing came to me.
Yeah, I really want to hurry up
and build this pop-up store.
I want to see it. I want to go already.
-Starting next week...
-Next week?
-We start building if we can.
We're just starting to build.
-I thought you meant finish.
-That won't be for two or three weeks.
-If we work hard.
-I'll come visit when it's done.
Yeah, come on by.
We've been here for a month...
but there isn't much...
-How can I put it?
-I know.
-Nothing's really happened.
-Yup, not really.
Previous seasons of Terrace House
had things happen immediately.
-Like, a week into it.
-Yeah, like Byrnes, for example.
-Yeah.
-Like what I saw today.
He came and immediately liked Misaki.
He went for it right away?
He immediately knew he liked her.
That kind of thing hasn't happened, but...
there are moments when it feels like
something could happen.
Especially with Naomi.
I know what you mean.
Things seem to be going well lately.
From my perspective,
I think Yuya just sees her as a friend.
But for example, Yuya's...
-His earring?
-His earring is Naomi's.
-That's true.
-He's wearing hers.
-They straighten their hair together.
-Really?
That's the first I heard of that.
-Yeah.
-I didn't know at all.
Did someone knock?
-I'm coming in.
-Okay.
I wanted to talk to Avian.
-Avian? Oh, should I...
-No, stay.
-You sure?
-It's fine. Are you free Sunday?
-Yeah.
-You're free?
In the morning.
Let's go surfing in the morning
and then grab some food.
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
Sure.
-That's all.
-Alright, let's go.
-Sunday, then.
-Sunday. Okay.
Surfing.
-Good night.
Good night.
Should I have left?
Left? No.
-Why?
-Well...
he came to ask you out,
so I thought
maybe you guys wanted to talk more.
Isn't it just to go surfing and eat?
I don't know.
I think so, right?