-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes, that's how it is.
Torichan is at a very important job
once again this week.
-Today's the last day.
-Yes.
We might easily go off track today.
Please bear with us.
Hold on...
It's better than I imagined.
She was nervous
and dressed nicely for the occasion.
And Yuya, who was with Naomi, said...
"I'm bored."
-I've had enough.
-Bored of it?
For a while now.
But this isn't a date.
-What is it, then?
-We're hanging out.
Just killing time.
-His choice of words...
-He was a little cold.
I'm sure his intentions aren't bad, but...
-it was a poor choice.
-It wasn't considerate.
And the troubles continue.
Eric, Yuya, Naomi, and Avian
all went surfing so Naomi could learn.
But Eric and Yuya left Naomi
so they could enjoy themselves
and surf alone.
She felt a little sad about that.
But the terrible truth is revealed...
-In the evening.
-Yes.
The night before you went surfing...
Eric said, "It would be better
if Naomi weren't coming."
Like he didn't want her to come?
He said it wouldn't be fun.
I see.
I didn't think Eric was that kind of guy.
I thought he'd be mature...
and be able to pick up on how people feel.
-Yeah, he's the oldest.
-He wasn't at all.
And thought he'd be like a big brother.
-He's done for, right, Kentaro?
-He's... Yes.
I wanna hear you say it.
He's done for, right?
Yes, he's... Yes.
-You said it.
-Is he trying to make him look bad?
-He said it.
-He's noting the time!
You can't arrest him.
Today is Eric's last chance.
Depending on his response,
he may burn bridges.
He'll be hated.
Maybe we'll witness
Lauren's witchcraft for the first time.
Lauren's going to be like...
And her drawings will come to life.
-The ones with the horns?
-Yeah, the ones with the horns.
-Strange bugs will come.
-Scary!
If he announces his bedtime again,
we're replacing him.
I'm sure that's not what she's mad about.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
Still watching basketball?
I am. The NBA.
You know the other day...
-when we all went surfing together?
-Yeah.
Would you like to sit here?
-Okay.
-You're a bit far.
So...
when we went surfing...
I really didn't take into consideration...
what you were feeling.
When you heard what I said earlier...
I'm sure you thought...
that I didn't want you there.
I feel really bad about that.
Since Avian was around,
I assumed you'd tag along with her.
I'm really sorry about that.
I didn't realize you felt hurt.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Thank you.
I don't want you to think
that I don't like you.
I'm glad.
-You're okay?
-Yeah.
-Hold on a second.
It's okay. Take your time.
Coming to Hawaii from Japan...
Right now...
the only friends I have...
are the people in Terrace House.
So if I can't get along...
with the people here...
then...
I'm not going to have any friends.
And...
it was my first time surfing.
I was really scared.
I couldn't really swim when I first came.
But I've been practicing
in the pool every day.
-You have.
-I didn't want to slow everyone down.
I even practiced freestyle.
So...
Well, I understand that you're the type
who prefers to do things alone.
But I'd like to surf.
Not just surf,
but enjoy other things with you, too.
Oh, of course.
We can all enjoy it together.
-Please bear with me next time.
-Of course.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to cry.
He's arrogant in a way
that's typical of men.
He called her over
even though he's doing the apologizing.
-Usually you go to the other person.
-Yeah.
-Is that how it is in America?
-I don't think that matters.
-It doesn't, right?
-Yeah.
She's doing something,
but he called her over because it's far.
It's far for his own purposes.
He's the one who sat there.
-Wasn't there a chair next to her?
-There was.
-Yusuke sat there before.
-Seriously? Unacceptable.
And what Naomi said when she was crying...
It's true.
She's come from Japan entirely on her own.
So if the other members don't like her,
it's all over for her.
And they've shared drinks together,
talked and...
-That's right.
-Just as she started to get to know him,
hearing that he felt that way
would be tough on her.
Man, why did Lauren and Avian
solve that so unenthusiastically.
"Should we hug?"
"No, let's have coffee and call it a hug."
What's with that?
-What's with that?
-But, but...
they clearly said they thought
what he did wasn't right.
That was good. It was very American.
It was a very American solution.
-It feels like Eric got away with it.
-I don't know about that.
Eric's reaction
to what they said was fine.
It didn't seem
like he really felt that bad.
He probably doesn't really understand
what the problem was.
It hasn't sunk in.
Even when she cried,
he said, "Take your time."
Yeah, it's like, what do you mean?
You're the one making her cry.
-I know!
-"Take your time." No, that's not it.
He wouldn't be a good lover.
-Yes, that type.
-Right? That type.
The type that just bangs and then says,
"That was good."
Yeah, like, "That was great, baby."
It's like, are you an idiot?
-Like, "I haven't gotten off yet."
-Exactly!
Torichan!
-Torichan!
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
MOVED TO JAPAN AT AGE 7
'11 GRADUATED DAIICHI PHARMACEUTICAL
HIGH SCHOOL
'14 SIGNED BY TALENT AGENCY IN TOKYO
LAST RELATIONSHIP: ONE YEAR AGO
-You helped me with my résumé yesterday.
-Yeah.
Thank you for that.
Thanks to you, I think it went well today.
I'm glad it went well.
I've been here for three years,
but there were many words I didn't know.
-It was hard, wasn't it?
-Yeah.
Résumé vocabulary is difficult.
-I'd never written one before, so...
-Yeah.
Are you starting your job soon?
-Have you started already?
-What? No.
-When do you start?
-They're going to call me to let me know.
If I get the job,
they'll tell me when I start.
-I see.
-Yeah.
This is how you make a burger, right?
I think so.
Well, I think you mix it more, but...
I'm making my own lunch.
-That's sad.
-Yeah, it's sad.
There's no one to make it for you.
How did the talk go yesterday?
-With Naomi?
-Yeah, you talked, right?
We did.
She started to cry, and that surprised me.
It's been a while.
-Since a girl cried in front of you?
-Yeah.
-You made her cry.
-I don't really...
-Naomi's really girly, right?
-Yeah.
All of my friends tend to be frank.
Avian is easy in that sense.
-Yeah, she's easy to read.
-Yeah. She's got a temper.
She can look really scary when she's mad.
Like, she'll kill you
if you don't apologize.
Lauren, too.
Lauren's the scariest.
Lauren is really smart.
I like girls who speak their minds.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Girls who can have a serious conversation.
-Two more days, I think.
-That's right.
-Two more days until the break.
-Fall break.
-Oh, already?
-It's only a week, though.
-Only a week?
-Yeah.
-I thought it'd be two or three months.
-That's summer break.
When's your next...
You know, for this?
Is there an event or something?
This Friday, at an elementary school.
-Kaha...
-Kahala?
An elementary school.
-I think that's it.
-Friday?
-I'd like to come.
-Right? Can we come?
I'm sure you can. It's after school.
Will you ask?
Avian's really easy to talk to.
-Is she?
-Yeah.
The two of us were home today
before she left for work.
She was really easy to talk to.
It's fun talking with her.
She's really engaged in conversations.
Yeah, that's true.
We always laugh when we talk.
-Do you want some?
-What?
-That.
-The burger?
-I want one.
-Let's eat them since they're ready.
But isn't it for your lunch?
It is, but there'll be enough
left over for lunch.
Will you ask Yusuke if he wants one, too?
Sure, okay.
It's strangely stylish.
-A little disturbing.
-Thank you.
Oh, wow!
Is it hard?
Yeah, the meat's hard.
It's so hard.
It's definitely going to be
harder tomorrow.
I was just thinking that.
It's a man's meal.
-It works your jaw.
-Feels like I'm eating meat.
Do you talk to girls like you talk to us?
In the same way?
-Sort of?
-There hasn't been an issue.
-Finally.
-You seem okay.
You think so?
I made it on time.
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
STAGE NAME: EDEN KAI
'13 MOVED TO HAWAII
BEGAN HENRY J. KAISER HIGH SCHOOL
'15 RELEASED SOLO GUITAR ALBUM
"TOUCH THE SKY"
LAST RELATIONSHIP: NONE
Where's Yusuke?
-Where's Eden Kai?
-Yes, Eden Kai.
I was just about to come to you.
Is that for me?
-Good job.
-Thank you.
Good job.
-Were you nervous?
-No, it was fun.
-You weren't nervous?
-No.
-You seemed happy.
-Like you were having fun.
You were smiling the whole time.
-You were totally different.
-Yeah, I'm different when I perform.
-I got goose bumps.
-Goose bumps?
I didn't realize you were that good.
It was crazy.
-Should we head home?
-Let's go home.
-Should we head back?
-Good job.
-Nice job!
-Thanks.
-Want me to hold one?
-That's all right.
-Should we meet at home?
-What should we eat?
-We should eat out.
-Let's eat out.
-But Lauren's eating with her grandma.
-Yeah, with my grandma.
-Oh, really?
-So maybe it's better we go home first.
-Bye!
-See you at home.
Will we fit?
-Bon appétit!
So you don't get nervous when you play?
Not really.
I just enjoy it.
-You just enjoy it?
-Yeah.
Why did you start playing?
I was in a brass band.
In junior high school,
I played the trombone.
I came to love it.
But I wanted an instrument
that could express my music better.
I thought the guitar could work,
so I checked out YouTube.
I watched the videos there
and decided I'd do it.
It started out as a hobby.
But since I moved here, I really...
-Got into it?
-Yeah, I became passionate about it.
You learned ukulele
just by watching YouTube, right?
-Yeah.
-Really?
-I taught myself.
-I see.
Here I go.
You're up early.
Super early.
I haven't gotten up this early in a while
unless I'm going surfing.
That's true.
-Feels like I'm back in school.
-Yeah.
I have class from 8:20 a.m.,
until about 3:00 p.m.
Until about 3:00 p.m. starting today.
-Seriously?
-Yeah, every day.
But I end at noon on Fridays
because it's Happy Friday.
I'm supposed to meet
my other classmates today.
-About 30 people.
-Really?
Yeah, they said there are a lot.
From Brazil, Saudi Arabia...
-Sounds like you'll make a lot of friends.
-Yeah.
-I'm going.
-Okay.
-Good luck.
-I didn't finish my coffee.
Don't worry, I'll drink it.
-Good luck, Yuya.
-Thanks.
See you!
-See you.
-Bye.
-What are you doing?
-There he is.
-The guys--
-You're eating cereal? At this hour?
-What? Why?
-No, I'm not complaining.
-Is that not okay?
-It's fine.
Your painting... Where is that?
What's it a scene of?
Where is this?
Some Chinatown somewhere.
Oh, Chinatown.
Amazing. How many did you do today?
Two. This is the third.
-The third?
-Seriously?
-Crazy.
-I have to work hard.
Why are you doing a different style today?
I want to submit my work to a gallery.
So I have to...
I have to work hard,
or nothing will happen.
-Like, my dreams.
-That's true.
What are you doing this week, Yusuke?
I don't have any plans.
Are you going to work on your music?
I do that every day,
just like you draw every day to improve.
Yeah, every day.
You can't continue
if you aren't passionate.
That's true.
Continue talking.
Why?
Where are you going?
-To the room. I'm going to call a friend.
-Oh, I see.
How are things lately?
Really good.
I get to see my sister and my grandma.
I really like my job.
And I like living here
and making friends with everyone.
-Is it really fun? You're okay?
-It's fun.
It can be stressful at times,
but I think that's normal.
You can speak in English
when you're struggling.
Yeah, my Japanese...
I want to improve,
but I can't communicate what I'm thinking.
So sometimes I don't speak.
Or when I do,
I'm worried that I sound stupid.
I don't think you have to worry
about that.
Thank you.
When I first moved here,
I couldn't speak English at all.
Back then, I sounded really stupid
when I spoke.
But you really don't...
At least the people here don't care.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Tomorrow?
What should I do?
I haven't decided. I might...
Maybe I'll hang out with friends.
I'm totally free.
-Really free.
-Yeah.
When's your day off?
Let me see, I'm off Friday and Saturday
this week.
And...
Thursday evening, too.
-I'm free.
-Nice.
Should we all go to North Shore?
-North Shore?
-Everyone keeps talking about it.
-Oh, yeah.
-Like, "Let's go to North Shore."
They were saying that.
-I was saying it, too.
-Yeah.
-I think it'll be fun.
-Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Saturday?
-Saturday?
-Saturday.
Okay.
Are you going to paint for a while?
I won't bother you then.
-Not at all.
-I'll go.
See you.
-Good night.
Lauren, please ask him more.
-Because he can't, and he's a virgin.
-Well, but...
-He tried.
His mind is as good as
his ukulele playing.
He's really playing it.
-All around...
-He's hitting it.
He's hitting it!
-Playing and hitting.
But he can't bring himself to ask.
And Lauren, too.
She wants to ask, but...
"Let's all go to North Shore"
was the best she could do.
-And for Yusuke, it's "Oh, with everyone."
-Yes, of course.
But it felt like a conversation between
18 year olds. It was cute.
And they're both talented. It's so great.
It's the first time
I'm cheering for a couple.
And the way he left,
saying "I don't want to bother you."
-She said, "Not at all."
-Right?
I don't think God will know what to do
with that information.
That was so uncalled for.
You're so annoying.
Why do you say stuff like that?
When Lauren called out Eric
and they talked about hugging,
she said she normally doesn't hug
and wanted to have coffee instead.
-But she gave Yusuke a hug.
-That's true!
So that hug had some meaning.
Yusuke placed his ukulele
in front of him right after.
-Which ukulele?
-There's only one ukulele!
-The instrument.
-Oh, the instrument.
There's only one ukulele!
He'll have the ukulele in front,
and suddenly you'll hear a sound.
He's getting out of control.
You'll hear it crack.
Quiet, you!
He played it!
He didn't play it.
-The ukulele played the ukulele!
-Torichan!
School finally started.
-What happened with the girl?
-Which girl?
-The Japanese girl.
-The really forward one?
The one I told you about?
We didn't really talk today.
It's nice that you can meet people.
-That's true.
-I don't get to.
Avian and I have been talking
a lot lately.
Seriously?
Like, "What are you up to?"
Something like that.
-I plan to get her.
-Seriously?
-It's easy to be with her?
-It is.
I'm pretty...
You've been close to Naomi lately.
-Me and Naomi? Really?
-Yeah.
It seems like you pick on her a lot.
-You both pick on her.
-Yeah, I do, too.
-You?
-What?
Do you like anyone here?
Is there anyone you want to hang out with
on your own?
Yeah, like go out
and have something happen.
At first, it wasn't like this at all,
but when I was talking to Lauren...
-it felt really natural.
-Oh, Lauren.
You're choosing the cutest one.
-You're just attracted to her looks.
-Let me just say that that's not it.
What do you like about Lauren?
I like how she finds inspiration.
-As a musician?
-Tonight, too.
When we were talking,
she said when she draws,
she sometime listens to music
and draws inspiration from it.
You know her well.
The two of you have been talking a lot.
Oh, that thing on Saturday. What is it?
Where is it?
-Ah, North Shore?
-North Shore.
Lauren's coming to that.
-Yeah, she said she would.
-Yeah.
You should bring your ukulele.
-Bring it all the way there?
-Yusuke, we'll just be...
watching over you from afar.
I see. Well, I'll think about it.
Don't overthink it.
-If you overthink it...
-That's true.
You'll explode if you overthink.
It'll become awkward.
I'm looking forward to it.
-Right?
-Yeah.