-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers picked to live in a house
and have their lives taped.
All that has been prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
There is no script at all.
Last time,
they all went to the North Shore together.
-Enjoying the days of their youth.
-It was beautiful.
Yusuke tried to talk with Lauren...
but he couldn't.
-Yeah, he was overthinking it.
-That's right.
I couldn't find the right timing.
I know I shouldn't worry about that.
-But you do?
-Yeah, I can't help it.
I don't think I have the confidence yet.
Then came
the infamous Terrace House issue.
-Yes, the cleaning Incident.
-You sound like a cartoon character.
And like, the towels, for example...
Sometimes there's a bunch of used towels
that aren't hung back up.
They're all wet
and lying all over the place.
And you think that's me?
And after
those nasty attacks from both sides
Naomi sought out advice from Yuya.
And Yuya just kept saying
one good thing after another.
And then Lauren just told me that...
she felt like we were saying she
was in the wrong and we were accusing her.
You have to just speak up.
Otherwise, it might be taken
the wrong way.
But thank you
for wording things so gently.
She's thinking,
"Oh, Yuya's saying such great things."
She's feel grateful.
We even found out
that Yuya was wearing Naomi's earring.
-And despite all that...
-That's when it happened.
Right in front of her.
I wanted to talk to Avian.
-Avian? Oh, should I...
-No, stay.
-You sure?
-It's fine. Are you free Sunday?
In the morning.
Let's go surfing in the morning
and then grab some food.
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
Sure.
-That's all.
-Alright, let's go.
Naomi was the only one who felt like
she and Yuya had gotten a little closer.
-"It's okay. You can stay."
-Yeah, that was rough.
It's like, "You're just an extra."
He didn't say that!
-No one said "extra."
-That's horrible.
-Just horrible.
-Things are happening romantically.
And how close will Yusuke be able to get
to Lauren this week?
-We didn't finish our project yet.
-Oh, really?
That's what you get for
drinking yesterday.
I'm gonna get in trouble.
-Can you still go to the farmers' market?
-Yup.
You sure?
You don't have to if you're busy.
-It's no problem.
-Really?
I've never gone this early before.
Never?
What do you want to get?
Ummm...
Some fruit, yeah?
-Exotic fruit?
-Exotic fruit.
And some vegetables,
if there's some cheap ones.
Maybe some good coffee, too,
if they have any.
-Yeah.
-Coffee beans.
-Let's go!
There's a line.
-There's a crowd, as usual.
-Yeah, as usual.
-Let's look at everything and then decide.
-Sounds good.
-Those daikon look really good.
-Yeah, this one.
-Can't go wrong.
-How much is it?
-For a daikon salad.
-Oh, yeah, let's make that!
These look good, too.
-Wooow!
-Nice.
-These look good, too.
-What is it?
-It's like jam.
-Ahhh.
Hold on, I'm gonna take a picture.
I feel like i'm on a survival show.
Want this, too? Here.
So, have you gotten used to things?
The first week was a little tough.
Everyone was always home.
-But I like being alone.
-Ahhh.
I like hanging out with everyone...
but I need some alone time, too.
I hear you.
Everyone was worried for a while.
-Like, "is Lauren okay?"
-I know.
I was surprised to hear that.
We bought a lot of vegetables.
I couldn't find any fruits I liked.
I just bought a few bananas.
-Wanna head home?
-Yeah, let's go.
Where'd we park?
Ah, over there.
-The farmers' market was fun.
-Right?
I'd come again,
but I got too much sun.
-You're definitely getting darker.
-I know.
-So?
-It stresses me out.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
MODEL, ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
HIRONORI AIZAWA
YUSUKE'S FATHER
It sounds like his dad
saw some wild days in his youth.
"Are you guys dancing at all?"
-That's not a question from a normal dad.
-You're right.
Does that mean
Yusuke normally dances at home?
I thought that, too!
Maybe he's got a special dance
to entertain his family.
Maybe he's outgoing at home
but shy in public.
It'd be hilarious if he busted out
some weird dance from home.
How cute!
-That's adorable!
-So cute!
Lauren and Eric went
to the farmers' market.
It made for a nice scene.
-That's true.
-Yes.
Do you think Lauren is trying to take down
her walls and be friendly
after the cleaning incident last time?
It seems she's making more of an effort
to communicate with everyone.
She didn't realize how people saw her.
It was just important to her
to have her time alone.
She was just being her normal self,
but the others were worried about her.
It feels like we might get to see
Yusuke take the initiative soon.
Good luck.
But Yusuke is still
the only one Lauren hugged.
-And the only one she touched, right?
-Right.
When she still had her walls up...
Yusuke was the only one
she let them down for.
Or maybe it's because they're the same age
and she feels comfortable hugging him
without there being
any sexual connotations.
Man, that would be so tough on a virgin!
Naomi, what time did you say
you were leaving tomorrow? 8:00 a.m.?
Ummm...
I'm leaving the house around 8:00 a.m.
Isn't that early?
-So early!
-When's takeoff?
My flight's at 11:30 a.m.
-8:00 sounds right, then.
-Yup, 8:00.
Are you sad to be going back to Japan?
A little bit.
-You'll be gone for about a week?
-About a week, yeah.
That's pretty long.
-Yeah, pretty long.
- A whole week!
I wonder what'll happen in the house.
-Yeah, everyone...
-It's going to be so quiet.
-It'll be boring.
-Thanks for saying that.
We should've gone out to eat
for your last night.
-I totally forgot.
-Don't worry about it.
I wanna eat something sweet.
-Wanna go get some dessert?
-Yeah.
-Where should we go? Kahala?
-Kahala.
-Wanna go?
-Yeah, let's go.
-Should we go?
-Let's go.
-Off we go.
-Naomi, you drive.
-No!
-You always scrape the Mustang.
Hey! Stop telling lies!
Will you eat a parfait if I make you one?
Yeah, I'll have it later.
-What do you mean, "later"?
-I've got homework to do.
Really? But the ice cream will melt.
-So I won't make it yet, then.
-Just take the fruit.
I can eat later. No problem.
-Have fun.
-What? Are you going to sleep?
-Me? I'll be in our room.
-In the girls' room? Okay.
-How many kiwis should I use?
-As many as you want.
I'll use two for now.
-I'm gonna go do my homework
-Okay.
Where's he going? Downstairs?
-Probably the bedroom.
-Why?
He's not gonna eat?
-Later, probably.
-He said he'd have some.
Is this enough strawberries?
Are you a strawberry fiend?
-You want more, right?
-Yeah.
-You don't have to give them all to me.
-I know. I just...
-I figured you liked strawberries.
-I love them.
Thanks.
That looks great!
-Let's take it downstairs.
-Okay.
It's cold.
-It's raining a little.
-This is good!
-You're eating already?
-Yeah.
-It's raining a little.
-More than a little!
-This sucks.
-You're right, it's more than a little.
Well, it'll stop.
-You said it's easier to talk outside.
-Yeah, I like it outside.
But it's a bit cold.
-Want a jacket? I'll go get one.
-Yeah, please.
Thanks.
-Thanks!
-Sure.
It's the one I lent you before.
Sorry if it smells.
-Does it smell sweaty?
-Not at all.
-Does it smell like the closet?
-No, it smells more like detergent.
Thanks again.
I wonder if Yusuke is gonna eat.
Maybe I'll make one for him.
Whatever.
I'll make it when he's ready.
-Your last meal.
-Yup.
The Last Supper.
It's delicious.
-Thanks for making it.
-No problem.
-Are you sad you'll be gone for a week?
-I am.
-You said you just started being positive.
-Yeah.
What do you mean by "positive"?
In terms of both my work and my love life.
I actually already made a move.
You did?
Really?
That's why Yusuke's not here.
-What?
-I asked him not to come.
You did?
I told him I wanted to talk to you alone
before I left.
What did you want to talk about?
Is it a date?
Did you ask her out on a date?
I did.
Where will you go?
Diamond Head.
-To surf.
-Surfing? What about after that?
We'll go get something to eat.
But...
she doesn't seem to see it that way.
So for now, as long as she has fun
then I'm fine with that.
Have you guys hung out together before?
-We haven't.
-Oh, you haven't.
Not once. You're the only one
I've gone somewhere alone with.
In the beginning.
-Back when we went to the beach together
-That was way back in the beginning.
-I don't know if that was a date or what.
-Yeah, whatever that was.
Yeah, yeah.
It was good the way it was.
It was fun for what it was.
It's raining again.
-Yup. Wanna go back inside?
-Yeah, let's go in.
-Before we get cold.
-Okay.
Thanks for the food.
-The dishes are all you.
-Fiiine.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
Gone to Japan for an Internet TV job.
Naomi
I'm so sleepy. Seriously.
Are you taking the shortboard?
-The longboard today.
-The longboard?
Wait a second!
-Thanks.
-You forgot to turn it on.
Yeah, I forgot.
-Should we load this first?
-Yeah.
It's fine.
The weather's so nice.
-No, it's totally not.
-It totally is.
-Really? Oh, yeah, it is.
-See?
-Diamond Head's got some clouds over it.
-Yeah, you're right.
But I like that.
Like, when...
The rainfall as you sit on your board,
waiting for the wave.
-You like that?
-Yeah, I love it.
I was just thinking...
you're such a romantic, Yuya.
-Surprisingly.
-Surprisingly?
-Am I?
-Yeah, I think so.
Do you prefer romantics?
Yeah, I do.
Romantics are good.
-Is it better to be a romantic?
-Yeah.
There's a rainbow.
Where? Oh, you're right!
That's awesome.
-What do you want to eat?
-What do I want to eat?
Hmmm... That's tough.
Deciding what to eat is tough?
-You're okay with anything?
-I'm okay with anything.
-What's good here? Do you know this place?
-I do!
-You do?
-I love this place.
-Really? Nice.
-Yeah.
-Did I choose a good place?
-Thanks.
-So, what's good?
-The loco moco is good.
-Oh, maybe I'll have that.
Everything here is good.
You're buying?
Thank you.
It looks so good.
-Looks delicious.
-Looks like breakfast.
-Bon appétit.
This is gonna be good.
I'm gonna put some lemon on it.
So good!
Delicious!
I'm so happy!
I feel totally revived.
I'm glad you chose this place.
This place?
I wasn't sure where to take you.
Really? Why?
-I wasn't sure where's good.
-This is so good!
-Sorry to interrupt.
-It is good.
But yeah, I wasn't sure where to go.
I even asked Eric for advice.
I was really surprised.
What do you girls talk about?
We talk about boys and stuff.
You do? So is there someone you like?
Who?
Me?
Right now?
Hmmm...
-No one.
-No one?
No.
-No, but...
-No, but?
-No, but... you know.
-What?
"You know" what?
Are you interested in anyone?
Right now?
You are?
Let's go eat somewhere again.
-What?
-Let's go to that other place next time.
The other place you said was good.
-Let's go there next time.
-Sure.
Let's go.
Would you go if I asked you again?
Yeah.
I'll go.
Plan on it, then.
-Let's go.
-Will you make the plans?
-A lot happened.
-Yeah.
-A lot.
-First, Naomi's going to Japan for work.
-She sort of confessed her feelings.
-She did!
-But what happened?
-He lightly...
-Yuya lightly brushed it off.
-He did.
Like this.
-And Naomi lightly went to Japan.
-Yes, she did.
She said, "I already made a move."
Do you know the manga Nana?
There's a famous scene where Sachiko says,
"It was on purpose."
She's having a drink with a guy she likes.
When it gets late, she says,
"I'll miss the last train."
The guy says,
"Hurry. Run. It's your last train."
But as they run up the stairs
at the station, Sachiko trips
and misses the last train.
The guy says, "Oh, no, you missed it."
But Sachiko says,
"It was on purpose."
-Oh, that's good.
-Right?
It was like that.
"I already made a move."
She reveals her intentions indirectly.
She's not gonna have fun on that plane.
-She'll be thinking about a lot.
-Like what everyone's up to.
To be gone for a week at this point...
-It's a little too long, isn't it?
-It's long.
And Yuya is pretty forward with Avian.
-He makes new plans with her.
-Right.
It's nice when a guy is forward.
-It is nice.
-He's confident.
When Yuya asks,
"So is there someone you like?"
And Avian says,
"Hmmm..."
"No one."
-After that "no one..."
-Those sunglasses...
may have been hiding her feelings.
"Thank goodness I have these.
He can't see how nervous I am."
She isn't in love with Yuya or anything,
but she's willing to go out.
-She said "but" at the end.
-Yes, as in, "but this is a possibility."
-Like, we don't know what may happen?
-Yeah.
When she asks Yuya, "What about you?"
He says, "Yeah, there's someone."
-"You do?"
-It seems so fun.
The expression
after the "there is someone."
That expression was so good.
That was good.
-So many great scenes, right?
-So many.
-Did you guys make dinner today?
-No, I haven't eaten yet.
-You haven't?
-No.
When did you get back?
Around 7:00.
I ate a lot for lunch,
so I'm not hungry at all.
-The pasta that took three hours?
-Yeah.
Oh, and today...
we had a meeting about the pop-up store.
Will you come around and look?
This wall and all...
This front wall...
-We were wondering what to do.
-Okay.
We were going to just paint it at first...
but then we thought we'd put wallpaper
and add a pattern.
But since we came up with that...
we haven't been able to settle on one.
Something geometric like this?
That'll definitely look good.
-It's stylish.
-Like this...
-Oh, I really like that.
-It's nice, right? Kind of modern.
The design we'll use for the pop-up...
Yeah.
We want a design
we can use for future stores.
So you want something like this
If you see this,
you'd think "Oh, it's Punch Bowl Café."
That's what we want.
Something like this.
Are you drawing that yourself?
-Or are you printing it?
-So that's where I want your help.
Of course!
Help me out, then!
If we can do this...
we can keep using it in future stores.
I talked about asking Lauren out, right?
But I haven't been able to do anything.
I still haven't been able to...
mentally prepare myself.
You should be able
to ask her out on a date.
But Lauren's always doing something.
Like when she's drawing.
She says she doesn't mind talking,
but I feel like I shouldn't bother her.
I can't help but think that way.
And then I end up...
-You can't talk.
-Yeah, I fall silent.
I want to talk to her
when she's 100% focused.
Focused on drawing?
-When she's focused on the conversation.
-Oh, I see.
Why don't you just try talking with her?
A normal conversation.
Like, "Hey, let's talk."
And talk outside by the pool or something.
If you can do that,
it might make things easier.
It's also easier to ask
if the two of you are already talking.
It's really unknown territory for me.
Seriously.
Do you totally have no clue?
Yeah, I've seriously never considered...
asking someone out on a date before.
But still...
it's important I find
my own way of doing it...
I think.