-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Firstly, the love triangle of Yuya,
Avian, and Naomi.
That was a scary scene.
Should we go somewhere?
Maybe a café?
Sure. Let's go.
Why are you embarrassed?
I'm not embarrassed.
She was listening
as they flirted next door.
It was painful to watch.
-And Yuya and Avian went to lunch.
-That's right.
She pointed out how his behavior
is leading Naomi on.
Being too nice to her.
For example, when Naomi says she's cold...
you'll lend her your jacket.
-That's not my intention.
-People don't usually do that.
I think there's a line
to how nice you should be.
He said it was unconscious on his part,
but girls take that the wrong way.
He's being a real brat.
-That's right.
-Go to school, you idiot.
We don't see him going to school much.
He must be close to dropping out
by this episode.
-You think so?
-Definitely.
He's going to be expelled
within three weeks.
-Lauren's fashion show.
-She looked so cool in her bathing suit.
-Her body is outrageous.
-Yeah, so amazing.
-Yusuke was in awe.
-He got to see her in a bathing suit.
It must have been quite a day.
-It's enough to make your nose bleed.
-For sure.
And Yusuke,
inspired by a certain person...
-That's right!
-That's right.
They came!
-Seina!
-Yes!
She arrived like a new Godzilla.
I was one of the first members.
-I'm pretty much a legend.
-I knew I heard your name before.
I am a legend.
-Wow.
-I recognized your name.
Are you in love? Are you?
-Are you?
-Not at all.
Well...
-Why are you being vague?
-You definitely are.
So if there's someone
you're interested in,
you should ask them out on a date.
Thank you.
-See you!
-Thank you.
That was fun.
"Hug me," isn't it?
-She did say that.
-We got to hear her say, "Hug me."
It's the only English she knows.
-Thanks to Seina's urging...
-That's right.
Yusuke...
-This will probably be this week's focus.
-Yeah!
You want to see a movie together?
Is there anything you want to see?
I'm sure there is. I'm sure.
-Seriously?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
Something must be playing.
-But Lauren said it pretty clearly, right?
-Yeah.
She doesn't see him that way.
-At least not now.
-She doesn't see him like that.
I'm sure you know,
but I don't feel that way towards Yusuke.
You don't know what to do?
I should give him a chance.
If you go and you have fun...
then you're okay?
If nothing romantic happens,
then that's fine with me.
He asked her out because he likes her.
She's hesitant, but she'll give it
a chance, like a trial period.
She said if she has fun, then maybe...
It's a test. The first in his life.
What was your first date movie?
What was it?
We'll wait while you remember.
Oh, that's right!
The theater happened
to be showing old films.
-How hipster.
-So it was Stand By Me.
-Nice!
-One hundred points!
-One hundred points? For real?
-It's so nice!
I'm hot now.
In my case, it was Cape Fear,
the serial murderer film
with Robert De Niro.
-The scary one!
-It was heavy stuff.
De Niro just kept killing.
But somehow I still
managed to get my first kiss.
-Amazing.
-Yeah.
-You left the theater and...
-And...
while we walked,
I tried my best to lighten the mood by...
-Distracting her.
-...distracting her.
And when we reached the river bank,
I kissed her.
That's so nice.
-What a great comeback.
-I did make a comeback.
What's wrong?
I'm just waiting to be asked, too.
-Should we start?
-Yes.
It was a cartoon movie for me, by the way.
Well, Yusuke asked me out today...
-to a movie.
-He asked you?
-He asked me to go.
-Oh, he asked you?
I've been pretty clear about
my feelings towards Yusuke.
-That's true.
-You know already.
I've said it...
but everyone still egged Yusuke on.
Like, "Yeah, go for it. It'll work out."
That kind of thing.
Everyone still supported him.
But you all knew how I felt.
So...
you all knew I'd reject him if he asked.
And yet, you still egged him on.
It made me mad.
It was like this was a game for you guys.
-Like it was just a joke.
-Yeah.
Yusuke was saying
that he was ready for it.
So we were letting him do
what he wanted to do.
It was ultimately Yusuke's decision.
It seems wrong for us
to tell him how you feel.
Everyone's cheering Yusuke on,
and if I reject him...
I was thinking
it would make me the bad guy.
-I don't think that at all.
-No.
MANAGER
KOZO UBUKATA
-What should we do today?
-Well...
So the day after tomorrow...
This is a little embarrassing but...
-I'm going on my very first date.
-Oh, a date.
I have the opportunity...
-I want to look my best.
-Okay.
-If you can help.
-Got it.
-She said okay, but...
-Yeah.
I'm not sure if it's because
she has feelings for me, or...
How should I put this?
If it's because she felt sorry for me.
I'm not sure which one it is.
You shouldn't think about it like that.
It might have been
a little reckless on my part, but...
I want to be honest with my feelings.
I want to be clear.
I'm just going for it.
For the first date...
you usually hold hands.
-So soon?
-That's the goal.
-No way.
-That should be the goal.
There are things that can only be conveyed
by touch between a man and a woman.
I've only just recently
been able to talk to her.
When you're going up the theater stairs...
you can take her hand to guide her.
You can imagine doing that, right?
It'd be cool if I could.
Wow.
-Here you go.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Do your best.
-I will.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
Thanks.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
NAOMI LORRAINE FRANK, 23 YEARS OLD
UNDECIDED
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
You're doing that on purpose!
-Cold?
-It's very cold.
-Okay.
-Is that it?
Okay.
Ouch!
-It didn't break.
-Ouch!
-Why didn't it break?
-That caught me by surprise.
-It didn't break.
-You're the worst!
Hey!
No fair.
That's too close.
-It's too hard to throw otherwise.
-You can do it.
Ow!
You did it!
We were hanging out here today.
-With who?
-With Naomi.
We played with water balloons.
And Avian was in a bad mood before that.
-Even before?
-Yeah.
I asked her if she wanted to join,
and she said, "No, you guys go."
So we did.
And then she asked how it went
after she came home.
I said it was fun.
Then she said I'm like a kid
and she can't keep up with me.
And I got really pissed.
-Annoyed?
-Yeah.
Our age difference has bothered me.
But I thought maybe it'd be fine.
But I've been seeing it more lately.
Yuya...
is the type of person
who always needs attention.
That neediness.
-You don't like it?
-No, I don't like it.
And I don't know how Yuya feels.
He said he comes on strong...
but he's actually not like that.
So rather than me always talking to him...
I mean...
-What he says and does are different?
-They are.
It's not just that though.
The age difference is the main thing.
Would you think that about his personality
even if you ignored the fact that he's 18?
You don't feel the same?
Me? Not really.
No?
No.
Do you talk about things
like that with him?
About what?
Like how he feels?
I was thinking of asking.
Sounds like you don't at all, then.
Even though you're so close.
So when you're with him,
-you don't have any deep conversations?
-Not at all.
We watch comedies,
or we throw water balloons
at each other. That's it.
There's no deep conversation.
We've only talked about useless stuff.
I'm sorry, but that's exactly
what I can't keep up with.
-So that's the problem?
-I'm sorry, but yeah.
What's that look for?
No, I was just like, "I see."
I still get along with him.
-We talk at night.
-Yeah.
That's how it is.
From Avian's point of view,
you always ask her out.
-Yeah.
-If I were her,
I'd probably get sick of it.
Like maybe you're just leading her on.
I think it was a similar situation.
We're not really a couple yet.
I'm attracted to her...
but I'm just hanging out with Naomi
as friends.
You're not in a relationship,
but you've shown interest
to a certain degree.
She might be feeling confused.
Avian, let's talk.
-Huh?
-Come out for a bit.
It's not happening.
To be honest with you...
I asked you out
because I'm interested in you.
I talk to you
because I want to get to know you.
So this afternoon,
I was being insensitive to your feelings.
I apologize for being inconsiderate.
You said that...
when you're interested in someone,
you're the type to take action, right?
-Yeah.
-But you're always with Naomi.
So I'm not sure how you feel about me.
To be honest, I just don't know.
You're saying I don't seem interested?
Then why would I ask you out?
Why would I ask you on a date?
You wanted to try and see how it went?
I don't know.
That's not why I asked you out at all.
You're the best for me.
I asked you out because
I want to get to know you.
I still plan to ask you out.
I just don't really understand.
So the way I act with you...
and the way I act with Naomi
is too different.
Yeah, I don't get it.
You seem to have more fun with her.
You seem to be more yourself
when you're with her.
And when you're with me,
you don't seem like yourself.
Seeing that, it just makes me think
we're not a good fit.
It just makes me wonder
if you are even aware of that.
But I think it's obvious
if you look at it from the outside.
I haven't noticed that at all.
In my mind, Naomi is a friend.
And you're someone I want to be
more than friends with.
-That part...
-It's not like that at all.
That part...
isn't distinguishable.
And that pisses me off.
But the one thing I want you to know
is that even if I seem close with Naomi...
the person I'm interested in is you.
Okay.
-I'm going in.
-Okay.
-She's annoyed.
-She's pretty upset.
There was some friction when she said,
"What's with that look?"
It's like, "If you're not interested
in me, that's fine.
But if you're interested
and asking me out on dates...
and you act like that?"
She's made it clear
she doesn't get it, right?
But Avian has never said
that she likes Shibusawa.
That's true.
She was almost cheering Naomi on.
So it's not right for her
to go yelling at Naomi.
That's true!
I'd be confused if I were Naomi.
I don't think she was yelling at Naomi.
Okay, right, she wasn't yelling.
Do you think it's jealousy?
Jealousy?
If it's not, then why did she say,
"What's with that look?"
-Maybe there's a little jealousy.
-It's a little scary.
Because she's been asked out...
-It's like jealousy oil.
-Oil?
Like truffle oil.
It's not truffle, but...
-Just a touch of aroma.
-Yes, an aroma.
-The aroma of jealousy?
-Oh, yeah.
Yes, an aroma of annoyance and jealousy.
-Annoyance topped with jealousy?
-Yes!
I see.
The chef's salad.
-Careless Yuya has done it again!
-Exactly.
That's what it is.
Aside from this, what do you think
of Lauren's behavior?
Is it acceptable? I mean...
I'm a little turned off.
If everyone takes Yusuke's side
and she doesn't go out with him,
she thinks they'll think badly of her.
She feels pressured.
But does she...
have to tell everyone
she's not interested in him?
As Yusuke becomes a man...
"Ask a girl out on a first date."
"Done." Stamp.
-"Stamped."
-He gets a stamp.
"Research and prepare for the date."
-"Done." Stamped.
-Stamped.
But Yusuke getting rejected
also gives him another stamp.
That's right. It's fine.
It all depends on how she rejects him.
But she's not the type of girl
that'll take young Yusuke
and play with him
in the palm of her hands.
-She takes him seriously.
-Yes.
Remember there was the girl
who held hands with Arman?
And then said she saw him as a brother?
The hat-maker from Kagoshima.
-You loved the hat-maker from Kagoshima!
-That's right.
It was her black hair
and that she's from Kagoshima.
Why wouldn't she be good?
-So you've stamped "black-haired."
-Yes.
Not all black-haired girls are good.
-You've graduated from that.
-Yes. Blondes can be good people, too.
Yes, so you learn one by one.
I hope Yusuke gets a lot of stamps.
That's right.
What's with the straw hat?
-Oh, a friend--
-I'm back.
Welcome back.
Where were you?
-I bought clothes.
-You serious?
It's tomorrow.
Wow.
-I'm nervous, but excited.
-That's right, it's tomorrow.
Yeah. Kozo, the hair stylist,
gave me some advice.
-Like what?
-That if it's a date...
then I should at least hold her hand.
That's what he told me.
-I was like, "Really?"
-Are you going to?
He said touching brings you closer.
-You mean physical contact?
-Yeah, he said it's important.
So...
I was thinking maybe that's true.
I'm considering it.
It's best to do it naturally.
If you make awkward physical contact,
it might be like sexual harassment.
Be careful.
That's true.
I'd hate if she thought that of me.
So this is what I bought today.
According to Kozo,
you can't go wrong with white.
A white shirt.
Or so he told me.
But I tried various ones on today.
This isn't quite pink, but reddish.
I got confused and couldn't decide.
-What about your pants?
-It depends on your pants.
I also bought boots.
-You bought boots?
-Boots, too?
Yeah, they're brown.
It really depends on the pants.
Should I do black or these?
Denim.
-That.
-This?
White looks super serious.
-So it's better to be more casual?
-Yeah.
I see.
After the movie,
you're gonna go out and eat?
Yeah, maybe dinner.
-Wow.
-Where?
It should be somewhere she could eat.
-Like vegan food?
-Yeah, somewhere with vegan food.
Otherwise, it wouldn't work.
I was going to give some options.
I took quite some time.
You've already asked her to dinner?
-Not yet.
-Not yet? So tomorrow?
-After the movie?
-Probably.
-Sounds good.
-Sounds fun.
It sounds like fun.
Are you nervous?
Yeah.
Pretty nervous.
-Good.
-Good? Good.
Okay, then should we go?
-What time does it start?
-Let's see.
I think it's at 4:30 p.m.
-Oh, then let's get tickets.
-Should we go?
It's been a long time.
This isn't a sequel or anything, right?
It's a new work?
-Yeah.
-But it's the same...
It's a new work by J.K. Rowling.
So it's by the same author
as Harry Potter?
It's not Harry Potter,
but it's the same author.
-The feel will probably be similar.
-Oh, the same author.
I'm looking forward to it.
-I'm also looking forward to it.
-It'll be good I'm sure.
-Here?
-Is it here?
All right.
-What'd you think?
-It was insane.
-Did you like it?
-I want to talk about it more.
-You know?
-Ah, the movie.
It got dark so early.
It's already 7:00 p.m.
Yeah.
Already? 7:00 p.m., huh?
It's late.
Are you hungry, Lauren?
I'm a little hungry.
Do you want to get dinner?
-No?
-I have dinner with my grandma on Fridays.
-I see.
-We eat together.
Then don't worry about it.
-I'm sorry today doesn't work.
-Don't worry about it.
Thanks.
-Bye. Thanks.
-Bye.
He still followed through
with his reservations.
That's so true.
-Yeah, you'd normally cancel it.
-Bittersweet.
But he went by himself
and told them he had reservations.
I'm giving him three stamps!
-He got a lot this time.
-He did well.
What do you get for these stamps?
You can't ask that.
You can't think of it like that.
What would you exchange them for?
Well, for example...
an easy woman.
-You're the worst!
-No, Yamachan! No. Just no!
Why would five stamps get you
an easy woman?
What do you think women are?
So if you collect stamps...
If you collect a lot of stamps,
easy women will be around
before you realize.
Will they?
A lot of stamps means
you've become an impressive man.
At one point, God will reward you
with an easy woman.
Don't look this way, Triendl.
What do you mean by "easy women"?
By "easy women", he means "angels."
"Angels"?
A different type of girl from you.
A different class of "angels."
You're an angel in class one.
But there are angels in class eight, too.
A class pretty far away.
Yes, so you'd never cross paths
in the hall.
-It's a different department.
-Yes.
We have to ease the mood
to offset that sad scene.
It really was sad.
In the end,
after being rejected by a woman,
you eat catfish?
What's with that?
If this were a movie or a drama,
it'd be pretty cliché.
-But this is real.
-That's right.
If the context hadn't been set,
and she had dinner plans with her grandma,
then I'd think that
this was just bad timing for Yusuke.
But right up until then,
she kept saying how she didn't
want to be the bad guy.
And for her to say
she's having dinner with her grandma,
isn't that a little...
terrible of her?
By limiting it to just the movie,
she's hinting how she feels towards him.
That she doesn't like him?
So there's Lauren, who lives
by her own rules and expresses herself,
and then there's Yusuke,
who took a step towards adulthood.
Then he said, "Don't worry about it",
and went to eat alone
since he made a reservation.
-That was impressive.
-Right?
He experienced all the flavors
of the catfish.
He'll never forget that taste.
I'm sure he couldn't taste anything.
That's why, years down the line,
when he goes to the movies
with a girl he really likes,
and they have catfish after,
that's when he'll really taste catfish
for the first time.
How romantic!
It is, but can we move the focus
away from catfish?
Yusuke would say,
"So this is what catfish tastes like,"
And his future girlfriend would say,
"Is this your first time having catfish?"
And Yusuke would answer,
"Yeah, it's my first time."
And he'd look at the camera and...
And then...
It turns into a comedy.
It turns into a comedy!
-You're not satisfied?
-I can't agree.
You're all being too positive,
and not caring enough.
But then, what is caring?
Oops, sorry. I'll do this on YouTube.
-Welcome back.
What?
How was it?
-We went to see a movie.
-What did you see?
Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
-Harry Potter?
-It's the same world, but new.
-I wanted to see that.
-That sounds good!
-I want to see it.
-It was really good.
Yeah, the movie was good.
-Entertaining?
-It was.
How was Yusuke?
What was he like?
He asked if I wanted to have dinner after.
To go have dinner with him.
But I told him it's Friday
and my grandma cooked already
so I was going to have dinner with her.
And that was it.
-So it was just the movie?
-Yeah, just the movie.
We didn't talk much
since we were in a movie theater.
That's how it went.
Are you okay?
I'm not interested in him.
-No interest?
-None.
-He's good as a friend?
-He's good as a friend.
You can't see him as anything more.
It was...
How should I put this?
We couldn't talk much.
Or, I mean...
there was no time to talk.
-None?
-Yeah, none.
There must have been some.
While we were in line for tickets,
and a little during the previews,
I tried to talk to her.
What about during dinner?
Dinner...
She had plans with her grandma.
-What?
-Really?
-She said she does every Friday.
I had forgotten.
-I see.
-So I went to eat by myself.
She does go every Friday, that's right.
-Totally forgot about that.
-Me, too.
It was a surprise.
-But did you ask her to dinner anyway?
-I did.
And she said she can't
because of her grandma?
Yeah, she apologized.
But, actually...
she cares about her family.
And she should take care of her grandma.
It can't be helped.
-Yeah, it can't be helped.
-Yeah.
Still, it must have been a shock.
Yeah, it definitely got to me.
It felt like she was just being nice.
Like she came to be nice.
It didn't feel right to me.
It felt uncomfortable.
Yeah.
It was a really good experience.
And Lauren...
she's a really good person
for even coming with me.
But for me...
after today...
going out together made me think...
that maybe we're not a good fit.
But you wouldn't have known that
without going on a date.
It's not something you'd know
from just hanging out at home.
I think it was good.
So, what I'm thinking at this point...
is that I'm going to give up.
Yeah.
If you're saying you want to give up,
then you're free to do that.
If you say you want to try asking her
out again, then I'm here for you.
I don't know...
what'll happen in the future.
But for now...
I think...
I should focus more on what I need to do
and what I'm working on now.
There's something
that's been bothering me.
Everyone seems to have the wrong idea
about Yuya and me...
and our relationship.
It's true that, at first,
I was certainly interested in him.
But the biggest reason for that
was because my last boyfriend of six years
had the exact same name.
-Yuya?
-Yeah.
And I used to call him Yuya-kun.
I was drunk on the feeling
of calling him that.
So I was interested,
but not because I liked him.
I really think of him as a friend now.
Yeah.
I wanted to apologize,
if I made you feel uncomfortable...
every time you were out
on a date with him.
I want you to go out with him
without worrying about anything.
I'm not sure where you guys are at, but--
-I'm glad you told me.
-Was it better I did?
Yeah, it's better.
Of course.
I was really worried about it.
And I wanted to hear your thoughts, too.
I was going to talk to you about it.
I've wanted to tell you that.
Thank you.
-Oh, wow.
-Looks so good!
Wow.
Now, on to the main topic.
I'm leaving.
What?
You're kidding.