-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobile.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Let's see, last week...
Oh, the new member, Tamaki!
-Taishi.
I work as an actor in Hollywood.
-How long have you lived there?
-A year and a half, almost two.
What do you plan on doing in Hawaii?
I plan on falling in love in Hawaii.
Falling in love is great motivation.
He's a passionate man.
Anna showed him around Waikiki
and they had lunch together.
He also invited Lauren to lunch.
-He's a man of action.
-Yes.
You have a beautiful face.
-Lauren seemed quite happy about it.
-That's right.
And from his conversations
with both Lauren and Anna...
I would give him 100%
-Yes, he's very likeable.
-Very mature.
Just as it seemed like everything was
peachy at Terrace House,
a terrible incident--
Sorry, I can't help but laugh.
You seem so happy.
It's just so entertaining.
-Yuya and Avian...
-Was there?
The basketball incident, Torichan!
Let's go out on a date.
A Christmas date.
I don't know. I can't think of anything.
I'll come up with some options.
What would be good?
I want to have Christmas dinner.
-Things like that happen sometimes.
-Do they?
Because the moment
she really started liking Yuya,
he was like, "You're coming on too strong,
old hag. Gross."
-He said no such thing!
-You've added to it.
-Wasn't it like that?
-Not at all.
Like, "Old hag!" and then, wham!
-There was no "old hag, wham!"
-There was none of that.
-But Ken, too...
-Yeah.
For her to say she's his Cinderella
while Yuya is feeling that way...
It's like, "Cinderella?"
Such a realist!
It's very real.
It's fine if you're both
at the same emotional place.
These are all just our conjectures.
In reality, maybe we had Yuya all wrong.
-He is empty-headed after all.
-You're being harsh.
Maybe he just happened
to have less energy.
Maybe he happened to be at the sad part
of the manga he's reading.
So he answered with that vibe.
-How simple of him!
-It's a possibility.
-Things may be clarified today.
-Maybe.
-You're working tomorrow, too?
-Yes, tomorrow, too.
-Can I come visit?
-Sure.
Come.
They made lunch plans, too.
And Eric...
when are you going to finish your store?
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
MOVED TO OKINAWA WHEN HE WAS SIX
'13 GRADUATED COLLEGE
BEGAN MODELLING & ACTING
'15 MOVED TO HOLLYWOOD
JOINS HYPER TALENT MANAGEMENT
LAST RELATIONSHIP: 4 YEARS AGO
-It's spacious.
-It is.
-It's pretty big.
-I'm surprised.
-Is it your first time here?
-Yeah, it is.
-Have any recommendations for me?
-Recommendations?
This one's popular.
Diamond Head.
I see. Nice, it's cute.
What about this one?
I was just thinking that.
It's in gray, too.
Maybe I'll buy it.
-Which color do you want?
-This one.
It's a gift from me.
What?
Seriously?
-Are you sure?
-That's why I was pushing you to get two.
-Seriously? Are you sure?
-Sure.
Well, then I'm grateful.
-I'll pay for lunch.
-Don't worry about it.
No, I'll pay. I'd feel too bad otherwise.
-Are you sure though?
-Yeah.
Should we go eat? It's noon.
-Should I wait outside?
-Yeah.
-This is a nice place.
-And the weather's so nice today.
-Yeah.
This is cute.
Maybe I'll work at a place like this.
-I think that'll be good.
-Yeah?
-Looks so good.
-Right?
-Bon appétit.
Omelet...
-How is it?
-It's good.
Is it?
It's good!
I feel so good.
It's good, isn't it?
Good food, good weather...
I love Hawaii.
What did you study in college?
Graphic design and business.
I also studied management.
You studied in Shanghai...
-for two or four years?
-Four years.
I studied Chinese and some business.
And then you went to Los Angeles?
Los Angeles and then Shanghai.
So LA was first. What did you study there?
I studied graphic design in LA.
Have you ever dated an American?
-Yes.
-Have you dated someone Japanese?
-A Japanese guy?
-No, not Japanese.
-So you don't have experience with them?
-No, I don't.
You seem like the type to commit.
Maybe. Well, I'm not sure.
-You seem like you'd be a good mom.
-A good mom?
A mom? What do you mean?
-I don't know if that's good or bad.
-It's good.
It's a good thing.
What did you talk about today?
With Avian? Well...
why she came to Terrace House,
what type of person she's dated...
-and vice versa.
-Wait.
-You've had lunch with each of the girls?
-I have.
I'm a little tired.
Going out for lunch
on consecutive days is tiring.
Having gone out with each of them,
who made the best impression?
-Best impression?
-Well, I mean...
Having gone out with them,
did you feel anything?
Well, I felt more with Anna.
I think she is the most similar...
to the type of girls I have dated.
-Are you having boy talk?
-You can join.
I don't want to interrupt.
You should have
some of the soup Lauren made.
Really? Can I have some?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
-It was good.
-What did you do today, Lauren?
I went to art class and drew a nude--
Well, it's not really a class,
but there was a nude model.
-Oh, you mentioned that.
-The model holds a pose for ten minutes.
Are they totally naked?
You want to try?
-There's no way.
-No way!
You guys are downstairs?
You've been home?
-I just got back.
-Oh, really?
-Did you pass by upstairs?
-I did.
No way. I didn't notice.
You're dressed in mellow colors today.
-I was at hula earlier.
-I see.
Do you have an early day tomorrow?
No plans apart from surfing.
Then let's talk, Taishi,
just the two of us.
Sure. Should we go somewhere?
-Outside? Do you think it's cold?
-I think it's fine.
Let's go outside.
How can we get out... from here?
I wonder if it's raining.
There was a little on my way back.
I don't think it is.
-It might be a little cold though.
-Right?
It's winter. It's been really cold lately.
The wind is so cold!
Are you okay? Do you need a blanket?
I do. Do you have one?
-I'll go get one. Hold on.
-Thank you.
So cold!
-Here.
-Thank you.
-It looks super warm.
-Is it yours?
No, it was here.
Thank you. It's so warm!
-It almost looks hot, actually.
-Not at all.
Was there something
you wanted to talk about?
I wanted to talk about the girls.
The other two girls...
have been living together
for two and a half months.
They've formed a relationship.
It's a little tough to break into that.
-It's tough being a girl.
-And...
even though they both speak Japanese,
they're not Japanese.
-That's right, neither one is Japanese.
-Yes!
When I hear them speaking in English
in the bathroom...
I'll unconsciously decide not to go in.
-I see.
-Yeah.
You and I came around the same time.
The same day, actually.
So I wanted to talk to you
and hear your thoughts as well.
It's tough at first.
To be honest, this is the most stress
I've felt in my life.
Seriously?
Is there something you want to do here?
What are you thinking?
I do think I should spend more time
with them.
Yeah, talking with only me
and talking with everyone
are totally different things.
So I think... it's just the beginning.
Yeah, it's just the beginning.
-We just started.
-Yeah.
It's gotten a little chilly.
-Should we go in?
-Should we?
Thanks for bringing this.
Will you take it back?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
-I've got the coffee.
-Are you okay? Need a hug?
-Hugs are important.
-Thank you.
LAUREN TSAI, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ILLUSTRATOR, MODEL
YUYA SHIBUSAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
ASPIRING ACTOR
AVIAN KU, 26 YEARS OLD
SALESCLERK
ERIC DE MENDONCA, 27 YEARS OLD
CARPENTER
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
TAISHI TAMAKI, 29 YEARS OLD
ACTOR
Where should we put this?
-For now...
-For now.
Will it stand?
-This is fine.
-Should we flip it?
This is fine.
I'll be looking forward
to what it'll look like at 6:00.
-Okay, thanks.
-Are you okay?
We're good.
-Seriously, thanks. It helped a lot.
-We're cheering you on.
-Later. See you later.
-I'll treat you guys.
Thanks.
-It's finished.
-It is.
-Nice work.
-Good work.
-You're going to have coffee makers?
-Yeah.
Nice.
-It's finally done.
-Nice work.
-A long road?
-A seriously long road.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Did you see Lauren's work?
It's so cute!
YUSUKE AIZAWA, 18 YEARS OLD
MUSICIAN, UKULELE PLAYER
How are you? Long time no see!
It's nice to meet you.
-Taishi?
-Taishi, nice to meet you.
-I heard a lot about you.
-Nice to meet you. I'm Anna.
I brought you a little food.
-Seriously?
-You two, eat.
We're so hungry.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
How's school, everything, life?
I'm so busy. There's so much to do.
-How's the music?
-Music?
I'm going to Japan next year.
Seriously? When?
In May, the day after I graduate.
I'm going to Tokyo.
-We're going to get dinner!
-Bye, Eric!
-Thank you very much!
-See you later!
-See you! Good luck!
-Thanks!
Good luck!
Thanks for yesterday.
-It meant a lot...
-No problem.
...your help.
If you and Taishi weren't there,
the opening would've been delayed
by three hours.
It doesn't feel like I'm leaving today.
You don't have to leave.
I'm glad that someone like you was
at Terrace House.
That's my line.
We messed around most of the time.
You were the only one
I could mess around with.
Are you good on time?
I guess I should get going soon.
See ya.
-What's that?
-You already know, don't you?
-You saw it, right?
-I didn't, I didn't.
Here.
Oh, man!
Thank you.
Seriously, thank you.
I...
What's wrong?
I shouldn't be the one crying.
No worries.
He's been crying all morning.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-All morning.
I'm glad I met you.
-I think it's toughest on Yuya.
-Me, too.
-Please keep in touch with him.
-I definitely will.
He really thinks of you as a brother.
-I do, too.
-Really.
-Thank you, Eric.
-You, too.
I should get going then.
Well, my bag...
A false start.
-It wasn't a hug.
-Thank you.
It's not really goodbye.
-Bye, Eric. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-See you.
Be well.
-See you!
ENOSHIMA, KANAGAWA
CHIGASAKI, KANAGAWA
-You're leaving tomorrow?
-Yeah.
-Are you gonna take it?
Thank you.
-So I should return it?
-Yeah.
-If you break it...
-If I break it? That can't be helped.
I thought it'd be interesting
to be in the competitions there.
-You're okay living with a group?
-With a group?
-Maybe you're used to it.
-Yeah.
-But it's with girls, right?
But I'm not too worried, to be honest.
You're going to have to interact
with the girls.
-Yeah.
-I've seen the show a little.
You have to establish
your personal life there.
It'll be great if you can balance it
with surfing.
-He finally finished.
-He finally did.
He spent a long time on it
and it was... that.
You stop that.
The inside of that counter was amazing.
-The way the bottle moves across?
-It's very high-tech.
There were only two things on the menu,
hot coffee and iced coffee.
-You be quiet.
-It was really just a soft opening.
Are you sure?
And Anna, since she and Taishi
are both new members,
opened up to him
and told him her anxieties.
He said, "Are you okay?
Do you need a hug?"
-He's so sweet.
-"Thank you."
He did do that.
-He seemed to have an ulterior motive.
-Definitely.
He mentioned right before
that Anna is like the girls he's dated.
He did say they tended to be like Anna.
Of course he's worried, sincerely worried,
hence the hug.
If the hug means more, then so be it.
-There was that.
-There was a little of that.
But before that, when she says she wants
to talk to him alone,
there was a quick shot
of only Lauren's head.
She had a cushion.
She didn't take her head off.
"I'm going to the bathroom.
Continue talking."
The body went to the bathroom.
It's connected by Bluetooth.
-Bluetooth?
-Bluetooth.
-Really?
-How very advanced.
Lauren Tsai.
Even the name sounds like a mobile suit.
-That's true.
-So the body is Tsai?
There's a hint
that Lauren might like Tamaki.
-Just a hint.
-Yes, there is.
They did seem like they had fun.
Their first outing was nice.
It's like she's totally forgotten
about Yusuke.
-That's not true.
-Completely forgotten.
It's like, "The chubby one's gone.
The hot one's here. Yay!"
Chubby out, hot in!
Stop that.
And after the pop-up party,
he said he would leave.
And now we have a new member from Shonan.
-From Chigasaki.
-A surfer.
The place where Terrace House began.
He did seem attractive.
I'm looking forward
to seeing the top half of his face.
-Okay, ready.
-Nice.
-It finally feels like Christmas here.
-Doesn't it?
Ready? Go!
This is fun.
-I love this stuff.
-I won't lose!
Lauren looks like she doesn't.
-She's making tea.
-No, no.
-I'm a little out of it because I'm sick.
-You should rest.
Two, four, six, eight.
-I don't understand these two.
-Be quiet!
Be quiet.
The task was a little tedious,
so we made it into a race.
-Seriously?
-Two, four, six...
Watch out!
That's cute.
-Why won't you respond?
-Oh, me?
No way!
Now?
Who is it?
The tree looks really good! It's cute.
-Seriously?
-Get ready everyone.
-I'm getting nervous.
-Oh, man.
-I'm getting really nervous.
-Everybody get ready.
I'll go get the door.
It's a new guy, right?
Get ready.
-Good evening!
Wow, he's got a surfboard.
-Good evening.
Amazing.
Excuse me.
-It's nice to meet you. I'm Guy.
-Guy?
-Are you a surfer?
-Yes, I'm a pro surfer.
-Seriously?
-I work at the beach.
Are you from Hawaii?
No, I'm from Shonan.
From Shonan?
-You arrived today?
-Yes, this afternoon.
-How old are you?
-I just turned 20.
Oh, 20.
-So you can drink then.
-Not over here.
-Oh, you can't!
-That's right.
GUY SATO, 20 YEARS OLD
PRO SURFER
How long have you surfed?
It's been 15 years already.
-Fifteen years?
-I've surfed since I was five.
Competitions?
Yes, I've been in many.
So if I look up "Guy, surfer,"
you'd come up?
I think so.
-Have you been to Hawaii before?
-I used to come every year.
-I see.
-For surfing?
Yes, ever year I'd mainly go
to the North Shore.
-For competitions?
-Yeah.
Insane! Let's have him teach us all.
I surf, but only as a hobby.
I saw you surf on TV.
The level is totally different!
You looked like you were enjoying it.
Did you get your tan
from surfing in Japan?
From the sun in different places.
-So you've surfed in different places?
-Yes, different places.
-For competitions, you mean?
-Yes, mainly competitions.
Amazing!
Should we finish the tree first?
-I agree.
-We're decorating the tree right now.
-Let's do it.
Do you plan to surf here?
-Here?
-Mainly competitions?
Yes, I plan to attack the big wave.
-The pipeline?
-How cool!
-My sponsor's house is right in front.
-Oh, Volcom!
-Volcom house!
-Oh, Volcom.
They were saying
the pro surfers stay there.
-But, wow, a pro at 20.
-Yeah, definitely.
When did you start competing?
When I was about seven or eight.
-What made you start surfing?
-What made me start?
-You were five.
-Yes.
-Your dad...
-Yes, the usual. My dad used to surf.
-Isn't this starting to look messy?
-That's what's cute!
Amazing! It's finished!
-A pro surfer...
-Do you want to see the boards?
Can I? I want to see.
Nothing weird should come out.
It would be amazing if something did.
Oh, you have it all wrapped.
Wow.
Seems very professional.
This is the one you always use?
Yeah, but I use all of them.
Amazing.
-These are your sponsors?
-Yes, clothing...
-Wow.
-Yuya, your school...
How long are you going for?
I haven't decided,
but no later than March.
No later than March?
So you can do that?
It's nice that you can study English.
I want to go, too.
Can I go just like that?
You'd have to start next session,
but I think so.
I want to try different things right now.
So that's why you came to Terrace House?
You want a challenge?
Well, not challenge myself, but...
I thought it'd be a good opportunity
to experience
what other people experience.
I'm 20, but the past 15 years
have been about surfing.
I want other passions, too.
Is it your first time living
with girls and guys?
Yes, it is.
By the way,
what kind of girl is your type?
I like girls who are a little quirky.
-Natural?
What about looks?
Do you prefer someone cute or cool?
-The girly type.
-Me, too.
-You're rivals?
-Are we?
I can't afford to lose.
-This seems like it'll be fun.
-It is.
-He's so cute! Guy.
-He's a good guy.
All I hear is "Cute! So cute!"
-He's cute.
-It's comforting.
I want one at home!
-You want a Guy at home?
-Yes, one at home.
I want him to say, "Welcome home!"
Another kind of Guy will appear
in the middle of the night, Torichan.
Night Guy? Seriously?
Night Guy?
Night Guy is going to be something.
He talks with that slow pace,
but when he surfs...
Oh, that contrast!
All the girls are imagining him
attacking the big wave.
I see, I see.
He speaks with a lisp
and seems a little nervous.
-He's cute when he smiles.
-He is.
I want to give him a rice ball.
Like, "Here, good luck."
"Here, good luck."
"Thanks for the rice ball.
It was really tasty.
I like pickled sour plums inside.
Thank you."
It's so cute!
I wonder what he's like when he surfs.
-I wanna see!
-Like, "Oh, Guy, you're so different."
I'm sure.
He's going to be amazing.
We've had some surfing scenes.
Some of the members surfed.
-But this is on a different level.
-I'm sure.
Like, "Wait, Guy, you're on a sea turtle!"
He doesn't even need a board.
This isn't about
whether he's good or not anymore.
He's like Urashima Taro
from the folk legend.
But he brought all his boards.
"There was a turtle,
so I rode the turtle."
"I rode the turtle."
I wanna see that scene.
-Will they have the turtle scene?
-I want him to ride a turtle.
-It would be so cute.
-They all like the girly type.
-Is Anna the only girly one of the three?
-For now.
So there might be a battle.
Will there be?
-What about Yuya and Avian?
-They seemed fine.
What was that all about?
I told you so.
Did you say that, Torichan?
So it was just his mood.
Damn you for making me hope.
I hope he confesses his feelings to her.
How will the episode end?
Right as he's about to attack a big wave,
it'll end.
-End on the attack?
-Then it would be a surfing show.
ANNA HANEISHI, 22 YEARS OLD
PART-TIMER
'14 MOVED TO HAWAII
ENROLLED AT LEEWARD COMMUNITY COLLEGE
'15 BEGAN WORKING AT THE SANDBAR
AND VINTAGE CAVE HONOLULU
'16 GRADUATED COLLEGE
LAST RELATIONSHIP: 2 YEARS AGO
-Avian, I'm sorry I'm late!
-That's all right.
-Did you wait long?
-No, it's fine.
Wow! I've never been here.
-It's our date.
-That's true. This is a date spot.
Did you make plans for Christmas?
The 24th?
The 24th... It's tomorrow, right?
-It's tomorrow!
-You're going to dinner and...
-And ice skating.
-That's right!
We're gonna go ice skating
and then we'll probably go for dinner.
So there isn't anyone specific
you want to be with?
Hanging out with Taishi is fun.
You should go on dates with each of them.
Wow!
It's so romantic!
This is totally a date.
Are you going to surf on Christmas, too?
What are your plans?
-If there are waves, I'd like to.
-I'm sure it'll be fine in the morning.
How old were you when you turned pro?
-I was in seventh grade.
-So young!
-You're at the top?
-I'm ranked about 15th.
-15th?
-Amazing!
This year.
It makes me disappointed in myself.
-Why?
-It makes me think I need to work harder.
You're 20, right? It's amazing.
But surfing on Christmas is a little sad,
isn't it?
What about you, Taishi?
Me?
I'm interested in Anna right now.
-The one who came on the same day as you?
-Yeah. She's cute.
Anna, huh?
Were you nervous when you asked Avian out?
-I didn't ask her out. She asked me.
-Oh, really?
But I was embarrassed.
I was cold to her out of embarrassment.
I know what you mean.
I tend to say the opposite of what I mean
to hide my embarrassment.
But it's already Christmas.
I'm hoping to tell her how I feel now.
For me, the things to look out for
would be...
to always open the car door for her...
or to pull out the chair for her.
Guys, especially Japanese guys,
are hesitant to do that kind of thing.
I've gotten better
since I moved to the US.
But truly treating women
like they're women in this way...
seems to make them happy.
It helps to focus on them
and not on yourself.
Focus on their happiness
instead of your own embarrassment.
It makes it easier.
If you think of how happy it'll make her,
you'll want to do it
even if it's embarrassing.
-That's really great.
-What if it doesn't make her happy?
-That's why dating is scary.
-Yeah.
I've failed so many times because of it.
I know it can be really scary.
But that's what I came here to do,
so you should to.
You're right.
So what if you get hurt?
So you both like each other.
I wonder...
I'm just kidding. That's a lie.
What made you like Yuya?
His personality.
I like people who are sweet.
But he gets embarrassed easily.
-Yuya? Does he?
-Really embarrassed.
His tone can be harsh,
but he doesn't really think that way.
His words can be harsh,
but he's just hiding his embarrassment.
-He's sweet.
-But you're not going out?
Yeah. The timing...
Won't it happen on your Christmas date?
It's all going to happen
on the Christmas date?
It's Christmas!
I don't know.
I have a lot of worries, too.
I'm scared our relationship will change.
I'm a little scared.
But what will you do
if Yuya asks you to go steady tomorrow?
-He won't.
-Why?
He won't.