ROOM 305
Alright!
Good morning.
Hey, about tomorrow...
Tomorrow?
He is here, he is here! Excuse me.
Quickly, quickly!
Oh my God!
Second Grade A class! Uehara Hisashi.
He's so cool.
Any cool guy, that's enough for you right?
But he's just so cool!
Just looking at him gives me strength.
Uehara!
Yes?
Um, we would really like you to join
our first year Xmas party
as a special guest.
This is an invitation.
I don't want it.
You must have a death wish,
breaking the "Top three" rules like that.
The top three boys are for everyone.
It is unforgivable for you,
especially when you're a freshman.
Let's discuss things slowly.
You must be taught the rules properly.
INCOMING CALL
FROM MOM
Wait... hang on...
Hello, hang on a second.
Hang on.
What do you want, Mom?
I called them. Don't worry about it.
Just make sure you do things properly.
If anything happens,
I'll come straight away.
Got it. OK, I've got to go.
Hey.
You scared me!
What did you want to talk about?
What?
I don't want to go out with anyone.
Also, I don't know how you got my address,
but this kind of threat is unacceptable.
"Dear Uehara Hisashi,
I'll be waiting on the roof at lunchtime.
If you don't come..."
Oh my God! That's scary.
You're surprised even though you wrote it?
Huh? You've confused me with someone else.
I didn't write that mail.
I see...
Hey, you made a mistake!
What's with the attitude?
And...
You should speak more kindly to girls.
You even let them down.
What would you do if they jumped for real?
Leave me alone.
Hey, I'm just trying to help--
Hey,
your zipper is undone.
Just saying it to be kind.
You're the worst!
So when are we going to do this?
Her really important friend...
-Got it.
Nao?
-What?
-Here you go.
What's this?
A bit early, but, it's a moving gift
from Marina and I.
Really? For me?
Thank you, can I open it?
Of course.
I wonder what it is.
What?
The perfect item for a girl living alone!
Keep away robbers by hanging it
on the balcony.
It's also good as pajamas!
Ta-da!
What's wrong? Isn't it funny?
What? Did you even gift wrap it?
It's Mitsuishi's old ones!
Just a joke!
-Really? Sorry.
-How rude!
What is this?
Nao!
Oh... Daichi!
Hang on.
Hi, Daichi.
-Good Morning.
-Hi.
What the heck is that?
It's from these two,
in case there's a robber.
Oh, I see, you're moving tomorrow, right?
Had you forgotten?
Tomorrow, would you be able
to help us move, Daichi?
Sorry, I promised I'd go watch the match.
You still help them after retiring?
Sorry, I can't help.
No big deal. Come and visit anytime!
You shouldn't invite boys, you know!
You live by yourself now.
What do you say?
Alright.
-OK, see ya.
-Bye.
Bye, bye.
-He's so cool.
-What?
You've known him for so long.
You're slow-witted.
Daichi is the oldest guy of the top three
in Megurogaoka High School.
Top three?
Nao, you're so naive...
They were selected at the Autumn Festival.
They selected the best guy
from each grade.
Daichi from the third grade
and Uehara Hisashi from the second grade.
Uehara...
I have never been selected...
It's OK.
What do you mean "it's OK?"
Don't worry about it.
THE MOVING DAY
-Where is it?
-I don't know.
This one!
What? Really?
Yep!
-It's amazing!
-Awesome! For real?
-Let's go!
-Please let us in.
Ta-da!
Wow!
-What do you think?
-It's amazing!
It's furnished too!
-Yep.
-Hold on.
Wow, what an amazing kitchen!
Wait, what is this?
What's with this great sofa?
Yahoo!
Everyone, over here.
What is it, Mitsuishi?
It's so hot... so hot...
It's taking so long to arrange things.
I'll do the rest.
As long as I have a bed, I'll be fine.
Thanks for all your help, you two.
-It's going to be tough living alone.
-Yeah.
I'm really glad you're staying here, Nao.
-Marina!
-Nao!
This place is huge.
$800 for rent this? It's so cheap!
Yep, even the agent said I was very lucky.
You sure there's no other reason?
-What?
Mitsuishi, don't say things like that.
I mean, come on.
In the heart of town,
a new, huge place like this is for $800.
It's too good to be true.
I wonder why the last tenant moved out?
I'm sure there's a perfectly good reason.
New job, getting married...
Dying...
This place
might be haunted.
You're really going home?
Don't worry about what Mi said.
It's OK, I exorcised the place.
I'm not sure flavored salt works the same.
It's cold.
I should get the table heater out first.
It will be fine.
You've got mail.
What the hell?
FROM DATING SITE
Junk mail.
Don't scare me!
-Robber!
-Ouch, ow, hey!
What?
Huh?
You?
What?
Hang on, why are you here?
Why? My lease here starts from today.
What are you talking about?
My lease starts here today.
-What?
-You sure you are in the right room?
Get out, get out.
Hey! That hurts.
It's you that are mistaken!
Not me! Look, Room 305!
Me too, Room 305!
-Huh?
I get it, you're in the wrong building.
No, it's this one.
So, maybe you have the wrong floor?
Nope, definitely the third floor.
Sorry to interrupt,
I'll bring your things in now.
What?
CONTRACT FOR LEASE
What the...
Exactly the same contents...
The number you have dialed
has been disconnected.
Let's go.
Hang on a second, where are we going?
REAL ESTATE, CLOSED FOR GOOD
Right, next place.
What?
This is a double contract, it's a scam.
-Scam?
Usually, there would be key money,
but in this case, there is none.
In addition,
they have taken two lots of fees
from both of you and run away.
Oh no...
You mean we can't get our money back?
Probably not possible.
So, who gets to live in the house?
It looks like Mr. Uehara made
his contract first, however,
whoever pays the $1500 rent first
can live there, no problems.
-$1500?
It says $800 on the contract.
These days, that kind of place
would never let for $800, right?
What?
Nao! Congratulations on your move.
From Daichi.
Looks like Daichi came after all.
Whether we move, or stay here for $1500,
we need lots of money.
I used all my savings to move here.
Can't you ask your parents for help?
Nope.
Why do you need to live alone?
-None of your business.
-Yes, it is!
How about you?
I live alone because my parents
took over the family farm in the country.
I will stay here alone, till I graduate.
There are no dormitories available now,
so I decided to live alone.
Well, that's no big deal.
What do you mean? That's so rude.
You just stayed here because you didn't
want to live in the country, right?
You are relying
on your parents too, right?
Don't you have anyone else? Any relatives?
If you need anything,
I'll come right away.
No way...
If my parents find out,
they'll take me back to the country.
That's it!
Why don't we just live together?
What?
Think about it, there are two rooms,
and we can split the rent,
making it cheaper than before.
This is no joke, you know.
Do you know what you're saying?
Yes, it's not forever,
just until we find a new place, OK?
No way.
Not possible.
Can you afford $1500 a month, Uehara?
I can't.
So I guess I'll just have to go.
But my old place has already let,
so I have absolutely nowhere to go.
Are you sure we can't make this work?
Alright.
Really?
Yes, but just for now.
Just for now, got it.
Once we find a new place, we move.
-Both of us.
-Once we find a new place.
Once we both have the money or find
a new place, we'll move straight away.
When the girls' dorm is vacant, too.
Oh, and we got nothing to worry about us.
What?
I'm not interested in you at all.
Hey, same for me too!
I couldn't care less about you!
So, Uehara is moved by women's tears...
THREE HOURS LATER
It's not enough.
And my room is still a mess!
Pizza!
I love pizza!
What? There's none for you.
What?
But you have so much!
I'm going to eat it all.
You can have this.
KIDS MEAL COUPON
What the hell? Goddamn Kids Set!
How the hell is that skinny guy
going to eat all that pizza?
So selfish!
What are you upset about?
I'm the victim here.
-What's that?
-I made some rules.
"One, don't eat my things from the fridge.
Two, you have the bath until nine,
me, Uehara, after that.
Make sure you take a bath before that.
Three, clean the bathroom everyday
by turns.
Four, don't go in each other's room."
We can talk about the rest later.
Also, keep common areas clean!
-What a tiring...
-Also,
no boys allowed, okay?
I'm... not like that--
As if you have a boyfriend! Friends, too.
What, even girls?
It's not just your house,
and don't tell others we live together.
Don't talk to me at school either.
We are strangers, OK?
Got it.
I don't know the way.
Stay away, at least three meters.
Making rolled cabbage
What's up? Tired from moving?
Not so much...
I thought so.
Living alone in a place like that...
Sounds like paradise!
-After I finish it...
-I'd give it to Uehara.
Should I give it to him?
But I don't think Uehara would
eat so much. He's so skinny.
You're right.
No, he is like a champion eating fighter!
Uehara is so popular with girls.
I really like him. He's so my type.
What do you mean?
-What?
Yesterday you said that
you like a kind person like Daichi.
To marry, for sure, Daichi.
To date though, Uehara for sure.
I see...
Uehara!
Do you like rolled cabbage and mince?
We made it just for you!
I can't accept that.
Is it an intrusion?
To be honest, yes.
Well, see ya.
He's still so cool...
What?
-Yeah, so cool.
-I don't care if he's cold.
COFFEE SHOP
I never thought you'd actually move.
Boss, I have a favor to ask.
What's that?
Could I get a few extra shifts?
I'm a bit broke after moving.
It's no big deal for me,
but are you sure
you need to work so hard to live alone?
Please.
Dad.
Hi, Nanako. Welcome home.
Hey, don't give him grief,
just give him some extra shifts, OK?
What?
You said that
the days Uehara works,
a lot more girls come.
I guess that's true.
If it's a hassle, don't worry about it.
I'm thinking of getting another job too.
No, you can't!
What?
I mean, you already work in the morning
at the gas station, right?
If you work too much, you'll get sick.
Hey, it's got nothing to do with you,
why don't you go
and do your studies.
She's hopeless.
I'll work out some extra shifts for you.
But, have you told your family yet?
Your new address and all that?
He's out every night... playing, no doubt.
What is that?
I can let you in if you want.
Hey, this is the common space--
The table heater is perfect for winter.
It's my first time seeing that thing.
It looks pretty plain.
Fine, I'll put it away if you want.
What?
I mean...
Not now, you'll cause a commotion.
So cold.
What can I do?
I'm frozen from my part time job.
The table heater is ideal to warm you up.
Well...
The electricity cost is shared.
I am just getting my fair share.
You have a part time job?
I'm no freeloader, that's why.
Jeez, I'm so hungry.
You should have accepted it.
What?
The rolled cabbage from the girls.
What? Are you stalking me?
No, I just overheard. That's all.
We'll see.
Don't you like rolled cabbage?
No, it's one of my favorites actually.
Wow, you're strange.
But if I accept, it'll happen every day.
I see, it's so tough being popular.
INCOMING CALL
FROM MOM
-Hey, your phone's buzzing.
-Don't worry about it.
My mom is a pain,
calling three times a day.
You should answer.
Hi, Mom.
What is it?
Yeah, I know.
So damn loud!
Uehara, your alarm is ringing.
Hey, wake up, it's so loud.
I'm coming in.
What is this?
So many alarms!
So damn loud.
If you're going to work,
turn them off first!
Wow, he has some cute side.
It says "H".
Ueha...
Excuse me.
Welcome home, Uehara.
I'm so tired.
I'll take my bath in the morning.
Hey, Uehara.
Goodnight.
Hey, you didn't
go into my room, right?
I'm so sorry.
The alarm clocks were all ringing,
so I was turning them off
and I accidentally dropped
the photo frame.
I'm really sorry.
We agreed not to go in each other's room.
You broke the rules, and my stuff.
It's too much.
I didn't mean to, and the alarm clocks...
I'll replace the frame.
The photo is fine--
That's not the issue!
What?
Forget it. It doesn't matter what I say.
You're taking this too far!
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Hi!
Marina, where's your lunchbox?
I just felt like a change, that's all.
I see what you're trying to do.
-Busted!
-What are you on about?
The top three boy, Uehara, buys bread too.
Nao, are you OK?
I'm fine.
She's trying to get close to him
at the bakery.
Wow, your private eye skills are amazing!
You know Uehara lost his parents
in a car crash when he was young.
That's why he always buys his lunch.
Didn't you know? Most people know this.
Can't you ask your parents or something?
Nope.
He's just so cool.
Alone in life...
Alone in life.
Nao?
Sorry, I've got to go.
You know Uehara lost his parents
in a car crash when he was young.
You're freeloading off your parents too.
My mom is a pain,
calling three times a day.
You should answer.
Forget it. It doesn't matter what I say.
Oh, no.
RE-USE SHOP
Forget it.
Alright...
Excuse me, I'm looking for something.
It's a photo frame, there is an H here.
Nao!
Daichi.
-You're so late.
-Yes, I was looking for something.
-Were you at your sports club?
-Yes.
Because of sports, I got into university.
Everyone else is busy with their exams,
but I just kill time there.
Once you graduate, will you live alone?
No, even though the school is a bit far,
I'll commute from home, I think.
Living alone sounds great,
but it's tough, right?
Well, it's fun at the moment.
Cooking and doing laundry
sounds like a pain too.
I'm not so good at that stuff.
I'd probably order pizza every day!
That's pretty bad for you!
I know!
As you know, I'm pretty into sports.
Yeah, you're right,
it is pretty tough living alone.
What, you're already over it?
Huh? No, that's not it.
That's good.
If you need anything, call anytime.
My mom was asking about you too.
Yep, thanks.
Perfect!
Today's top news!
There have been ongoing random assaults
these past few days in Meguro District.
The victims were women in their 20's
attacked in residential areas.
They were attacked at the same time
in the same manner.
The local police are treating
these cases as connected.
The investigation is ongoing.
Still not home...
MILK PUDDING
Maybe one of these is for me?
Welcome home.
Hey, Uehara.
Hey, you ate my milk pudding.
What?
This one?
There were two,
so I thought one was for me--
What the fuck?
Huh?
First you go in my room, break stuff,
and then you eat my food?
I feel really bad about that--
There is a limit to how much I can take!
Why are you so angry with me?
I get it...
I'll buy a new one.
-That's it, right?
-Obviously!
If I go out at night and get attacked,
I hope it haunts you for life!
If anyone does dare to attack you,
I'd like to see his damn face!
Asshole!
It's just stupid pudding. What an asshole!
What's so special about him?
How is he the top three?
Excuse me.
Do you have milk puddings?
Sorry, all sold out for today.
I see.
There's a store on the
other side of the station.
Dear Uehara, I'm so sorry.
From Nao.
So cold...
There have been ongoing random assaults
these past few days in Meguro District.
I forgot my cell phone.
I'm so sorry, excuse me.
Did anyone come here and buy milk pudding?
Oh, yes.
She asked if we had any, so I told her
to go to the other side of the station.
Wow, milk pudding is so popular.
Uehara.
What are you doing?
I...
I can't understand what you're saying.
Someone was chasing me.
I was scared, so I hid.
What the...
Uehara.
What are you doing here?
What?
Oh...
I was going to buy some milk.
What an ugly face.
Okay, let's go home.
It's a bit difficult for me to say this...
You're so damn heavy,
and such a pain in the ass.
I'm really sorry about the photo frame.
You are right. I'm thoughtless.
The photo is your parents, right?
I didn't know you had lost them.
I didn't know anything.
You did well finding that same old frame.
But, it's not exactly the same.
I'm so sorry.
Rolled cabbage.
What?
For that, let's call it even.
Okay.
DELICIOUS MILK
There is already milk here.
Uehara, your alarms are going off.
Uehara.
So loud...
Everyone will be upset.
Uehara, the alarms...
You'll be late for work.
Hey, get up.
Hey...
Yuri?
What?
THIS IS A FICTIONAL DRAMA.