Wow! This is so beautiful!
What?
Quit staring at me like that.
Sorry.
Huh?
It's just that you're
a thousand times more beautiful.
Oh, Uehara.
Ow!
Huh? Where'd Uehara go?
What a handsome guy!
I forgot how popular Uehara is.
Oh, my god! You're so good looking!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Hey! What are you doing?
-Are you OK?
-Huh?
I'm just fine.
You were the one who was in trouble.
What?
-So, where to?
-Huh?
Where do you want to go?
KISHIGON FOOT SPA
You still haven't decided?
Hmm, this place is nice too.
But I don't want to miss this either.
Just choose one.
Why?
You can't go everywhere
when we don't have much time.
But...
We can come again.
Huh?
What?
Nothing.
Yeah, you're right.
We can come again... just the two of us.
Okay, let's go here!
I wanted to go here no matter what.
At this shrine,
they have these wooden votive plaques,
that grant eternal love for a couple.
Really?
I'm buying one for sure.
Dang, these stairs are steep.
Yeah. Votive plaque! Votive plaque!
PRAY FOR LOVE
ROMANCE FULFILLMENT VOTIVE PLAQUES
I'd like one of your
romance fulfillment votive plaques.
Make it two!
No, ten, please!
What are you thinking?
You don't need that many.
I want enough to last all eternity.
-What?
-Uhm...
I'm terribly sorry,
but the votive plaques just sold out.
-Huh?
-Another customer wanted all that we had.
Someone just like you.
I can't believe it.
Oh! There you guys are!
So, how did it go?
Are you two getting closer?
Our future together is unclear.
Oh! Hey, you guys!
Huh? Kitaura, you're here?
We met by chance
and wanted to go to all the same places!
You just followed me around!
It must be thanks to these.
I'm glad I bought them all.
Hey! Those are the votive plaques!
You mean you're the one
who bought them all?
Yeah.
Aw, come on! Give me one!
-Give me one!
-Why?
-No way!
I guess we're all here.
-You can't use that many!
-There are only five!
Oh, Kitaura.
They said we could add you to our room.
Why?
"Why?"
But, I thought you were all friends.
No.
Uehara just happened to give me--
Oh, by the way...
Keep quiet about that.
Right?
So, those tickets were yours,
but you want to protect her so much,
that you gave them to me.
I like knowing your weakness.
Okay, I'll take you up on your offer
and stay with you guys.
I'm looking forward to it, Nao.
Me too.
Hey! Wait for me!
Yea! Look at this! Come on!
The Mejiro room is for the men.
The ladies will stay in the Tsugumi room
on the second floor.
Okay. Thank you.
What? You mean we're not together
in the same room?
Young guys and girls in the same room?
Are you nuts?
I made sure they separated us.
I thought I was going to have a chance
to hit it off with Kitaura.
Oh!
There's a place nearby
for fulfilling romantic hopes.
-Really?
The legend is related
to those votive plaques that you have.
It's called Tragic Lovers Hill.
"It became known to help in achieving
a successful romance."
Please tell us all about it!
-Of course.
-So, tell us!
But the two of them died
without ever consummating their love.
The villagers felt so sorry for them
that they built Tragic Lovers Hill.
-Or so I've heard.
-What do you mean by that?
I'm sorry.
I've only been the hostess of this inn
for a short while.
But I've also heard that a lot of couples
that go up that hill, have had their
romantic wishes fulfilled.
Their wishes have been fulfilled?
-You've already got a boyfriend.
-She can't hear a word you're saying.
I will be going now.
Oh, that's right.
The house where the woman
in the legend was born
is right where this part of the inn is.
Sometimes
she comes here to visit...
or so I've heard.
That scared me!
But it's only a rumor.
Make yourselves at home. Good bye.
What was that?
That scared you, didn't it?
You were scared, right?
I'll have one too.
That scared you too, right?
Won't any of you admit it?
Come to think of it,
there was something
about close couples visiting the hill
and being cursed, or maybe not.
I forget which it was.
Come out.
I think it's a great plan
for bringing happiness to
me and Kitaura,
Nao and Uehara
and you two as well, of course.
I agree that it's the right thing to do.
Now we just have to figure out
how to get Nao and Uehara to join in.
But what about Issei?
Yeah.
I know. I'll treat him to ramen tomorrow.
-What?
-You forgot about him?
Crane Room
Yoshikawa Party
-This is so good!
-This is great!
-Could I have your scallops?
-My scallops?
-Yeah.
-Then give me your sukiyaki.
Here!
Okay, you two. Draw one out each.
What is this? Some kind of lottery?
You might win something nice.
Here.
Okay.
This one is for you, Kitaura.
Here, Issei.
What? Don't we even get to choose?
If it's food, I don't want it.
It's time for the Tragic Lovers Hill Dare!
-Yeah! A dare!
-Yahoo! What fun!
-This will be great!
-And scary!
Count me out.
Uhm...
I don't really want to take part
in a dare either.
Huh? "Participation Required"?
Are you crazy?
No way.
-A man can't break his promise.
-Your romantic wishes could be fulfilled.
-Are you sure you don't want to, Nao?
-Fine. I'll go. Let me eat.
-But, her ghost might show up.
-Pass me the tuna
-What?
-I'll participate, so give it to me.
Oh, that's too bad.
It seemed like such a good chance
for you to get that votive plaque
that you wanted so badly.
Votive plaque?
Votive plaque.
Votive plaque!
TRAGIC LOVERS HILL
The rules are simple.
You must bring back
my precious votive plaque that is up on...
Tragic Lovers Hill.
-I'll let you have it!
-He'll give it to you!
-Really?
-You want one, right, Nao?
Yes! I do! I do!
Oh, but do I have to go alone?
Don't you worry!
A dare should always be done in a pair.
Now check those tickets you drew earlier.
You just might be matched up
with the person of your dreams!
-Oh! It's you, Mitsuishi!
-Cool!
-Yeah!
Huh?
What happened?
Sorry! You play the ghost!
How did that happen?
Oh, dear, Abe.
You're such an idiot.
Okay, I'll be the ghost.
Leave some time between each pair.
What a totally useless ghost
he's going to be.
Is this going to be any good?
Well, to be honest,
I'm more afraid of the real ghost
than I am of Abe.
Are you seriously that scared?
-After hearing that story, yes!
-There's no ghost.
If that ghost really does show up,
I'll just run away.
-Don't run away!
-Why not?
-Uehara.
-What?
-Don't run away!
-You're looking pretty unhappy.
-Good thing it's dark, huh?
-You can't.
-Come on, let's get this over with.
-Please don't!
Boo!
Thanks for setting this up.
Why does this always happen to me?
TRAGIC LOVERS HILL
Okay, shall we go?
I'll get that votive plaque
and fulfill my romantic wishes!
Let's do it!
-Eek!
-What's wrong?
-I'm afraid!
-You're scared already?
-I can't do this!
-Let's go!
No! Wait!
You want that dumb votive plaque, right?
I'm scared! I'm scared!
SUCCESSFUL ROMANCE
Aren't you going to pray so that
your romantic wishes will come true?
I don't believe in that kind of thing.
Same here.
You decide your own fate by yourself.
Yep, that's right.
I don't like the type
that expects other people
to do things for them.
It just shows how dedicated she is to you.
She's a really cute girl.
Hold on tight to her.
Her type is actually pretty popular.
I never asked for your advice.
You sure get upset when I touch
your sensitive spot.
Would you just shut up?
Oh! Hey, you guys.
You guys sure are fast.
Did you get it already?
Yeah.
That guy is so curt.
You know they really do make a good pair.
Oh, Nao.
Just kidding.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to complain to you.
Okay, it's not far to the top
of Tragic Lovers Hill.
Let's go, Issei.
Okay.
After praying this hard,
it should work out.
Don't you agree, Issei?
That'll be enough for sure!
-Issei! Hurry! Let's go!
-Okay.
What's that?
-Huh?
-What?
What happened? Oh, no!
Let's get out of here, Issei!
It's all right. Just calm down.
Oh, no! What's that?
It's taking those two awfully long.
What are they doing?
Do you think they got lost?
How? There's only one trail.
Yeah, you're right.
Finally, they're coming back.
What took you so long, Nao?
Huh? Abe?
What are you doing here?
How come you came down first?
You mean Nao and Issei are still up there?
It was getting late,
so I totally thought they'd come down.
I wonder if something happened to them.
I'm so sorry about this.
How could you faint
at the sight of a raccoon dog?
It jumped out so suddenly,
it frightened me.
Dang, you're heavy!
Really? You're kidding! I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry, Issei.
-Just kidding.
Your boyfriend sure must have it rough.
-Ugh!
-Yeah, maybe so.
I fainted with Uehara once too.
You're so damn heavy,
and such a pain in the ass.
He carried me on his back then too.
He complained a whole lot.
When I really think about it,
I guess I do cause him a lot of trouble.
It won't take long for him
to run out of patience for me.
I've got to get my act together.
I need to think more clearly
and be more careful.
And study harder too.
How come you're the only one
who has to change?
Huh?
Shouldn't a real couple
be equal?
Shouldn't you have an effect on each other
and turn into something great together?
Yeah, there's a lot of things
you need to change.
But, there are a ton of things about him
that I think he really needs to change
as well.
Oh, Issei.
So, you see
I think it's wrong
for you to change everything
about yourself.
So a true couple should be equal, huh?
Is that the kind of romance you want?
What does that matter?
This isn't about me, anyway!
They sure are taking long.
Are you going to find them?
This won't end
until those two come back down.
You're just worried about Nao, aren't you?
-Oh, shut up!
-Uehara!
Did something happen to you?
Nao fainted.
Sorry for taking so long.
It was probably just a raccoon dog,
or something dumb like that.
How did you know?
I don't even know why you care so much
about that stupid plaque anyway.
She's doing it because she wants
you two to become closer!
I'm leaving.
-What?
-Hey!
Wait up, Uehara! Wait for me!
Hey, Uehara! Hold up!
Listen to what Nao has to say!
Dammit, Uehara! Get down.
-Huh?
-Are you okay?
Hey, Uehara! God damn, you!
I challenge you to a duel!
Winner gets Nao!
-What?
-What are you talking about, Issei?
-Issei?
How can you fight for her?
She and Uehara are dating.
This is so stupid.
Oh, I get it.
You're running away
because you're afraid you might lose.
I didn't think you were such a loser.
I'm not doing it
because it's stupid to fight over Nao.
But if you want to fight me,
go right ahead.
Then that settles it.
What?
Oh! Wait! Wait! Hold on a second here!
-What?
-Get over here!
What are you doing?
We're not finished yet!
To be honest, I really don't think Nao
has eyes for anyone else besides Uehara.
-So, please--
-Yeah, I know.
Don't worry about it. I'll lose.
-Huh?
I can't stand that Uehara isn't honest
about his feelings for Nao.
So I was thinking
this is a good way for Nao to see
how he really feels about her.
Oh, I see. That's why.
-I'm totally for that!
-Good idea, huh?
-Yeah!
-However...
what should I duel him in?
Oh, you haven't figured that out yet?
Since we're at a hot spring,
there's always the usual way.
-What's that?
-Yeah. What?
It's time now to start
the First Hot Springs
Ping Pong Competition for Yoshikawa Nao!
-Yeah!
-All right! Ping pong!
Ping pong?
Sounds like fun.
What? You're interested too, Kitaura?
The winner will be determined
after one set.
The uniforms will be yukata!
Yukata!
-Why yukata?
-It's a secret!
The winner of the competition
can do whatever they want
with Yoshikawa Nao!
What?
Who gave you the right to decide that?
Don't worry. Just watch, okay?
The heroine should simply watch
as her prince battles it out for her.
-That's not right.
-Huh?
-A real couple isn't like that!
-What?
All right, everyone, line up!
If you think you can win, step forward.
Why are you joining, Kitaura?
Because it's a perfect chance
to crush you.
What a pain this is.
-Huh?
What are you doing?
Why are you joining in?
Because I want to be equal with you,
Uehara.
I want us to be an authentic
and true couple!
Isn't that right, Issei?
Huh?
Uh... yeah.
Match one!
Yoshikawa Nao versus Uehara Hisashi!
Our bright future together
hinges upon my victory here!
I'm ready for you!
Bring it on.
One point.
I guess our future together
doesn't look good.
Match two!
Abe versus Issei!
I'm totally serious about this!
You're going down!
I thought you'd given up on Nao.
Didn't you know?
Nao and I get along really well together.
We do?
Really?
You'll never see my serve coming.
This is going to be fun.
I couldn't see it.
11 points.
-Didn't we just see the same thing?
-Yep.
Tournament Line Up
Match three.
-Kitaura Nozomi versus...
-Uehara Hisashi!
Why the heck are you taking part?
I just told you.
-This is the perfect chance.
-For what?
To crush you!
Oh, come to think of it...
Oh, yeah.
You've got some kind of grudge against me?
You snatched away the one person
who was precious to me.
Momoyama Mami.
You remember her, right?
It was when I was in elementary school.
I was really popular with the girls.
EIGHT YEARS EARLIER
Compared to those crude and vulgar boys,
I was way smarter
and way more masculine.
Mami was the one I liked the most
out of all of them.
She was as cute as a button
and would always be by my side.
-Uhm...
-Yes?
I've found a guy that I like.
What?
Uehara Hisashi.
After that,
Mami was with you all the time.
On Christmas and Valentine's Day!
"Uehara! Uehara!"
You swiped Mami's pure
and innocent heart from me!
I'll say it again.
I don't know what you're talking about.
He might just be aggravating her more.
Yeah.
Kitaura's actually has
a very interesting personality.
Uh-huh.
Today, I'm going to put an end
to this long dispute between us!
Yeah, whatever. Anyway, bring it on.
Here goes!
I did my best for you, Mami.
You're pretty awful at ping pong, Kitaura.
The time has finally come...
for the final match!
Uehara Hisashi
versus Sata Issei!
This is it, Nao!
The final match
we've all been waiting for!
Why are you getting your phone out?
If I win, I'll take Nao for mine.
Say what you like.
Here goes.
Like my snap serve?
I got good at that from making ramen!
Yes! Handsome guys dressed
in yukata are so nice!
Their exposed chests
and their flying sweat!
Yukata are so awesome!
That's why we're wearing yukata?
Keep it up, you two!
And loosen up those yukata a little too.
Oh, darn you, Uehara! What are you doing?
You could have gotten that
with your right!
Shut up and just watch.
You've got to make better use
of your footwork!
Who made you my coach?
And you've got a lot of wasted movements.
What?
Hey!
Your fault for not focusing.
That was your fault, Nao!
You pay attention, Uehara.
You'd better win.
You don't have to tell me that. I will!
-Use your right next time.
-Nah, left.
What? No, your right.
-Shut up and butt out.
-Your right!
-Don't touch me! Go away!
-Use your right.
Let's do this, Uehara.
Yes!
-Hey, Uehara.
-Yeah?
Even if you lose,
don't break your promise.
You don't have to worry about that
because I'm not going to lose.
Uehara.
Here goes.
Ow! That hurt!
-Yes!
-Huh?
What? You won?
You mean you didn't see that?
Really? You won? For real?
Yeah.
Yes! Yes, Uehara! Yay!
Of course I won.
-The winner is Uehara!
-Yay!
I'm super thirsty. Let's go.
-Huh?
-Let's get something to drink.
But why me too?
I won, right?
Being able to do whatever I want with you,
means you do what I tell you.
But you said it was stupid
to fight over me.
Let's go!
I thought this was supposed to make Uehara
show how serious he is about her,
so they'd become closer.
-Looks like it didn't work.
-Yeah.
I don't know about that.
I think Uehara has changed a little.
Really?
He's always been so unsociable.
You could never know what he was thinking.
But since he's been with Nao,
he sometimes lets his feelings show to us.
You mean he's become more open?
I'm not sure if he's more open
to you, Abe.
-What?
-Huh?
I think Uehara has changed.
You know, you're a really good actor,
Issei!
Yeah, you are!
At the end there,
I totally thought you were going to win.
I was very nervous.
Oh, really? You think so?
Well, yeah. You know,
it just comes with experience. Experience.
Here you go.
What is it?
What's gotten into--
You're supposed to do as I say, right?
Then hold still.
You know, he really does...
Huh?
No. It's nothing.
What's with you? Be more careful
who you're around when you faint.
I'm sorry.
Silly girl.
I sweated a lot. I'm going to take a bath.
Wait. Do I smell sweaty?
I can't let things go
any farther than this.
I've got to be careful.
Don't you think that's a great idea?
Sounds good to me.
I'll call them right now.
Okay!
Girls are way bolder
about this kind of stuff.
Oh! Are you okay with this too, Issei?
Huh? Oh, yeah. Sure.
-Okay!
-Yeah.
I wonder what I should tell her.
That was a really nice bath.
Oh, I probably took too long.
Huh?
What?
Hey! Those guys' bags are gone...
The girls are gone too?
Huh?
That means...
it's just us two alone?
YUSANNOSATO TODOROKI MOTEL
This place was really close.
We got here in no time.
-And it smells nice too.
-It's like a laundromat.
I got another room.
-Thank you, Kitaura.
-Thanks.
It's Nao. That was fast.
Hello?
Where are you, Marina?
It's a secret.
What?
Why did you disappear all of a sudden?
This was supposed to be a trip
for just you two, right?
Yeah, but...
Besides, you've still got two rooms.
It's the same as your place.
Yeah, I guess so.
But still--
Anyway, see you later.
-What?
-Bye!
Hey! Wait a minute, Marina!
-That's so mean!
-I hung up as fast as I could.
So, where are they?
Uh...
I think they went home.
What?
Then... let's go to bed.
Don't be stupid! I'll go downstairs.
Oh. Yeah. I get it.
You're right.
TSUGUMI ROOM
Yoshikawa Party
What was that?
Sometimes
she comes here to visit...
or so I've heard.
Uhm... I, uh...
I was kind of hoping
I could sleep here too.
In my room,
it feels like there might be... a ghost...
Excuse me! Excuse me! Terribly sorry!
Sorry it took me so long.
I thought that all of you
had gone back home.
But you two will be staying, right?
-Oh, yes.
-Yes.
You must be a happy man,
with such a pretty wife.
Oh! Should I put out just one futon?
-No! Two!
Good night. Enjoy yourselves.
Uhm...
Yes?
You know...
I'm going to sleep upstairs.
What?
Wait, Uehara!
Good night.
Don't you...
Don't you think...
I'm attractive?
What?
It just seemed like
you rejected me just now.
So I...
Being with you can be really exhausting.
I don't trust myself.
Huh?
Don't you see?
I don't trust myself. I don't know if I'll
behave if we sleep in the same room.
Do you see? Now, let go of me.
Don't you worry.
I'm not interested in anyone
but you right now.
Me either.
I'm not interested in anyone besides you,
Uehara.
You're the most important person to me.
So...
So, this kind of thing...
I wouldn't mind... if we did it.
Nao.
You're really hot right now.
Yeah, I feel really warm.
I'm kind of dizzy
and feel faint.
CHIGIRA INN
I'm sorry.
I wonder why I got a fever.
Maybe I was in the bath too long.
Forget about it. Just sleep.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, whatever.
You're a handful.
I can't believe you actually fell asleep.
Dang, now I'm wide awake.
Hi.
Hey, don't go.
What happened with Nao?
She's asleep.
Asleep? You've got to be kidding!
What the heck are you doing
out here, anyway?
-Taking a walk.
-This late at night?
I've got a lot on my mind.
Who cares about me, anyway?
You just do whatever you want
and leave Nao behind?
Oh, now I see.
What are you so happy about?
I'm not happy.
I'm going back.
Hold on a second!
-What?
-Come on! Just come with me!
But why?
YUSANNOSATO TODOROKI MOTEL
-Got a pair!
-Really?
My natural ability
at cards is shining through!
Yes!
Come on! Give it to me! Give it to me!
-Why that one?
-Come on! Let me have that one!
What a pain you are!
You're a pain too. You're both the same.
Quit fooling around.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Okay, got one!
Cut that out!
-Yes!
-You peeked!
I did not!
Why isn't Uehara here
when I really need him?
Darn you, Uehara!
A FEW DAYS LATER
Nao.
You're creeping me out.
Hey! Wait! Wait for me!
-Where do you want to go next time?
-Huh?
You want to go abroad?
We could get a private beach
over the summer!
We don't have that kind of money.
What's wrong with having high hopes?
Oh, yeah. I had a crazy dream last night.
THIS IS A FICTIONAL DRAMA.