Yes?
Nice to meet you. Thank you
for always looking after my brother.
Your brother?
I'm Uehara's older brother, Takuya.
Oh! You're Uehara's big brother?
I'm sorry.
Since Yuri was still asleep,
I think Uehara left already.
Don't worry. It's my fault
for dropping in all of a sudden.
It's OK.
I've been busy with work
since Hisashi came to my place,
so we haven't had a chance to talk.
But I was able to take a day off,
and decided to come for a visit.
I see.
I agree...
that it's better to talk directly
with Yuri.
Here you go.
Thank you.
This is good.
I hate to admit it
but he is really super handsome.
More than Uehara?
Yep. They're like chalk and cheese.
Chalk...
Oh, yeah, Nao... is that right?
Yes.
Here. I hope that you like it.
Oh, thank you.
I appreciate your thoughtfulness.
It's my way of saying thank you
for always taking care of Hisashi.
He's quite fortunate to live with someone
as pretty as you.
Oh, no, no... I'm not so...
This situation is like...
Nao.
Please look after my younger brother.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for everything as well.
What are you doing, Nao?
Hisashi!
Yikes! Hisashi!
What's up with you? That's creepy.
I thought you went back to your home.
I forgot my phone, so I came back for it.
I thought I told you not to come here.
But, Hisa!
Hisa?
I'd like to see where you live and stuff.
Do you have enough money?
Are you sure money isn't tight?
I'm so worried, I can't help it.
I'm not just your older brother,
but like your parent as well.
How come you told Yuri your address,
but didn't tell me?
Aw, shut up.
This is why I didn't want you to know.
Come on, I'm sure you're in a pinch,
aren't you?
I mean, just look how skinny you've--
Quit touching me!
You know I don't gain weight easily.
If you eat properly, you'll grow more.
Pipe down!
Yuri.
From what I've heard,
it sounds like you couldn't care
less about me.
Aw, man. What a pain.
Are you drinking, Yuri?
Acting like you're Mr. Common Sense,
you traitor!
Now, like I told you several times before,
I haven't betrayed you, Yuri.
-Just come back--
-Liar!
You met your former girlfriend.
-She's a work acquaintance.
-Work acquaintance?
I'm in sales for a home builder.
She is an employee for one of our clients.
Oh, that's it? Yuri, if it's for work--
You planned a vacation with her,
didn't you?
Huh?
The two of you were cozily planning
a vacation abroad.
That's what you were planning, right?
Uh...
Oh...
My friend just happened to see you
and sent it to me.
Hey, is that really Takuya?
This is... me...
-Huh? Hey!
-This thing...
Stop and listen to me, would you!
Hey! Where are you going?
Huh? What are you going to do
with your wedding ring?
Excuse me!
I'm divorcing you! Divorce, you hear!
-Yuri, wait!
-Let go of me!
-No! Don't! Don't!
-Darn you!
I will never forgive you!
-Ah!
Oh my.
Anyway, when Yuri calms down,
I'll tell her to return.
-Sorry for all the trouble.
-Just forget about it.
When Yuri gets like that,
there's nothing that can be done.
Yeah.
That's true, Hisa,
but are you cooking for yourself?
Don't tell me you're eating whatever,
like cup ramen or pizza?
You've always been like that.
Hisa!
-Leave me alone.
-Hey! Hisa!
You're brother really loves you,
doesn't he?
It's really annoying.
He's overly obsessive.
Aren't you going back home today?
Not when things are like this.
I'll start staying here again.
I see.
I wonder
if Takuya really did have an affair.
I don't think he's that type.
Divorce! Divorce!
What a hopeless case.
Does Takuya know?
That you've always liked Yu--
Don't you dare tell him.
-Huh?
-You saw how he acts toward me.
If he ever found that out,
I'm sure he'd tell me to have her.
-But--
-He's always been like that.
If I said I wanted something...
he'd always...
give a silly smile and let me have it.
At any rate, don't you dare tell him.
Uehara's brother came over?
-Marina!
-Here! Ah.
So, what kind of guy is he?
If he's Uehara's big brother,
he must be so totally high level!
Cool type? Fresh faced?
He's going on my handsome list.
-Do I even exist to you?
-Huh?
Hmm, he's a nice guy,
but maybe a little flaky.
At any rate, he totally loves Uehara.
But then he hardly seems to know himself.
He's kind of thickheaded.
Which sounds like his brother is...
a male version of Nao?
I wonder what Uehara is really thinking
about this.
Huh?
If things don't work out with Yuri
and his brother
I wonder if he'll want her again.
Are you still worried about that?
I mean, he's always liked her.
He liked her in a special way.
He said he's gotten over her.
But I'm not sure he really has.
What about the other
of the top three boys?
He's totally truthful about his feelings
with you, right?
Yeah.
Oh, could it be that you've become serious
about him since he said he likes you?
No, of course I haven't.
It's just that being with him is getting
more awkward every day.
That's what we mean
by you're getting serious about him.
Huh?
-Yoshikawa Nao.
-Here!
ENGLISH MINI TEST, 32 POINTS
Uh oh.
Her troubled heart
has affected her scores.
-What was her score?
-32.
-That's good for her.
-Mitsuishi!
Nao.
Daichi.
-What about practice?
-We're off this week.
I see.
-Uhm, you know.
-Uh...
Oh... Go ahead.
Yuri is still at your place, right?
Uh-huh.
Actually, Uehara's brother came by.
Seriously? So everything's been settled?
More like it added fuel to the fire.
It just makes matters more complicated.
You know,
this is no time for you to be worrying
over another family's problems.
Finals are coming up pretty soon.
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'll be fine. Just fine.
You're so easy to read.
If you're stuck with your studies,
just give me a call.
I told you I'll be fine.
Do you feel awkward?
Huh?
When you're with me.
Well, uh...
I guess it's only natural.
Daichi... has your character changed?
You think so?
Uh-huh.
I think you just didn't know
this side of me.
Huh?
I said I'd wait for you,
but I didn't say I'd wait silently.
Bye.
I've told Nao that I like her.
Oh.
Yo.
Huh? Isn't that Takuya?
I wonder what he's doing?
The ring!
Hisa! Nao!
I'm going to work.
What? Wait a second!
Hey, Hisa!
I see you didn't find the ring, did you?
-No, but I'll keep looking.
-OK.
-Come in here.
-Thank you.
Sorry, but Uehara is at work.
What am I apologizing for?
It's OK. I was just glad to see his face.
You really do love your brother,
don't you?
Well,
it's always been just the two of us
for a long time.
You really are against
Uehara living alone, aren't you?
Well, he's not exactly alone, though.
He's never been much trouble at all.
He never showed much emotion,
and acted strangely mature.
-A man-brat.
-Huh?
Yuri told me about that.
Yes, a man-brat.
He always tolerates things
so he wouldn't cause me any worry.
-But--
-Oh, I know.
He is sometimes childish.
And he gets angry so easily.
Yeah, but that's what's
so cute about him.
-You think so?
-Yes, of course.
He's desperately trying to be mature,
but his emotions are showing all over.
But he never says a word
when it comes to what's crucial.
That's why I've never thought of
forcing him to come back home.
Huh?
He's got his own reasons for doing things.
But I've always had a dream.
A dream?
I'm a little old to be thinking like this,
but ever since I was a kid
I've always dreamed of living in a house
that I built.
Yuri would be there... and Hisa.
I always thought it'd be nice
if we could live like that someday.
But I don't think
that "someday" will be arriving soon.
Takuya...
Takuya!
I want you to make up with Yuri.
What?
I mean, you can't let it go on like this.
For Uehara as well,
if you two aren't happy,
you'll never achieve that dream.
Or did you actually have an affair?
No, I didn't!
Like I told you yesterday,
we weren't planning a trip.
It was a business meeting.
She wanted to clear up
the misunderstanding,
so she went and called Yuri.
Then why haven't you explained that
to Yuri?
I did.
But she won't even listen to me.
-Takuya!
-Yes?
I've got an idea. Trust me!
Here, here, here. Here you go!
Here's your special ramen!
Nao... What's the meaning of this?
Don't you worry about it.
This new ramen is on me.
That's not what worries me.
What's he doing here?
You know what they say about a man
and woman eating ramen together.
-They can say what their really thinking.
-That's right.
Our place is really popular with couples.
Even when things are all mixed up,
they get straightened out like ramen.
I eat here every day,
but it hasn't helped a bit.
That's because you're eating alone.
No meaning in that.
That's so stupid.
-Oh, this is delicious.
-This is great!
Manager!
Well, since we're here, I guess
I'll listen to what you have to say.
Hey, that'd be perfect for Hisa!
-Huh?
-When is this?
The beginning of next week.
"Ramen eating competition.
Champion eats for free."
Hisa would win for sure,
don't you agree, Yuri...
Oh!
Damn him.
He's so obsessed with his brother.
Yuri!
Uhm, Yuri--
Sorry about that.
I've caused you trouble now too, Nao.
-That doesn't bother me.
-Nao,
I know you told me
it's OK to be a fool if you like someone.
But...
that's not exactly easy either.
Maybe I'll have an affair too.
-Huh?
-Yeah, that's what I'll do.
I mean, I've got lots of guy friends.
First I'll contact Onishi.
Ah! Don't do that!
You can't do that.
Having an affair...
That's just plain cruel.
Naturally it would be so to Takuya.
And to this Onishi as well.
And to... Uehara...
Uehara...
has always liked you, Yuri.
But he removed himself from the picture...
so you two could be happy.
So how can you...
how can you say you'll get divorced...
or have an affair so easily?
That kind of thing...
would be super cruel to Uehara!
I'm sorry.
ISSEI
-Go back.
-Huh?
I won't be having any affair.
-But--
-Don't you worry.
OK?
Thank you... Nao.
COFFEE SHOP
I've told Nao that I like her.
Uehara's as sullen as ever again today.
-I wonder if it's about that?
-What?
That guy from my class
who came here the other day.
He and I were getting along really well.
Yeah, so?
No matter how handsome a guy is,
when he thinks about the girl he likes,
you can tell he's in love when he's
happy and anxious at the same time.
Hey!
Hey.
Dad,
how will I get him to forgive me?
Hold on here. Where's today's horoscope?
Uh, let's see. It says to face north.
Which is north?
Yes?
-Oh.
-Daichi.
These are the test sheets from last year.
I thought you could study from them.
Thanks. They'll be a big help.
Sorry that I'm dressed so sloppy.
Huh? Do I look funny?
-No, I'm actually really happy.
-Huh?
I mean, the other day you also
let me see you in that jersey at work.
Oh, well that's--
It seems like you're taking me
more seriously since I said I like you.
That's not what's going on--
What are you doing standing there
at my door?
Why don't you take this opportunity
to clear things up.
Huh?
What are your feelings?
Hey, Daichi.
Are you still--
What are your feelings about Yuri now?
You liked her, didn't you?
Thanks to Nao,
it looks like you're eating properly.
But also as a way
of saying thanks to you two,
I thought I'd make dinner.
Hisa will eat anything,
but he's never liked stew
since he was little.
Well, I didn't either. I wonder why?
Maybe since it's
so clearly a family dish--
How come you haven't said anything?
Huh?
Could it be... you always knew?
You knew that I always liked Yuri?
Are you even listening?
Look at me!
Not Yuri.
Huh?
Yuri is the one thing
I won't let you have.
Takuya.
Sorry, Hisa.
Wait, Uehara!
Damn you!
Yuri, when did you get here?
Uehara.
For eight whole years...
he acted like he didn't know.
God damn that jerk!
I feel like such an idiot.
This whole time
I was desperately hiding my feelings.
He didn't let you have her.
What?
He didn't give you a silly smile
and let you have her, right?
That was really admirable of Takuya.
He's the kind of big brother you deserve.
Uehara?
-Get me closer.
-You're heavy, you know.
-But I can't see.
-What?
-Lift me a little higher.
-I can't go any higher. Ow!
-Uh, it's not here.
-What?
Oh!
-There it is!
-Really?
Here it is!
Oh.
Hey, come on. Let me see.
Hey, what're you hiding it for? Show me!
-Fine!
-What's with you?
It's just a key ring!
Nao?
Daichi.
What are you doing out here?
It's freezing. You'll catch a cold.
-I've got to find a ring.
-A ring?
Yuri's marriage ring.
Uehara's looking for it.
But that's got nothing to do with you,
Nao.
-You've got tests--
-It matters to me.
It's more important than tests.
I see.
You get back home.
I can't do that.
-I'll keep looking until--
-Go home.
This is...
my responsibility.
Besides, unlike me, you're pretty dumb.
I won't be having you hate me
because you failed your tests.
What a joke it would be
if you were held back.
My grades aren't that bad.
Besides, if I take remedial lessons,
I won't be held back.
Taking remedial lessons
is a problem itself.
Your problem is
that you never usually study anyway.
Whose fault do you think it is
that I've gotten all wrapped up in this?
Like I said,
forget about this and go home!
OK, fine! I will go home!
Are you sure you want me to?
Oh dear!
Sorry.
Jeez! What's wrong with you? You're heavy.
Ow!
I am not heavy!
I can't believe this.
Uehara!
Here it is!
Here it is! Here it is!
Here it is! Here it is, Uehara!
Uehara!
Here it is! Here it is! We did it, Uehara!
That's dangerous. Give it back to me.
Thank you.
Huh?
-Huh?
-Aw, jeez.
I said, "Thank you."
Huh?
Don't get carried away.
Ow.
Oh, all right. Here, let me see.
Pain, pain, go away!
That made it worse.
Welcome back, Hisa.
Thanks.
We're back.
Hey.
What have you two been up to?
Yuri!
Wait a sec. Have you two already made up?
Don't talk like that.
What I want to know is
where you guys have been.
Oh!
Don't let her take it off again.
Hisa!
Thank you.
Nao.
Thanks for scolding me,
and saying it would be cruel to Uehara.
You're absolutely right.
Yuri.
What are you talking about?
-It's none of your business.
-Why?
-Right?
What's that all about?
This is my responsibility.
Hello, Daichi?
Can I meet you somewhere today?
I have something important to tell you.
Here goes.
EVENING STAR RAMEN
-Welcome!
-Sorry.
I couldn't wait, and started without you.
Closer to your house would have been fine.
I don't mind. I like the ramen here.
Besides, this place isn't dark or boring.
Here you go.
Thank you, Issei.
Daichi.
I've come to apologize to you today.
I'm sorry.
Nao?
I...
I've taken advantage of your kindness
to me.
I always have.
-Don't worry about that.
-I'm sorry.
Like I said, don't apologize.
You haven't done anything
to apologize for, anyway.
Daichi.
This is really good!
The ramen here really is great, isn't it?
This is great.
-It's cold.
Here.
I'm fine.
Oh, OK.
So, I'll see you later.
Yeah.
Don't make that face.
I'm glad that thing
with Yuri has been cleared up now.
See you.
The ring...
I'm home.
Hey, how's it going?
Huh? Did you eat already?
Yeah. I'm full.
Oh, I see.
It's all quiet now
without Yuri and Takuya.
Yeah. So, you want to watch some TV?
What do you want for lunch?
Huh? I thought you already ate.
Oh, yeah.
But I was just thinking how I'd like
some of the stew Takuya made.
-OK?
-Yeah.
OK, I'll have to heat it up.
By the way...
Yes?
Yesterday... Well, I mean...
This thing that's happened...
Well, I mean, this whole time lately
I'm sorry I got you involved.
I don't mind.
Thanks to you... I've been able to
get over a lot of things.
I mean...
This time it's for real.
Me too.
Because of this, I guess you could say
I've learned a lot about myself.
Oh.
I see.
-Uh-huh.
-I'm glad to hear it.
Thanks.
This stew is delicious.
Yeah.
It's really good.
Uh-huh.
Hello?
Good morning, Nao.
Is Hisa there?
He isn't answering his phone at all.
Takuya,
what are you calling at this time for?
Yuri and I had a long talk
and decided that the three of us
would live together.
I believe
good news should be delivered promptly.
What?
I'm really sorry for all the trouble
we've caused you, Nao.
-Huh?
-Nao?
Huh? Uh...
But isn't this awfully sudden?
Don't worry.
We'll keep paying half the rent.
No, that's not the problem.
Oh, sorry. I've got to move the car.
Hey! Wait!
So what's preventing you?
Keep it down. She's still asleep in there.
If you've gotten over it,
then what's the problem?
Do you hate living with us that much?
That's not what it is.
I've got no problems
the way things are now.
What are you talking about?
What about money?
Then send me more.
Are you joking? What a waste of money.
This is close to school.
You never complained
when you lived at our place.
Or could it be...
you have another reason
why you have to live here.
What kind of question is that?
For example...
you don't want to leave Nao, or something.
Or that you like Nao?
What?
Today was just like you said.
It was a date.
Even though we've only been together
for a short time,
we've already got this in common.
Today, this pudding is better than usual.
Do you like her? Do you like Nao?
Yeah, I do.
Did you hear that, Nao?
Yuri!
What? What's going on?
OK, I'm going.
Oh, and you can stay here
for as long as you like, OK?
Besides, we're newlyweds,
so it's best to leave us alone anyway.
Thank you for letting me visit.
Hey! Hey, Yuri!
Hey.
-No, I can't.
-Hey!
I can't! I can't!
-What are you doing?
-I can't!
-Hey!
-I said I can't!
Hurry up and open up this door.
TOUKEN HOME - SYDNEY OFFICE
-It went perfectly!
-Yea!
That really went well.
Now I feel like we've returned the favor.
He's pretty settled in already too.
And besides,
Nao was a really big help to me.
Which makes it nice to see that
Nao's feelings finally got through to him.
I'm really glad.
OK, let's go!
You got it.
TOUKEN HOME - SYDNEY OFFICE
TOUKEN HOME CO., LTD.
PROJECT LEADER: TAKUYA
Did you... hear what I just said?
Yes.
It's true.
What?
THIS IS A FICTIONAL DRAMA.